{
    "# * #": [
        {
            "Question": "1 * 2",
            "Answer": 2,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 12",
            "Answer": 72,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 8",
            "Answer": 32,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 9",
            "Answer": 45,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 1",
            "Answer": 16,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 1",
            "Answer": 12,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 18",
            "Answer": 198,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 6",
            "Answer": 60,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 16",
            "Answer": 224,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 9",
            "Answer": 135,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 12",
            "Answer": 96,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 4",
            "Answer": 28,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 0",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 18",
            "Answer": 198,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 5",
            "Answer": 70,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 3",
            "Answer": 45,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 3",
            "Answer": 9,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 13",
            "Answer": 208,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 3",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 3",
            "Answer": 45,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 16",
            "Answer": 112,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 3",
            "Answer": 3,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 15",
            "Answer": 75,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 5",
            "Answer": 35,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 16",
            "Answer": 80,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 18",
            "Answer": 234,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 15",
            "Answer": 150,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 12",
            "Answer": 72,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 0",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 11",
            "Answer": 77,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 16",
            "Answer": 112,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 14",
            "Answer": 210,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 13",
            "Answer": 195,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 0",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 15",
            "Answer": 270,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 11",
            "Answer": 132,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 13",
            "Answer": 182,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 19",
            "Answer": 304,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 19",
            "Answer": 76,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 10",
            "Answer": 120,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 8",
            "Answer": 72,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 10",
            "Answer": 20,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 16",
            "Answer": 288,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 18",
            "Answer": 342,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 18",
            "Answer": 18,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 16",
            "Answer": 304,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 15",
            "Answer": 105,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 15",
            "Answer": 150,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 18",
            "Answer": 72,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 1",
            "Answer": 3,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 9",
            "Answer": 63,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 13",
            "Answer": 182,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 15",
            "Answer": 270,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 16",
            "Answer": 32,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 0",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 14",
            "Answer": 28,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 12",
            "Answer": 228,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 9",
            "Answer": 144,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 10",
            "Answer": 50,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 0",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 2",
            "Answer": 26,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 14",
            "Answer": 84,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 11",
            "Answer": 110,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 6",
            "Answer": 36,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 18",
            "Answer": 198,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 17",
            "Answer": 85,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 12",
            "Answer": 60,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 9",
            "Answer": 45,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 3",
            "Answer": 9,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 6",
            "Answer": 48,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 14",
            "Answer": 28,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 10",
            "Answer": 100,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 3",
            "Answer": 3,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 5",
            "Answer": 35,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 8",
            "Answer": 48,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 10",
            "Answer": 180,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 19",
            "Answer": 19,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 18",
            "Answer": 198,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 4",
            "Answer": 52,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 8",
            "Answer": 152,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 18",
            "Answer": 342,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 10",
            "Answer": 50,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 6",
            "Answer": 84,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 19",
            "Answer": 285,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 3",
            "Answer": 36,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 6",
            "Answer": 108,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 17",
            "Answer": 204,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 16",
            "Answer": 288,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 4",
            "Answer": 68,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 7",
            "Answer": 63,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 12",
            "Answer": 120,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 17",
            "Answer": 221,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 16",
            "Answer": 160,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 11",
            "Answer": 165,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 6",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 5",
            "Answer": 40,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 15",
            "Answer": 240,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 18",
            "Answer": 216,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 0",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 17",
            "Answer": 221,
            "Predicate": "# * #"
        }
    ],
    "# + #": [
        {
            "Question": "6 + 14",
            "Answer": 20,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 2",
            "Answer": 16,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 6",
            "Answer": 13,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 4",
            "Answer": 22,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 2",
            "Answer": 18,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 15",
            "Answer": 15,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 8",
            "Answer": 26,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 1",
            "Answer": 16,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 10",
            "Answer": 27,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 0",
            "Answer": 14,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 12",
            "Answer": 26,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 19",
            "Answer": 32,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 17",
            "Answer": 33,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 19",
            "Answer": 23,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 15",
            "Answer": 20,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 5",
            "Answer": 8,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 15",
            "Answer": 20,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 0",
            "Answer": 11,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 18",
            "Answer": 26,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 14",
            "Answer": 26,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 14",
            "Answer": 24,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 4",
            "Answer": 17,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 11",
            "Answer": 13,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 16",
            "Answer": 35,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 0",
            "Answer": 6,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 15",
            "Answer": 28,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 8",
            "Answer": 18,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 17",
            "Answer": 33,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 11",
            "Answer": 16,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 6",
            "Answer": 18,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 4",
            "Answer": 23,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 11",
            "Answer": 23,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 19",
            "Answer": 32,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 2",
            "Answer": 4,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 1",
            "Answer": 11,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 17",
            "Answer": 36,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 12",
            "Answer": 20,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 16",
            "Answer": 29,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 0",
            "Answer": 10,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 9",
            "Answer": 12,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 4",
            "Answer": 8,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 12",
            "Answer": 18,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 16",
            "Answer": 16,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 10",
            "Answer": 13,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 17",
            "Answer": 36,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 13",
            "Answer": 14,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 18",
            "Answer": 34,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 7",
            "Answer": 22,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 13",
            "Answer": 30,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 15",
            "Answer": 19,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 10",
            "Answer": 26,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 8",
            "Answer": 10,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 16",
            "Answer": 33,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 12",
            "Answer": 24,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 17",
            "Answer": 21,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 17",
            "Answer": 27,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 6",
            "Answer": 14,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 2",
            "Answer": 20,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 18",
            "Answer": 21,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 16",
            "Answer": 20,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 13",
            "Answer": 13,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 4",
            "Answer": 11,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 3",
            "Answer": 14,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 13",
            "Answer": 17,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 2",
            "Answer": 18,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 9",
            "Answer": 10,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 6",
            "Answer": 15,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 10",
            "Answer": 18,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 2",
            "Answer": 16,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 6",
            "Answer": 12,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 4",
            "Answer": 9,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 18",
            "Answer": 34,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 5",
            "Answer": 13,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 10",
            "Answer": 24,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 13",
            "Answer": 13,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 5",
            "Answer": 5,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 16",
            "Answer": 17,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 16",
            "Answer": 28,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 1",
            "Answer": 19,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 5",
            "Answer": 17,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 1",
            "Answer": 11,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 10",
            "Answer": 18,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 16",
            "Answer": 30,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 17",
            "Answer": 21,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 5",
            "Answer": 7,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 2",
            "Answer": 20,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 8",
            "Answer": 11,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 7",
            "Answer": 7,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 18",
            "Answer": 19,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 11",
            "Answer": 19,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 14",
            "Answer": 21,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 12",
            "Answer": 23,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 19",
            "Answer": 35,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 12",
            "Answer": 18,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 16",
            "Answer": 29,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 4",
            "Answer": 9,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 17",
            "Answer": 30,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 17",
            "Answer": 24,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 14",
            "Answer": 21,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 19",
            "Answer": 22,
            "Predicate": "# + #"
        }
    ],
    "# + # * #": [
        {
            "Question": "18 + 14 * 9",
            "Answer": 144,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 8 * 2",
            "Answer": 34,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 17 * 4",
            "Answer": 80,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 10 * 11",
            "Answer": 126,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 19 * 16",
            "Answer": 309,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 8 * 13",
            "Answer": 110,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 18 * 17",
            "Answer": 323,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 1 * 17",
            "Answer": 19,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 5 * 7",
            "Answer": 53,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 10 * 5",
            "Answer": 66,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 8 * 5",
            "Answer": 43,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 17 * 6",
            "Answer": 107,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 7 * 2",
            "Answer": 23,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 17 * 12",
            "Answer": 208,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 1 * 5",
            "Answer": 18,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 3 * 4",
            "Answer": 28,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 18 * 10",
            "Answer": 195,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 1 * 5",
            "Answer": 19,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 7 * 19",
            "Answer": 136,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 12 * 1",
            "Answer": 14,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 16 * 3",
            "Answer": 55,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 15 * 17",
            "Answer": 265,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 6 * 7",
            "Answer": 50,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 6 * 8",
            "Answer": 58,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 18 * 3",
            "Answer": 64,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 0 * 4",
            "Answer": 19,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 0 * 5",
            "Answer": 10,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 12 * 1",
            "Answer": 18,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 19 * 2",
            "Answer": 39,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 17 * 12",
            "Answer": 212,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 8 * 1",
            "Answer": 12,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 13 * 19",
            "Answer": 257,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 14 * 11",
            "Answer": 165,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 3 * 8",
            "Answer": 41,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 6 * 18",
            "Answer": 125,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 14 * 8",
            "Answer": 116,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 13 * 12",
            "Answer": 165,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 12 * 6",
            "Answer": 83,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 13 * 4",
            "Answer": 53,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 1 * 2",
            "Answer": 4,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 5 * 18",
            "Answer": 103,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 4 * 9",
            "Answer": 44,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 16 * 12",
            "Answer": 210,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 11 * 12",
            "Answer": 148,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 4 * 14",
            "Answer": 71,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 19 * 17",
            "Answer": 327,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 12 * 7",
            "Answer": 97,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 19 * 17",
            "Answer": 330,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 10 * 10",
            "Answer": 110,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 7 * 6",
            "Answer": 55,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 3 * 4",
            "Answer": 26,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 0 * 5",
            "Answer": 3,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 3 * 9",
            "Answer": 40,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 3 * 9",
            "Answer": 29,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 4 * 9",
            "Answer": 40,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 2 * 12",
            "Answer": 30,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 15 * 13",
            "Answer": 204,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 0 * 1",
            "Answer": 1,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 5 * 0",
            "Answer": 8,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 13 * 10",
            "Answer": 145,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 8 * 4",
            "Answer": 40,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 5 * 17",
            "Answer": 104,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 19 * 13",
            "Answer": 259,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 7 * 11",
            "Answer": 92,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 3 * 2",
            "Answer": 8,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 8 * 17",
            "Answer": 145,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 15 * 6",
            "Answer": 104,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 0 * 7",
            "Answer": 13,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 11 * 2",
            "Answer": 35,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 16 * 9",
            "Answer": 151,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 4 * 6",
            "Answer": 34,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 5 * 13",
            "Answer": 67,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 5 * 16",
            "Answer": 93,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 3 * 6",
            "Answer": 32,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 7 * 19",
            "Answer": 136,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 19 * 17",
            "Answer": 340,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 11 * 6",
            "Answer": 75,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 17 * 19",
            "Answer": 338,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 16 * 12",
            "Answer": 205,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 10 * 17",
            "Answer": 178,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 5 * 19",
            "Answer": 105,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 10 * 1",
            "Answer": 28,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 13 * 17",
            "Answer": 222,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 8 * 12",
            "Answer": 111,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 8 * 10",
            "Answer": 86,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 9 * 6",
            "Answer": 54,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 9 * 18",
            "Answer": 172,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 12 * 11",
            "Answer": 142,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 10 * 10",
            "Answer": 114,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 19 * 0",
            "Answer": 4,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 18 * 15",
            "Answer": 280,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 0 * 5",
            "Answer": 3,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 19 * 11",
            "Answer": 222,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 10 * 8",
            "Answer": 80,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 11 * 16",
            "Answer": 177,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 3 * 10",
            "Answer": 45,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 3 * 1",
            "Answer": 13,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 14 * 16",
            "Answer": 226,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 18 * 14",
            "Answer": 268,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 0 * 5",
            "Answer": 19,
            "Predicate": "# + # * #"
        }
    ],
    "# * # * #": [
        {
            "Question": "17 * 12 * 12",
            "Answer": 2448,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 6 * 6",
            "Answer": 360,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 6 * 11",
            "Answer": 1188,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 14 * 12",
            "Answer": 2016,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 0 * 1",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 8 * 7",
            "Answer": 112,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 12 * 13",
            "Answer": 1404,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 3 * 5",
            "Answer": 15,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 8 * 4",
            "Answer": 320,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 15 * 5",
            "Answer": 375,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 12 * 8",
            "Answer": 1248,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 6 * 10",
            "Answer": 840,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 16 * 3",
            "Answer": 96,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 18 * 0",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 19 * 8",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 8 * 2",
            "Answer": 96,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 18 * 18",
            "Answer": 5184,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 14 * 3",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 10 * 17",
            "Answer": 1700,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 13 * 17",
            "Answer": 1105,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 5 * 19",
            "Answer": 1140,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 2 * 6",
            "Answer": 228,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 16 * 10",
            "Answer": 640,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 16 * 2",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 6 * 4",
            "Answer": 24,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 11 * 11",
            "Answer": 847,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 8 * 19",
            "Answer": 152,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 1 * 16",
            "Answer": 96,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 17 * 7",
            "Answer": 1666,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 1 * 14",
            "Answer": 126,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 0 * 10",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 11 * 3",
            "Answer": 429,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 2 * 7",
            "Answer": 84,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 17 * 17",
            "Answer": 1734,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 7 * 13",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 2 * 14",
            "Answer": 196,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 5 * 14",
            "Answer": 1260,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 3 * 10",
            "Answer": 240,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 1 * 7",
            "Answer": 112,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 14 * 0",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 4 * 0",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 4 * 4",
            "Answer": 144,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 17 * 19",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 11 * 1",
            "Answer": 110,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 8 * 11",
            "Answer": 1408,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 9 * 8",
            "Answer": 864,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 4 * 17",
            "Answer": 68,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 12 * 1",
            "Answer": 168,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 16 * 17",
            "Answer": 2720,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 18 * 8",
            "Answer": 2448,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 7 * 18",
            "Answer": 252,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 19 * 9",
            "Answer": 2223,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 18 * 19",
            "Answer": 1368,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 1 * 13",
            "Answer": 13,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 4 * 9",
            "Answer": 108,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 1 * 19",
            "Answer": 171,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 0 * 1",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 3 * 3",
            "Answer": 144,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 14 * 19",
            "Answer": 2128,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 1 * 1",
            "Answer": 15,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 16 * 15",
            "Answer": 960,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 9 * 4",
            "Answer": 396,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 19 * 7",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 7 * 15",
            "Answer": 525,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 10 * 7",
            "Answer": 980,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 9 * 6",
            "Answer": 702,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 14 * 11",
            "Answer": 2310,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 4 * 5",
            "Answer": 220,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 13 * 14",
            "Answer": 1820,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 15 * 6",
            "Answer": 1710,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 1 * 4",
            "Answer": 28,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 19 * 0",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 3 * 19",
            "Answer": 228,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 8 * 10",
            "Answer": 240,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 10 * 2",
            "Answer": 380,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 3 * 5",
            "Answer": 105,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 10 * 6",
            "Answer": 540,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 9 * 1",
            "Answer": 144,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 8 * 0",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 17 * 2",
            "Answer": 578,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 7 * 14",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 4 * 14",
            "Answer": 448,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 6 * 12",
            "Answer": 936,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 17 * 2",
            "Answer": 306,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 3 * 17",
            "Answer": 51,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 15 * 16",
            "Answer": 720,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 7 * 5",
            "Answer": 560,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 4 * 4",
            "Answer": 96,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 1 * 0",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 9 * 13",
            "Answer": 1053,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 2 * 14",
            "Answer": 224,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 16 * 19",
            "Answer": 2128,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 8 * 8",
            "Answer": 1152,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 15 * 19",
            "Answer": 1425,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 8 * 9",
            "Answer": 144,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 3 * 17",
            "Answer": 918,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 9 * 18",
            "Answer": 972,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 2 * 6",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 15 * 14",
            "Answer": 2520,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 18 * 10",
            "Answer": 2700,
            "Predicate": "# * # * #"
        }
    ],
    "# + # + #": [
        {
            "Question": "2 + 10 + 3",
            "Answer": 15,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 14 + 10",
            "Answer": 37,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 19 + 19",
            "Answer": 38,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 15 + 8",
            "Answer": 30,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 19 + 3",
            "Answer": 28,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 8 + 1",
            "Answer": 24,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 1 + 14",
            "Answer": 23,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 5 + 12",
            "Answer": 19,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 7 + 3",
            "Answer": 16,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 3 + 4",
            "Answer": 25,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 17 + 1",
            "Answer": 22,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 15 + 16",
            "Answer": 42,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 8 + 16",
            "Answer": 31,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 7 + 18",
            "Answer": 33,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 13 + 3",
            "Answer": 21,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 12 + 0",
            "Answer": 27,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 4 + 6",
            "Answer": 26,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 8 + 1",
            "Answer": 20,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 14 + 9",
            "Answer": 23,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 8 + 11",
            "Answer": 26,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 9 + 15",
            "Answer": 43,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 17 + 8",
            "Answer": 35,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 15 + 0",
            "Answer": 32,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 19 + 14",
            "Answer": 52,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 15 + 7",
            "Answer": 41,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 15 + 18",
            "Answer": 37,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 18 + 7",
            "Answer": 33,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 5 + 16",
            "Answer": 32,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 17 + 6",
            "Answer": 28,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 3 + 3",
            "Answer": 24,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 8 + 9",
            "Answer": 31,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 19 + 15",
            "Answer": 49,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 18 + 14",
            "Answer": 43,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 10 + 8",
            "Answer": 24,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 12 + 0",
            "Answer": 23,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 10 + 1",
            "Answer": 16,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 5 + 3",
            "Answer": 27,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 9 + 1",
            "Answer": 22,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 14 + 15",
            "Answer": 48,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 12 + 7",
            "Answer": 26,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 14 + 15",
            "Answer": 40,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 3 + 5",
            "Answer": 27,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 5 + 17",
            "Answer": 35,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 19 + 7",
            "Answer": 32,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 17 + 16",
            "Answer": 34,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 14 + 6",
            "Answer": 27,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 10 + 5",
            "Answer": 21,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 10 + 16",
            "Answer": 27,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 9 + 14",
            "Answer": 35,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 13 + 3",
            "Answer": 32,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 17 + 5",
            "Answer": 38,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 8 + 7",
            "Answer": 20,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 13 + 14",
            "Answer": 36,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 15 + 11",
            "Answer": 40,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 4 + 5",
            "Answer": 20,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 10 + 10",
            "Answer": 39,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 11 + 8",
            "Answer": 23,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 15 + 10",
            "Answer": 33,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 6 + 14",
            "Answer": 25,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 9 + 13",
            "Answer": 40,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 0 + 0",
            "Answer": 2,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 7 + 18",
            "Answer": 30,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 7 + 17",
            "Answer": 26,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 4 + 8",
            "Answer": 25,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 4 + 6",
            "Answer": 26,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 9 + 6",
            "Answer": 32,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 11 + 16",
            "Answer": 34,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 16 + 9",
            "Answer": 28,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 9 + 19",
            "Answer": 34,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 6 + 5",
            "Answer": 16,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 2 + 16",
            "Answer": 26,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 5 + 0",
            "Answer": 6,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 0 + 14",
            "Answer": 33,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 1 + 18",
            "Answer": 21,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 5 + 18",
            "Answer": 40,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 2 + 3",
            "Answer": 9,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 12 + 18",
            "Answer": 42,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 13 + 2",
            "Answer": 26,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 15 + 8",
            "Answer": 26,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 15 + 15",
            "Answer": 46,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 1 + 19",
            "Answer": 34,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 6 + 10",
            "Answer": 21,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 11 + 10",
            "Answer": 31,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 6 + 14",
            "Answer": 21,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 18 + 8",
            "Answer": 45,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 8 + 8",
            "Answer": 18,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 0 + 19",
            "Answer": 28,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 2 + 6",
            "Answer": 19,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 13 + 18",
            "Answer": 39,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 12 + 8",
            "Answer": 21,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 14 + 13",
            "Answer": 31,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 9 + 9",
            "Answer": 24,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 5 + 9",
            "Answer": 21,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 7 + 5",
            "Answer": 19,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 12 + 4",
            "Answer": 32,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 4 + 7",
            "Answer": 18,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 0 + 6",
            "Answer": 10,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 14 + 2",
            "Answer": 23,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 2 + 7",
            "Answer": 15,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 15 + 7",
            "Answer": 41,
            "Predicate": "# + # + #"
        }
    ],
    "# * # + #": [
        {
            "Question": "3 * 2 + 19",
            "Answer": 25,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 6 + 0",
            "Answer": 30,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 18 + 10",
            "Answer": 154,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 8 + 13",
            "Answer": 69,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 11 + 3",
            "Answer": 25,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 7 + 10",
            "Answer": 136,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 17 + 14",
            "Answer": 320,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 4 + 5",
            "Answer": 61,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 1 + 5",
            "Answer": 16,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 16 + 0",
            "Answer": 288,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 19 + 0",
            "Answer": 133,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 6 + 16",
            "Answer": 64,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 12 + 14",
            "Answer": 98,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 9 + 18",
            "Answer": 171,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 17 + 8",
            "Answer": 93,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 4 + 8",
            "Answer": 36,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 16 + 19",
            "Answer": 163,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 17 + 4",
            "Answer": 140,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 2 + 8",
            "Answer": 36,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 19 + 16",
            "Answer": 92,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 7 + 9",
            "Answer": 79,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 6 + 5",
            "Answer": 113,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 10 + 1",
            "Answer": 11,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 18 + 17",
            "Answer": 251,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 10 + 5",
            "Answer": 135,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 17 + 1",
            "Answer": 154,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 9 + 16",
            "Answer": 16,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 16 + 12",
            "Answer": 60,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 10 + 19",
            "Answer": 89,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 8 + 0",
            "Answer": 72,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 8 + 15",
            "Answer": 135,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 12 + 15",
            "Answer": 159,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 11 + 16",
            "Answer": 16,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 13 + 17",
            "Answer": 173,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 18 + 8",
            "Answer": 332,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 2 + 16",
            "Answer": 26,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 12 + 6",
            "Answer": 126,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 9 + 11",
            "Answer": 74,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 14 + 11",
            "Answer": 179,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 12 + 8",
            "Answer": 164,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 19 + 2",
            "Answer": 230,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 12 + 4",
            "Answer": 4,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 5 + 19",
            "Answer": 39,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 5 + 7",
            "Answer": 57,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 13 + 4",
            "Answer": 173,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 0 + 7",
            "Answer": 7,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 18 + 10",
            "Answer": 46,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 19 + 18",
            "Answer": 322,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 16 + 8",
            "Answer": 152,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 7 + 11",
            "Answer": 88,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 11 + 1",
            "Answer": 122,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 7 + 14",
            "Answer": 98,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 12 + 15",
            "Answer": 63,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 14 + 11",
            "Answer": 25,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 1 + 15",
            "Answer": 31,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 17 + 7",
            "Answer": 143,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 13 + 15",
            "Answer": 106,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 0 + 15",
            "Answer": 15,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 1 + 10",
            "Answer": 10,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 4 + 10",
            "Answer": 10,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 8 + 5",
            "Answer": 13,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 19 + 2",
            "Answer": 116,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 15 + 18",
            "Answer": 78,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 7 + 1",
            "Answer": 99,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 19 + 15",
            "Answer": 72,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 18 + 8",
            "Answer": 206,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 0 + 3",
            "Answer": 3,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 8 + 17",
            "Answer": 113,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 1 + 11",
            "Answer": 18,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 7 + 10",
            "Answer": 38,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 13 + 9",
            "Answer": 74,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 9 + 10",
            "Answer": 19,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 13 + 19",
            "Answer": 149,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 18 + 2",
            "Answer": 92,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 12 + 13",
            "Answer": 241,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 1 + 9",
            "Answer": 15,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 12 + 11",
            "Answer": 119,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 9 + 2",
            "Answer": 65,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 5 + 19",
            "Answer": 74,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 11 + 1",
            "Answer": 67,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 12 + 15",
            "Answer": 27,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 5 + 3",
            "Answer": 48,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 11 + 15",
            "Answer": 136,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 16 + 6",
            "Answer": 230,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 11 + 2",
            "Answer": 24,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 16 + 12",
            "Answer": 284,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 2 + 2",
            "Answer": 18,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 14 + 8",
            "Answer": 120,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 16 + 11",
            "Answer": 299,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 1 + 7",
            "Answer": 24,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 0 + 14",
            "Answer": 14,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 0 + 8",
            "Answer": 8,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 12 + 15",
            "Answer": 171,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 13 + 6",
            "Answer": 19,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 13 + 14",
            "Answer": 157,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 16 + 11",
            "Answer": 75,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 19 + 9",
            "Answer": 142,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 14 + 13",
            "Answer": 139,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 4 + 11",
            "Answer": 43,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 15 + 6",
            "Answer": 81,
            "Predicate": "# * # + #"
        }
    ],
    "# + # + # * #": [
        {
            "Question": "7 + 12 + 12 * 8",
            "Answer": 115,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 17 + 0 * 16",
            "Answer": 33,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 13 + 14 * 10",
            "Answer": 160,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 1 + 11 * 10",
            "Answer": 112,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 0 + 2 * 7",
            "Answer": 25,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 1 + 11 * 19",
            "Answer": 217,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 11 + 19 * 8",
            "Answer": 177,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 2 + 18 * 12",
            "Answer": 235,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 17 + 0 * 17",
            "Answer": 24,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 12 + 5 * 1",
            "Answer": 18,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 10 + 14 * 17",
            "Answer": 248,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 0 + 15 * 9",
            "Answer": 145,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 11 + 6 * 3",
            "Answer": 40,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 19 + 17 * 15",
            "Answer": 291,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 4 + 12 * 0",
            "Answer": 16,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 5 + 2 * 2",
            "Answer": 20,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 8 + 19 * 13",
            "Answer": 269,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 18 + 13 * 11",
            "Answer": 180,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 15 + 9 * 6",
            "Answer": 81,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 11 + 11 * 13",
            "Answer": 171,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 6 + 17 * 17",
            "Answer": 297,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 7 + 7 * 0",
            "Answer": 19,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 16 + 4 * 5",
            "Answer": 52,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 0 + 3 * 6",
            "Answer": 34,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 7 + 8 * 13",
            "Answer": 129,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 13 + 0 * 5",
            "Answer": 27,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 3 + 3 * 11",
            "Answer": 45,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 2 + 18 * 4",
            "Answer": 84,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 15 + 0 * 13",
            "Answer": 24,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 13 + 1 * 15",
            "Answer": 29,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 2 + 7 * 18",
            "Answer": 146,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 5 + 5 * 14",
            "Answer": 77,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 16 + 0 * 15",
            "Answer": 16,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 12 + 14 * 0",
            "Answer": 22,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 0 + 15 * 11",
            "Answer": 167,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 12 + 6 * 18",
            "Answer": 138,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 5 + 0 * 4",
            "Answer": 21,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 10 + 19 * 12",
            "Answer": 257,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 0 + 9 * 12",
            "Answer": 115,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 16 + 7 * 1",
            "Answer": 28,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 9 + 15 * 9",
            "Answer": 149,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 1 + 3 * 8",
            "Answer": 35,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 17 + 12 * 7",
            "Answer": 111,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 11 + 1 * 6",
            "Answer": 21,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 16 + 11 * 10",
            "Answer": 133,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 0 + 18 * 6",
            "Answer": 124,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 12 + 5 * 1",
            "Answer": 23,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 0 + 11 * 8",
            "Answer": 88,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 13 + 2 * 2",
            "Answer": 24,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 6 + 7 * 15",
            "Answer": 127,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 15 + 0 * 1",
            "Answer": 16,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 16 + 12 * 2",
            "Answer": 40,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 15 + 3 * 19",
            "Answer": 89,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 12 + 8 * 13",
            "Answer": 131,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 16 + 14 * 2",
            "Answer": 58,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 14 + 8 * 1",
            "Answer": 33,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 13 + 17 * 4",
            "Answer": 86,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 8 + 0 * 11",
            "Answer": 16,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 17 + 1 * 19",
            "Answer": 46,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 19 + 3 * 6",
            "Answer": 37,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 0 + 18 * 5",
            "Answer": 93,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 3 + 15 * 11",
            "Answer": 174,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 10 + 1 * 10",
            "Answer": 30,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 4 + 13 * 11",
            "Answer": 156,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 15 + 14 * 9",
            "Answer": 157,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 0 + 7 * 16",
            "Answer": 126,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 6 + 14 * 9",
            "Answer": 143,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 13 + 19 * 3",
            "Answer": 78,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 4 + 16 * 3",
            "Answer": 64,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 17 + 10 * 10",
            "Answer": 121,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 18 + 9 * 3",
            "Answer": 50,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 8 + 12 * 14",
            "Answer": 189,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 16 + 14 * 5",
            "Answer": 101,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 3 + 16 * 19",
            "Answer": 307,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 4 + 7 * 6",
            "Answer": 46,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 7 + 10 * 4",
            "Answer": 50,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 6 + 13 * 8",
            "Answer": 122,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 12 + 2 * 16",
            "Answer": 61,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 3 + 14 * 19",
            "Answer": 281,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 13 + 9 * 4",
            "Answer": 67,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 3 + 19 * 4",
            "Answer": 81,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 18 + 16 * 13",
            "Answer": 226,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 12 + 11 * 19",
            "Answer": 234,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 17 + 15 * 4",
            "Answer": 85,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 1 + 7 * 12",
            "Answer": 87,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 11 + 9 * 5",
            "Answer": 70,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 19 + 3 * 10",
            "Answer": 59,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 14 + 14 * 16",
            "Answer": 256,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 6 + 11 * 8",
            "Answer": 100,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 5 + 8 * 10",
            "Answer": 103,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 15 + 17 * 5",
            "Answer": 116,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 4 + 1 * 10",
            "Answer": 20,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 8 + 4 * 7",
            "Answer": 37,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 13 + 16 * 1",
            "Answer": 47,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 12 + 1 * 12",
            "Answer": 25,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 13 + 13 * 14",
            "Answer": 200,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 3 + 18 * 13",
            "Answer": 256,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 14 + 4 * 7",
            "Answer": 59,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 6 + 12 * 9",
            "Answer": 132,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 1 + 0 * 16",
            "Answer": 5,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * #"
        }
    ],
    "# * # + # * #": [
        {
            "Question": "2 * 15 + 8 * 11",
            "Answer": 118,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 13 + 10 * 18",
            "Answer": 284,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 19 + 12 * 9",
            "Answer": 279,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 14 + 11 * 8",
            "Answer": 228,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 5 + 19 * 10",
            "Answer": 255,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 18 + 14 * 19",
            "Answer": 482,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 11 + 14 * 16",
            "Answer": 433,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 9 + 18 * 11",
            "Answer": 333,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 15 + 13 * 9",
            "Answer": 192,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 2 + 13 * 1",
            "Answer": 25,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 19 + 2 * 12",
            "Answer": 195,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 11 + 12 * 14",
            "Answer": 322,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 1 + 13 * 0",
            "Answer": 3,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 13 + 9 * 12",
            "Answer": 238,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 5 + 18 * 10",
            "Answer": 240,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 10 + 13 * 15",
            "Answer": 255,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 12 + 9 * 14",
            "Answer": 306,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 0 + 1 * 1",
            "Answer": 1,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 15 + 12 * 14",
            "Answer": 438,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 4 + 4 * 3",
            "Answer": 28,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 18 + 15 * 14",
            "Answer": 372,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 12 + 14 * 4",
            "Answer": 164,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 12 + 7 * 9",
            "Answer": 135,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 16 + 9 * 9",
            "Answer": 241,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 17 + 3 * 0",
            "Answer": 119,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 5 + 11 * 0",
            "Answer": 45,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 9 + 5 * 0",
            "Answer": 9,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 19 + 0 * 0",
            "Answer": 190,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 16 + 15 * 11",
            "Answer": 405,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 19 + 16 * 6",
            "Answer": 191,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 11 + 8 * 13",
            "Answer": 247,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 19 + 14 * 19",
            "Answer": 380,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 4 + 7 * 10",
            "Answer": 138,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 18 + 3 * 2",
            "Answer": 312,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 18 + 0 * 15",
            "Answer": 234,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 1 + 8 * 18",
            "Answer": 157,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 4 + 11 * 10",
            "Answer": 170,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 11 + 6 * 1",
            "Answer": 50,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 14 + 5 * 10",
            "Answer": 288,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 16 + 12 * 17",
            "Answer": 460,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 4 + 8 * 1",
            "Answer": 16,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 11 + 16 * 0",
            "Answer": 143,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 8 + 3 * 17",
            "Answer": 107,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 0 + 11 * 14",
            "Answer": 154,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 1 + 0 * 18",
            "Answer": 10,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 7 + 16 * 13",
            "Answer": 222,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 10 + 15 * 7",
            "Answer": 195,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 7 + 15 * 0",
            "Answer": 105,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 13 + 19 * 7",
            "Answer": 315,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 7 + 16 * 7",
            "Answer": 133,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 7 + 8 * 18",
            "Answer": 151,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 15 + 2 * 16",
            "Answer": 197,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 13 + 11 * 2",
            "Answer": 165,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 6 + 11 * 18",
            "Answer": 198,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 16 + 0 * 8",
            "Answer": 64,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 2 + 10 * 13",
            "Answer": 154,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 14 + 6 * 13",
            "Answer": 260,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 8 + 8 * 16",
            "Answer": 240,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 12 + 1 * 12",
            "Answer": 84,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 10 + 14 * 10",
            "Answer": 300,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 11 + 16 * 9",
            "Answer": 155,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 10 + 11 * 18",
            "Answer": 368,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 6 + 12 * 14",
            "Answer": 234,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 7 + 17 * 15",
            "Answer": 318,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 7 + 2 * 15",
            "Answer": 58,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 4 + 18 * 5",
            "Answer": 126,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 6 + 1 * 14",
            "Answer": 128,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 14 + 7 * 13",
            "Answer": 147,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 6 + 14 * 4",
            "Answer": 164,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 2 + 4 * 6",
            "Answer": 44,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 13 + 8 * 14",
            "Answer": 151,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 15 + 9 * 10",
            "Answer": 285,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 18 + 5 * 16",
            "Answer": 242,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 9 + 0 * 15",
            "Answer": 162,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 7 + 1 * 6",
            "Answer": 97,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 7 + 8 * 10",
            "Answer": 178,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 7 + 12 * 16",
            "Answer": 269,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 17 + 4 * 17",
            "Answer": 374,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 2 + 10 * 7",
            "Answer": 106,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 12 + 15 * 17",
            "Answer": 267,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 0 + 1 * 17",
            "Answer": 17,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 3 + 11 * 6",
            "Answer": 93,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 18 + 18 * 3",
            "Answer": 306,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 5 + 0 * 17",
            "Answer": 15,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 16 + 17 * 13",
            "Answer": 397,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 10 + 10 * 8",
            "Answer": 190,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 14 + 16 * 8",
            "Answer": 380,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 6 + 6 * 14",
            "Answer": 156,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 16 + 4 * 2",
            "Answer": 88,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 19 + 14 * 10",
            "Answer": 140,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 6 + 12 * 10",
            "Answer": 228,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 15 + 12 * 13",
            "Answer": 411,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 12 + 17 * 4",
            "Answer": 200,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 14 + 15 * 4",
            "Answer": 312,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 15 + 14 * 6",
            "Answer": 114,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 1 + 7 * 10",
            "Answer": 87,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 14 + 16 * 16",
            "Answer": 452,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 15 + 13 * 4",
            "Answer": 127,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 13 + 7 * 17",
            "Answer": 210,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 0 + 18 * 15",
            "Answer": 270,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * #"
        }
    ],
    "# + # * # + #": [
        {
            "Question": "15 + 8 * 18 + 14",
            "Answer": 173,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 7 * 6 + 5",
            "Answer": 56,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 14 * 5 + 13",
            "Answer": 88,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 18 * 12 + 7",
            "Answer": 231,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 17 * 8 + 5",
            "Answer": 158,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 0 * 17 + 10",
            "Answer": 29,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 6 * 9 + 3",
            "Answer": 74,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 6 * 19 + 11",
            "Answer": 132,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 12 * 7 + 2",
            "Answer": 98,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 19 * 13 + 10",
            "Answer": 260,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 15 * 11 + 3",
            "Answer": 172,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 12 * 5 + 13",
            "Answer": 73,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 14 * 16 + 3",
            "Answer": 244,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 5 * 0 + 4",
            "Answer": 9,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 6 * 17 + 5",
            "Answer": 119,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 15 * 11 + 1",
            "Answer": 171,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 11 * 10 + 10",
            "Answer": 121,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 1 * 16 + 0",
            "Answer": 23,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 2 * 16 + 0",
            "Answer": 33,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 1 * 16 + 0",
            "Answer": 20,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 15 * 19 + 17",
            "Answer": 309,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 0 * 12 + 9",
            "Answer": 22,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 16 * 6 + 11",
            "Answer": 109,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 6 * 0 + 16",
            "Answer": 18,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 12 * 12 + 1",
            "Answer": 163,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 17 * 7 + 3",
            "Answer": 126,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 10 * 2 + 7",
            "Answer": 28,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 5 * 17 + 16",
            "Answer": 108,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 11 * 17 + 13",
            "Answer": 214,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 3 * 4 + 19",
            "Answer": 39,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 10 * 15 + 5",
            "Answer": 165,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 12 * 4 + 6",
            "Answer": 55,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 9 * 11 + 2",
            "Answer": 120,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 8 * 10 + 6",
            "Answer": 99,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 14 * 17 + 1",
            "Answer": 243,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 13 * 0 + 5",
            "Answer": 7,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 10 * 19 + 2",
            "Answer": 192,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 9 * 10 + 13",
            "Answer": 120,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 15 * 0 + 3",
            "Answer": 6,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 12 * 16 + 19",
            "Answer": 220,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 4 * 1 + 3",
            "Answer": 25,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 2 * 10 + 14",
            "Answer": 35,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 19 * 16 + 6",
            "Answer": 327,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 6 * 3 + 1",
            "Answer": 19,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 11 * 16 + 14",
            "Answer": 202,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 8 * 0 + 2",
            "Answer": 11,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 12 * 8 + 15",
            "Answer": 129,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 0 * 4 + 1",
            "Answer": 5,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 17 * 13 + 19",
            "Answer": 247,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 13 * 16 + 19",
            "Answer": 232,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 10 * 5 + 2",
            "Answer": 52,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 7 * 14 + 16",
            "Answer": 126,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 12 * 15 + 16",
            "Answer": 212,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 19 * 12 + 19",
            "Answer": 248,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 4 * 13 + 5",
            "Answer": 69,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 17 * 12 + 4",
            "Answer": 220,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 19 * 17 + 1",
            "Answer": 341,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 10 * 16 + 1",
            "Answer": 163,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 7 * 2 + 16",
            "Answer": 30,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 11 * 1 + 14",
            "Answer": 32,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 1 * 16 + 14",
            "Answer": 35,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 8 * 3 + 7",
            "Answer": 40,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 13 * 4 + 7",
            "Answer": 68,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 9 * 17 + 18",
            "Answer": 174,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 13 * 16 + 5",
            "Answer": 232,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 17 * 19 + 4",
            "Answer": 344,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 18 * 0 + 5",
            "Answer": 16,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 19 * 17 + 10",
            "Answer": 341,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 10 * 4 + 12",
            "Answer": 52,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 15 * 13 + 15",
            "Answer": 217,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 13 * 1 + 15",
            "Answer": 32,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 16 * 3 + 9",
            "Answer": 58,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 0 * 7 + 9",
            "Answer": 19,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 17 * 19 + 18",
            "Answer": 342,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 17 * 14 + 6",
            "Answer": 251,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 7 * 0 + 3",
            "Answer": 16,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 16 * 1 + 8",
            "Answer": 34,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 4 * 7 + 14",
            "Answer": 59,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 17 * 2 + 4",
            "Answer": 47,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 14 * 7 + 16",
            "Answer": 127,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 18 * 11 + 10",
            "Answer": 221,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 5 * 2 + 12",
            "Answer": 29,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 7 * 18 + 15",
            "Answer": 149,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 5 * 17 + 16",
            "Answer": 109,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 0 * 5 + 18",
            "Answer": 32,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 4 * 17 + 4",
            "Answer": 87,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 9 * 10 + 9",
            "Answer": 108,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 15 * 0 + 2",
            "Answer": 9,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 18 * 1 + 2",
            "Answer": 27,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 14 * 3 + 4",
            "Answer": 50,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 7 * 10 + 12",
            "Answer": 96,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 14 * 5 + 0",
            "Answer": 83,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 17 * 17 + 18",
            "Answer": 321,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 15 * 0 + 15",
            "Answer": 15,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 3 * 11 + 5",
            "Answer": 53,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 6 * 6 + 17",
            "Answer": 70,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 3 * 12 + 18",
            "Answer": 54,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 19 * 1 + 12",
            "Answer": 44,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 14 * 1 + 13",
            "Answer": 41,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 17 * 2 + 4",
            "Answer": 47,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + #"
        }
    ],
    "# * # * # + #": [
        {
            "Question": "5 * 6 * 18 + 16",
            "Answer": 556,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 10 * 9 + 6",
            "Answer": 366,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 18 * 5 + 7",
            "Answer": 1357,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 18 * 18 + 19",
            "Answer": 19,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 1 * 7 + 16",
            "Answer": 30,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 16 * 1 + 7",
            "Answer": 39,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 18 * 19 + 14",
            "Answer": 6512,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 12 * 17 + 0",
            "Answer": 816,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 6 * 17 + 6",
            "Answer": 1230,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 9 * 3 + 1",
            "Answer": 82,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 2 * 7 + 3",
            "Answer": 115,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 2 * 9 + 15",
            "Answer": 339,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 19 * 13 + 6",
            "Answer": 3958,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 18 * 10 + 1",
            "Answer": 1621,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 10 * 19 + 19",
            "Answer": 2869,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 10 * 14 + 9",
            "Answer": 1829,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 11 * 16 + 1",
            "Answer": 1937,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 5 * 3 + 14",
            "Answer": 269,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 8 * 19 + 17",
            "Answer": 473,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 0 * 5 + 11",
            "Answer": 11,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 10 * 8 + 12",
            "Answer": 1132,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 12 * 5 + 1",
            "Answer": 361,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 18 * 7 + 6",
            "Answer": 1770,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 4 * 8 + 0",
            "Answer": 576,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 9 * 18 + 2",
            "Answer": 1784,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 12 * 12 + 11",
            "Answer": 2459,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 0 * 4 + 19",
            "Answer": 19,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 3 * 10 + 1",
            "Answer": 271,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 13 * 3 + 6",
            "Answer": 240,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 5 * 12 + 0",
            "Answer": 960,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 15 * 15 + 8",
            "Answer": 2933,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 17 * 4 + 9",
            "Answer": 621,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 5 * 16 + 2",
            "Answer": 962,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 6 * 10 + 0",
            "Answer": 840,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 8 * 6 + 1",
            "Answer": 289,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 12 * 2 + 10",
            "Answer": 394,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 13 * 11 + 1",
            "Answer": 287,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 9 * 8 + 11",
            "Answer": 1091,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 8 * 16 + 3",
            "Answer": 2179,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 18 * 17 + 19",
            "Answer": 4915,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 6 * 17 + 12",
            "Answer": 1746,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 12 * 6 + 3",
            "Answer": 1083,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 1 * 10 + 4",
            "Answer": 144,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 0 * 0 + 6",
            "Answer": 6,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 17 * 13 + 0",
            "Answer": 3978,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 17 * 17 + 12",
            "Answer": 879,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 8 * 2 + 17",
            "Answer": 241,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 0 * 10 + 1",
            "Answer": 1,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 3 * 16 + 11",
            "Answer": 251,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 12 * 12 + 3",
            "Answer": 147,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 9 * 14 + 5",
            "Answer": 383,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 2 * 0 + 2",
            "Answer": 2,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 1 * 8 + 11",
            "Answer": 19,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 16 * 15 + 8",
            "Answer": 3848,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 7 * 15 + 18",
            "Answer": 18,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 10 * 14 + 11",
            "Answer": 1411,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 11 * 13 + 10",
            "Answer": 1869,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 5 * 2 + 4",
            "Answer": 44,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 1 * 15 + 19",
            "Answer": 64,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 5 * 4 + 3",
            "Answer": 303,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 9 * 0 + 3",
            "Answer": 3,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 17 * 10 + 3",
            "Answer": 2383,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 8 * 4 + 10",
            "Answer": 522,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 11 * 7 + 15",
            "Answer": 862,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 18 * 12 + 10",
            "Answer": 2602,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 13 * 9 + 3",
            "Answer": 471,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 15 * 6 + 7",
            "Answer": 97,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 7 * 4 + 18",
            "Answer": 74,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 7 * 2 + 18",
            "Answer": 46,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 9 * 9 + 17",
            "Answer": 1232,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 7 * 2 + 9",
            "Answer": 247,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 16 * 5 + 4",
            "Answer": 1364,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 10 * 7 + 13",
            "Answer": 293,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 19 * 11 + 19",
            "Answer": 646,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 14 * 16 + 6",
            "Answer": 1126,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 14 * 16 + 13",
            "Answer": 2477,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 2 * 6 + 4",
            "Answer": 232,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 14 * 9 + 11",
            "Answer": 641,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 4 * 11 + 0",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 18 * 15 + 2",
            "Answer": 2702,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 12 * 19 + 15",
            "Answer": 1839,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 6 * 13 + 8",
            "Answer": 1100,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 18 * 6 + 19",
            "Answer": 775,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 16 * 17 + 2",
            "Answer": 4082,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 4 * 11 + 19",
            "Answer": 415,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 14 * 18 + 6",
            "Answer": 1266,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 1 * 15 + 15",
            "Answer": 180,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 15 * 0 + 7",
            "Answer": 7,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 2 * 5 + 1",
            "Answer": 81,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 16 * 12 + 9",
            "Answer": 3273,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 18 * 5 + 12",
            "Answer": 912,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 0 * 18 + 4",
            "Answer": 4,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 12 * 5 + 0",
            "Answer": 120,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 12 * 16 + 11",
            "Answer": 3083,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 0 * 3 + 0",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 17 * 12 + 1",
            "Answer": 2449,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 6 * 16 + 0",
            "Answer": 1824,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 5 * 16 + 19",
            "Answer": 1299,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 6 * 4 + 19",
            "Answer": 403,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 5 * 13 + 9",
            "Answer": 594,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + #"
        }
    ],
    "# + # + # + #": [
        {
            "Question": "5 + 18 + 8 + 19",
            "Answer": 50,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 13 + 12 + 6",
            "Answer": 41,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 16 + 19 + 1",
            "Answer": 44,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 0 + 9 + 13",
            "Answer": 37,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 14 + 17 + 18",
            "Answer": 57,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 17 + 12 + 7",
            "Answer": 43,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 2 + 18 + 1",
            "Answer": 24,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 18 + 11 + 12",
            "Answer": 55,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 16 + 17 + 4",
            "Answer": 51,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 16 + 10 + 5",
            "Answer": 45,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 0 + 4 + 3",
            "Answer": 7,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 5 + 17 + 0",
            "Answer": 33,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 9 + 19 + 9",
            "Answer": 53,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 15 + 17 + 18",
            "Answer": 67,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 4 + 16 + 15",
            "Answer": 45,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 8 + 2 + 19",
            "Answer": 47,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 11 + 2 + 0",
            "Answer": 24,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 6 + 4 + 8",
            "Answer": 26,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 8 + 2 + 14",
            "Answer": 40,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 7 + 13 + 10",
            "Answer": 41,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 14 + 15 + 8",
            "Answer": 52,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 7 + 10 + 8",
            "Answer": 27,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 7 + 2 + 5",
            "Answer": 21,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 9 + 16 + 4",
            "Answer": 36,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 19 + 16 + 18",
            "Answer": 60,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 13 + 6 + 14",
            "Answer": 43,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 17 + 9 + 14",
            "Answer": 48,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 4 + 13 + 12",
            "Answer": 32,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 5 + 2 + 0",
            "Answer": 12,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 18 + 12 + 1",
            "Answer": 49,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 4 + 3 + 1",
            "Answer": 26,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 12 + 19 + 13",
            "Answer": 57,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 19 + 8 + 1",
            "Answer": 40,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 9 + 18 + 7",
            "Answer": 45,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 13 + 13 + 9",
            "Answer": 49,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 13 + 16 + 1",
            "Answer": 48,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 12 + 15 + 6",
            "Answer": 37,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 6 + 10 + 4",
            "Answer": 34,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 0 + 17 + 5",
            "Answer": 25,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 18 + 7 + 18",
            "Answer": 48,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 0 + 9 + 16",
            "Answer": 44,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 5 + 6 + 7",
            "Answer": 35,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 14 + 14 + 6",
            "Answer": 34,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 12 + 14 + 15",
            "Answer": 45,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 7 + 10 + 15",
            "Answer": 46,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 10 + 5 + 1",
            "Answer": 16,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 2 + 18 + 13",
            "Answer": 41,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 0 + 4 + 10",
            "Answer": 27,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 13 + 19 + 14",
            "Answer": 48,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 4 + 2 + 3",
            "Answer": 14,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 13 + 8 + 8",
            "Answer": 46,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 1 + 2 + 16",
            "Answer": 36,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 1 + 5 + 12",
            "Answer": 30,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 11 + 3 + 3",
            "Answer": 35,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 5 + 8 + 17",
            "Answer": 30,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 0 + 8 + 3",
            "Answer": 25,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 4 + 19 + 5",
            "Answer": 33,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 18 + 9 + 16",
            "Answer": 56,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 12 + 7 + 16",
            "Answer": 51,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 19 + 11 + 5",
            "Answer": 54,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 4 + 6 + 11",
            "Answer": 37,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 6 + 12 + 6",
            "Answer": 36,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 9 + 11 + 10",
            "Answer": 31,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 12 + 12 + 10",
            "Answer": 35,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 9 + 15 + 19",
            "Answer": 46,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 4 + 19 + 6",
            "Answer": 46,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 19 + 5 + 13",
            "Answer": 49,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 8 + 14 + 11",
            "Answer": 36,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 15 + 10 + 5",
            "Answer": 40,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 17 + 7 + 11",
            "Answer": 46,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 11 + 9 + 8",
            "Answer": 41,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 2 + 8 + 3",
            "Answer": 18,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 13 + 2 + 11",
            "Answer": 27,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 14 + 9 + 8",
            "Answer": 35,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 13 + 15 + 13",
            "Answer": 60,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 9 + 17 + 8",
            "Answer": 47,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 5 + 9 + 18",
            "Answer": 37,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 5 + 6 + 15",
            "Answer": 43,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 11 + 17 + 4",
            "Answer": 51,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 19 + 5 + 16",
            "Answer": 51,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 6 + 0 + 4",
            "Answer": 28,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 8 + 2 + 3",
            "Answer": 23,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 1 + 18 + 14",
            "Answer": 45,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 6 + 4 + 7",
            "Answer": 34,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 5 + 4 + 9",
            "Answer": 35,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 19 + 13 + 8",
            "Answer": 40,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 3 + 15 + 18",
            "Answer": 39,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 6 + 15 + 2",
            "Answer": 42,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 0 + 12 + 5",
            "Answer": 27,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 3 + 8 + 0",
            "Answer": 19,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 10 + 1 + 14",
            "Answer": 36,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 18 + 1 + 18",
            "Answer": 42,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 14 + 7 + 17",
            "Answer": 47,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 8 + 0 + 2",
            "Answer": 24,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 17 + 9 + 9",
            "Answer": 40,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 12 + 9 + 9",
            "Answer": 45,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 8 + 10 + 18",
            "Answer": 47,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 19 + 3 + 1",
            "Answer": 39,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 9 + 13 + 8",
            "Answer": 30,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 5 + 19 + 14",
            "Answer": 41,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + #"
        }
    ],
    "# + # * # * #": [
        {
            "Question": "16 + 13 * 10 * 14",
            "Answer": 1836,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 10 * 19 * 3",
            "Answer": 572,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 3 * 16 * 15",
            "Answer": 728,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 0 * 13 * 6",
            "Answer": 1,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 15 * 8 * 9",
            "Answer": 1089,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 0 * 11 * 0",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 18 * 1 * 7",
            "Answer": 129,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 3 * 4 * 10",
            "Answer": 121,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 18 * 6 * 15",
            "Answer": 1622,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 13 * 6 * 7",
            "Answer": 554,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 18 * 7 * 6",
            "Answer": 760,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 16 * 8 * 11",
            "Answer": 1427,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 0 * 7 * 1",
            "Answer": 5,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 8 * 17 * 17",
            "Answer": 2324,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 11 * 11 * 18",
            "Answer": 2189,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 2 * 7 * 2",
            "Answer": 47,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 12 * 18 * 1",
            "Answer": 222,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 1 * 9 * 18",
            "Answer": 167,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 6 * 3 * 6",
            "Answer": 122,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 7 * 12 * 17",
            "Answer": 1439,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 4 * 5 * 3",
            "Answer": 79,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 10 * 12 * 2",
            "Answer": 247,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 15 * 19 * 18",
            "Answer": 5145,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 8 * 18 * 6",
            "Answer": 880,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 18 * 18 * 13",
            "Answer": 4223,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 11 * 0 * 12",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 12 * 5 * 15",
            "Answer": 901,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 5 * 19 * 16",
            "Answer": 1526,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 15 * 4 * 14",
            "Answer": 842,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 0 * 16 * 17",
            "Answer": 5,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 2 * 19 * 19",
            "Answer": 722,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 5 * 17 * 10",
            "Answer": 850,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 1 * 7 * 9",
            "Answer": 66,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 1 * 8 * 12",
            "Answer": 96,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 1 * 8 * 3",
            "Answer": 25,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 19 * 12 * 13",
            "Answer": 2971,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 4 * 2 * 15",
            "Answer": 137,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 13 * 2 * 15",
            "Answer": 407,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 15 * 17 * 9",
            "Answer": 2309,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 4 * 0 * 16",
            "Answer": 10,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 8 * 2 * 18",
            "Answer": 306,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 8 * 10 * 6",
            "Answer": 490,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 19 * 16 * 5",
            "Answer": 1526,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 16 * 7 * 14",
            "Answer": 1581,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 17 * 10 * 9",
            "Answer": 1538,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 14 * 2 * 16",
            "Answer": 463,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 13 * 1 * 11",
            "Answer": 144,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 16 * 1 * 13",
            "Answer": 214,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 12 * 2 * 12",
            "Answer": 301,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 5 * 17 * 18",
            "Answer": 1540,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 2 * 16 * 0",
            "Answer": 11,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 0 * 12 * 0",
            "Answer": 9,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 5 * 19 * 17",
            "Answer": 1630,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 0 * 18 * 11",
            "Answer": 14,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 18 * 8 * 17",
            "Answer": 2463,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 14 * 10 * 9",
            "Answer": 1261,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 5 * 11 * 5",
            "Answer": 275,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 14 * 17 * 8",
            "Answer": 1921,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 4 * 1 * 13",
            "Answer": 67,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 8 * 4 * 6",
            "Answer": 202,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 15 * 0 * 8",
            "Answer": 6,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 8 * 17 * 9",
            "Answer": 1235,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 18 * 9 * 7",
            "Answer": 1153,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 9 * 2 * 12",
            "Answer": 226,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 7 * 5 * 19",
            "Answer": 676,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 1 * 11 * 1",
            "Answer": 19,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 5 * 19 * 12",
            "Answer": 1147,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 12 * 6 * 13",
            "Answer": 944,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 1 * 18 * 2",
            "Answer": 38,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 3 * 16 * 7",
            "Answer": 336,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 18 * 13 * 3",
            "Answer": 715,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 8 * 4 * 3",
            "Answer": 107,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 12 * 4 * 6",
            "Answer": 294,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 15 * 13 * 9",
            "Answer": 1773,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 5 * 17 * 16",
            "Answer": 1367,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 4 * 16 * 19",
            "Answer": 1219,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 0 * 9 * 2",
            "Answer": 3,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 8 * 9 * 6",
            "Answer": 450,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 15 * 2 * 12",
            "Answer": 365,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 13 * 4 * 5",
            "Answer": 260,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 17 * 8 * 4",
            "Answer": 549,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 7 * 12 * 4",
            "Answer": 355,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 9 * 17 * 15",
            "Answer": 2304,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 0 * 16 * 5",
            "Answer": 9,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 2 * 5 * 6",
            "Answer": 76,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 11 * 11 * 7",
            "Answer": 863,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 17 * 18 * 7",
            "Answer": 2149,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 15 * 9 * 11",
            "Answer": 1502,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 13 * 17 * 6",
            "Answer": 1342,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 0 * 14 * 3",
            "Answer": 2,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 5 * 11 * 10",
            "Answer": 550,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 18 * 19 * 13",
            "Answer": 4465,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 10 * 12 * 19",
            "Answer": 2284,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 5 * 10 * 2",
            "Answer": 108,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 5 * 2 * 11",
            "Answer": 124,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 17 * 6 * 5",
            "Answer": 516,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 6 * 5 * 11",
            "Answer": 332,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 8 * 13 * 2",
            "Answer": 225,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 8 * 16 * 13",
            "Answer": 1669,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 9 * 11 * 16",
            "Answer": 1602,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * #"
        }
    ],
    "# * # + # + #": [
        {
            "Question": "17 * 1 + 7 + 4",
            "Answer": 28,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 11 + 13 + 7",
            "Answer": 196,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 10 + 2 + 18",
            "Answer": 200,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 3 + 13 + 0",
            "Answer": 43,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 7 + 18 + 17",
            "Answer": 63,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 4 + 1 + 6",
            "Answer": 7,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 5 + 14 + 4",
            "Answer": 98,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 1 + 5 + 0",
            "Answer": 10,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 6 + 12 + 3",
            "Answer": 69,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 13 + 18 + 13",
            "Answer": 148,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 3 + 11 + 12",
            "Answer": 56,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 16 + 16 + 14",
            "Answer": 302,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 5 + 12 + 17",
            "Answer": 69,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 6 + 15 + 8",
            "Answer": 137,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 15 + 8 + 13",
            "Answer": 231,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 18 + 5 + 0",
            "Answer": 329,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 15 + 9 + 10",
            "Answer": 64,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 13 + 17 + 2",
            "Answer": 110,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 4 + 11 + 14",
            "Answer": 33,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 13 + 19 + 10",
            "Answer": 120,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 12 + 9 + 2",
            "Answer": 11,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 3 + 7 + 0",
            "Answer": 46,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 15 + 16 + 11",
            "Answer": 57,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 9 + 13 + 17",
            "Answer": 57,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 3 + 13 + 10",
            "Answer": 80,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 3 + 17 + 13",
            "Answer": 75,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 3 + 10 + 18",
            "Answer": 58,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 14 + 15 + 9",
            "Answer": 108,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 18 + 5 + 3",
            "Answer": 80,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 10 + 9 + 10",
            "Answer": 89,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 8 + 16 + 5",
            "Answer": 37,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 16 + 5 + 6",
            "Answer": 155,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 2 + 0 + 0",
            "Answer": 2,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 11 + 3 + 2",
            "Answer": 104,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 15 + 8 + 15",
            "Answer": 53,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 11 + 1 + 0",
            "Answer": 144,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 10 + 0 + 6",
            "Answer": 136,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 17 + 9 + 3",
            "Answer": 182,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 9 + 14 + 6",
            "Answer": 101,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 1 + 19 + 18",
            "Answer": 54,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 13 + 7 + 15",
            "Answer": 152,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 19 + 7 + 16",
            "Answer": 80,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 19 + 13 + 17",
            "Answer": 353,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 15 + 4 + 19",
            "Answer": 218,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 13 + 13 + 3",
            "Answer": 250,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 17 + 9 + 18",
            "Answer": 129,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 0 + 2 + 4",
            "Answer": 6,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 11 + 14 + 19",
            "Answer": 242,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 17 + 5 + 7",
            "Answer": 250,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 13 + 1 + 2",
            "Answer": 107,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 2 + 6 + 4",
            "Answer": 28,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 6 + 18 + 3",
            "Answer": 57,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 16 + 14 + 0",
            "Answer": 30,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 15 + 2 + 1",
            "Answer": 183,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 0 + 5 + 14",
            "Answer": 19,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 17 + 15 + 13",
            "Answer": 300,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 14 + 13 + 14",
            "Answer": 195,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 4 + 16 + 17",
            "Answer": 45,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 18 + 14 + 12",
            "Answer": 98,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 11 + 5 + 15",
            "Answer": 218,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 16 + 14 + 3",
            "Answer": 113,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 13 + 11 + 16",
            "Answer": 248,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 12 + 10 + 19",
            "Answer": 41,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 19 + 2 + 3",
            "Answer": 157,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 9 + 14 + 5",
            "Answer": 73,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 1 + 14 + 4",
            "Answer": 32,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 16 + 19 + 11",
            "Answer": 174,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 6 + 10 + 14",
            "Answer": 120,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 5 + 14 + 4",
            "Answer": 18,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 19 + 19 + 14",
            "Answer": 337,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 12 + 4 + 9",
            "Answer": 181,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 0 + 10 + 4",
            "Answer": 14,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 10 + 1 + 5",
            "Answer": 36,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 15 + 14 + 6",
            "Answer": 155,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 6 + 19 + 3",
            "Answer": 124,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 6 + 16 + 15",
            "Answer": 91,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 0 + 11 + 10",
            "Answer": 21,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 10 + 3 + 19",
            "Answer": 172,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 11 + 5 + 19",
            "Answer": 156,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 8 + 4 + 10",
            "Answer": 94,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 0 + 9 + 9",
            "Answer": 18,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 9 + 10 + 14",
            "Answer": 159,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 17 + 5 + 9",
            "Answer": 167,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 17 + 2 + 11",
            "Answer": 285,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 19 + 16 + 15",
            "Answer": 354,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 2 + 6 + 4",
            "Answer": 40,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 18 + 9 + 4",
            "Answer": 265,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 12 + 19 + 9",
            "Answer": 184,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 12 + 17 + 11",
            "Answer": 196,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 3 + 7 + 0",
            "Answer": 61,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 6 + 2 + 13",
            "Answer": 129,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 14 + 9 + 7",
            "Answer": 128,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 16 + 9 + 9",
            "Answer": 274,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 16 + 10 + 7",
            "Answer": 209,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 3 + 8 + 10",
            "Answer": 45,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 12 + 1 + 11",
            "Answer": 84,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 2 + 19 + 15",
            "Answer": 36,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 14 + 2 + 10",
            "Answer": 180,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 9 + 5 + 5",
            "Answer": 109,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 0 + 7 + 10",
            "Answer": 17,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + #"
        }
    ],
    "# * # * # * #": [
        {
            "Question": "5 * 7 * 0 * 1",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 8 * 4 * 6",
            "Answer": 3072,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 12 * 8 * 13",
            "Answer": 21216,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 18 * 14 * 14",
            "Answer": 67032,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 8 * 8 * 1",
            "Answer": 704,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 12 * 18 * 11",
            "Answer": 28512,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 17 * 16 * 7",
            "Answer": 13328,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 11 * 14 * 5",
            "Answer": 7700,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 5 * 16 * 7",
            "Answer": 1680,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 9 * 4 * 13",
            "Answer": 7020,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 14 * 17 * 0",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 13 * 14 * 9",
            "Answer": 9828,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 10 * 18 * 11",
            "Answer": 1980,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 7 * 4 * 1",
            "Answer": 140,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 6 * 14 * 12",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 7 * 9 * 13",
            "Answer": 5733,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 1 * 6 * 12",
            "Answer": 1224,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 12 * 6 * 3",
            "Answer": 216,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 14 * 14 * 16",
            "Answer": 3136,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 12 * 15 * 3",
            "Answer": 1080,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 11 * 1 * 5",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 16 * 19 * 7",
            "Answer": 27664,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 10 * 11 * 8",
            "Answer": 3520,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 13 * 17 * 7",
            "Answer": 15470,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 17 * 16 * 11",
            "Answer": 14960,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 15 * 16 * 2",
            "Answer": 4320,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 13 * 6 * 6",
            "Answer": 8424,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 19 * 14 * 7",
            "Answer": 7448,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 1 * 16 * 13",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 8 * 4 * 9",
            "Answer": 1152,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 18 * 8 * 5",
            "Answer": 8640,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 10 * 13 * 3",
            "Answer": 1560,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 19 * 2 * 7",
            "Answer": 2128,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 9 * 12 * 15",
            "Answer": 8100,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 3 * 9 * 9",
            "Answer": 4374,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 5 * 17 * 6",
            "Answer": 1020,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 11 * 5 * 6",
            "Answer": 1650,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 11 * 17 * 14",
            "Answer": 5236,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 7 * 4 * 11",
            "Answer": 616,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 0 * 14 * 16",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 17 * 17 * 17",
            "Answer": 9826,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 0 * 11 * 9",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 2 * 4 * 2",
            "Answer": 144,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 10 * 19 * 12",
            "Answer": 6840,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 9 * 16 * 10",
            "Answer": 27360,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 11 * 7 * 4",
            "Answer": 924,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 8 * 3 * 0",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 18 * 5 * 11",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 7 * 18 * 0",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 5 * 16 * 16",
            "Answer": 23040,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 0 * 0 * 12",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 11 * 1 * 4",
            "Answer": 836,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 16 * 14 * 13",
            "Answer": 5824,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 2 * 19 * 12",
            "Answer": 1368,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 15 * 10 * 1",
            "Answer": 750,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 1 * 8 * 5",
            "Answer": 520,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 16 * 2 * 5",
            "Answer": 1280,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 13 * 8 * 19",
            "Answer": 9880,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 14 * 19 * 18",
            "Answer": 28728,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 17 * 0 * 14",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 18 * 7 * 18",
            "Answer": 15876,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 12 * 2 * 7",
            "Answer": 2688,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 10 * 3 * 6",
            "Answer": 2520,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 8 * 18 * 16",
            "Answer": 11520,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 13 * 3 * 1",
            "Answer": 585,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 12 * 7 * 2",
            "Answer": 3192,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 2 * 19 * 4",
            "Answer": 2888,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 0 * 19 * 18",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 18 * 7 * 7",
            "Answer": 15876,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 3 * 15 * 10",
            "Answer": 7200,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 7 * 19 * 19",
            "Answer": 42959,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 12 * 16 * 19",
            "Answer": 65664,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 17 * 15 * 9",
            "Answer": 22950,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 6 * 14 * 5",
            "Answer": 5460,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 1 * 6 * 4",
            "Answer": 216,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 7 * 17 * 9",
            "Answer": 20349,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 15 * 17 * 18",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 3 * 4 * 6",
            "Answer": 360,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 0 * 16 * 10",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 15 * 18 * 1",
            "Answer": 1080,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 5 * 16 * 15",
            "Answer": 2400,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 9 * 2 * 2",
            "Answer": 216,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 15 * 6 * 16",
            "Answer": 8640,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 15 * 15 * 17",
            "Answer": 15300,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 19 * 18 * 16",
            "Answer": 60192,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 3 * 0 * 9",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 4 * 0 * 6",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 4 * 14 * 14",
            "Answer": 6272,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 16 * 5 * 7",
            "Answer": 560,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 4 * 1 * 17",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 12 * 2 * 10",
            "Answer": 4080,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 19 * 2 * 6",
            "Answer": 3876,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 0 * 15 * 8",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 9 * 13 * 15",
            "Answer": 19305,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 9 * 6 * 8",
            "Answer": 8208,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 10 * 14 * 13",
            "Answer": 1820,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 18 * 6 * 3",
            "Answer": 4860,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 18 * 3 * 5",
            "Answer": 1890,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 10 * 8 * 2",
            "Answer": 1120,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 15 * 19 * 18",
            "Answer": 76950,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * #"
        }
    ],
    "# + # * # * # * #": [
        {
            "Question": "5 + 12 * 6 * 15 * 13",
            "Answer": 14045,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 1 * 18 * 1 * 9",
            "Answer": 168,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 13 * 11 * 17 * 1",
            "Answer": 2432,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 5 * 14 * 19 * 12",
            "Answer": 15965,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 3 * 9 * 18 * 10",
            "Answer": 4876,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 18 * 7 * 19 * 3",
            "Answer": 7193,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 13 * 11 * 9 * 4",
            "Answer": 5151,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 6 * 2 * 0 * 16",
            "Answer": 8,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 0 * 9 * 11 * 3",
            "Answer": 15,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 1 * 0 * 14 * 8",
            "Answer": 1,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 19 * 15 * 12 * 17",
            "Answer": 58148,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 1 * 6 * 13 * 19",
            "Answer": 1482,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 15 * 12 * 14 * 16",
            "Answer": 40329,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 18 * 13 * 11 * 8",
            "Answer": 20603,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 7 * 18 * 19 * 17",
            "Answer": 40705,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 18 * 10 * 3 * 12",
            "Answer": 6493,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 19 * 8 * 11 * 15",
            "Answer": 25093,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 8 * 3 * 2 * 5",
            "Answer": 249,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 11 * 13 * 7 * 2",
            "Answer": 2006,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 5 * 3 * 15 * 8",
            "Answer": 1804,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 1 * 5 * 13 * 1",
            "Answer": 73,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 17 * 15 * 17 * 8",
            "Answer": 34699,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 1 * 0 * 1 * 2",
            "Answer": 15,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 15 * 12 * 13 * 0",
            "Answer": 6,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 8 * 6 * 6 * 8",
            "Answer": 2311,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 0 * 0 * 0 * 3",
            "Answer": 10,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 12 * 17 * 3 * 12",
            "Answer": 7348,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 0 * 11 * 14 * 15",
            "Answer": 11,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 4 * 9 * 9 * 7",
            "Answer": 2270,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 5 * 9 * 17 * 13",
            "Answer": 9950,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 14 * 9 * 11 * 10",
            "Answer": 13869,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 4 * 0 * 4 * 2",
            "Answer": 1,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 5 * 6 * 14 * 8",
            "Answer": 3377,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 10 * 9 * 15 * 2",
            "Answer": 2708,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 13 * 3 * 9 * 3",
            "Answer": 1057,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 0 * 10 * 3 * 6",
            "Answer": 19,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 17 * 4 * 2 * 13",
            "Answer": 1773,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 8 * 4 * 3 * 12",
            "Answer": 1161,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 7 * 19 * 12 * 19",
            "Answer": 30333,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 4 * 10 * 1 * 15",
            "Answer": 611,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 18 * 1 * 0 * 18",
            "Answer": 1,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 12 * 16 * 3 * 19",
            "Answer": 10946,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 5 * 6 * 5 * 12",
            "Answer": 1810,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 16 * 10 * 2 * 14",
            "Answer": 4491,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 18 * 12 * 8 * 0",
            "Answer": 15,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 5 * 14 * 11 * 10",
            "Answer": 7716,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 5 * 6 * 1 * 18",
            "Answer": 547,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 0 * 5 * 10 * 17",
            "Answer": 18,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 18 * 18 * 18 * 9",
            "Answer": 52495,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 16 * 9 * 14 * 17",
            "Answer": 34275,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 2 * 4 * 14 * 12",
            "Answer": 1348,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 13 * 9 * 11 * 6",
            "Answer": 7740,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 0 * 12 * 14 * 19",
            "Answer": 9,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 13 * 17 * 3 * 10",
            "Answer": 6645,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 8 * 11 * 17 * 0",
            "Answer": 16,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 14 * 18 * 8 * 9",
            "Answer": 18162,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 3 * 10 * 4 * 4",
            "Answer": 492,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 2 * 17 * 3 * 5",
            "Answer": 511,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 6 * 19 * 0 * 1",
            "Answer": 2,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 11 * 10 * 19 * 13",
            "Answer": 27174,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 14 * 1 * 15 * 6",
            "Answer": 1265,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 1 * 6 * 16 * 7",
            "Answer": 684,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 12 * 17 * 4 * 5",
            "Answer": 4098,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 14 * 13 * 1 * 14",
            "Answer": 2557,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 0 * 18 * 9 * 1",
            "Answer": 11,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 15 * 19 * 12 * 12",
            "Answer": 41045,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 15 * 16 * 10 * 9",
            "Answer": 21613,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 11 * 19 * 1 * 19",
            "Answer": 3988,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 0 * 12 * 19 * 3",
            "Answer": 2,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 14 * 17 * 6 * 0",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 8 * 18 * 10 * 4",
            "Answer": 5774,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 12 * 10 * 5 * 9",
            "Answer": 5402,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 4 * 8 * 8 * 17",
            "Answer": 4366,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 16 * 13 * 14 * 17",
            "Answer": 49519,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 15 * 18 * 11 * 4",
            "Answer": 11899,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 4 * 0 * 3 * 3",
            "Answer": 8,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 0 * 1 * 8 * 15",
            "Answer": 3,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 3 * 7 * 5 * 12",
            "Answer": 1271,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 16 * 11 * 14 * 14",
            "Answer": 34511,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 10 * 17 * 9 * 11",
            "Answer": 16840,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 6 * 17 * 11 * 4",
            "Answer": 4506,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 14 * 10 * 11 * 12",
            "Answer": 18499,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 14 * 11 * 8 * 5",
            "Answer": 6173,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 10 * 13 * 2 * 12",
            "Answer": 3130,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 18 * 5 * 5 * 7",
            "Answer": 3151,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 14 * 4 * 18 * 1",
            "Answer": 1011,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 15 * 1 * 13 * 5",
            "Answer": 989,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 0 * 3 * 5 * 17",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 17 * 2 * 2 * 15",
            "Answer": 1032,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 19 * 7 * 8 * 13",
            "Answer": 13835,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 7 * 16 * 6 * 19",
            "Answer": 12780,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 8 * 1 * 0 * 17",
            "Answer": 8,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 7 * 13 * 19 * 4",
            "Answer": 6928,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 10 * 12 * 11 * 5",
            "Answer": 6606,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 3 * 12 * 16 * 13",
            "Answer": 7499,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 2 * 2 * 12 * 9",
            "Answer": 433,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 5 * 2 * 19 * 19",
            "Answer": 3615,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 2 * 13 * 6 * 14",
            "Answer": 2186,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 7 * 5 * 4 * 16",
            "Answer": 2243,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 15 * 10 * 6 * 8",
            "Answer": 7212,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * #"
        }
    ],
    "# + # + # * # + #": [
        {
            "Question": "13 + 15 + 2 * 14 + 1",
            "Answer": 57,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 15 + 18 * 9 + 0",
            "Answer": 180,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 0 + 15 * 18 + 3",
            "Answer": 289,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 4 + 15 * 8 + 8",
            "Answer": 135,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 6 + 4 * 2 + 13",
            "Answer": 29,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 2 + 2 * 19 + 12",
            "Answer": 53,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 3 + 12 * 15 + 1",
            "Answer": 196,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 10 + 16 * 6 + 3",
            "Answer": 123,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 13 + 17 * 4 + 6",
            "Answer": 101,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 18 + 14 * 13 + 16",
            "Answer": 218,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 18 + 13 * 19 + 16",
            "Answer": 284,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 13 + 13 * 9 + 2",
            "Answer": 136,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 6 + 9 * 16 + 1",
            "Answer": 158,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 12 + 5 * 2 + 4",
            "Answer": 43,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 4 + 5 * 12 + 12",
            "Answer": 81,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 2 + 5 * 8 + 5",
            "Answer": 57,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 9 + 16 * 11 + 7",
            "Answer": 209,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 4 + 9 * 11 + 10",
            "Answer": 131,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 9 + 9 * 15 + 3",
            "Answer": 155,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 19 + 17 * 3 + 10",
            "Answer": 87,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 7 + 9 * 0 + 19",
            "Answer": 31,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 0 + 19 * 1 + 10",
            "Answer": 36,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 19 + 15 * 1 + 9",
            "Answer": 46,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 4 + 18 * 0 + 17",
            "Answer": 26,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 3 + 9 * 12 + 11",
            "Answer": 127,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 12 + 4 * 18 + 8",
            "Answer": 94,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 14 + 13 * 8 + 13",
            "Answer": 146,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 9 + 15 * 7 + 6",
            "Answer": 128,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 11 + 12 * 18 + 19",
            "Answer": 253,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 1 + 5 * 17 + 8",
            "Answer": 97,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 14 + 7 * 17 + 17",
            "Answer": 158,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 2 + 12 * 18 + 8",
            "Answer": 243,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 7 + 8 * 9 + 19",
            "Answer": 103,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 12 + 6 * 17 + 19",
            "Answer": 152,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 13 + 17 * 0 + 1",
            "Answer": 32,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 9 + 13 * 9 + 8",
            "Answer": 139,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 3 + 12 * 3 + 0",
            "Answer": 57,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 12 + 3 * 18 + 7",
            "Answer": 83,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 19 + 9 * 4 + 15",
            "Answer": 89,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 8 + 1 * 9 + 18",
            "Answer": 39,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 19 + 3 * 7 + 18",
            "Answer": 70,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 11 + 18 * 18 + 18",
            "Answer": 353,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 11 + 15 * 4 + 3",
            "Answer": 91,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 19 + 5 * 19 + 9",
            "Answer": 141,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 5 + 19 * 16 + 4",
            "Answer": 322,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 10 + 6 * 12 + 7",
            "Answer": 96,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 14 + 17 * 7 + 6",
            "Answer": 147,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 10 + 19 * 18 + 16",
            "Answer": 372,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 3 + 17 * 1 + 7",
            "Answer": 28,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 5 + 3 * 13 + 15",
            "Answer": 62,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 4 + 13 * 11 + 10",
            "Answer": 166,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 17 + 18 * 3 + 9",
            "Answer": 83,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 7 + 11 * 11 + 2",
            "Answer": 134,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 16 + 0 * 11 + 7",
            "Answer": 35,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 1 + 6 * 4 + 4",
            "Answer": 46,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 7 + 0 * 3 + 19",
            "Answer": 41,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 10 + 4 * 11 + 4",
            "Answer": 72,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 14 + 6 * 19 + 10",
            "Answer": 156,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 16 + 4 * 12 + 1",
            "Answer": 68,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 15 + 1 * 10 + 1",
            "Answer": 26,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 18 + 19 * 4 + 0",
            "Answer": 113,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 15 + 16 * 14 + 1",
            "Answer": 250,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 11 + 19 * 7 + 16",
            "Answer": 166,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 1 + 13 * 14 + 14",
            "Answer": 202,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 1 + 10 * 12 + 7",
            "Answer": 140,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 1 + 13 * 14 + 7",
            "Answer": 195,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 18 + 18 * 16 + 4",
            "Answer": 316,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 12 + 17 * 0 + 3",
            "Answer": 32,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 18 + 4 * 6 + 1",
            "Answer": 52,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 0 + 2 * 5 + 1",
            "Answer": 16,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 19 + 0 * 16 + 16",
            "Answer": 43,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 5 + 5 * 18 + 7",
            "Answer": 120,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 19 + 8 * 13 + 14",
            "Answer": 150,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 2 + 17 * 1 + 19",
            "Answer": 39,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 7 + 5 * 14 + 1",
            "Answer": 88,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 8 + 8 * 2 + 13",
            "Answer": 45,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 3 + 4 * 1 + 2",
            "Answer": 22,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 2 + 2 * 1 + 11",
            "Answer": 28,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 10 + 5 * 16 + 8",
            "Answer": 113,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 16 + 10 * 14 + 10",
            "Answer": 172,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 3 + 14 * 0 + 16",
            "Answer": 36,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 16 + 9 * 6 + 19",
            "Answer": 96,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 13 + 14 * 18 + 4",
            "Answer": 275,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 15 + 17 * 13 + 17",
            "Answer": 258,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 0 + 0 * 11 + 15",
            "Answer": 16,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 12 + 8 * 10 + 4",
            "Answer": 115,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 17 + 17 * 8 + 5",
            "Answer": 167,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 18 + 15 * 14 + 15",
            "Answer": 246,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 12 + 5 * 13 + 19",
            "Answer": 100,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 2 + 7 * 18 + 11",
            "Answer": 146,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 15 + 2 * 18 + 15",
            "Answer": 71,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 6 + 8 * 9 + 1",
            "Answer": 86,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 12 + 2 * 9 + 6",
            "Answer": 44,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 19 + 5 * 0 + 18",
            "Answer": 38,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 7 + 13 * 10 + 11",
            "Answer": 155,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 11 + 15 * 14 + 12",
            "Answer": 234,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 0 + 7 * 3 + 19",
            "Answer": 43,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 0 + 16 * 11 + 19",
            "Answer": 199,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 17 + 0 * 15 + 14",
            "Answer": 50,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 1 + 7 * 7 + 7",
            "Answer": 71,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + #"
        }
    ],
    "# * # + # * # * #": [
        {
            "Question": "8 * 8 + 14 * 2 * 8",
            "Answer": 288,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 16 + 17 * 14 * 16",
            "Answer": 3984,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 5 + 10 * 0 * 13",
            "Answer": 15,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 16 + 8 * 16 * 5",
            "Answer": 912,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 6 + 17 * 8 * 1",
            "Answer": 214,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 17 + 6 * 5 * 0",
            "Answer": 289,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 2 + 17 * 5 * 9",
            "Answer": 777,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 2 + 7 * 12 * 2",
            "Answer": 170,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 11 + 10 * 13 * 5",
            "Answer": 848,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 12 + 16 * 8 * 9",
            "Answer": 1164,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 13 + 7 * 10 * 7",
            "Answer": 737,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 0 + 4 * 9 * 5",
            "Answer": 180,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 10 + 18 * 11 * 10",
            "Answer": 2120,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 12 + 13 * 12 * 3",
            "Answer": 636,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 15 + 12 * 16 * 7",
            "Answer": 1494,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 11 + 2 * 10 * 11",
            "Answer": 396,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 1 + 9 * 18 * 15",
            "Answer": 2444,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 17 + 11 * 5 * 7",
            "Answer": 589,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 9 + 13 * 1 * 12",
            "Answer": 318,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 15 + 11 * 15 * 6",
            "Answer": 1125,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 3 + 19 * 8 * 19",
            "Answer": 2939,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 12 + 2 * 14 * 9",
            "Answer": 348,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 18 + 0 * 12 * 10",
            "Answer": 342,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 4 + 8 * 14 * 19",
            "Answer": 2128,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 2 + 8 * 11 * 14",
            "Answer": 1238,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 3 + 15 * 18 * 7",
            "Answer": 1893,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 18 + 9 * 2 * 5",
            "Answer": 198,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 7 + 1 * 13 * 6",
            "Answer": 176,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 15 + 8 * 13 * 2",
            "Answer": 268,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 13 + 11 * 13 * 3",
            "Answer": 572,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 9 + 0 * 16 * 8",
            "Answer": 135,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 18 + 1 * 3 * 0",
            "Answer": 342,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 4 + 11 * 4 * 2",
            "Answer": 144,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 16 + 14 * 5 * 1",
            "Answer": 342,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 6 + 15 * 3 * 15",
            "Answer": 705,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 9 + 10 * 17 * 15",
            "Answer": 2586,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 6 + 18 * 14 * 8",
            "Answer": 2094,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 6 + 5 * 3 * 17",
            "Answer": 291,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 15 + 14 * 9 * 13",
            "Answer": 1833,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 12 + 6 * 15 * 4",
            "Answer": 576,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 7 + 8 * 10 * 2",
            "Answer": 188,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 14 + 12 * 4 * 14",
            "Answer": 882,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 10 + 19 * 19 * 4",
            "Answer": 1634,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 15 + 9 * 1 * 17",
            "Answer": 228,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 11 + 14 * 14 * 18",
            "Answer": 3605,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 12 + 15 * 2 * 2",
            "Answer": 192,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 11 + 2 * 3 * 7",
            "Answer": 229,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 5 + 7 * 4 * 15",
            "Answer": 475,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 1 + 1 * 9 * 3",
            "Answer": 39,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 2 + 0 * 4 * 7",
            "Answer": 36,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 10 + 12 * 2 * 14",
            "Answer": 496,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 6 + 3 * 19 * 10",
            "Answer": 570,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 8 + 14 * 4 * 7",
            "Answer": 416,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 8 + 17 * 0 * 14",
            "Answer": 32,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 6 + 2 * 11 * 9",
            "Answer": 306,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 6 + 12 * 12 * 13",
            "Answer": 1962,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 0 + 9 * 7 * 18",
            "Answer": 1134,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 1 + 15 * 2 * 10",
            "Answer": 316,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 5 + 7 * 12 * 11",
            "Answer": 994,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 14 + 4 * 1 * 11",
            "Answer": 212,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 16 + 9 * 3 * 18",
            "Answer": 694,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 16 + 3 * 8 * 7",
            "Answer": 424,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 4 + 13 * 2 * 14",
            "Answer": 400,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 7 + 15 * 7 * 15",
            "Answer": 1680,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 13 + 14 * 3 * 19",
            "Answer": 928,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 7 + 1 * 19 * 18",
            "Answer": 384,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 7 + 9 * 4 * 12",
            "Answer": 558,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 19 + 15 * 1 * 3",
            "Answer": 330,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 2 + 16 * 1 * 11",
            "Answer": 212,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 11 + 19 * 13 * 0",
            "Answer": 99,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 8 + 10 * 18 * 4",
            "Answer": 848,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 10 + 7 * 10 * 13",
            "Answer": 940,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 13 + 19 * 18 * 7",
            "Answer": 2420,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 1 + 0 * 12 * 13",
            "Answer": 19,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 2 + 10 * 2 * 5",
            "Answer": 112,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 13 + 15 * 8 * 18",
            "Answer": 2394,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 1 + 9 * 6 * 0",
            "Answer": 15,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 6 + 16 * 8 * 6",
            "Answer": 840,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 11 + 19 * 14 * 10",
            "Answer": 2671,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 10 + 12 * 3 * 15",
            "Answer": 600,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 13 + 17 * 16 * 5",
            "Answer": 1412,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 10 + 13 * 11 * 19",
            "Answer": 2867,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 17 + 19 * 18 * 3",
            "Answer": 1111,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 8 + 19 * 16 * 8",
            "Answer": 2560,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 9 + 6 * 6 * 1",
            "Answer": 171,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 9 + 17 * 13 * 6",
            "Answer": 1344,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 18 + 1 * 4 * 14",
            "Answer": 344,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 16 + 17 * 4 * 11",
            "Answer": 940,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 17 + 4 * 17 * 12",
            "Answer": 1003,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 1 + 16 * 1 * 13",
            "Answer": 216,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 0 + 14 * 15 * 17",
            "Answer": 3570,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 7 + 10 * 3 * 18",
            "Answer": 596,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 3 + 8 * 1 * 1",
            "Answer": 47,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 13 + 4 * 0 * 14",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 1 + 7 * 8 * 13",
            "Answer": 728,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 1 + 3 * 8 * 6",
            "Answer": 157,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 13 + 14 * 11 * 6",
            "Answer": 1054,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 14 + 3 * 6 * 8",
            "Answer": 214,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 17 + 5 * 17 * 17",
            "Answer": 1496,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 6 + 4 * 14 * 11",
            "Answer": 730,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * #"
        }
    ],
    "# * # * # * # * #": [
        {
            "Question": "0 * 4 * 3 * 17 * 19",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 16 * 4 * 3 * 13",
            "Answer": 44928,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 15 * 4 * 2 * 7",
            "Answer": 6720,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 7 * 5 * 2 * 4",
            "Answer": 2240,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 8 * 17 * 11 * 2",
            "Answer": 50864,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 19 * 11 * 5 * 6",
            "Answer": 75240,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 6 * 2 * 1 * 1",
            "Answer": 204,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 13 * 13 * 14 * 6",
            "Answer": 85176,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 4 * 8 * 0 * 0",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 7 * 18 * 14 * 16",
            "Answer": 84672,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 3 * 1 * 10 * 16",
            "Answer": 4800,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 3 * 14 * 1 * 14",
            "Answer": 5880,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 19 * 2 * 14 * 11",
            "Answer": 17556,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 15 * 5 * 10 * 18",
            "Answer": 202500,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 3 * 9 * 2 * 15",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 14 * 3 * 15 * 2",
            "Answer": 3780,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 11 * 5 * 7 * 11",
            "Answer": 80465,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 6 * 15 * 12 * 10",
            "Answer": 205200,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 17 * 6 * 15 * 18",
            "Answer": 468180,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 12 * 1 * 12 * 6",
            "Answer": 4320,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 2 * 17 * 16 * 3",
            "Answer": 4896,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 4 * 13 * 19 * 2",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 19 * 15 * 12 * 17",
            "Answer": 348840,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 0 * 16 * 5 * 14",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 15 * 12 * 18 * 0",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 2 * 1 * 17 * 1",
            "Answer": 340,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 8 * 9 * 13 * 6",
            "Answer": 39312,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 4 * 16 * 15 * 8",
            "Answer": 23040,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 10 * 12 * 1 * 5",
            "Answer": 1800,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 11 * 0 * 17 * 8",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 15 * 5 * 5 * 1",
            "Answer": 3375,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 16 * 19 * 10 * 11",
            "Answer": 334400,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 17 * 14 * 0 * 18",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 8 * 15 * 19 * 12",
            "Answer": 300960,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 1 * 4 * 12 * 17",
            "Answer": 3264,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 3 * 1 * 12 * 15",
            "Answer": 10260,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 7 * 16 * 7 * 12",
            "Answer": 9408,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 11 * 6 * 2 * 6",
            "Answer": 10296,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 18 * 3 * 14 * 0",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 18 * 6 * 16 * 6",
            "Answer": 103680,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 11 * 8 * 8 * 13",
            "Answer": 54912,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 11 * 7 * 4 * 18",
            "Answer": 44352,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 17 * 6 * 12 * 0",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 0 * 12 * 7 * 2",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 8 * 16 * 8 * 11",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 15 * 9 * 9 * 4",
            "Answer": 92340,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 19 * 3 * 2 * 10",
            "Answer": 21660,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 12 * 19 * 18 * 9",
            "Answer": 332424,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 16 * 12 * 3 * 14",
            "Answer": 137088,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 1 * 3 * 12 * 9",
            "Answer": 5508,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 9 * 11 * 8 * 13",
            "Answer": 92664,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 2 * 2 * 15 * 8",
            "Answer": 6720,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 14 * 11 * 9 * 4",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 12 * 19 * 12 * 3",
            "Answer": 131328,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 6 * 4 * 13 * 7",
            "Answer": 13104,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 4 * 12 * 19 * 15",
            "Answer": 13680,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 12 * 8 * 3 * 13",
            "Answer": 33696,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 6 * 4 * 1 * 6",
            "Answer": 2160,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 6 * 3 * 19 * 9",
            "Answer": 43092,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 11 * 3 * 11 * 3",
            "Answer": 11979,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 0 * 19 * 0 * 0",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 12 * 6 * 19 * 16",
            "Answer": 87552,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 10 * 15 * 8 * 7",
            "Answer": 25200,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 1 * 0 * 8 * 14",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 13 * 19 * 19 * 9",
            "Answer": 126711,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 13 * 9 * 5 * 14",
            "Answer": 16380,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 13 * 16 * 1 * 3",
            "Answer": 8736,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 6 * 5 * 1 * 10",
            "Answer": 1200,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 19 * 17 * 10 * 13",
            "Answer": 335920,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 14 * 16 * 12 * 9",
            "Answer": 362880,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 8 * 12 * 13 * 19",
            "Answer": 213408,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 4 * 15 * 3 * 1",
            "Answer": 3420,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 9 * 18 * 4 * 8",
            "Answer": 41472,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 14 * 11 * 18 * 6",
            "Answer": 182952,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 17 * 1 * 9 * 5",
            "Answer": 3060,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 5 * 16 * 9 * 17",
            "Answer": 12240,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 4 * 11 * 8 * 15",
            "Answer": 21120,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 3 * 7 * 14 * 1",
            "Answer": 882,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 2 * 6 * 3 * 6",
            "Answer": 432,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 4 * 3 * 4 * 19",
            "Answer": 10944,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 17 * 1 * 16 * 10",
            "Answer": 29920,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 10 * 16 * 14 * 17",
            "Answer": 723520,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 5 * 13 * 9 * 10",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 12 * 10 * 18 * 15",
            "Answer": 226800,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 19 * 0 * 5 * 15",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 5 * 1 * 12 * 13",
            "Answer": 13260,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 0 * 0 * 16 * 4",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 11 * 19 * 17 * 0",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 11 * 7 * 8 * 18",
            "Answer": 33264,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 4 * 19 * 18 * 10",
            "Answer": 27360,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 9 * 16 * 12 * 2",
            "Answer": 38016,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 13 * 17 * 0 * 15",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 0 * 15 * 18 * 14",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 8 * 16 * 14 * 0",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 13 * 12 * 3 * 7",
            "Answer": 29484,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 10 * 17 * 1 * 3",
            "Answer": 8160,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 4 * 7 * 12 * 13",
            "Answer": 4368,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 12 * 0 * 10 * 7",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 16 * 14 * 17 * 8",
            "Answer": 243712,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 9 * 6 * 6 * 17",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * #"
        }
    ],
    "# + # + # + # + #": [
        {
            "Question": "1 + 14 + 12 + 0 + 13",
            "Answer": 40,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 18 + 3 + 1 + 8",
            "Answer": 46,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 9 + 4 + 2 + 17",
            "Answer": 43,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 12 + 18 + 3 + 3",
            "Answer": 38,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 7 + 12 + 7 + 4",
            "Answer": 31,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 10 + 14 + 9 + 9",
            "Answer": 44,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 17 + 13 + 16 + 12",
            "Answer": 64,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 19 + 18 + 4 + 15",
            "Answer": 57,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 12 + 0 + 14 + 5",
            "Answer": 32,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 1 + 12 + 18 + 17",
            "Answer": 65,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 2 + 17 + 15 + 15",
            "Answer": 60,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 8 + 7 + 3 + 4",
            "Answer": 29,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 4 + 0 + 18 + 0",
            "Answer": 28,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 16 + 8 + 8 + 1",
            "Answer": 44,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 5 + 3 + 12 + 5",
            "Answer": 39,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 9 + 10 + 0 + 17",
            "Answer": 39,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 2 + 1 + 1 + 19",
            "Answer": 35,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 13 + 14 + 2 + 14",
            "Answer": 62,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 10 + 0 + 18 + 19",
            "Answer": 63,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 2 + 1 + 7 + 5",
            "Answer": 17,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 18 + 15 + 10 + 11",
            "Answer": 63,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 18 + 15 + 9 + 13",
            "Answer": 55,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 18 + 14 + 2 + 11",
            "Answer": 49,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 3 + 0 + 11 + 1",
            "Answer": 24,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 11 + 10 + 7 + 6",
            "Answer": 41,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 14 + 7 + 12 + 13",
            "Answer": 64,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 16 + 10 + 10 + 8",
            "Answer": 54,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 8 + 16 + 5 + 17",
            "Answer": 46,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 17 + 11 + 8 + 14",
            "Answer": 57,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 9 + 13 + 14 + 1",
            "Answer": 45,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 8 + 13 + 0 + 3",
            "Answer": 35,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 8 + 14 + 1 + 15",
            "Answer": 40,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 17 + 14 + 19 + 15",
            "Answer": 67,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 0 + 7 + 7 + 4",
            "Answer": 36,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 7 + 6 + 5 + 14",
            "Answer": 47,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 15 + 12 + 18 + 0",
            "Answer": 53,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 19 + 3 + 14 + 13",
            "Answer": 59,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 8 + 8 + 9 + 13",
            "Answer": 44,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 15 + 10 + 8 + 16",
            "Answer": 51,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 9 + 2 + 11 + 4",
            "Answer": 45,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 17 + 1 + 16 + 18",
            "Answer": 56,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 5 + 17 + 9 + 12",
            "Answer": 59,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 12 + 7 + 7 + 14",
            "Answer": 55,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 18 + 1 + 17 + 5",
            "Answer": 49,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 17 + 8 + 19 + 14",
            "Answer": 74,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 19 + 18 + 7 + 8",
            "Answer": 62,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 8 + 14 + 3 + 0",
            "Answer": 25,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 13 + 9 + 8 + 12",
            "Answer": 52,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 10 + 4 + 7 + 13",
            "Answer": 35,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 7 + 19 + 10 + 10",
            "Answer": 57,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 10 + 3 + 10 + 19",
            "Answer": 43,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 1 + 12 + 15 + 13",
            "Answer": 50,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 15 + 17 + 18 + 1",
            "Answer": 56,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 7 + 12 + 11 + 0",
            "Answer": 39,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 16 + 2 + 10 + 14",
            "Answer": 51,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 9 + 2 + 4 + 4",
            "Answer": 24,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 7 + 10 + 6 + 19",
            "Answer": 56,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 10 + 13 + 11 + 19",
            "Answer": 64,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 3 + 8 + 4 + 7",
            "Answer": 25,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 6 + 11 + 1 + 13",
            "Answer": 47,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 17 + 14 + 9 + 11",
            "Answer": 69,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 14 + 5 + 10 + 2",
            "Answer": 44,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 13 + 11 + 15 + 16",
            "Answer": 70,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 19 + 5 + 13 + 4",
            "Answer": 44,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 5 + 19 + 3 + 14",
            "Answer": 57,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 14 + 18 + 1 + 17",
            "Answer": 61,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 18 + 17 + 11 + 6",
            "Answer": 55,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 1 + 12 + 1 + 10",
            "Answer": 30,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 14 + 14 + 1 + 6",
            "Answer": 52,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 3 + 0 + 11 + 0",
            "Answer": 23,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 10 + 14 + 4 + 4",
            "Answer": 39,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 1 + 19 + 0 + 5",
            "Answer": 26,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 18 + 1 + 17 + 0",
            "Answer": 40,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 13 + 14 + 5 + 12",
            "Answer": 57,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 17 + 4 + 11 + 19",
            "Answer": 60,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 13 + 1 + 9 + 11",
            "Answer": 48,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 14 + 9 + 16 + 19",
            "Answer": 67,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 16 + 15 + 2 + 2",
            "Answer": 40,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 14 + 15 + 17 + 15",
            "Answer": 71,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 11 + 0 + 1 + 13",
            "Answer": 44,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 13 + 3 + 12 + 3",
            "Answer": 42,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 9 + 18 + 5 + 1",
            "Answer": 44,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 5 + 0 + 8 + 11",
            "Answer": 35,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 10 + 15 + 15 + 5",
            "Answer": 62,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 11 + 6 + 5 + 11",
            "Answer": 52,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 3 + 8 + 13 + 18",
            "Answer": 60,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 18 + 15 + 18 + 0",
            "Answer": 67,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 15 + 12 + 9 + 7",
            "Answer": 44,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 7 + 14 + 12 + 1",
            "Answer": 49,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 0 + 10 + 7 + 5",
            "Answer": 22,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 6 + 1 + 9 + 9",
            "Answer": 33,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 12 + 18 + 1 + 12",
            "Answer": 55,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 4 + 9 + 6 + 19",
            "Answer": 38,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 18 + 17 + 15 + 4",
            "Answer": 66,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 8 + 14 + 4 + 5",
            "Answer": 49,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 15 + 9 + 19 + 18",
            "Answer": 66,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 6 + 6 + 14 + 18",
            "Answer": 56,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 11 + 0 + 15 + 14",
            "Answer": 53,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 13 + 2 + 10 + 0",
            "Answer": 42,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 14 + 17 + 9 + 14",
            "Answer": 55,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + #"
        }
    ],
    "# + # * # + # * #": [
        {
            "Question": "19 + 18 * 5 + 1 * 6",
            "Answer": 115,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 14 * 15 + 16 * 10",
            "Answer": 373,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 6 * 18 + 13 * 19",
            "Answer": 355,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 1 * 4 + 1 * 3",
            "Answer": 9,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 15 * 19 + 17 * 6",
            "Answer": 403,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 9 * 0 + 2 * 1",
            "Answer": 10,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 12 * 3 + 17 * 14",
            "Answer": 288,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 6 * 2 + 15 * 18",
            "Answer": 289,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 7 * 18 + 15 * 7",
            "Answer": 234,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 13 * 8 + 17 * 1",
            "Answer": 134,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 6 * 10 + 16 * 18",
            "Answer": 351,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 11 * 18 + 4 * 18",
            "Answer": 288,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 5 * 17 + 7 * 8",
            "Answer": 158,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 16 * 12 + 6 * 0",
            "Answer": 198,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 1 * 0 + 4 * 13",
            "Answer": 56,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 15 * 5 + 4 * 13",
            "Answer": 131,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 7 * 0 + 16 * 12",
            "Answer": 201,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 18 * 6 + 8 * 16",
            "Answer": 247,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 5 * 12 + 13 * 17",
            "Answer": 300,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 15 * 3 + 15 * 0",
            "Answer": 55,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 13 * 10 + 12 * 0",
            "Answer": 138,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 11 * 14 + 3 * 4",
            "Answer": 167,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 7 * 0 + 18 * 14",
            "Answer": 266,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 5 * 19 + 6 * 8",
            "Answer": 149,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 13 * 15 + 14 * 8",
            "Answer": 318,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 1 * 17 + 0 * 9",
            "Answer": 21,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 13 * 2 + 17 * 10",
            "Answer": 211,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 1 * 12 + 16 * 6",
            "Answer": 119,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 7 * 15 + 12 * 7",
            "Answer": 192,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 9 * 2 + 17 * 18",
            "Answer": 324,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 3 * 15 + 9 * 7",
            "Answer": 118,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 2 * 3 + 17 * 5",
            "Answer": 98,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 13 * 16 + 6 * 8",
            "Answer": 275,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 8 * 19 + 11 * 9",
            "Answer": 270,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 10 * 18 + 7 * 0",
            "Answer": 197,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 2 * 17 + 7 * 2",
            "Answer": 50,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 9 * 7 + 18 * 14",
            "Answer": 331,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 16 * 0 + 1 * 2",
            "Answer": 15,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 3 * 6 + 3 * 1",
            "Answer": 26,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 5 * 4 + 6 * 13",
            "Answer": 111,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 18 * 12 + 19 * 5",
            "Answer": 321,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 11 * 18 + 4 * 9",
            "Answer": 248,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 19 * 6 + 0 * 9",
            "Answer": 115,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 9 * 10 + 15 * 7",
            "Answer": 204,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 2 * 15 + 1 * 2",
            "Answer": 50,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 9 * 16 + 13 * 4",
            "Answer": 208,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 3 * 17 + 19 * 12",
            "Answer": 290,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 15 * 1 + 3 * 14",
            "Answer": 58,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 3 * 0 + 7 * 15",
            "Answer": 118,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 2 * 11 + 17 * 9",
            "Answer": 176,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 10 * 5 + 16 * 4",
            "Answer": 127,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 16 * 14 + 5 * 4",
            "Answer": 262,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 9 * 13 + 18 * 14",
            "Answer": 375,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 11 * 2 + 2 * 12",
            "Answer": 62,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 14 * 0 + 7 * 6",
            "Answer": 52,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 18 * 18 + 15 * 8",
            "Answer": 456,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 15 * 16 + 15 * 12",
            "Answer": 422,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 5 * 1 + 17 * 9",
            "Answer": 161,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 5 * 2 + 7 * 13",
            "Answer": 114,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 6 * 3 + 13 * 15",
            "Answer": 220,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 10 * 5 + 2 * 13",
            "Answer": 84,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 12 * 18 + 0 * 1",
            "Answer": 232,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 2 * 10 + 5 * 7",
            "Answer": 65,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 4 * 6 + 19 * 8",
            "Answer": 189,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 6 * 0 + 9 * 9",
            "Answer": 85,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 4 * 12 + 12 * 12",
            "Answer": 211,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 13 * 17 + 9 * 3",
            "Answer": 257,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 17 * 6 + 13 * 1",
            "Answer": 124,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 5 * 14 + 0 * 1",
            "Answer": 85,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 17 * 17 + 17 * 2",
            "Answer": 335,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 4 * 17 + 19 * 9",
            "Answer": 239,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 9 * 8 + 12 * 1",
            "Answer": 90,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 7 * 6 + 11 * 4",
            "Answer": 103,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 14 * 11 + 13 * 13",
            "Answer": 340,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 2 * 9 + 17 * 13",
            "Answer": 240,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 7 * 16 + 9 * 4",
            "Answer": 160,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 7 * 10 + 6 * 2",
            "Answer": 87,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 16 * 11 + 11 * 7",
            "Answer": 259,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 12 * 5 + 11 * 4",
            "Answer": 122,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 2 * 8 + 9 * 5",
            "Answer": 79,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 2 * 17 + 13 * 5",
            "Answer": 100,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 7 * 1 + 19 * 13",
            "Answer": 254,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 4 * 15 + 6 * 3",
            "Answer": 88,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 1 * 2 + 12 * 13",
            "Answer": 163,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 16 * 3 + 4 * 13",
            "Answer": 106,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 7 * 11 + 19 * 10",
            "Answer": 277,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 5 * 12 + 17 * 16",
            "Answer": 332,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 13 * 13 + 2 * 1",
            "Answer": 187,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 17 * 9 + 19 * 10",
            "Answer": 356,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 15 * 10 + 12 * 3",
            "Answer": 205,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 8 * 1 + 9 * 4",
            "Answer": 52,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 4 * 10 + 13 * 15",
            "Answer": 254,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 2 * 6 + 13 * 15",
            "Answer": 212,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 12 * 1 + 8 * 11",
            "Answer": 117,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 6 * 17 + 1 * 8",
            "Answer": 114,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 12 * 8 + 3 * 0",
            "Answer": 104,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 19 * 11 + 11 * 13",
            "Answer": 357,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 7 * 8 + 0 * 4",
            "Answer": 64,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 14 * 7 + 5 * 7",
            "Answer": 140,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 14 * 10 + 13 * 9",
            "Answer": 268,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * #"
        }
    ],
    "# * # + # * # + #": [
        {
            "Question": "2 * 11 + 12 * 15 + 2",
            "Answer": 204,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 12 + 7 * 19 + 18",
            "Answer": 259,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 5 + 17 * 19 + 6",
            "Answer": 384,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 10 + 3 * 1 + 0",
            "Answer": 193,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 5 + 14 * 3 + 15",
            "Answer": 92,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 3 + 19 * 11 + 11",
            "Answer": 250,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 0 + 13 * 8 + 18",
            "Answer": 122,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 0 + 3 * 9 + 9",
            "Answer": 36,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 17 + 18 * 2 + 15",
            "Answer": 102,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 8 + 8 * 4 + 13",
            "Answer": 85,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 7 + 0 * 10 + 1",
            "Answer": 36,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 2 + 19 * 11 + 0",
            "Answer": 239,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 6 + 18 * 12 + 15",
            "Answer": 237,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 14 + 17 * 5 + 4",
            "Answer": 159,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 11 + 13 * 6 + 15",
            "Answer": 302,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 9 + 3 * 6 + 11",
            "Answer": 65,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 0 + 19 * 4 + 6",
            "Answer": 82,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 6 + 0 * 2 + 16",
            "Answer": 16,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 17 + 7 * 2 + 3",
            "Answer": 170,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 4 + 2 * 5 + 16",
            "Answer": 54,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 0 + 8 * 8 + 19",
            "Answer": 83,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 14 + 14 * 15 + 8",
            "Answer": 260,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 14 + 7 * 6 + 8",
            "Answer": 218,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 8 + 5 * 18 + 17",
            "Answer": 139,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 4 + 9 * 2 + 10",
            "Answer": 64,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 16 + 11 * 19 + 1",
            "Answer": 514,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 10 + 5 * 2 + 0",
            "Answer": 50,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 1 + 15 * 5 + 15",
            "Answer": 102,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 15 + 3 * 12 + 16",
            "Answer": 142,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 14 + 8 * 7 + 19",
            "Answer": 299,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 2 + 10 * 3 + 10",
            "Answer": 70,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 6 + 15 * 14 + 6",
            "Answer": 222,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 14 + 9 * 10 + 6",
            "Answer": 320,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 19 + 13 * 18 + 14",
            "Answer": 305,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 5 + 13 * 18 + 6",
            "Answer": 305,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 6 + 16 * 15 + 0",
            "Answer": 288,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 19 + 9 * 8 + 9",
            "Answer": 233,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 11 + 1 * 18 + 7",
            "Answer": 124,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 5 + 9 * 14 + 0",
            "Answer": 161,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 5 + 8 * 0 + 9",
            "Answer": 9,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 10 + 3 * 6 + 9",
            "Answer": 187,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 9 + 5 * 19 + 7",
            "Answer": 183,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 5 + 14 * 9 + 16",
            "Answer": 172,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 4 + 8 * 11 + 10",
            "Answer": 98,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 7 + 12 * 8 + 16",
            "Answer": 189,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 1 + 8 * 4 + 2",
            "Answer": 43,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 2 + 4 * 8 + 12",
            "Answer": 62,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 12 + 9 * 9 + 5",
            "Answer": 158,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 11 + 15 * 0 + 8",
            "Answer": 206,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 8 + 16 * 13 + 3",
            "Answer": 267,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 5 + 12 * 14 + 11",
            "Answer": 229,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 2 + 1 * 0 + 11",
            "Answer": 47,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 2 + 14 * 7 + 16",
            "Answer": 114,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 17 + 0 * 13 + 8",
            "Answer": 76,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 7 + 0 * 18 + 11",
            "Answer": 95,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 12 + 6 * 1 + 18",
            "Answer": 192,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 16 + 2 * 8 + 5",
            "Answer": 37,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 4 + 11 * 6 + 0",
            "Answer": 90,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 13 + 12 * 17 + 5",
            "Answer": 430,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 5 + 8 * 5 + 6",
            "Answer": 61,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 13 + 8 * 10 + 15",
            "Answer": 199,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 8 + 1 * 15 + 14",
            "Answer": 141,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 13 + 19 * 10 + 19",
            "Answer": 326,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 7 + 4 * 10 + 13",
            "Answer": 102,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 7 + 3 * 16 + 18",
            "Answer": 178,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 12 + 4 * 15 + 6",
            "Answer": 234,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 10 + 19 * 4 + 1",
            "Answer": 77,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 11 + 17 * 19 + 4",
            "Answer": 371,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 9 + 18 * 12 + 14",
            "Answer": 293,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 3 + 5 * 15 + 0",
            "Answer": 87,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 3 + 9 * 11 + 15",
            "Answer": 135,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 10 + 12 * 5 + 10",
            "Answer": 100,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 6 + 11 * 11 + 5",
            "Answer": 222,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 2 + 13 * 17 + 6",
            "Answer": 241,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 18 + 3 * 11 + 15",
            "Answer": 372,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 1 + 14 * 4 + 8",
            "Answer": 83,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 6 + 0 * 16 + 10",
            "Answer": 64,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 2 + 3 * 11 + 6",
            "Answer": 41,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 2 + 11 * 16 + 6",
            "Answer": 182,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 3 + 13 * 8 + 6",
            "Answer": 122,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 18 + 12 * 12 + 5",
            "Answer": 203,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 7 + 6 * 5 + 4",
            "Answer": 104,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 7 + 10 * 0 + 7",
            "Answer": 140,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 16 + 8 * 9 + 10",
            "Answer": 274,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 6 + 17 * 0 + 13",
            "Answer": 67,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 10 + 3 * 3 + 10",
            "Answer": 59,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 3 + 18 * 12 + 19",
            "Answer": 268,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 2 + 5 * 7 + 8",
            "Answer": 77,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 6 + 6 * 3 + 1",
            "Answer": 97,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 18 + 1 * 12 + 3",
            "Answer": 339,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 14 + 15 * 15 + 12",
            "Answer": 349,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 2 + 5 * 7 + 8",
            "Answer": 81,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 17 + 7 * 13 + 2",
            "Answer": 110,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 16 + 19 * 10 + 7",
            "Answer": 229,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 10 + 13 * 0 + 5",
            "Answer": 185,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 8 + 8 * 12 + 6",
            "Answer": 214,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 3 + 19 * 16 + 3",
            "Answer": 325,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 18 + 19 * 1 + 13",
            "Answer": 212,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 4 + 12 * 3 + 14",
            "Answer": 98,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 0 + 16 * 0 + 3",
            "Answer": 3,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + #"
        }
    ],
    "# + # + # * # * #": [
        {
            "Question": "8 + 5 + 16 * 7 * 5",
            "Answer": 573,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 4 + 11 * 3 * 1",
            "Answer": 51,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 5 + 2 * 1 * 2",
            "Answer": 18,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 10 + 2 * 17 * 9",
            "Answer": 323,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 15 + 12 * 15 * 18",
            "Answer": 3261,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 19 + 13 * 15 * 16",
            "Answer": 3144,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 6 + 0 * 8 * 17",
            "Answer": 24,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 3 + 0 * 17 * 17",
            "Answer": 22,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 4 + 17 * 9 * 10",
            "Answer": 1548,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 5 + 10 * 18 * 14",
            "Answer": 2540,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 2 + 14 * 13 * 2",
            "Answer": 374,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 6 + 14 * 16 * 3",
            "Answer": 697,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 16 + 1 * 11 * 8",
            "Answer": 118,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 16 + 18 * 2 * 0",
            "Answer": 22,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 16 + 8 * 3 * 10",
            "Answer": 264,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 17 + 3 * 9 * 17",
            "Answer": 486,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 19 + 13 * 8 * 4",
            "Answer": 437,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 12 + 16 * 16 * 1",
            "Answer": 286,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 16 + 13 * 11 * 0",
            "Answer": 34,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 6 + 14 * 13 * 18",
            "Answer": 3294,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 15 + 11 * 2 * 13",
            "Answer": 320,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 0 + 18 * 0 * 2",
            "Answer": 18,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 16 + 15 * 1 * 18",
            "Answer": 289,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 16 + 16 * 13 * 9",
            "Answer": 1898,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 1 + 2 * 16 * 13",
            "Answer": 436,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 11 + 17 * 7 * 3",
            "Answer": 368,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 3 + 16 * 19 * 11",
            "Answer": 3352,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 4 + 3 * 6 * 16",
            "Answer": 307,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 5 + 12 * 10 * 12",
            "Answer": 1453,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 16 + 15 * 0 * 0",
            "Answer": 33,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 7 + 13 * 11 * 0",
            "Answer": 10,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 4 + 18 * 9 * 12",
            "Answer": 1966,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 11 + 15 * 7 * 10",
            "Answer": 1064,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 14 + 2 * 1 * 16",
            "Answer": 60,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 9 + 8 * 17 * 15",
            "Answer": 2065,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 8 + 9 * 10 * 6",
            "Answer": 559,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 4 + 3 * 1 * 3",
            "Answer": 29,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 13 + 11 * 16 * 2",
            "Answer": 380,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 4 + 15 * 8 * 6",
            "Answer": 739,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 15 + 6 * 13 * 18",
            "Answer": 1427,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 1 + 7 * 15 * 13",
            "Answer": 1374,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 9 + 9 * 13 * 3",
            "Answer": 377,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 13 + 11 * 5 * 17",
            "Answer": 959,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 18 + 10 * 12 * 5",
            "Answer": 626,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 4 + 9 * 11 * 6",
            "Answer": 601,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 4 + 18 * 9 * 5",
            "Answer": 832,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 5 + 14 * 15 * 9",
            "Answer": 1901,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 15 + 0 * 15 * 9",
            "Answer": 19,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 19 + 6 * 4 * 19",
            "Answer": 478,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 5 + 14 * 2 * 16",
            "Answer": 457,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 3 + 12 * 18 * 9",
            "Answer": 1962,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 7 + 17 * 13 * 13",
            "Answer": 2884,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 9 + 17 * 7 * 6",
            "Answer": 742,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 18 + 6 * 12 * 6",
            "Answer": 457,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 12 + 0 * 11 * 16",
            "Answer": 21,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 13 + 16 * 7 * 15",
            "Answer": 1696,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 16 + 13 * 16 * 17",
            "Answer": 3569,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 11 + 16 * 6 * 4",
            "Answer": 400,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 18 + 12 * 12 * 7",
            "Answer": 1036,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 10 + 0 * 2 * 16",
            "Answer": 28,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 16 + 6 * 9 * 2",
            "Answer": 141,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 8 + 7 * 9 * 6",
            "Answer": 391,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 19 + 3 * 8 * 17",
            "Answer": 444,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 18 + 1 * 12 * 11",
            "Answer": 156,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 8 + 13 * 5 * 8",
            "Answer": 539,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 7 + 18 * 4 * 11",
            "Answer": 801,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 12 + 12 * 0 * 11",
            "Answer": 19,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 1 + 17 * 16 * 8",
            "Answer": 2183,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 13 + 9 * 0 * 2",
            "Answer": 19,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 3 + 0 * 5 * 9",
            "Answer": 19,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 16 + 1 * 15 * 9",
            "Answer": 163,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 7 + 11 * 5 * 15",
            "Answer": 851,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 6 + 9 * 15 * 11",
            "Answer": 1504,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 6 + 11 * 3 * 18",
            "Answer": 611,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 11 + 9 * 4 * 17",
            "Answer": 639,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 17 + 7 * 2 * 2",
            "Answer": 52,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 13 + 17 * 5 * 1",
            "Answer": 102,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 5 + 12 * 16 * 5",
            "Answer": 982,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 5 + 1 * 16 * 14",
            "Answer": 229,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 5 + 4 * 10 * 15",
            "Answer": 617,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 6 + 19 * 15 * 5",
            "Answer": 1433,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 13 + 15 * 3 * 4",
            "Answer": 206,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 18 + 9 * 7 * 19",
            "Answer": 1230,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 16 + 10 * 5 * 16",
            "Answer": 835,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 14 + 4 * 6 * 19",
            "Answer": 482,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 11 + 11 * 9 * 1",
            "Answer": 123,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 1 + 14 * 13 * 14",
            "Answer": 2562,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 12 + 4 * 14 * 12",
            "Answer": 697,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 3 + 13 * 6 * 0",
            "Answer": 9,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 10 + 19 * 3 * 11",
            "Answer": 656,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 2 + 13 * 14 * 7",
            "Answer": 1277,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 0 + 8 * 1 * 2",
            "Answer": 35,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 0 + 16 * 18 * 7",
            "Answer": 2032,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 3 + 8 * 9 * 17",
            "Answer": 1231,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 2 + 12 * 0 * 11",
            "Answer": 8,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 12 + 14 * 18 * 18",
            "Answer": 4564,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 9 + 19 * 3 * 19",
            "Answer": 1097,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 2 + 10 * 12 * 1",
            "Answer": 141,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 0 + 7 * 12 * 13",
            "Answer": 1098,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 8 + 9 * 5 * 4",
            "Answer": 189,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * #"
        }
    ],
    "# * # * # * # + #": [
        {
            "Question": "15 * 16 * 16 * 5 + 6",
            "Answer": 19206,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 4 * 14 * 2 + 17",
            "Answer": 2145,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 19 * 5 * 3 + 0",
            "Answer": 1425,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 19 * 14 * 8 + 9",
            "Answer": 2137,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 9 * 2 * 10 + 1",
            "Answer": 1,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 15 * 8 * 15 + 18",
            "Answer": 34218,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 2 * 19 * 13 + 10",
            "Answer": 7420,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 18 * 18 * 18 + 4",
            "Answer": 93316,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 15 * 17 * 13 + 18",
            "Answer": 49743,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 9 * 1 * 10 + 5",
            "Answer": 995,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 17 * 11 * 11 + 16",
            "Answer": 30871,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 8 * 5 * 8 + 16",
            "Answer": 976,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 14 * 6 * 11 + 1",
            "Answer": 4621,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 5 * 4 * 10 + 8",
            "Answer": 8,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 5 * 14 * 16 + 19",
            "Answer": 19059,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 16 * 2 * 0 + 1",
            "Answer": 1,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 4 * 11 * 4 + 1",
            "Answer": 1233,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 18 * 4 * 19 + 10",
            "Answer": 2746,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 18 * 10 * 11 + 14",
            "Answer": 31694,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 17 * 0 * 18 + 9",
            "Answer": 9,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 1 * 17 * 13 + 9",
            "Answer": 1335,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 7 * 4 * 18 + 12",
            "Answer": 1020,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 14 * 8 * 3 + 5",
            "Answer": 2693,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 6 * 14 * 17 + 9",
            "Answer": 20001,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 6 * 5 * 2 + 0",
            "Answer": 660,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 13 * 6 * 10 + 4",
            "Answer": 7804,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 19 * 15 * 2 + 2",
            "Answer": 5702,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 4 * 15 * 19 + 10",
            "Answer": 19390,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 5 * 12 * 10 + 2",
            "Answer": 3602,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 10 * 5 * 19 + 12",
            "Answer": 18062,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 15 * 16 * 6 + 7",
            "Answer": 1447,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 8 * 15 * 14 + 13",
            "Answer": 21853,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 14 * 2 * 2 + 7",
            "Answer": 903,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 8 * 10 * 11 + 18",
            "Answer": 13218,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 18 * 5 * 3 + 19",
            "Answer": 2989,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 5 * 7 * 4 + 10",
            "Answer": 1830,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 5 * 5 * 2 + 12",
            "Answer": 712,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 7 * 0 * 2 + 1",
            "Answer": 1,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 19 * 6 * 4 + 6",
            "Answer": 1374,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 14 * 18 * 12 + 5",
            "Answer": 15125,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 17 * 12 * 0 + 15",
            "Answer": 15,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 17 * 14 * 0 + 11",
            "Answer": 11,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 3 * 10 * 12 + 17",
            "Answer": 5777,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 17 * 6 * 3 + 3",
            "Answer": 309,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 0 * 15 * 10 + 4",
            "Answer": 4,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 12 * 2 * 9 + 2",
            "Answer": 1082,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 3 * 6 * 16 + 17",
            "Answer": 17,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 7 * 10 * 18 + 5",
            "Answer": 20165,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 2 * 5 * 4 + 17",
            "Answer": 17,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 3 * 0 * 7 + 4",
            "Answer": 4,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 5 * 4 * 3 + 8",
            "Answer": 368,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 1 * 7 * 15 + 15",
            "Answer": 330,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 14 * 12 * 7 + 7",
            "Answer": 19999,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 16 * 12 * 17 + 2",
            "Answer": 29378,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 3 * 16 * 16 + 16",
            "Answer": 13072,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 11 * 6 * 3 + 13",
            "Answer": 1399,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 12 * 7 * 19 + 13",
            "Answer": 23953,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 12 * 10 * 10 + 2",
            "Answer": 15602,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 18 * 19 * 16 + 18",
            "Answer": 27378,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 12 * 11 * 9 + 16",
            "Answer": 1204,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 13 * 3 * 19 + 6",
            "Answer": 4452,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 17 * 15 * 4 + 7",
            "Answer": 4087,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 11 * 9 * 0 + 6",
            "Answer": 6,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 1 * 14 * 19 + 19",
            "Answer": 817,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 16 * 19 * 8 + 14",
            "Answer": 12174,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 3 * 13 * 18 + 9",
            "Answer": 4923,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 14 * 13 * 5 + 1",
            "Answer": 16381,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 3 * 9 * 9 + 2",
            "Answer": 2432,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 11 * 17 * 2 + 4",
            "Answer": 2996,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 16 * 19 * 3 + 0",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 5 * 10 * 12 + 15",
            "Answer": 15,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 9 * 15 * 11 + 6",
            "Answer": 19311,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 2 * 19 * 4 + 3",
            "Answer": 2587,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 11 * 0 * 13 + 16",
            "Answer": 16,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 10 * 1 * 15 + 6",
            "Answer": 156,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 12 * 8 * 3 + 19",
            "Answer": 4051,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 7 * 3 * 9 + 3",
            "Answer": 1515,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 10 * 16 * 19 + 9",
            "Answer": 57769,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 5 * 6 * 16 + 1",
            "Answer": 5761,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 3 * 1 * 4 + 17",
            "Answer": 65,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 16 * 2 * 18 + 18",
            "Answer": 5778,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 13 * 10 * 16 + 8",
            "Answer": 18728,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 2 * 0 * 18 + 14",
            "Answer": 14,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 2 * 10 * 11 + 9",
            "Answer": 449,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 19 * 8 * 8 + 13",
            "Answer": 10957,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 14 * 3 * 1 + 1",
            "Answer": 295,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 5 * 2 * 7 + 1",
            "Answer": 701,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 3 * 10 * 13 + 12",
            "Answer": 4692,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 11 * 11 * 3 + 17",
            "Answer": 1106,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 16 * 11 * 5 + 19",
            "Answer": 14099,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 2 * 4 * 12 + 10",
            "Answer": 682,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 17 * 11 * 18 + 12",
            "Answer": 40404,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 1 * 4 * 7 + 6",
            "Answer": 426,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 10 * 14 * 17 + 0",
            "Answer": 9520,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 18 * 3 * 19 + 7",
            "Answer": 7189,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 15 * 0 * 4 + 2",
            "Answer": 2,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 9 * 19 * 13 + 9",
            "Answer": 15570,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 5 * 12 * 19 + 2",
            "Answer": 9122,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 15 * 11 * 3 + 16",
            "Answer": 6451,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 15 * 2 * 13 + 9",
            "Answer": 1179,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + #"
        }
    ],
    "# * # * # + # + #": [
        {
            "Question": "0 * 3 * 15 + 7 + 5",
            "Answer": 12,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 13 * 2 + 6 + 12",
            "Answer": 200,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 6 * 19 + 7 + 3",
            "Answer": 238,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 17 * 4 + 15 + 14",
            "Answer": 913,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 15 * 0 + 12 + 2",
            "Answer": 14,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 11 * 16 + 7 + 6",
            "Answer": 1069,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 0 * 7 + 8 + 6",
            "Answer": 14,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 6 * 5 + 5 + 3",
            "Answer": 248,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 14 * 16 + 1 + 9",
            "Answer": 1354,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 0 * 3 + 9 + 6",
            "Answer": 15,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 16 * 14 + 18 + 19",
            "Answer": 485,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 7 * 11 + 16 + 0",
            "Answer": 324,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 18 * 14 + 19 + 2",
            "Answer": 2793,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 11 * 18 + 13 + 2",
            "Answer": 2985,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 7 * 0 + 7 + 14",
            "Answer": 21,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 2 * 12 + 5 + 2",
            "Answer": 55,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 11 * 1 + 18 + 9",
            "Answer": 159,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 9 * 13 + 6 + 0",
            "Answer": 240,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 15 * 9 + 16 + 9",
            "Answer": 2590,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 19 * 10 + 4 + 19",
            "Answer": 3633,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 6 * 2 + 8 + 13",
            "Answer": 105,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 11 * 16 + 11 + 4",
            "Answer": 719,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 13 * 13 + 11 + 19",
            "Answer": 3072,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 8 * 3 + 7 + 16",
            "Answer": 23,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 2 * 6 + 17 + 6",
            "Answer": 107,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 1 * 10 + 7 + 2",
            "Answer": 119,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 7 * 7 + 16 + 11",
            "Answer": 566,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 18 * 8 + 16 + 6",
            "Answer": 1030,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 16 * 5 + 1 + 13",
            "Answer": 494,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 16 * 13 + 3 + 17",
            "Answer": 2100,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 0 * 11 + 10 + 10",
            "Answer": 20,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 14 * 15 + 17 + 10",
            "Answer": 1287,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 6 * 13 + 1 + 6",
            "Answer": 163,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 6 * 0 + 10 + 8",
            "Answer": 18,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 17 * 13 + 5 + 3",
            "Answer": 3765,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 5 * 4 + 17 + 15",
            "Answer": 192,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 9 * 0 + 0 + 14",
            "Answer": 14,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 8 * 17 + 9 + 4",
            "Answer": 1237,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 4 * 12 + 16 + 18",
            "Answer": 418,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 6 * 7 + 12 + 1",
            "Answer": 559,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 3 * 4 + 1 + 16",
            "Answer": 77,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 7 * 14 + 10 + 16",
            "Answer": 1496,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 13 * 12 + 9 + 3",
            "Answer": 12,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 13 * 12 + 18 + 11",
            "Answer": 1433,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 6 * 14 + 16 + 9",
            "Answer": 1369,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 7 * 5 + 17 + 8",
            "Answer": 165,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 5 * 1 + 0 + 14",
            "Answer": 69,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 3 * 15 + 16 + 2",
            "Answer": 288,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 19 * 17 + 15 + 13",
            "Answer": 3581,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 15 * 19 + 18 + 8",
            "Answer": 26,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 17 * 17 + 12 + 3",
            "Answer": 3772,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 16 * 9 + 2 + 13",
            "Answer": 1455,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 18 * 15 + 1 + 13",
            "Answer": 824,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 3 * 0 + 9 + 19",
            "Answer": 28,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 17 * 2 + 6 + 5",
            "Answer": 283,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 4 * 15 + 15 + 8",
            "Answer": 503,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 11 * 12 + 4 + 14",
            "Answer": 1338,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 6 * 1 + 3 + 17",
            "Answer": 32,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 6 * 18 + 17 + 9",
            "Answer": 1214,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 19 * 1 + 1 + 16",
            "Answer": 74,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 18 * 0 + 16 + 19",
            "Answer": 35,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 13 * 11 + 11 + 0",
            "Answer": 154,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 6 * 8 + 0 + 19",
            "Answer": 451,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 13 * 9 + 12 + 14",
            "Answer": 1313,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 8 * 16 + 8 + 11",
            "Answer": 1555,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 6 * 14 + 13 + 4",
            "Answer": 1529,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 19 * 12 + 8 + 0",
            "Answer": 236,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 14 * 14 + 19 + 0",
            "Answer": 2175,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 3 * 18 + 18 + 19",
            "Answer": 739,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 3 * 2 + 8 + 8",
            "Answer": 34,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 8 * 2 + 1 + 3",
            "Answer": 180,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 4 * 16 + 3 + 12",
            "Answer": 591,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 3 * 1 + 18 + 16",
            "Answer": 70,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 4 * 7 + 6 + 5",
            "Answer": 207,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 8 * 8 + 10 + 4",
            "Answer": 1230,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 0 * 8 + 14 + 12",
            "Answer": 26,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 13 * 9 + 5 + 0",
            "Answer": 1643,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 1 * 2 + 19 + 12",
            "Answer": 39,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 5 * 0 + 2 + 13",
            "Answer": 15,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 18 * 2 + 11 + 16",
            "Answer": 135,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 11 * 1 + 0 + 8",
            "Answer": 118,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 2 * 15 + 14 + 16",
            "Answer": 180,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 18 * 8 + 10 + 14",
            "Answer": 1896,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 12 * 8 + 15 + 11",
            "Answer": 506,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 14 * 5 + 17 + 10",
            "Answer": 797,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 5 * 17 + 6 + 7",
            "Answer": 863,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 14 * 9 + 3 + 7",
            "Answer": 2026,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 6 * 6 + 5 + 5",
            "Answer": 514,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 13 * 1 + 0 + 17",
            "Answer": 225,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 4 * 10 + 3 + 5",
            "Answer": 168,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 19 * 18 + 4 + 19",
            "Answer": 6179,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 8 * 16 + 13 + 6",
            "Answer": 2451,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 7 * 11 + 18 + 0",
            "Answer": 326,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 5 * 8 + 6 + 18",
            "Answer": 504,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 9 * 3 + 15 + 9",
            "Answer": 294,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 3 * 1 + 3 + 13",
            "Answer": 16,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 1 * 9 + 15 + 11",
            "Answer": 179,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 15 * 18 + 18 + 4",
            "Answer": 2722,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 12 * 19 + 8 + 5",
            "Answer": 1153,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 9 * 0 + 15 + 1",
            "Answer": 16,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + #"
        }
    ],
    "# * # + # + # + #": [
        {
            "Question": "19 * 14 + 15 + 3 + 19",
            "Answer": 303,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 18 + 14 + 5 + 18",
            "Answer": 55,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 8 + 3 + 19 + 12",
            "Answer": 114,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 11 + 0 + 12 + 19",
            "Answer": 152,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 8 + 7 + 6 + 12",
            "Answer": 41,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 8 + 6 + 4 + 6",
            "Answer": 152,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 0 + 6 + 19 + 17",
            "Answer": 42,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 4 + 16 + 5 + 5",
            "Answer": 78,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 14 + 16 + 0 + 0",
            "Answer": 212,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 16 + 11 + 11 + 10",
            "Answer": 112,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 12 + 9 + 10 + 3",
            "Answer": 82,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 7 + 6 + 3 + 17",
            "Answer": 47,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 2 + 17 + 1 + 16",
            "Answer": 64,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 17 + 16 + 17 + 17",
            "Answer": 135,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 5 + 10 + 6 + 13",
            "Answer": 39,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 10 + 3 + 14 + 2",
            "Answer": 69,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 2 + 7 + 4 + 1",
            "Answer": 46,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 8 + 18 + 4 + 0",
            "Answer": 102,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 1 + 3 + 2 + 6",
            "Answer": 11,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 13 + 17 + 17 + 0",
            "Answer": 177,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 2 + 18 + 19 + 8",
            "Answer": 69,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 1 + 8 + 5 + 10",
            "Answer": 30,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 10 + 14 + 18 + 0",
            "Answer": 152,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 12 + 15 + 2 + 17",
            "Answer": 202,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 2 + 7 + 19 + 13",
            "Answer": 51,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 4 + 7 + 5 + 17",
            "Answer": 77,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 13 + 16 + 0 + 4",
            "Answer": 137,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 6 + 19 + 11 + 17",
            "Answer": 107,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 6 + 12 + 15 + 18",
            "Answer": 129,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 11 + 18 + 6 + 5",
            "Answer": 62,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 8 + 15 + 0 + 15",
            "Answer": 78,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 16 + 5 + 8 + 17",
            "Answer": 110,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 9 + 7 + 12 + 16",
            "Answer": 116,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 11 + 2 + 1 + 4",
            "Answer": 117,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 14 + 16 + 15 + 0",
            "Answer": 73,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 1 + 10 + 12 + 4",
            "Answer": 28,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 17 + 15 + 9 + 19",
            "Answer": 43,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 4 + 0 + 3 + 9",
            "Answer": 84,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 14 + 11 + 8 + 7",
            "Answer": 138,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 0 + 1 + 3 + 12",
            "Answer": 16,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 10 + 1 + 15 + 19",
            "Answer": 75,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 8 + 0 + 17 + 4",
            "Answer": 61,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 15 + 1 + 10 + 8",
            "Answer": 184,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 7 + 15 + 10 + 17",
            "Answer": 161,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 8 + 12 + 2 + 17",
            "Answer": 71,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 14 + 19 + 19 + 19",
            "Answer": 141,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 8 + 3 + 16 + 1",
            "Answer": 148,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 11 + 15 + 10 + 14",
            "Answer": 127,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 1 + 11 + 19 + 13",
            "Answer": 61,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 19 + 8 + 16 + 9",
            "Answer": 147,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 17 + 17 + 0 + 12",
            "Answer": 131,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 6 + 18 + 9 + 7",
            "Answer": 106,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 8 + 14 + 10 + 19",
            "Answer": 59,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 10 + 13 + 10 + 18",
            "Answer": 141,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 10 + 16 + 19 + 4",
            "Answer": 79,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 7 + 15 + 10 + 2",
            "Answer": 62,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 6 + 12 + 5 + 10",
            "Answer": 75,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 16 + 5 + 16 + 17",
            "Answer": 294,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 4 + 16 + 3 + 16",
            "Answer": 99,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 15 + 14 + 13 + 11",
            "Answer": 143,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 7 + 0 + 6 + 8",
            "Answer": 84,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 2 + 12 + 1 + 3",
            "Answer": 20,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 0 + 1 + 9 + 18",
            "Answer": 28,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 0 + 7 + 0 + 6",
            "Answer": 13,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 6 + 12 + 11 + 5",
            "Answer": 106,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 6 + 11 + 5 + 9",
            "Answer": 49,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 10 + 5 + 4 + 6",
            "Answer": 35,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 13 + 14 + 5 + 2",
            "Answer": 73,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 5 + 7 + 1 + 9",
            "Answer": 87,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 0 + 16 + 7 + 10",
            "Answer": 33,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 14 + 0 + 0 + 12",
            "Answer": 180,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 10 + 15 + 7 + 4",
            "Answer": 66,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 12 + 8 + 7 + 6",
            "Answer": 165,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 2 + 3 + 19 + 3",
            "Answer": 43,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 5 + 6 + 9 + 5",
            "Answer": 90,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 3 + 9 + 15 + 13",
            "Answer": 55,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 0 + 6 + 10 + 4",
            "Answer": 20,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 17 + 18 + 3 + 13",
            "Answer": 289,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 4 + 7 + 8 + 1",
            "Answer": 24,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 19 + 11 + 18 + 6",
            "Answer": 111,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 9 + 1 + 12 + 5",
            "Answer": 108,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 15 + 8 + 16 + 16",
            "Answer": 70,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 6 + 19 + 6 + 8",
            "Answer": 87,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 9 + 17 + 6 + 6",
            "Answer": 164,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 7 + 4 + 13 + 5",
            "Answer": 127,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 19 + 10 + 19 + 6",
            "Answer": 206,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 16 + 19 + 5 + 2",
            "Answer": 138,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 19 + 16 + 5 + 19",
            "Answer": 325,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 17 + 2 + 1 + 2",
            "Answer": 311,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 11 + 2 + 19 + 0",
            "Answer": 164,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 12 + 17 + 8 + 17",
            "Answer": 210,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 3 + 12 + 10 + 7",
            "Answer": 83,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 15 + 3 + 18 + 0",
            "Answer": 216,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 3 + 7 + 10 + 4",
            "Answer": 42,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 1 + 8 + 19 + 11",
            "Answer": 45,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 10 + 11 + 16 + 6",
            "Answer": 173,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 17 + 12 + 2 + 8",
            "Answer": 277,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 15 + 7 + 5 + 3",
            "Answer": 30,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 5 + 6 + 10 + 13",
            "Answer": 74,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 0 + 18 + 19 + 2",
            "Answer": 39,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + #"
        }
    ],
    "# + # + # + # * #": [
        {
            "Question": "11 + 4 + 7 + 0 * 12",
            "Answer": 22,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 16 + 10 + 4 * 19",
            "Answer": 104,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 17 + 2 + 5 * 6",
            "Answer": 62,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 2 + 19 + 12 * 13",
            "Answer": 186,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 7 + 12 + 18 * 16",
            "Answer": 311,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 5 + 11 + 12 * 2",
            "Answer": 42,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 10 + 7 + 16 * 11",
            "Answer": 212,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 2 + 9 + 12 * 18",
            "Answer": 233,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 2 + 19 + 8 * 0",
            "Answer": 34,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 0 + 2 + 14 * 18",
            "Answer": 263,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 14 + 10 + 14 * 4",
            "Answer": 98,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 0 + 9 + 14 * 3",
            "Answer": 57,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 16 + 19 + 14 * 14",
            "Answer": 239,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 9 + 16 + 14 * 3",
            "Answer": 75,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 15 + 15 + 0 * 16",
            "Answer": 30,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 0 + 2 + 0 * 16",
            "Answer": 6,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 11 + 1 + 10 * 12",
            "Answer": 143,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 5 + 14 + 19 * 11",
            "Answer": 238,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 0 + 17 + 2 * 19",
            "Answer": 70,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 19 + 14 + 18 * 14",
            "Answer": 288,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 9 + 9 + 18 * 14",
            "Answer": 274,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 8 + 10 + 8 * 0",
            "Answer": 23,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 17 + 16 + 2 * 19",
            "Answer": 87,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 0 + 2 + 1 * 9",
            "Answer": 26,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 0 + 9 + 15 * 16",
            "Answer": 262,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 12 + 18 + 11 * 7",
            "Answer": 112,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 0 + 11 + 11 * 14",
            "Answer": 177,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 0 + 5 + 18 * 3",
            "Answer": 73,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 4 + 12 + 14 * 16",
            "Answer": 243,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 17 + 13 + 19 * 15",
            "Answer": 322,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 5 + 1 + 10 * 17",
            "Answer": 182,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 4 + 16 + 14 * 14",
            "Answer": 218,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 12 + 9 + 4 * 3",
            "Answer": 48,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 5 + 10 + 7 * 4",
            "Answer": 52,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 3 + 7 + 10 * 0",
            "Answer": 25,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 1 + 6 + 3 * 4",
            "Answer": 23,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 8 + 1 + 17 * 10",
            "Answer": 190,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 3 + 6 + 10 * 3",
            "Answer": 51,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 5 + 9 + 19 * 19",
            "Answer": 377,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 12 + 5 + 15 * 12",
            "Answer": 215,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 9 + 7 + 12 * 9",
            "Answer": 134,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 17 + 3 + 13 * 3",
            "Answer": 77,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 14 + 12 + 19 * 17",
            "Answer": 362,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 5 + 0 + 8 * 8",
            "Answer": 79,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 13 + 4 + 2 * 4",
            "Answer": 36,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 15 + 12 + 8 * 6",
            "Answer": 84,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 10 + 7 + 10 * 18",
            "Answer": 212,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 19 + 13 + 7 * 6",
            "Answer": 91,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 1 + 15 + 14 * 12",
            "Answer": 200,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 8 + 6 + 19 * 12",
            "Answer": 254,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 8 + 8 + 12 * 18",
            "Answer": 249,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 11 + 14 + 15 * 12",
            "Answer": 216,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 5 + 8 + 10 * 11",
            "Answer": 127,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 0 + 13 + 5 * 4",
            "Answer": 52,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 2 + 15 + 4 * 10",
            "Answer": 71,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 13 + 16 + 12 * 15",
            "Answer": 216,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 0 + 16 + 13 * 7",
            "Answer": 116,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 8 + 18 + 19 * 15",
            "Answer": 316,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 17 + 1 + 14 * 13",
            "Answer": 216,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 17 + 5 + 2 * 2",
            "Answer": 37,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 19 + 18 + 7 * 10",
            "Answer": 116,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 17 + 14 + 14 * 18",
            "Answer": 300,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 3 + 2 + 18 * 2",
            "Answer": 51,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 3 + 18 + 3 * 2",
            "Answer": 29,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 9 + 2 + 1 * 4",
            "Answer": 19,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 3 + 11 + 16 * 13",
            "Answer": 239,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 15 + 9 + 10 * 6",
            "Answer": 98,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 16 + 3 + 9 * 6",
            "Answer": 84,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 19 + 10 + 3 * 4",
            "Answer": 45,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 15 + 9 + 7 * 9",
            "Answer": 88,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 7 + 16 + 3 * 2",
            "Answer": 37,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 10 + 8 + 14 * 15",
            "Answer": 238,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 17 + 19 + 11 * 12",
            "Answer": 174,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 1 + 2 + 1 * 19",
            "Answer": 30,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 7 + 14 + 10 * 16",
            "Answer": 188,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 16 + 10 + 6 * 16",
            "Answer": 127,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 6 + 6 + 6 * 12",
            "Answer": 85,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 4 + 9 + 1 * 7",
            "Answer": 32,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 19 + 10 + 12 * 14",
            "Answer": 212,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 1 + 6 + 10 * 10",
            "Answer": 110,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 11 + 2 + 4 * 16",
            "Answer": 88,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 12 + 14 + 11 * 16",
            "Answer": 221,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 12 + 15 + 4 * 4",
            "Answer": 58,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 3 + 3 + 0 * 0",
            "Answer": 23,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 15 + 18 + 15 * 8",
            "Answer": 171,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 6 + 13 + 0 * 4",
            "Answer": 34,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 14 + 0 + 5 * 12",
            "Answer": 83,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 3 + 5 + 2 * 8",
            "Answer": 24,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 7 + 19 + 3 * 7",
            "Answer": 57,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 14 + 8 + 6 * 4",
            "Answer": 51,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 7 + 17 + 8 * 15",
            "Answer": 148,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 0 + 2 + 3 * 2",
            "Answer": 22,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 14 + 14 + 16 * 2",
            "Answer": 73,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 10 + 0 + 8 * 19",
            "Answer": 162,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 15 + 7 + 11 * 1",
            "Answer": 39,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 15 + 12 + 5 * 12",
            "Answer": 95,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 8 + 19 + 1 * 0",
            "Answer": 27,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 5 + 15 + 8 * 16",
            "Answer": 162,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 10 + 17 + 3 * 6",
            "Answer": 50,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 19 + 15 + 12 * 4",
            "Answer": 95,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * #"
        }
    ],
    "# + # * # * # + #": [
        {
            "Question": "6 + 3 * 6 * 13 + 16",
            "Answer": 256,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 10 * 4 * 17 + 0",
            "Answer": 681,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 5 * 12 * 7 + 15",
            "Answer": 442,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 4 * 16 * 0 + 9",
            "Answer": 19,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 8 * 1 * 10 + 19",
            "Answer": 109,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 10 * 18 * 10 + 15",
            "Answer": 1815,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 1 * 1 * 17 + 9",
            "Answer": 40,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 2 * 16 * 6 + 17",
            "Answer": 213,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 2 * 8 * 11 + 2",
            "Answer": 193,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 19 * 0 * 10 + 6",
            "Answer": 13,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 13 * 1 * 5 + 7",
            "Answer": 87,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 2 * 4 * 0 + 16",
            "Answer": 24,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 10 * 9 * 13 + 18",
            "Answer": 1200,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 6 * 5 * 12 + 12",
            "Answer": 380,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 16 * 14 * 3 + 17",
            "Answer": 705,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 8 * 5 * 7 + 4",
            "Answer": 301,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 13 * 10 * 1 + 6",
            "Answer": 137,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 18 * 0 * 7 + 1",
            "Answer": 13,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 12 * 4 * 10 + 17",
            "Answer": 509,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 2 * 12 * 4 + 2",
            "Answer": 98,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 1 * 15 * 12 + 6",
            "Answer": 200,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 7 * 9 * 12 + 11",
            "Answer": 772,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 17 * 6 * 11 + 15",
            "Answer": 1142,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 7 * 17 * 9 + 5",
            "Answer": 1094,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 11 * 9 * 19 + 11",
            "Answer": 1901,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 0 * 3 * 9 + 6",
            "Answer": 15,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 17 * 6 * 18 + 7",
            "Answer": 1853,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 6 * 4 * 15 + 3",
            "Answer": 363,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 13 * 4 * 6 + 7",
            "Answer": 338,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 14 * 18 * 9 + 18",
            "Answer": 2303,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 2 * 17 * 7 + 9",
            "Answer": 260,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 19 * 9 * 5 + 10",
            "Answer": 881,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 9 * 15 * 17 + 5",
            "Answer": 2315,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 2 * 6 * 6 + 2",
            "Answer": 85,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 2 * 4 * 10 + 19",
            "Answer": 104,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 0 * 5 * 3 + 17",
            "Answer": 26,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 11 * 14 * 10 + 10",
            "Answer": 1556,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 19 * 19 * 2 + 19",
            "Answer": 746,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 15 * 10 * 10 + 5",
            "Answer": 1520,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 6 * 9 * 17 + 16",
            "Answer": 935,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 0 * 6 * 13 + 1",
            "Answer": 2,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 6 * 19 * 13 + 5",
            "Answer": 1502,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 1 * 11 * 0 + 3",
            "Answer": 16,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 18 * 7 * 13 + 6",
            "Answer": 1660,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 18 * 3 * 18 + 4",
            "Answer": 986,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 9 * 17 * 17 + 5",
            "Answer": 2611,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 4 * 18 * 1 + 11",
            "Answer": 100,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 8 * 11 * 2 + 13",
            "Answer": 208,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 4 * 0 * 10 + 14",
            "Answer": 24,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 15 * 2 * 3 + 0",
            "Answer": 92,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 16 * 0 * 18 + 10",
            "Answer": 24,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 3 * 4 * 14 + 11",
            "Answer": 187,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 15 * 9 * 4 + 5",
            "Answer": 562,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 4 * 12 * 12 + 15",
            "Answer": 602,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 8 * 10 * 6 + 17",
            "Answer": 508,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 1 * 5 * 15 + 0",
            "Answer": 84,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 9 * 9 * 10 + 0",
            "Answer": 828,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 15 * 5 * 0 + 18",
            "Answer": 18,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 10 * 8 * 14 + 8",
            "Answer": 1141,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 13 * 2 * 11 + 14",
            "Answer": 312,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 16 * 13 * 2 + 13",
            "Answer": 445,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 9 * 14 * 13 + 8",
            "Answer": 1656,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 15 * 7 * 18 + 10",
            "Answer": 1918,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 15 * 5 * 3 + 3",
            "Answer": 243,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 18 * 0 * 11 + 0",
            "Answer": 9,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 2 * 7 * 4 + 19",
            "Answer": 76,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 12 * 12 * 12 + 7",
            "Answer": 1750,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 17 * 11 * 19 + 18",
            "Answer": 3574,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 4 * 8 * 10 + 10",
            "Answer": 343,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 8 * 18 * 9 + 13",
            "Answer": 1311,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 9 * 10 * 3 + 16",
            "Answer": 293,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 13 * 14 * 12 + 9",
            "Answer": 2212,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 6 * 10 * 19 + 7",
            "Answer": 1157,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 9 * 5 * 14 + 15",
            "Answer": 645,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 1 * 9 * 1 + 3",
            "Answer": 17,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 0 * 6 * 18 + 17",
            "Answer": 25,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 0 * 13 * 13 + 16",
            "Answer": 26,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 16 * 0 * 9 + 6",
            "Answer": 22,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 4 * 1 * 3 + 3",
            "Answer": 34,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 9 * 7 * 1 + 11",
            "Answer": 81,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 6 * 9 * 17 + 18",
            "Answer": 939,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 7 * 5 * 8 + 12",
            "Answer": 296,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 13 * 2 * 11 + 3",
            "Answer": 305,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 0 * 11 * 0 + 12",
            "Answer": 21,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 10 * 9 * 5 + 19",
            "Answer": 481,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 1 * 14 * 14 + 7",
            "Answer": 220,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 1 * 5 * 16 + 9",
            "Answer": 90,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 13 * 7 * 11 + 12",
            "Answer": 1015,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 2 * 17 * 18 + 9",
            "Answer": 632,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 18 * 0 * 17 + 13",
            "Answer": 29,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 12 * 10 * 5 + 0",
            "Answer": 606,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 9 * 0 * 1 + 9",
            "Answer": 22,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 3 * 9 * 3 + 13",
            "Answer": 102,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 3 * 11 * 18 + 10",
            "Answer": 606,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 2 * 14 * 16 + 4",
            "Answer": 462,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 7 * 13 * 12 + 6",
            "Answer": 1111,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 1 * 10 * 15 + 5",
            "Answer": 165,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 15 * 15 * 12 + 7",
            "Answer": 2716,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 9 * 11 * 5 + 8",
            "Answer": 509,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 18 * 4 * 9 + 6",
            "Answer": 668,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + #"
        }
    ],
    "# + # * # + # + #": [
        {
            "Question": "15 + 6 * 10 + 1 + 17",
            "Answer": 93,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 7 * 6 + 11 + 8",
            "Answer": 70,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 16 * 12 + 3 + 6",
            "Answer": 219,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 14 * 15 + 6 + 16",
            "Answer": 238,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 5 * 19 + 19 + 17",
            "Answer": 148,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 3 * 19 + 5 + 9",
            "Answer": 73,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 1 * 12 + 8 + 12",
            "Answer": 36,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 15 * 16 + 15 + 0",
            "Answer": 270,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 14 * 7 + 18 + 10",
            "Answer": 132,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 4 * 1 + 16 + 3",
            "Answer": 39,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 0 * 1 + 5 + 10",
            "Answer": 23,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 17 * 10 + 12 + 19",
            "Answer": 210,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 17 * 11 + 3 + 10",
            "Answer": 210,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 10 * 15 + 6 + 3",
            "Answer": 171,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 18 * 4 + 4 + 17",
            "Answer": 94,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 7 * 1 + 12 + 5",
            "Answer": 39,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 18 * 12 + 19 + 17",
            "Answer": 255,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 10 * 0 + 2 + 1",
            "Answer": 22,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 6 * 8 + 6 + 3",
            "Answer": 64,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 1 * 1 + 9 + 18",
            "Answer": 35,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 2 * 19 + 1 + 17",
            "Answer": 65,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 17 * 7 + 15 + 11",
            "Answer": 155,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 12 * 14 + 8 + 18",
            "Answer": 208,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 6 * 5 + 10 + 3",
            "Answer": 45,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 18 * 10 + 12 + 18",
            "Answer": 225,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 12 * 15 + 17 + 12",
            "Answer": 211,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 15 * 2 + 1 + 10",
            "Answer": 44,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 6 * 12 + 3 + 11",
            "Answer": 88,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 16 * 11 + 9 + 11",
            "Answer": 214,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 0 * 15 + 4 + 18",
            "Answer": 41,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 12 * 5 + 4 + 8",
            "Answer": 81,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 3 * 2 + 14 + 16",
            "Answer": 36,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 5 * 18 + 10 + 6",
            "Answer": 125,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 9 * 7 + 2 + 6",
            "Answer": 77,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 2 * 3 + 14 + 0",
            "Answer": 26,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 5 * 19 + 9 + 8",
            "Answer": 127,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 8 * 4 + 8 + 0",
            "Answer": 47,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 7 * 0 + 4 + 9",
            "Answer": 21,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 1 * 7 + 6 + 10",
            "Answer": 37,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 18 * 6 + 16 + 13",
            "Answer": 143,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 8 * 9 + 14 + 18",
            "Answer": 104,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 3 * 2 + 16 + 12",
            "Answer": 52,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 17 * 3 + 1 + 16",
            "Answer": 74,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 13 * 10 + 5 + 9",
            "Answer": 150,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 0 * 9 + 10 + 18",
            "Answer": 44,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 4 * 16 + 11 + 3",
            "Answer": 80,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 17 * 4 + 3 + 13",
            "Answer": 88,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 14 * 0 + 12 + 3",
            "Answer": 27,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 10 * 7 + 7 + 14",
            "Answer": 94,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 7 * 17 + 8 + 7",
            "Answer": 142,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 1 * 18 + 4 + 7",
            "Answer": 33,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 19 * 16 + 16 + 9",
            "Answer": 335,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 11 * 2 + 10 + 12",
            "Answer": 46,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 2 * 4 + 16 + 19",
            "Answer": 53,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 16 * 3 + 19 + 2",
            "Answer": 81,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 13 * 17 + 3 + 19",
            "Answer": 251,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 15 * 18 + 17 + 11",
            "Answer": 317,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 0 * 19 + 18 + 15",
            "Answer": 36,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 13 * 6 + 8 + 1",
            "Answer": 91,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 9 * 6 + 18 + 4",
            "Answer": 80,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 10 * 1 + 5 + 1",
            "Answer": 23,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 11 * 9 + 11 + 9",
            "Answer": 122,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 4 * 4 + 1 + 0",
            "Answer": 35,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 4 * 3 + 11 + 16",
            "Answer": 41,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 17 * 18 + 18 + 13",
            "Answer": 338,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 9 * 8 + 18 + 3",
            "Answer": 106,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 16 * 11 + 17 + 4",
            "Answer": 212,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 12 * 19 + 11 + 12",
            "Answer": 254,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 1 * 15 + 17 + 4",
            "Answer": 45,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 13 * 3 + 7 + 3",
            "Answer": 66,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 15 * 12 + 5 + 8",
            "Answer": 201,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 19 * 2 + 5 + 0",
            "Answer": 57,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 13 * 3 + 10 + 4",
            "Answer": 57,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 14 * 3 + 8 + 13",
            "Answer": 68,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 13 * 9 + 7 + 15",
            "Answer": 141,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 11 * 4 + 12 + 17",
            "Answer": 74,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 6 * 6 + 9 + 19",
            "Answer": 73,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 18 * 15 + 10 + 13",
            "Answer": 310,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 10 * 5 + 13 + 0",
            "Answer": 81,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 13 * 2 + 13 + 18",
            "Answer": 69,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 18 * 5 + 13 + 13",
            "Answer": 117,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 15 * 4 + 4 + 5",
            "Answer": 84,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 0 * 3 + 3 + 1",
            "Answer": 18,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 10 * 16 + 13 + 12",
            "Answer": 199,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 9 * 19 + 12 + 11",
            "Answer": 202,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 18 * 10 + 16 + 0",
            "Answer": 210,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 5 * 7 + 4 + 3",
            "Answer": 60,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 6 * 3 + 11 + 11",
            "Answer": 51,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 17 * 2 + 12 + 17",
            "Answer": 67,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 18 * 5 + 11 + 10",
            "Answer": 114,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 18 * 2 + 15 + 16",
            "Answer": 83,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 17 * 0 + 13 + 13",
            "Answer": 32,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 5 * 18 + 3 + 5",
            "Answer": 108,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 19 * 0 + 12 + 1",
            "Answer": 27,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 7 * 11 + 13 + 19",
            "Answer": 118,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 8 * 14 + 16 + 2",
            "Answer": 140,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 11 * 9 + 6 + 17",
            "Answer": 128,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 11 * 9 + 11 + 17",
            "Answer": 131,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 13 * 9 + 2 + 5",
            "Answer": 136,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 0 * 3 + 16 + 18",
            "Answer": 42,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + #"
        }
    ],
    "# * # + # + # * #": [
        {
            "Question": "12 * 19 + 3 + 15 * 8",
            "Answer": 351,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 15 + 11 + 13 * 10",
            "Answer": 321,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 13 + 11 + 5 * 11",
            "Answer": 183,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 16 + 3 + 1 * 10",
            "Answer": 173,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 12 + 18 + 6 * 3",
            "Answer": 144,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 7 + 13 + 4 * 16",
            "Answer": 112,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 12 + 9 + 7 * 4",
            "Answer": 97,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 2 + 1 + 3 * 5",
            "Answer": 22,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 7 + 3 + 16 * 13",
            "Answer": 323,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 7 + 0 + 17 * 7",
            "Answer": 189,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 2 + 11 + 8 * 2",
            "Answer": 35,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 18 + 4 + 8 * 7",
            "Answer": 330,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 4 + 17 + 14 * 16",
            "Answer": 265,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 6 + 1 + 0 * 2",
            "Answer": 79,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 14 + 8 + 10 * 5",
            "Answer": 100,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 16 + 8 + 1 * 6",
            "Answer": 254,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 1 + 13 + 18 * 13",
            "Answer": 254,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 17 + 18 + 11 * 19",
            "Answer": 482,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 3 + 0 + 12 * 17",
            "Answer": 204,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 1 + 9 + 9 * 3",
            "Answer": 36,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 8 + 7 + 1 * 0",
            "Answer": 71,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 9 + 13 + 19 * 7",
            "Answer": 182,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 5 + 15 + 16 * 14",
            "Answer": 264,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 7 + 8 + 9 * 5",
            "Answer": 158,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 14 + 14 + 2 * 4",
            "Answer": 190,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 17 + 12 + 18 * 11",
            "Answer": 482,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 7 + 11 + 18 * 13",
            "Answer": 364,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 19 + 1 + 0 * 16",
            "Answer": 115,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 1 + 13 + 10 * 4",
            "Answer": 58,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 1 + 1 + 5 * 4",
            "Answer": 25,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 4 + 15 + 6 * 13",
            "Answer": 105,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 18 + 7 + 17 * 10",
            "Answer": 231,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 9 + 4 + 16 * 18",
            "Answer": 382,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 9 + 9 + 12 * 1",
            "Answer": 21,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 13 + 16 + 0 * 8",
            "Answer": 172,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 2 + 7 + 10 * 0",
            "Answer": 31,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 10 + 6 + 9 * 13",
            "Answer": 293,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 17 + 16 + 5 * 15",
            "Answer": 363,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 3 + 18 + 8 * 2",
            "Answer": 55,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 13 + 14 + 8 * 6",
            "Answer": 153,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 0 + 19 + 7 * 10",
            "Answer": 89,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 6 + 12 + 4 * 14",
            "Answer": 176,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 0 + 14 + 7 * 11",
            "Answer": 91,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 15 + 6 + 19 * 14",
            "Answer": 512,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 13 + 8 + 13 * 4",
            "Answer": 255,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 7 + 17 + 11 * 8",
            "Answer": 217,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 9 + 12 + 2 * 0",
            "Answer": 102,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 2 + 11 + 9 * 19",
            "Answer": 202,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 18 + 12 + 4 * 17",
            "Answer": 152,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 15 + 14 + 2 * 9",
            "Answer": 137,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 8 + 5 + 16 * 9",
            "Answer": 205,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 13 + 9 + 13 * 1",
            "Answer": 256,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 4 + 13 + 18 * 18",
            "Answer": 397,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 17 + 7 + 18 * 0",
            "Answer": 262,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 13 + 13 + 17 * 12",
            "Answer": 282,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 11 + 5 + 2 * 3",
            "Answer": 143,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 0 + 9 + 5 * 14",
            "Answer": 79,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 10 + 19 + 11 * 7",
            "Answer": 226,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 14 + 17 + 5 * 12",
            "Answer": 217,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 9 + 0 + 0 * 10",
            "Answer": 27,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 18 + 14 + 11 * 10",
            "Answer": 412,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 5 + 16 + 12 * 3",
            "Answer": 52,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 1 + 5 + 8 * 11",
            "Answer": 100,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 8 + 11 + 4 * 13",
            "Answer": 191,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 9 + 15 + 14 * 9",
            "Answer": 222,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 9 + 13 + 7 * 0",
            "Answer": 22,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 0 + 15 + 3 * 6",
            "Answer": 33,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 18 + 13 + 19 * 10",
            "Answer": 221,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 4 + 11 + 18 * 0",
            "Answer": 15,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 1 + 13 + 12 * 1",
            "Answer": 36,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 19 + 18 + 1 * 1",
            "Answer": 247,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 1 + 11 + 12 * 12",
            "Answer": 157,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 0 + 18 + 0 * 17",
            "Answer": 18,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 12 + 2 + 10 * 3",
            "Answer": 200,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 6 + 19 + 4 * 9",
            "Answer": 133,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 19 + 17 + 14 * 14",
            "Answer": 479,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 7 + 18 + 10 * 14",
            "Answer": 263,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 3 + 8 + 2 * 15",
            "Answer": 71,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 13 + 9 + 19 * 11",
            "Answer": 244,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 12 + 10 + 6 * 8",
            "Answer": 178,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 10 + 18 + 14 * 0",
            "Answer": 168,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 14 + 9 + 12 * 18",
            "Answer": 477,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 8 + 3 + 3 * 7",
            "Answer": 96,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 15 + 16 + 2 * 15",
            "Answer": 166,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 16 + 11 + 2 * 16",
            "Answer": 299,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 7 + 2 + 13 * 3",
            "Answer": 111,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 3 + 18 + 3 * 0",
            "Answer": 60,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 9 + 12 + 19 * 10",
            "Answer": 229,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 10 + 5 + 17 * 0",
            "Answer": 55,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 14 + 19 + 14 * 13",
            "Answer": 229,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 11 + 3 + 16 * 11",
            "Answer": 366,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 6 + 12 + 1 * 1",
            "Answer": 43,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 10 + 15 + 5 * 3",
            "Answer": 70,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 15 + 13 + 18 * 19",
            "Answer": 520,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 7 + 10 + 18 * 7",
            "Answer": 227,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 6 + 19 + 9 * 4",
            "Answer": 163,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 12 + 0 + 4 * 4",
            "Answer": 112,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 16 + 2 + 16 * 0",
            "Answer": 66,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 3 + 7 + 1 * 0",
            "Answer": 34,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 11 + 13 + 9 * 10",
            "Answer": 191,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * #"
        }
    ],
    "# * # * # + # * #": [
        {
            "Question": "1 * 12 * 4 + 18 * 12",
            "Answer": 264,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 1 * 15 + 1 * 15",
            "Answer": 15,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 7 * 10 + 18 * 13",
            "Answer": 934,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 15 * 16 + 1 * 13",
            "Answer": 4573,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 12 * 17 + 0 * 3",
            "Answer": 1428,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 4 * 7 + 14 * 14",
            "Answer": 504,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 14 * 18 + 13 * 6",
            "Answer": 2598,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 17 * 12 + 7 * 12",
            "Answer": 3960,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 8 * 8 + 18 * 16",
            "Answer": 288,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 13 * 11 + 10 * 16",
            "Answer": 2305,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 2 * 1 + 9 * 4",
            "Answer": 60,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 12 * 17 + 19 * 3",
            "Answer": 2709,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 5 * 10 + 10 * 8",
            "Answer": 180,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 3 * 15 + 1 * 16",
            "Answer": 646,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 2 * 17 + 5 * 15",
            "Answer": 347,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 2 * 4 + 8 * 9",
            "Answer": 224,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 7 * 5 + 16 * 10",
            "Answer": 160,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 19 * 14 + 7 * 3",
            "Answer": 3213,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 16 * 15 + 0 * 17",
            "Answer": 3360,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 5 * 19 + 0 * 12",
            "Answer": 855,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 6 * 1 + 0 * 12",
            "Answer": 42,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 13 * 0 + 11 * 1",
            "Answer": 11,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 11 * 5 + 14 * 15",
            "Answer": 1090,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 13 * 2 + 1 * 16",
            "Answer": 224,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 4 * 19 + 13 * 5",
            "Answer": 901,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 4 * 1 + 17 * 18",
            "Answer": 334,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 2 * 14 + 7 * 18",
            "Answer": 378,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 3 * 5 + 16 * 14",
            "Answer": 374,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 5 * 10 + 19 * 15",
            "Answer": 535,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 10 * 2 + 10 * 14",
            "Answer": 480,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 17 * 12 + 9 * 15",
            "Answer": 2175,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 9 * 0 + 19 * 7",
            "Answer": 133,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 5 * 8 + 7 * 10",
            "Answer": 150,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 9 * 12 + 18 * 12",
            "Answer": 2268,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 3 * 0 + 15 * 7",
            "Answer": 105,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 4 * 17 + 18 * 1",
            "Answer": 1106,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 15 * 17 + 11 * 3",
            "Answer": 1818,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 12 * 8 + 10 * 19",
            "Answer": 1246,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 11 * 4 + 10 * 1",
            "Answer": 274,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 2 * 18 + 14 * 15",
            "Answer": 642,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 9 * 12 + 2 * 16",
            "Answer": 896,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 2 * 1 + 2 * 14",
            "Answer": 36,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 7 * 18 + 18 * 19",
            "Answer": 2610,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 7 * 3 + 12 * 2",
            "Answer": 108,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 3 * 9 + 4 * 6",
            "Answer": 510,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 1 * 19 + 3 * 15",
            "Answer": 406,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 8 * 5 + 9 * 10",
            "Answer": 690,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 3 * 8 + 7 * 5",
            "Answer": 443,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 19 * 10 + 17 * 1",
            "Answer": 1347,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 10 * 0 + 10 * 6",
            "Answer": 60,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 3 * 8 + 7 * 11",
            "Answer": 533,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 4 * 5 + 6 * 2",
            "Answer": 252,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 13 * 2 + 11 * 10",
            "Answer": 370,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 5 * 19 + 18 * 4",
            "Answer": 832,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 10 * 6 + 3 * 10",
            "Answer": 150,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 18 * 7 + 9 * 18",
            "Answer": 2556,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 1 * 7 + 10 * 13",
            "Answer": 249,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 12 * 5 + 12 * 0",
            "Answer": 1080,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 8 * 9 + 19 * 9",
            "Answer": 1179,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 16 * 13 + 2 * 19",
            "Answer": 2534,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 0 * 10 + 9 * 12",
            "Answer": 108,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 15 * 16 + 12 * 11",
            "Answer": 132,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 7 * 12 + 12 * 3",
            "Answer": 456,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 19 * 13 + 16 * 9",
            "Answer": 1873,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 16 * 1 + 17 * 1",
            "Answer": 145,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 13 * 15 + 7 * 19",
            "Answer": 133,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 0 * 13 + 1 * 10",
            "Answer": 10,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 19 * 0 + 7 * 13",
            "Answer": 91,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 15 * 6 + 13 * 6",
            "Answer": 1068,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 3 * 17 + 10 * 15",
            "Answer": 405,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 4 * 16 + 17 * 6",
            "Answer": 870,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 4 * 10 + 0 * 3",
            "Answer": 440,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 10 * 19 + 15 * 16",
            "Answer": 810,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 9 * 11 + 11 * 4",
            "Answer": 836,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 19 * 11 + 7 * 2",
            "Answer": 223,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 3 * 4 + 11 * 1",
            "Answer": 215,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 12 * 10 + 0 * 7",
            "Answer": 1920,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 14 * 3 + 5 * 0",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 11 * 4 + 7 * 12",
            "Answer": 480,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 1 * 3 + 18 * 13",
            "Answer": 261,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 13 * 3 + 3 * 4",
            "Answer": 558,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 5 * 9 + 8 * 17",
            "Answer": 946,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 16 * 14 + 0 * 1",
            "Answer": 1120,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 1 * 13 + 7 * 17",
            "Answer": 119,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 6 * 8 + 6 * 5",
            "Answer": 558,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 14 * 7 + 2 * 19",
            "Answer": 234,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 14 * 3 + 17 * 1",
            "Answer": 563,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 12 * 19 + 8 * 8",
            "Answer": 2344,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 13 * 15 + 15 * 1",
            "Answer": 405,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 16 * 0 + 9 * 2",
            "Answer": 18,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 8 * 11 + 3 * 5",
            "Answer": 1423,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 0 * 7 + 8 * 0",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 2 * 4 + 14 * 3",
            "Answer": 138,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 13 * 1 + 5 * 18",
            "Answer": 90,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 0 * 14 + 19 * 9",
            "Answer": 171,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 10 * 12 + 5 * 13",
            "Answer": 905,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 1 * 19 + 19 * 5",
            "Answer": 209,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 16 * 13 + 11 * 11",
            "Answer": 2201,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 12 * 3 + 7 * 18",
            "Answer": 666,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 7 * 19 + 19 * 7",
            "Answer": 2261,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * #"
        }
    ],
    "# + # * # * # * # + #": [
        {
            "Question": "18 + 0 * 14 * 2 * 19 + 6",
            "Answer": 24,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 9 * 15 * 3 * 7 + 10",
            "Answer": 2862,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 19 * 2 * 6 * 2 + 18",
            "Answer": 483,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 15 * 11 * 5 * 3 + 9",
            "Answer": 2501,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 18 * 4 * 0 * 19 + 16",
            "Answer": 33,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 6 * 0 * 2 * 15 + 2",
            "Answer": 2,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 5 * 14 * 12 * 10 + 16",
            "Answer": 8425,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 9 * 4 * 11 * 19 + 8",
            "Answer": 7535,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 15 * 18 * 17 * 16 + 10",
            "Answer": 73456,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 12 * 12 * 17 * 4 + 15",
            "Answer": 9825,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 4 * 16 * 8 * 10 + 15",
            "Answer": 5152,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 2 * 19 * 6 * 15 + 5",
            "Answer": 3425,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 1 * 15 * 1 * 10 + 17",
            "Answer": 176,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 0 * 5 * 3 * 3 + 12",
            "Answer": 12,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 10 * 1 * 11 * 3 + 12",
            "Answer": 351,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 10 * 9 * 14 * 11 + 0",
            "Answer": 13877,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 0 * 14 * 17 * 5 + 8",
            "Answer": 19,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 19 * 4 * 17 * 3 + 15",
            "Answer": 3905,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 15 * 10 * 10 * 15 + 5",
            "Answer": 22506,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 16 * 6 * 9 * 19 + 10",
            "Answer": 16426,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 16 * 17 * 11 * 19 + 17",
            "Answer": 56867,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 0 * 7 * 11 * 3 + 15",
            "Answer": 32,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 13 * 7 * 9 * 15 + 14",
            "Answer": 12307,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 15 * 12 * 19 * 8 + 15",
            "Answer": 27375,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 14 * 11 * 8 * 14 + 1",
            "Answer": 17249,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 11 * 18 * 7 * 10 + 6",
            "Answer": 13876,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 18 * 15 * 1 * 2 + 0",
            "Answer": 540,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 15 * 12 * 3 * 5 + 19",
            "Answer": 2726,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 12 * 9 * 8 * 11 + 15",
            "Answer": 9537,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 2 * 7 * 9 * 6 + 6",
            "Answer": 764,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 10 * 11 * 5 * 17 + 9",
            "Answer": 9375,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 4 * 13 * 0 * 4 + 18",
            "Answer": 33,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 17 * 4 * 19 * 16 + 5",
            "Answer": 20694,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 1 * 15 * 3 * 9 + 17",
            "Answer": 435,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 8 * 9 * 14 * 4 + 13",
            "Answer": 4057,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 7 * 14 * 5 * 2 + 12",
            "Answer": 996,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 1 * 17 * 11 * 7 + 19",
            "Answer": 1329,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 11 * 5 * 7 * 5 + 4",
            "Answer": 1944,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 19 * 2 * 15 * 4 + 9",
            "Answer": 2291,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 10 * 9 * 16 * 7 + 14",
            "Answer": 10096,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 1 * 4 * 7 * 19 + 9",
            "Answer": 551,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 4 * 19 * 12 * 14 + 4",
            "Answer": 12776,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 18 * 16 * 12 * 1 + 13",
            "Answer": 3479,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 10 * 2 * 17 * 3 + 6",
            "Answer": 1044,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 18 * 0 * 6 * 19 + 11",
            "Answer": 29,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 7 * 16 * 17 * 6 + 17",
            "Answer": 11447,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 4 * 13 * 14 * 10 + 17",
            "Answer": 7313,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 6 * 18 * 16 * 12 + 5",
            "Answer": 20752,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 16 * 1 * 15 * 8 + 8",
            "Answer": 1929,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 0 * 16 * 18 * 10 + 5",
            "Answer": 23,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 6 * 0 * 12 * 9 + 7",
            "Answer": 17,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 7 * 4 * 19 * 16 + 5",
            "Answer": 8520,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 6 * 4 * 2 * 3 + 7",
            "Answer": 170,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 19 * 12 * 3 * 8 + 3",
            "Answer": 5494,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 3 * 15 * 1 * 5 + 12",
            "Answer": 241,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 4 * 17 * 9 * 17 + 16",
            "Answer": 10438,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 4 * 12 * 6 * 10 + 15",
            "Answer": 2903,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 15 * 9 * 11 * 12 + 12",
            "Answer": 17842,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 19 * 16 * 18 * 18 + 8",
            "Answer": 98523,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 6 * 2 * 14 * 4 + 14",
            "Answer": 686,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 10 * 6 * 15 * 15 + 16",
            "Answer": 13528,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 9 * 15 * 13 * 19 + 3",
            "Answer": 33348,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 11 * 17 * 5 * 11 + 4",
            "Answer": 10291,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 5 * 6 * 10 * 18 + 9",
            "Answer": 5417,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 9 * 17 * 3 * 4 + 16",
            "Answer": 1852,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 18 * 16 * 13 * 16 + 13",
            "Answer": 59932,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 13 * 6 * 7 * 4 + 4",
            "Answer": 2192,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 2 * 6 * 19 * 5 + 0",
            "Answer": 1149,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 7 * 19 * 1 * 11 + 0",
            "Answer": 1473,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 16 * 2 * 14 * 18 + 7",
            "Answer": 8075,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 0 * 7 * 11 * 11 + 14",
            "Answer": 22,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 1 * 3 * 2 * 0 + 14",
            "Answer": 14,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 3 * 12 * 9 * 7 + 7",
            "Answer": 2281,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 15 * 10 * 17 * 10 + 4",
            "Answer": 25523,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 9 * 16 * 7 * 14 + 9",
            "Answer": 14129,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 7 * 11 * 5 * 1 + 9",
            "Answer": 406,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 9 * 15 * 14 * 15 + 10",
            "Answer": 28362,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 1 * 14 * 0 * 13 + 13",
            "Answer": 31,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 15 * 6 * 15 * 4 + 8",
            "Answer": 5408,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 8 * 1 * 5 * 14 + 3",
            "Answer": 582,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 11 * 16 * 3 * 15 + 9",
            "Answer": 7941,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 12 * 19 * 11 * 19 + 4",
            "Answer": 47674,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 17 * 5 * 9 * 11 + 19",
            "Answer": 8444,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 3 * 12 * 0 * 9 + 11",
            "Answer": 17,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 18 * 0 * 12 * 9 + 7",
            "Answer": 19,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 5 * 12 * 1 * 5 + 5",
            "Answer": 318,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 16 * 1 * 2 * 10 + 7",
            "Answer": 331,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 18 * 8 * 2 * 0 + 9",
            "Answer": 25,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 6 * 14 * 4 * 3 + 5",
            "Answer": 1013,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 0 * 19 * 10 * 5 + 17",
            "Answer": 17,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 17 * 15 * 8 * 14 + 15",
            "Answer": 28585,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 9 * 17 * 7 * 3 + 6",
            "Answer": 3223,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 3 * 9 * 9 * 11 + 6",
            "Answer": 2697,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 8 * 10 * 9 * 11 + 10",
            "Answer": 7935,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 12 * 16 * 12 * 3 + 11",
            "Answer": 6935,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 11 * 4 * 9 * 1 + 6",
            "Answer": 420,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 7 * 8 * 2 * 8 + 7",
            "Answer": 919,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 14 * 13 * 19 * 8 + 16",
            "Answer": 27694,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 0 * 7 * 1 * 14 + 0",
            "Answer": 4,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 12 * 9 * 14 * 0 + 3",
            "Answer": 16,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + #"
        }
    ],
    "# * # * # + # * # * #": [
        {
            "Question": "12 * 12 * 7 + 17 * 15 * 13",
            "Answer": 4323,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 18 * 16 + 12 * 5 * 9",
            "Answer": 6012,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 2 * 7 + 9 * 19 * 1",
            "Answer": 367,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 16 * 2 + 10 * 7 * 19",
            "Answer": 1746,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 2 * 9 + 15 * 5 * 17",
            "Answer": 1581,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 10 * 15 + 19 * 7 * 12",
            "Answer": 2346,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 10 * 15 + 15 * 3 * 7",
            "Answer": 315,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 18 * 5 + 13 * 19 * 2",
            "Answer": 1484,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 15 * 0 + 18 * 9 * 13",
            "Answer": 2106,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 0 * 16 + 16 * 13 * 8",
            "Answer": 1664,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 6 * 10 + 12 * 10 * 5",
            "Answer": 600,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 19 * 0 + 5 * 1 * 2",
            "Answer": 10,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 19 * 12 + 2 * 13 * 18",
            "Answer": 924,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 17 * 16 + 16 * 13 * 4",
            "Answer": 4368,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 4 * 15 + 12 * 14 * 5",
            "Answer": 1500,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 19 * 10 + 9 * 11 * 18",
            "Answer": 1972,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 18 * 17 + 19 * 12 * 16",
            "Answer": 5484,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 17 * 12 + 10 * 0 * 3",
            "Answer": 1224,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 13 * 1 + 7 * 14 * 4",
            "Answer": 574,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 12 * 17 + 6 * 1 * 14",
            "Answer": 2328,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 14 * 4 + 5 * 1 * 0",
            "Answer": 672,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 2 * 15 + 6 * 18 * 16",
            "Answer": 1998,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 3 * 19 + 1 * 7 * 11",
            "Answer": 191,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 11 * 2 + 11 * 12 * 8",
            "Answer": 1254,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 5 * 18 + 13 * 15 * 7",
            "Answer": 2175,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 11 * 6 + 13 * 2 * 12",
            "Answer": 840,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 7 * 19 + 11 * 18 * 15",
            "Answer": 5364,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 15 * 6 + 18 * 5 * 0",
            "Answer": 1080,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 0 * 4 + 8 * 7 * 0",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 8 * 1 + 0 * 15 * 7",
            "Answer": 64,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 1 * 0 + 15 * 8 * 15",
            "Answer": 1800,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 6 * 15 + 2 * 8 * 15",
            "Answer": 1320,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 6 * 19 + 11 * 4 * 5",
            "Answer": 1360,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 14 * 12 + 15 * 18 * 8",
            "Answer": 3168,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 7 * 12 + 7 * 6 * 0",
            "Answer": 168,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 9 * 6 + 3 * 17 * 8",
            "Answer": 462,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 14 * 16 + 6 * 17 * 7",
            "Answer": 1834,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 5 * 10 + 8 * 4 * 5",
            "Answer": 1010,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 11 * 12 + 5 * 5 * 19",
            "Answer": 1531,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 15 * 0 + 3 * 4 * 8",
            "Answer": 96,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 10 * 9 + 18 * 13 * 0",
            "Answer": 1350,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 16 * 9 + 2 * 9 * 13",
            "Answer": 2394,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 19 * 0 + 0 * 1 * 0",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 12 * 5 + 3 * 4 * 18",
            "Answer": 1176,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 1 * 5 + 10 * 18 * 4",
            "Answer": 765,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 19 * 0 + 16 * 10 * 4",
            "Answer": 640,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 12 * 9 + 17 * 1 * 11",
            "Answer": 1807,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 7 * 17 + 17 * 9 * 2",
            "Answer": 1615,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 15 * 5 + 6 * 14 * 8",
            "Answer": 1497,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 8 * 15 + 7 * 4 * 10",
            "Answer": 400,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 0 * 1 + 9 * 13 * 15",
            "Answer": 1755,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 7 * 6 + 17 * 5 * 0",
            "Answer": 336,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 13 * 14 + 15 * 18 * 17",
            "Answer": 7320,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 7 * 15 + 19 * 3 * 8",
            "Answer": 771,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 2 * 8 + 10 * 11 * 9",
            "Answer": 1038,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 9 * 7 + 14 * 2 * 1",
            "Answer": 406,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 8 * 17 + 16 * 1 * 9",
            "Answer": 1776,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 5 * 14 + 7 * 14 * 8",
            "Answer": 2044,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 19 * 6 + 10 * 1 * 9",
            "Answer": 204,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 19 * 4 + 12 * 15 * 10",
            "Answer": 2332,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 11 * 7 + 19 * 4 * 14",
            "Answer": 1911,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 12 * 7 + 19 * 1 * 17",
            "Answer": 659,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 0 * 13 + 5 * 9 * 16",
            "Answer": 720,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 16 * 5 + 17 * 9 * 9",
            "Answer": 2657,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 16 * 14 + 8 * 10 * 19",
            "Answer": 4208,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 16 * 6 + 17 * 6 * 16",
            "Answer": 2016,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 5 * 3 + 4 * 11 * 18",
            "Answer": 792,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 6 * 4 + 16 * 0 * 1",
            "Answer": 48,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 6 * 8 + 16 * 7 * 12",
            "Answer": 1536,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 14 * 8 + 2 * 3 * 6",
            "Answer": 1380,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 5 * 16 + 2 * 12 * 5",
            "Answer": 760,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 17 * 6 + 18 * 8 * 15",
            "Answer": 3792,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 16 * 1 + 11 * 14 * 8",
            "Answer": 1328,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 12 * 18 + 17 * 12 * 17",
            "Answer": 3468,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 18 * 0 + 17 * 14 * 19",
            "Answer": 4522,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 0 * 7 + 12 * 16 * 17",
            "Answer": 3264,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 16 * 8 + 1 * 19 * 7",
            "Answer": 389,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 11 * 0 + 10 * 9 * 18",
            "Answer": 1620,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 14 * 7 + 10 * 1 * 8",
            "Answer": 864,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 13 * 10 + 2 * 17 * 3",
            "Answer": 1662,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 15 * 16 + 9 * 10 * 17",
            "Answer": 1770,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 2 * 2 + 14 * 1 * 14",
            "Answer": 216,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 12 * 0 + 16 * 0 * 11",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 10 * 5 + 5 * 16 * 7",
            "Answer": 810,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 16 * 19 + 1 * 11 * 16",
            "Answer": 5648,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 12 * 14 + 19 * 19 * 2",
            "Answer": 2234,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 12 * 15 + 19 * 17 * 19",
            "Answer": 7397,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 18 * 7 + 8 * 6 * 4",
            "Answer": 2334,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 15 * 17 + 8 * 5 * 10",
            "Answer": 4735,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 0 * 10 + 3 * 11 * 12",
            "Answer": 396,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 7 * 14 + 8 * 19 * 15",
            "Answer": 2476,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 7 * 2 + 3 * 18 * 11",
            "Answer": 776,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 18 * 17 + 18 * 15 * 17",
            "Answer": 9486,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 8 * 6 + 2 * 5 * 1",
            "Answer": 346,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 6 * 11 + 18 * 15 * 1",
            "Answer": 864,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 11 * 17 + 8 * 6 * 13",
            "Answer": 811,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 10 * 7 + 14 * 9 * 19",
            "Answer": 2814,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 11 * 12 + 17 * 8 * 5",
            "Answer": 1736,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 18 * 15 + 5 * 8 * 16",
            "Answer": 4960,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 6 * 12 + 19 * 9 * 14",
            "Answer": 3690,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * #"
        }
    ],
    "# * # * # * # * # + #": [
        {
            "Question": "11 * 19 * 17 * 5 * 5 + 13",
            "Answer": 88838,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 2 * 7 * 0 * 5 + 13",
            "Answer": 13,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 19 * 2 * 1 * 6 + 6",
            "Answer": 4338,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 16 * 1 * 4 * 17 + 15",
            "Answer": 18511,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 13 * 9 * 11 * 11 + 9",
            "Answer": 169893,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 8 * 13 * 19 * 8 + 4",
            "Answer": 173892,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 15 * 9 * 14 * 9 + 19",
            "Answer": 34039,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 6 * 8 * 18 * 16 + 7",
            "Answer": 82951,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 5 * 13 * 19 * 7 + 16",
            "Answer": 43241,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 19 * 7 * 15 * 15 + 1",
            "Answer": 29926,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 17 * 19 * 17 * 4 + 7",
            "Answer": 241611,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 10 * 9 * 14 * 10 + 1",
            "Answer": 176401,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 9 * 6 * 19 * 10 + 7",
            "Answer": 112867,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 5 * 0 * 16 * 3 + 17",
            "Answer": 17,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 4 * 7 * 19 * 2 + 9",
            "Answer": 15969,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 8 * 6 * 5 * 2 + 2",
            "Answer": 2402,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 11 * 15 * 1 * 7 + 12",
            "Answer": 12717,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 11 * 8 * 3 * 9 + 2",
            "Answer": 28514,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 6 * 8 * 13 * 11 + 8",
            "Answer": 41192,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 11 * 17 * 12 * 8 + 5",
            "Answer": 17957,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 18 * 17 * 9 * 18 + 10",
            "Answer": 446158,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 3 * 7 * 3 * 1 + 2",
            "Answer": 65,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 5 * 15 * 11 * 4 + 7",
            "Answer": 49507,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 2 * 11 * 6 * 13 + 4",
            "Answer": 10300,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 9 * 4 * 11 * 16 + 5",
            "Answer": 76037,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 17 * 15 * 0 * 13 + 19",
            "Answer": 19,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 6 * 6 * 18 * 14 + 16",
            "Answer": 36304,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 5 * 2 * 9 * 8 + 6",
            "Answer": 13686,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 4 * 5 * 5 * 5 + 14",
            "Answer": 3014,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 16 * 4 * 11 * 19 + 17",
            "Answer": 53521,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 6 * 10 * 17 * 5 + 8",
            "Answer": 71408,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 7 * 7 * 15 * 4 + 13",
            "Answer": 17653,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 0 * 16 * 0 * 15 + 7",
            "Answer": 7,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 3 * 16 * 2 * 5 + 14",
            "Answer": 8654,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 9 * 6 * 15 * 15 + 5",
            "Answer": 72905,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 12 * 12 * 2 * 13 + 13",
            "Answer": 7501,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 1 * 0 * 3 * 14 + 10",
            "Answer": 10,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 16 * 11 * 0 * 8 + 1",
            "Answer": 1,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 11 * 18 * 15 * 15 + 3",
            "Answer": 3,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 12 * 0 * 4 * 6 + 17",
            "Answer": 17,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 19 * 18 * 8 * 5 + 6",
            "Answer": 27366,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 13 * 16 * 15 * 15 + 7",
            "Answer": 140407,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 1 * 3 * 4 * 13 + 1",
            "Answer": 625,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 3 * 18 * 16 * 16 + 15",
            "Answer": 110607,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 2 * 4 * 13 * 14 + 19",
            "Answer": 26227,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 15 * 5 * 10 * 14 + 18",
            "Answer": 18,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 4 * 4 * 9 * 9 + 6",
            "Answer": 10374,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 3 * 12 * 4 * 13 + 3",
            "Answer": 28083,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 17 * 2 * 4 * 4 + 8",
            "Answer": 2184,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 15 * 8 * 13 * 12 + 8",
            "Answer": 262088,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 16 * 13 * 8 * 12 + 7",
            "Answer": 7,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 6 * 2 * 1 * 2 + 10",
            "Answer": 274,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 7 * 3 * 1 * 16 + 5",
            "Answer": 677,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 5 * 8 * 0 * 14 + 19",
            "Answer": 19,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 18 * 4 * 5 * 5 + 16",
            "Answer": 5416,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 6 * 0 * 1 * 6 + 13",
            "Answer": 13,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 6 * 2 * 1 * 7 + 16",
            "Answer": 1108,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 10 * 18 * 5 * 13 + 16",
            "Answer": 140416,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 0 * 4 * 14 * 1 + 17",
            "Answer": 17,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 10 * 16 * 0 * 18 + 1",
            "Answer": 1,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 13 * 8 * 3 * 19 + 18",
            "Answer": 59298,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 8 * 17 * 2 * 3 + 10",
            "Answer": 8986,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 6 * 3 * 10 * 14 + 16",
            "Answer": 27736,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 5 * 12 * 7 * 1 + 17",
            "Answer": 5477,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 6 * 10 * 13 * 3 + 4",
            "Answer": 39784,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 0 * 19 * 10 * 4 + 11",
            "Answer": 11,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 6 * 4 * 11 * 4 + 8",
            "Answer": 3176,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 1 * 4 * 0 * 9 + 7",
            "Answer": 7,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 12 * 18 * 13 * 17 + 6",
            "Answer": 716046,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 9 * 9 * 2 * 3 + 7",
            "Answer": 6811,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 16 * 8 * 3 * 1 + 3",
            "Answer": 5379,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 3 * 15 * 18 * 7 + 3",
            "Answer": 3,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 6 * 7 * 8 * 6 + 1",
            "Answer": 1,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 14 * 4 * 11 * 5 + 12",
            "Answer": 36972,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 15 * 10 * 2 * 10 + 17",
            "Answer": 45017,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 5 * 17 * 8 * 7 + 17",
            "Answer": 14297,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 18 * 17 * 2 * 4 + 5",
            "Answer": 4901,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 1 * 19 * 4 * 16 + 6",
            "Answer": 21894,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 2 * 16 * 9 * 6 + 13",
            "Answer": 13837,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 7 * 12 * 3 * 6 + 3",
            "Answer": 16635,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 19 * 9 * 4 * 18 + 2",
            "Answer": 86186,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 7 * 7 * 2 * 7 + 4",
            "Answer": 4806,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 1 * 14 * 14 * 13 + 18",
            "Answer": 18,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 18 * 2 * 2 * 15 + 1",
            "Answer": 18361,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 11 * 19 * 5 * 13 + 3",
            "Answer": 230948,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 0 * 15 * 9 * 1 + 11",
            "Answer": 11,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 18 * 0 * 19 * 16 + 15",
            "Answer": 15,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 12 * 14 * 9 * 3 + 3",
            "Answer": 81651,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 13 * 15 * 8 * 16 + 1",
            "Answer": 124801,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 4 * 13 * 9 * 11 + 12",
            "Answer": 46344,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 5 * 18 * 14 * 10 + 8",
            "Answer": 113408,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 14 * 17 * 9 * 16 + 6",
            "Answer": 68550,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 14 * 12 * 17 * 1 + 9",
            "Answer": 31425,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 15 * 16 * 11 * 0 + 17",
            "Answer": 17,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 2 * 7 * 11 * 9 + 14",
            "Answer": 13874,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 8 * 0 * 12 * 2 + 4",
            "Answer": 4,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 17 * 17 * 19 * 0 + 13",
            "Answer": 13,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 17 * 15 * 18 * 9 + 11",
            "Answer": 123941,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 3 * 16 * 5 * 0 + 19",
            "Answer": 19,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 7 * 13 * 2 * 16 + 11",
            "Answer": 43691,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + #"
        }
    ],
    "# + # + # * # + # + #": [
        {
            "Question": "7 + 11 + 5 * 18 + 6 + 10",
            "Answer": 124,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 15 + 5 * 8 + 9 + 1",
            "Answer": 77,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 16 + 8 * 1 + 11 + 7",
            "Answer": 55,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 12 + 0 * 1 + 4 + 4",
            "Answer": 21,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 17 + 10 * 15 + 8 + 4",
            "Answer": 180,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 7 + 2 * 1 + 8 + 19",
            "Answer": 55,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 9 + 5 * 8 + 3 + 7",
            "Answer": 66,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 2 + 16 * 3 + 9 + 6",
            "Answer": 83,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 19 + 15 * 0 + 7 + 12",
            "Answer": 52,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 12 + 7 * 15 + 18 + 14",
            "Answer": 167,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 16 + 16 * 17 + 8 + 11",
            "Answer": 319,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 0 + 6 * 16 + 19 + 9",
            "Answer": 135,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 9 + 7 * 19 + 11 + 13",
            "Answer": 172,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 2 + 11 * 19 + 5 + 19",
            "Answer": 240,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 15 + 15 * 18 + 17 + 14",
            "Answer": 328,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 3 + 1 * 19 + 11 + 2",
            "Answer": 42,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 3 + 15 * 17 + 5 + 8",
            "Answer": 285,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 7 + 7 * 10 + 18 + 17",
            "Answer": 119,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 15 + 17 * 17 + 0 + 0",
            "Answer": 305,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 0 + 11 * 16 + 3 + 17",
            "Answer": 212,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 1 + 19 * 4 + 10 + 2",
            "Answer": 91,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 18 + 17 * 18 + 18 + 1",
            "Answer": 344,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 5 + 8 * 15 + 12 + 10",
            "Answer": 155,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 14 + 17 * 9 + 10 + 16",
            "Answer": 210,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 14 + 12 * 8 + 10 + 5",
            "Answer": 135,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 5 + 4 * 14 + 7 + 8",
            "Answer": 84,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 7 + 19 * 4 + 4 + 4",
            "Answer": 91,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 17 + 3 * 9 + 17 + 10",
            "Answer": 89,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 15 + 11 * 19 + 8 + 8",
            "Answer": 250,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 5 + 12 * 5 + 6 + 13",
            "Answer": 90,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 10 + 5 * 16 + 15 + 8",
            "Answer": 120,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 18 + 7 * 6 + 11 + 1",
            "Answer": 84,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 11 + 1 * 10 + 19 + 1",
            "Answer": 42,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 15 + 14 * 6 + 1 + 2",
            "Answer": 117,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 8 + 7 * 1 + 2 + 0",
            "Answer": 33,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 4 + 14 * 8 + 15 + 3",
            "Answer": 141,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 8 + 13 * 12 + 4 + 2",
            "Answer": 173,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 2 + 8 * 12 + 17 + 14",
            "Answer": 137,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 18 + 10 * 13 + 15 + 7",
            "Answer": 178,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 4 + 18 * 4 + 5 + 10",
            "Answer": 91,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 15 + 10 * 9 + 16 + 2",
            "Answer": 142,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 6 + 13 * 10 + 9 + 7",
            "Answer": 160,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 0 + 2 * 19 + 0 + 2",
            "Answer": 44,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 14 + 8 * 4 + 8 + 16",
            "Answer": 77,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 6 + 15 * 4 + 2 + 14",
            "Answer": 98,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 16 + 14 * 13 + 10 + 11",
            "Answer": 238,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 1 + 15 * 15 + 12 + 0",
            "Answer": 243,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 9 + 14 * 6 + 12 + 12",
            "Answer": 121,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 12 + 3 * 7 + 12 + 4",
            "Answer": 66,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 10 + 6 * 18 + 6 + 13",
            "Answer": 145,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 2 + 15 * 16 + 16 + 9",
            "Answer": 285,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 10 + 2 * 3 + 7 + 19",
            "Answer": 55,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 2 + 0 * 12 + 14 + 3",
            "Answer": 27,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 7 + 17 * 11 + 14 + 1",
            "Answer": 225,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 2 + 9 * 14 + 0 + 1",
            "Answer": 129,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 5 + 7 * 11 + 19 + 4",
            "Answer": 121,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 17 + 13 * 9 + 7 + 10",
            "Answer": 167,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 16 + 1 * 18 + 13 + 10",
            "Answer": 62,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 19 + 15 * 18 + 8 + 6",
            "Answer": 304,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 4 + 2 * 9 + 18 + 7",
            "Answer": 65,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 10 + 7 * 17 + 8 + 1",
            "Answer": 139,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 15 + 16 * 6 + 4 + 9",
            "Answer": 141,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 10 + 14 * 8 + 11 + 15",
            "Answer": 156,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 5 + 5 * 13 + 7 + 12",
            "Answer": 97,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 15 + 9 * 13 + 14 + 11",
            "Answer": 157,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 15 + 2 * 13 + 8 + 15",
            "Answer": 83,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 18 + 16 * 0 + 13 + 18",
            "Answer": 51,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 2 + 7 * 11 + 1 + 1",
            "Answer": 85,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 7 + 17 * 7 + 7 + 5",
            "Answer": 140,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 17 + 13 * 13 + 17 + 3",
            "Answer": 222,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 10 + 2 * 17 + 3 + 14",
            "Answer": 68,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 12 + 5 * 13 + 9 + 10",
            "Answer": 111,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 9 + 13 * 1 + 16 + 7",
            "Answer": 59,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 7 + 0 * 17 + 4 + 17",
            "Answer": 40,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 1 + 12 * 1 + 6 + 0",
            "Answer": 20,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 3 + 14 * 19 + 14 + 0",
            "Answer": 298,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 19 + 2 * 13 + 8 + 11",
            "Answer": 68,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 3 + 12 * 15 + 13 + 7",
            "Answer": 203,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 7 + 8 * 7 + 2 + 8",
            "Answer": 74,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 7 + 18 * 15 + 13 + 15",
            "Answer": 315,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 3 + 10 * 7 + 6 + 9",
            "Answer": 96,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 19 + 5 * 3 + 1 + 12",
            "Answer": 57,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 14 + 12 * 7 + 17 + 11",
            "Answer": 141,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 14 + 3 * 14 + 4 + 19",
            "Answer": 83,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 5 + 3 * 16 + 19 + 10",
            "Answer": 83,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 19 + 8 * 13 + 13 + 13",
            "Answer": 162,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 9 + 2 * 6 + 0 + 13",
            "Answer": 39,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 10 + 7 * 16 + 11 + 0",
            "Answer": 150,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 16 + 15 * 9 + 9 + 5",
            "Answer": 180,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 18 + 15 * 11 + 19 + 7",
            "Answer": 225,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 4 + 5 * 9 + 0 + 9",
            "Answer": 61,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 6 + 11 * 12 + 13 + 9",
            "Answer": 170,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 11 + 13 * 6 + 4 + 9",
            "Answer": 119,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 13 + 16 * 3 + 12 + 1",
            "Answer": 85,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 18 + 18 * 1 + 2 + 1",
            "Answer": 55,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 3 + 16 * 13 + 16 + 3",
            "Answer": 242,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 17 + 14 * 9 + 10 + 8",
            "Answer": 162,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 4 + 4 * 10 + 15 + 1",
            "Answer": 61,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 11 + 11 * 7 + 8 + 1",
            "Answer": 109,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 18 + 16 * 0 + 8 + 19",
            "Answer": 55,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + #"
        }
    ],
    "# + # * # + # + # * #": [
        {
            "Question": "7 + 1 * 7 + 9 + 2 * 10",
            "Answer": 43,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 13 * 1 + 3 + 2 * 4",
            "Answer": 35,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 8 * 2 + 3 + 4 * 0",
            "Answer": 36,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 16 * 4 + 8 + 7 * 14",
            "Answer": 173,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 7 * 16 + 14 + 7 * 5",
            "Answer": 167,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 7 * 11 + 8 + 1 * 0",
            "Answer": 94,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 5 * 10 + 14 + 6 * 16",
            "Answer": 178,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 10 * 19 + 1 + 17 * 17",
            "Answer": 492,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 13 * 12 + 6 + 7 * 5",
            "Answer": 209,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 16 * 18 + 2 + 2 * 13",
            "Answer": 317,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 8 * 7 + 5 + 6 * 0",
            "Answer": 62,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 9 * 2 + 0 + 0 * 1",
            "Answer": 34,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 7 * 13 + 5 + 3 * 4",
            "Answer": 127,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 5 * 7 + 5 + 6 * 16",
            "Answer": 141,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 17 * 5 + 14 + 18 * 8",
            "Answer": 257,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 5 * 7 + 8 + 13 * 11",
            "Answer": 195,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 18 * 18 + 4 + 5 * 15",
            "Answer": 412,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 9 * 16 + 9 + 9 * 13",
            "Answer": 272,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 4 * 5 + 7 + 9 * 7",
            "Answer": 99,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 15 * 13 + 11 + 1 * 2",
            "Answer": 211,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 17 * 13 + 3 + 16 * 0",
            "Answer": 225,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 18 * 18 + 8 + 13 * 4",
            "Answer": 400,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 13 * 10 + 0 + 10 * 10",
            "Answer": 234,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 15 * 4 + 2 + 10 * 5",
            "Answer": 115,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 1 * 13 + 1 + 19 * 14",
            "Answer": 285,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 11 * 8 + 11 + 0 * 17",
            "Answer": 103,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 7 * 18 + 7 + 16 * 8",
            "Answer": 276,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 2 * 7 + 14 + 12 * 9",
            "Answer": 151,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 14 * 16 + 4 + 18 * 18",
            "Answer": 565,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 19 * 7 + 17 + 8 * 15",
            "Answer": 279,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 5 * 12 + 3 + 12 * 9",
            "Answer": 178,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 9 * 4 + 10 + 11 * 9",
            "Answer": 153,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 3 * 2 + 18 + 8 * 5",
            "Answer": 72,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 11 * 13 + 18 + 13 * 17",
            "Answer": 382,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 0 * 12 + 7 + 13 * 16",
            "Answer": 216,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 19 * 0 + 8 + 11 * 2",
            "Answer": 36,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 9 * 7 + 7 + 18 * 12",
            "Answer": 301,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 4 * 3 + 11 + 6 * 12",
            "Answer": 95,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 10 * 18 + 18 + 13 * 2",
            "Answer": 228,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 4 * 16 + 0 + 16 * 11",
            "Answer": 242,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 18 * 5 + 11 + 2 * 3",
            "Answer": 118,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 18 * 12 + 6 + 14 * 17",
            "Answer": 463,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 19 * 5 + 8 + 5 * 14",
            "Answer": 188,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 18 * 17 + 4 + 15 * 11",
            "Answer": 493,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 18 * 1 + 4 + 11 * 6",
            "Answer": 105,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 18 * 2 + 12 + 6 * 18",
            "Answer": 156,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 6 * 18 + 0 + 15 * 10",
            "Answer": 264,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 7 * 17 + 15 + 9 * 15",
            "Answer": 277,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 15 * 9 + 12 + 16 * 9",
            "Answer": 303,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 16 * 11 + 19 + 0 * 10",
            "Answer": 214,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 3 * 18 + 19 + 2 * 15",
            "Answer": 104,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 16 * 1 + 11 + 9 * 19",
            "Answer": 199,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 3 * 7 + 14 + 3 * 2",
            "Answer": 45,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 8 * 14 + 5 + 0 * 10",
            "Answer": 122,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 19 * 3 + 6 + 2 * 6",
            "Answer": 80,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 0 * 11 + 15 + 14 * 19",
            "Answer": 298,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 3 * 6 + 18 + 17 * 8",
            "Answer": 184,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 6 * 17 + 15 + 19 * 6",
            "Answer": 250,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 3 * 16 + 19 + 0 * 2",
            "Answer": 67,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 1 * 11 + 15 + 15 * 9",
            "Answer": 163,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 11 * 3 + 1 + 6 * 7",
            "Answer": 92,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 9 * 4 + 12 + 17 * 4",
            "Answer": 126,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 12 * 8 + 6 + 13 * 19",
            "Answer": 354,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 14 * 0 + 3 + 7 * 16",
            "Answer": 134,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 2 * 19 + 2 + 2 * 7",
            "Answer": 62,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 15 * 13 + 9 + 3 * 3",
            "Answer": 214,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 8 * 6 + 1 + 1 * 6",
            "Answer": 61,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 6 * 13 + 15 + 7 * 11",
            "Answer": 181,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 12 * 7 + 11 + 4 * 1",
            "Answer": 99,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 17 * 15 + 1 + 19 * 16",
            "Answer": 562,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 6 * 0 + 14 + 2 * 12",
            "Answer": 49,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 6 * 7 + 0 + 10 * 9",
            "Answer": 147,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 16 * 7 + 0 + 4 * 18",
            "Answer": 198,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 5 * 5 + 9 + 14 * 5",
            "Answer": 115,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 6 * 10 + 9 + 1 * 4",
            "Answer": 90,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 11 * 4 + 15 + 15 * 1",
            "Answer": 78,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 12 * 12 + 18 + 12 * 12",
            "Answer": 320,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 8 * 17 + 1 + 7 * 19",
            "Answer": 275,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 5 * 1 + 2 + 19 * 7",
            "Answer": 146,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 1 * 18 + 7 + 0 * 2",
            "Answer": 44,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 10 * 9 + 1 + 17 * 4",
            "Answer": 162,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 19 * 16 + 3 + 15 * 3",
            "Answer": 353,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 4 * 0 + 11 + 3 * 4",
            "Answer": 27,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 17 * 18 + 2 + 4 * 18",
            "Answer": 390,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 11 * 1 + 6 + 9 * 16",
            "Answer": 180,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 9 * 9 + 17 + 15 * 6",
            "Answer": 199,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 6 * 16 + 16 + 9 * 6",
            "Answer": 177,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 17 * 10 + 2 + 9 * 3",
            "Answer": 205,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 10 * 16 + 15 + 3 * 17",
            "Answer": 239,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 6 * 6 + 18 + 6 * 4",
            "Answer": 78,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 1 * 6 + 3 + 17 * 4",
            "Answer": 91,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 5 * 15 + 7 + 1 * 3",
            "Answer": 85,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 13 * 6 + 6 + 18 * 8",
            "Answer": 243,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 12 * 9 + 18 + 1 * 19",
            "Answer": 156,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 16 * 9 + 9 + 2 * 6",
            "Answer": 179,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 15 * 8 + 11 + 6 * 17",
            "Answer": 244,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 19 * 0 + 18 + 8 * 17",
            "Answer": 157,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 15 * 7 + 19 + 12 * 12",
            "Answer": 275,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 9 * 19 + 6 + 16 * 6",
            "Answer": 289,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 18 * 19 + 3 + 1 * 10",
            "Answer": 362,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * #"
        }
    ],
    "# + # + # + # * # + #": [
        {
            "Question": "15 + 15 + 17 + 9 * 15 + 12",
            "Answer": 194,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 18 + 12 + 5 * 7 + 10",
            "Answer": 86,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 11 + 11 + 6 * 0 + 13",
            "Answer": 53,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 9 + 2 + 12 * 16 + 16",
            "Answer": 236,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 19 + 8 + 17 * 12 + 15",
            "Answer": 250,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 1 + 17 + 4 * 4 + 17",
            "Answer": 53,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 8 + 12 + 14 * 9 + 0",
            "Answer": 147,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 12 + 16 + 9 * 14 + 13",
            "Answer": 185,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 2 + 4 + 0 * 8 + 15",
            "Answer": 28,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 15 + 4 + 3 * 1 + 9",
            "Answer": 47,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 2 + 12 + 1 * 11 + 3",
            "Answer": 31,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 3 + 8 + 11 * 2 + 0",
            "Answer": 38,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 17 + 13 + 14 * 19 + 12",
            "Answer": 320,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 13 + 4 + 10 * 6 + 11",
            "Answer": 94,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 18 + 16 + 8 * 9 + 6",
            "Answer": 115,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 14 + 3 + 3 * 11 + 11",
            "Answer": 78,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 10 + 0 + 7 * 14 + 12",
            "Answer": 128,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 2 + 18 + 14 * 12 + 16",
            "Answer": 207,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 5 + 0 + 12 * 14 + 9",
            "Answer": 200,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 12 + 14 + 6 * 8 + 14",
            "Answer": 90,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 10 + 16 + 7 * 10 + 8",
            "Answer": 109,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 19 + 6 + 1 * 14 + 7",
            "Answer": 46,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 13 + 19 + 14 * 11 + 17",
            "Answer": 219,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 10 + 7 + 17 * 4 + 3",
            "Answer": 100,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 14 + 15 + 16 * 3 + 2",
            "Answer": 80,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 14 + 2 + 12 * 4 + 17",
            "Answer": 81,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 15 + 5 + 9 * 10 + 6",
            "Answer": 130,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 8 + 3 + 17 * 16 + 8",
            "Answer": 303,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 17 + 5 + 8 * 5 + 5",
            "Answer": 83,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 5 + 11 + 2 * 2 + 17",
            "Answer": 51,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 2 + 5 + 10 * 10 + 15",
            "Answer": 123,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 2 + 3 + 13 * 12 + 8",
            "Answer": 180,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 9 + 9 + 5 * 0 + 9",
            "Answer": 32,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 10 + 17 + 8 * 18 + 1",
            "Answer": 177,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 11 + 17 + 15 * 2 + 12",
            "Answer": 88,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 18 + 3 + 11 * 0 + 8",
            "Answer": 32,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 8 + 7 + 19 * 4 + 15",
            "Answer": 109,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 16 + 2 + 14 * 5 + 8",
            "Answer": 98,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 1 + 10 + 2 * 16 + 15",
            "Answer": 59,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 17 + 5 + 4 * 13 + 10",
            "Answer": 91,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 1 + 13 + 13 * 8 + 1",
            "Answer": 132,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 4 + 13 + 3 * 0 + 10",
            "Answer": 38,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 13 + 11 + 4 * 11 + 1",
            "Answer": 82,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 6 + 5 + 2 * 9 + 15",
            "Answer": 57,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 1 + 17 + 6 * 4 + 4",
            "Answer": 49,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 2 + 0 + 9 * 3 + 2",
            "Answer": 50,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 18 + 12 + 18 * 15 + 8",
            "Answer": 313,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 3 + 15 + 7 * 1 + 10",
            "Answer": 45,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 8 + 11 + 19 * 4 + 15",
            "Answer": 126,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 1 + 2 + 17 * 16 + 9",
            "Answer": 299,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 12 + 15 + 10 * 19 + 17",
            "Answer": 245,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 13 + 10 + 8 * 15 + 9",
            "Answer": 162,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 2 + 17 + 13 * 14 + 17",
            "Answer": 232,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 19 + 19 + 15 * 14 + 13",
            "Answer": 266,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 5 + 10 + 16 * 19 + 1",
            "Answer": 323,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 3 + 12 + 9 * 11 + 19",
            "Answer": 142,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 11 + 8 + 19 * 1 + 5",
            "Answer": 49,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 13 + 11 + 1 * 4 + 17",
            "Answer": 50,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 3 + 14 + 18 * 8 + 15",
            "Answer": 191,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 17 + 19 + 9 * 15 + 19",
            "Answer": 204,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 19 + 0 + 7 * 12 + 2",
            "Answer": 109,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 18 + 11 + 13 * 15 + 14",
            "Answer": 248,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 4 + 0 + 11 * 3 + 2",
            "Answer": 58,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 11 + 3 + 8 * 0 + 2",
            "Answer": 16,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 16 + 16 + 12 * 8 + 11",
            "Answer": 149,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 2 + 16 + 13 * 4 + 18",
            "Answer": 100,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 3 + 3 + 4 * 17 + 12",
            "Answer": 105,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 3 + 13 + 0 * 14 + 15",
            "Answer": 50,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 16 + 19 + 17 * 0 + 6",
            "Answer": 60,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 7 + 2 + 7 * 16 + 1",
            "Answer": 124,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 19 + 19 + 1 * 8 + 12",
            "Answer": 69,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 7 + 17 + 15 * 10 + 5",
            "Answer": 196,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 7 + 6 + 10 * 11 + 5",
            "Answer": 133,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 14 + 8 + 2 * 15 + 19",
            "Answer": 83,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 1 + 16 + 2 * 4 + 2",
            "Answer": 31,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 14 + 15 + 5 * 12 + 9",
            "Answer": 112,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 19 + 17 + 1 * 17 + 14",
            "Answer": 77,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 5 + 18 + 1 * 17 + 12",
            "Answer": 60,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 10 + 15 + 16 * 3 + 0",
            "Answer": 87,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 10 + 7 + 14 * 4 + 15",
            "Answer": 106,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 1 + 1 + 13 * 16 + 3",
            "Answer": 216,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 11 + 6 + 12 * 3 + 3",
            "Answer": 60,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 11 + 16 + 8 * 9 + 11",
            "Answer": 122,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 6 + 10 + 17 * 17 + 13",
            "Answer": 325,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 7 + 16 + 18 * 3 + 11",
            "Answer": 101,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 7 + 3 + 18 * 17 + 13",
            "Answer": 332,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 4 + 14 + 6 * 19 + 14",
            "Answer": 150,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 15 + 3 + 10 * 14 + 19",
            "Answer": 186,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 9 + 7 + 13 * 6 + 14",
            "Answer": 127,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 9 + 17 + 10 * 19 + 4",
            "Answer": 222,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 2 + 5 + 9 * 1 + 0",
            "Answer": 25,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 3 + 3 + 3 * 8 + 2",
            "Answer": 37,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 16 + 12 + 3 * 3 + 0",
            "Answer": 38,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 18 + 8 + 15 * 15 + 17",
            "Answer": 275,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 13 + 14 + 5 * 1 + 11",
            "Answer": 48,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 10 + 16 + 11 * 4 + 13",
            "Answer": 84,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 8 + 11 + 7 * 8 + 13",
            "Answer": 98,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 1 + 15 + 14 * 9 + 0",
            "Answer": 148,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 7 + 7 + 5 * 7 + 12",
            "Answer": 79,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 18 + 9 + 19 * 12 + 9",
            "Answer": 277,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + #"
        }
    ],
    "# * # * # + # * # + #": [
        {
            "Question": "5 * 1 * 15 + 11 * 16 + 3",
            "Answer": 254,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 10 * 3 + 17 * 17 + 3",
            "Answer": 502,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 7 * 6 + 3 * 18 + 11",
            "Answer": 611,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 8 * 15 + 3 * 18 + 13",
            "Answer": 1627,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 15 * 14 + 14 * 8 + 1",
            "Answer": 743,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 4 * 11 + 19 * 0 + 15",
            "Answer": 279,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 6 * 7 + 2 * 4 + 18",
            "Answer": 404,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 12 * 15 + 1 * 17 + 14",
            "Answer": 931,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 18 * 3 + 3 * 7 + 0",
            "Answer": 291,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 1 * 16 + 10 * 2 + 7",
            "Answer": 203,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 4 * 10 + 3 * 6 + 5",
            "Answer": 143,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 3 * 17 + 3 * 7 + 14",
            "Answer": 545,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 1 * 18 + 4 * 14 + 2",
            "Answer": 184,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 17 * 5 + 6 * 15 + 8",
            "Answer": 438,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 11 * 9 + 15 * 6 + 16",
            "Answer": 1195,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 16 * 3 + 15 * 2 + 0",
            "Answer": 654,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 4 * 10 + 15 * 11 + 11",
            "Answer": 656,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 3 * 2 + 18 * 17 + 7",
            "Answer": 391,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 12 * 10 + 0 * 19 + 4",
            "Answer": 1444,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 8 * 14 + 13 * 8 + 19",
            "Answer": 1019,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 14 * 0 + 2 * 15 + 12",
            "Answer": 42,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 19 * 17 + 9 * 15 + 16",
            "Answer": 2412,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 0 * 8 + 2 * 7 + 4",
            "Answer": 18,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 13 * 12 + 4 * 0 + 6",
            "Answer": 2502,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 5 * 10 + 19 * 9 + 4",
            "Answer": 1075,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 13 * 0 + 3 * 7 + 17",
            "Answer": 38,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 14 * 8 + 0 * 8 + 18",
            "Answer": 1698,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 9 * 15 + 7 * 12 + 3",
            "Answer": 2517,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 5 * 10 + 19 * 18 + 4",
            "Answer": 1146,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 4 * 18 + 18 * 9 + 2",
            "Answer": 1100,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 6 * 5 + 18 * 10 + 17",
            "Answer": 467,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 4 * 9 + 9 * 19 + 18",
            "Answer": 225,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 1 * 10 + 3 * 16 + 3",
            "Answer": 81,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 8 * 7 + 3 * 7 + 13",
            "Answer": 90,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 3 * 15 + 4 * 5 + 6",
            "Answer": 521,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 19 * 1 + 14 * 17 + 1",
            "Answer": 353,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 6 * 6 + 5 * 1 + 4",
            "Answer": 657,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 14 * 13 + 16 * 2 + 19",
            "Answer": 1871,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 7 * 18 + 3 * 4 + 17",
            "Answer": 1793,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 4 * 15 + 13 * 13 + 0",
            "Answer": 169,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 8 * 18 + 9 * 18 + 10",
            "Answer": 2908,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 19 * 15 + 5 * 9 + 18",
            "Answer": 2343,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 19 * 10 + 1 * 19 + 9",
            "Answer": 1928,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 10 * 9 + 6 * 6 + 17",
            "Answer": 953,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 14 * 6 + 16 * 15 + 8",
            "Answer": 1760,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 2 * 4 + 4 * 17 + 1",
            "Answer": 141,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 14 * 4 + 15 * 14 + 11",
            "Answer": 1285,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 10 * 0 + 8 * 16 + 16",
            "Answer": 144,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 18 * 13 + 4 * 8 + 12",
            "Answer": 2384,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 0 * 16 + 11 * 16 + 18",
            "Answer": 194,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 3 * 16 + 11 * 5 + 7",
            "Answer": 782,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 18 * 1 + 17 * 19 + 17",
            "Answer": 664,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 13 * 4 + 12 * 16 + 6",
            "Answer": 510,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 10 * 16 + 2 * 0 + 8",
            "Answer": 808,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 12 * 9 + 11 * 14 + 8",
            "Answer": 2214,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 16 * 5 + 7 * 6 + 3",
            "Answer": 445,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 18 * 13 + 6 * 3 + 1",
            "Answer": 1657,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 0 * 16 + 5 * 4 + 3",
            "Answer": 23,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 8 * 4 + 17 * 13 + 4",
            "Answer": 353,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 10 * 7 + 10 * 9 + 11",
            "Answer": 731,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 6 * 3 + 5 * 7 + 14",
            "Answer": 265,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 15 * 11 + 8 * 13 + 8",
            "Answer": 2257,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 2 * 2 + 10 * 3 + 5",
            "Answer": 103,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 1 * 15 + 9 * 19 + 17",
            "Answer": 308,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 5 * 3 + 0 * 15 + 6",
            "Answer": 231,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 2 * 6 + 12 * 14 + 11",
            "Answer": 191,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 9 * 6 + 14 * 12 + 13",
            "Answer": 721,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 15 * 9 + 10 * 17 + 8",
            "Answer": 2338,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 4 * 2 + 0 * 2 + 1",
            "Answer": 65,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 11 * 12 + 2 * 10 + 14",
            "Answer": 34,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 4 * 16 + 4 * 11 + 14",
            "Answer": 1210,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 10 * 18 + 8 * 1 + 18",
            "Answer": 746,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 12 * 17 + 16 * 17 + 0",
            "Answer": 4148,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 6 * 17 + 16 * 2 + 2",
            "Answer": 340,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 17 * 7 + 4 * 18 + 11",
            "Answer": 321,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 19 * 3 + 11 * 1 + 12",
            "Answer": 251,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 3 * 18 + 18 * 4 + 11",
            "Answer": 515,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 13 * 14 + 9 * 18 + 5",
            "Answer": 2169,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 3 * 3 + 10 * 12 + 16",
            "Answer": 145,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 11 * 3 + 2 * 12 + 14",
            "Answer": 500,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 17 * 9 + 3 * 13 + 3",
            "Answer": 2490,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 10 * 5 + 18 * 2 + 19",
            "Answer": 505,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 10 * 17 + 1 * 17 + 7",
            "Answer": 534,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 11 * 17 + 5 * 10 + 7",
            "Answer": 1366,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 14 * 18 + 19 * 4 + 8",
            "Answer": 2352,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 14 * 10 + 19 * 8 + 10",
            "Answer": 2542,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 17 * 4 + 9 * 1 + 18",
            "Answer": 1183,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 5 * 4 + 18 * 13 + 14",
            "Answer": 248,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 16 * 11 + 9 * 17 + 4",
            "Answer": 2621,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 11 * 10 + 3 * 13 + 12",
            "Answer": 491,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 12 * 4 + 8 * 9 + 9",
            "Answer": 561,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 7 * 0 + 15 * 9 + 7",
            "Answer": 142,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 3 * 19 + 0 * 6 + 4",
            "Answer": 688,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 12 * 14 + 1 * 11 + 13",
            "Answer": 360,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 4 * 1 + 9 * 5 + 2",
            "Answer": 111,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 2 * 3 + 8 * 11 + 18",
            "Answer": 160,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 19 * 3 + 14 * 14 + 4",
            "Answer": 200,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 0 * 1 + 2 * 10 + 9",
            "Answer": 29,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 19 * 4 + 1 * 12 + 6",
            "Answer": 1462,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 1 * 6 + 0 * 8 + 1",
            "Answer": 61,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + #"
        }
    ],
    "# * # + # * # + # * #": [
        {
            "Question": "15 * 15 + 5 * 0 + 5 * 1",
            "Answer": 230,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 5 + 2 * 2 + 8 * 14",
            "Answer": 166,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 2 + 16 * 8 + 10 * 3",
            "Answer": 174,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 9 + 5 * 10 + 13 * 3",
            "Answer": 143,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 11 + 5 * 16 + 6 * 18",
            "Answer": 254,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 7 + 13 * 12 + 7 * 5",
            "Answer": 289,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 6 + 15 * 2 + 15 * 17",
            "Answer": 357,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 15 + 7 * 6 + 14 * 0",
            "Answer": 162,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 14 + 10 * 10 + 19 * 4",
            "Answer": 260,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 7 + 6 * 7 + 6 * 8",
            "Answer": 181,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 8 + 5 * 8 + 18 * 14",
            "Answer": 300,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 13 + 10 * 7 + 8 * 1",
            "Answer": 143,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 10 + 16 * 13 + 4 * 5",
            "Answer": 278,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 4 + 15 * 6 + 5 * 7",
            "Answer": 153,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 6 + 0 * 2 + 15 * 5",
            "Answer": 159,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 7 + 13 * 5 + 11 * 14",
            "Answer": 338,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 7 + 1 * 12 + 13 * 12",
            "Answer": 273,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 0 + 4 * 14 + 6 * 8",
            "Answer": 104,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 1 + 11 * 13 + 4 * 16",
            "Answer": 208,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 11 + 9 * 12 + 7 * 19",
            "Answer": 406,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 12 + 0 * 13 + 11 * 18",
            "Answer": 366,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 2 + 13 * 17 + 11 * 18",
            "Answer": 443,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 2 + 14 * 19 + 11 * 18",
            "Answer": 472,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 11 + 1 * 19 + 4 * 11",
            "Answer": 151,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 5 + 17 * 4 + 7 * 10",
            "Answer": 218,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 4 + 6 * 7 + 18 * 16",
            "Answer": 334,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 16 + 9 * 4 + 19 * 5",
            "Answer": 179,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 17 + 8 * 14 + 0 * 2",
            "Answer": 367,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 2 + 15 * 10 + 17 * 1",
            "Answer": 203,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 5 + 14 * 2 + 16 * 17",
            "Answer": 345,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 19 + 11 * 1 + 5 * 6",
            "Answer": 345,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 0 + 5 * 2 + 19 * 1",
            "Answer": 29,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 4 + 18 * 18 + 8 * 9",
            "Answer": 400,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 8 + 6 * 19 + 19 * 17",
            "Answer": 549,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 18 + 0 * 7 + 16 * 16",
            "Answer": 256,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 14 + 4 * 19 + 14 * 18",
            "Answer": 384,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 16 + 3 * 18 + 19 * 5",
            "Answer": 405,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 1 + 15 * 6 + 1 * 8",
            "Answer": 100,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 7 + 16 * 13 + 3 * 10",
            "Answer": 280,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 15 + 14 * 15 + 3 * 16",
            "Answer": 468,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 15 + 6 * 19 + 8 * 13",
            "Answer": 293,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 12 + 1 * 5 + 13 * 0",
            "Answer": 29,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 0 + 19 * 11 + 9 * 18",
            "Answer": 371,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 9 + 16 * 12 + 11 * 18",
            "Answer": 453,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 5 + 15 * 7 + 16 * 8",
            "Answer": 323,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 4 + 16 * 10 + 3 * 8",
            "Answer": 260,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 5 + 19 * 7 + 4 * 2",
            "Answer": 196,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 8 + 18 * 3 + 17 * 4",
            "Answer": 234,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 15 + 14 * 10 + 18 * 7",
            "Answer": 296,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 12 + 13 * 11 + 7 * 8",
            "Answer": 259,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 2 + 15 * 18 + 18 * 6",
            "Answer": 408,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 19 + 17 * 18 + 9 * 3",
            "Answer": 656,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 12 + 14 * 10 + 13 * 4",
            "Answer": 324,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 16 + 18 * 6 + 6 * 13",
            "Answer": 250,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 15 + 11 * 1 + 11 * 7",
            "Answer": 328,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 8 + 7 * 10 + 4 * 18",
            "Answer": 262,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 2 + 4 * 2 + 14 * 2",
            "Answer": 68,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 9 + 5 * 18 + 18 * 7",
            "Answer": 315,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 5 + 18 * 9 + 7 * 5",
            "Answer": 257,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 12 + 11 * 11 + 16 * 14",
            "Answer": 501,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 0 + 13 * 8 + 18 * 4",
            "Answer": 176,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 13 + 18 * 3 + 3 * 12",
            "Answer": 259,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 16 + 14 * 11 + 1 * 13",
            "Answer": 471,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 13 + 3 * 9 + 17 * 16",
            "Answer": 312,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 13 + 13 * 18 + 4 * 9",
            "Answer": 465,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 17 + 0 * 19 + 4 * 0",
            "Answer": 102,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 5 + 18 * 6 + 4 * 17",
            "Answer": 211,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 12 + 18 * 10 + 13 * 17",
            "Answer": 521,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 11 + 1 * 15 + 1 * 6",
            "Answer": 54,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 1 + 11 * 12 + 3 * 19",
            "Answer": 196,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 14 + 12 * 1 + 15 * 13",
            "Answer": 459,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 19 + 19 * 11 + 17 * 8",
            "Answer": 497,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 15 + 12 * 11 + 6 * 0",
            "Answer": 357,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 9 + 0 * 2 + 16 * 13",
            "Answer": 307,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 2 + 3 * 11 + 8 * 3",
            "Answer": 85,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 13 + 3 * 1 + 9 * 2",
            "Answer": 34,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 3 + 11 * 7 + 1 * 1",
            "Answer": 132,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 17 + 7 * 9 + 2 * 4",
            "Answer": 71,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 8 + 15 * 14 + 15 * 9",
            "Answer": 377,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 10 + 18 * 18 + 0 * 15",
            "Answer": 434,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 5 + 8 * 0 + 14 * 10",
            "Answer": 175,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 15 + 7 * 17 + 9 * 17",
            "Answer": 362,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 18 + 7 * 11 + 7 * 6",
            "Answer": 425,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 17 + 9 * 6 + 4 * 8",
            "Answer": 120,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 5 + 16 * 5 + 10 * 7",
            "Answer": 205,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 15 + 5 * 13 + 12 * 1",
            "Answer": 332,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 7 + 12 * 9 + 10 * 15",
            "Answer": 293,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 17 + 12 * 16 + 8 * 7",
            "Answer": 265,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 9 + 0 * 16 + 7 * 15",
            "Answer": 114,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 1 + 7 * 15 + 12 * 6",
            "Answer": 177,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 9 + 2 * 15 + 7 * 15",
            "Answer": 306,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 17 + 4 * 3 + 19 * 4",
            "Answer": 411,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 9 + 19 * 11 + 9 * 16",
            "Answer": 452,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 1 + 3 * 1 + 4 * 13",
            "Answer": 65,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 16 + 0 * 3 + 15 * 13",
            "Answer": 275,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 18 + 8 * 10 + 0 * 13",
            "Answer": 260,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 16 + 17 * 4 + 4 * 6",
            "Answer": 316,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 8 + 5 * 12 + 2 * 2",
            "Answer": 80,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 8 + 15 * 19 + 7 * 15",
            "Answer": 446,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 5 + 5 * 11 + 6 * 2",
            "Answer": 82,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * #"
        }
    ],
    "# * # * # * # + # + #": [
        {
            "Question": "8 * 13 * 8 * 8 + 17 + 14",
            "Answer": 6687,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 6 * 14 * 3 + 17 + 6",
            "Answer": 2291,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 8 * 8 * 13 + 13 + 13",
            "Answer": 5850,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 16 * 5 * 7 + 7 + 6",
            "Answer": 5613,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 6 * 6 * 19 + 2 + 10",
            "Answer": 2748,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 0 * 9 * 8 + 6 + 15",
            "Answer": 21,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 7 * 1 * 6 + 0 + 2",
            "Answer": 590,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 17 * 16 * 16 + 3 + 12",
            "Answer": 26127,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 5 * 6 * 6 + 13 + 9",
            "Answer": 2362,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 7 * 19 * 5 + 19 + 15",
            "Answer": 4689,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 13 * 2 * 15 + 0 + 10",
            "Answer": 400,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 12 * 9 * 8 + 3 + 5",
            "Answer": 8648,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 13 * 18 * 17 + 17 + 6",
            "Answer": 47759,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 9 * 9 * 16 + 0 + 14",
            "Answer": 3902,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 3 * 11 * 6 + 19 + 19",
            "Answer": 1424,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 5 * 3 * 16 + 6 + 16",
            "Answer": 2662,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 7 * 7 * 5 + 4 + 19",
            "Answer": 3943,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 7 * 4 * 2 + 4 + 9",
            "Answer": 237,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 18 * 9 * 7 + 13 + 13",
            "Answer": 13634,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 15 * 10 * 19 + 1 + 5",
            "Answer": 25656,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 19 * 13 * 12 + 2 + 8",
            "Answer": 32614,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 7 * 3 * 9 + 1 + 5",
            "Answer": 1518,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 18 * 3 * 17 + 11 + 2",
            "Answer": 9193,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 17 * 3 * 8 + 6 + 4",
            "Answer": 2050,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 13 * 9 * 6 + 0 + 12",
            "Answer": 11946,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 12 * 0 * 2 + 13 + 13",
            "Answer": 26,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 5 * 14 * 2 + 14 + 17",
            "Answer": 1711,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 8 * 12 * 14 + 11 + 18",
            "Answer": 17501,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 12 * 9 * 1 + 12 + 12",
            "Answer": 780,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 9 * 3 * 6 + 12 + 17",
            "Answer": 515,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 7 * 12 * 2 + 10 + 7",
            "Answer": 3209,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 14 * 15 * 12 + 9 + 18",
            "Answer": 37827,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 10 * 18 * 12 + 19 + 4",
            "Answer": 32423,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 7 * 11 * 4 + 9 + 11",
            "Answer": 5564,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 8 * 10 * 5 + 18 + 9",
            "Answer": 5227,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 10 * 2 * 1 + 3 + 10",
            "Answer": 213,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 8 * 19 * 0 + 2 + 19",
            "Answer": 21,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 9 * 17 * 4 + 5 + 16",
            "Answer": 3693,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 3 * 10 * 5 + 8 + 19",
            "Answer": 1677,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 18 * 8 * 6 + 17 + 18",
            "Answer": 16451,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 11 * 6 * 4 + 18 + 16",
            "Answer": 2938,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 7 * 5 * 1 + 7 + 9",
            "Answer": 471,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 8 * 5 * 13 + 9 + 18",
            "Answer": 1587,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 7 * 5 * 15 + 18 + 14",
            "Answer": 1607,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 4 * 9 * 16 + 7 + 19",
            "Answer": 8666,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 18 * 2 * 16 + 10 + 2",
            "Answer": 6348,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 2 * 1 * 8 + 2 + 4",
            "Answer": 230,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 8 * 3 * 6 + 17 + 10",
            "Answer": 1755,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 2 * 17 * 10 + 6 + 15",
            "Answer": 3761,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 15 * 15 * 7 + 5 + 19",
            "Answer": 6324,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 2 * 11 * 15 + 18 + 7",
            "Answer": 6295,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 12 * 4 * 7 + 14 + 8",
            "Answer": 1366,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 0 * 17 * 1 + 9 + 12",
            "Answer": 21,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 16 * 8 * 5 + 11 + 0",
            "Answer": 2571,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 9 * 13 * 1 + 6 + 12",
            "Answer": 2007,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 16 * 4 * 9 + 4 + 8",
            "Answer": 1740,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 2 * 10 * 1 + 3 + 16",
            "Answer": 379,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 7 * 8 * 3 + 19 + 7",
            "Answer": 2546,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 11 * 10 * 18 + 18 + 0",
            "Answer": 35658,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 7 * 8 * 6 + 10 + 0",
            "Answer": 5050,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 5 * 13 * 11 + 9 + 14",
            "Answer": 13608,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 7 * 19 * 17 + 11 + 4",
            "Answer": 29408,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 2 * 12 * 4 + 10 + 8",
            "Answer": 1650,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 15 * 17 * 5 + 4 + 11",
            "Answer": 12765,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 3 * 8 * 7 + 9 + 9",
            "Answer": 3042,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 8 * 16 * 7 + 17 + 2",
            "Answer": 11667,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 2 * 0 * 14 + 10 + 14",
            "Answer": 24,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 5 * 7 * 10 + 8 + 18",
            "Answer": 376,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 6 * 15 * 1 + 10 + 10",
            "Answer": 560,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 6 * 4 * 18 + 14 + 16",
            "Answer": 5214,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 18 * 11 * 4 + 6 + 16",
            "Answer": 3190,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 15 * 16 * 11 + 13 + 14",
            "Answer": 21147,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 8 * 0 * 8 + 17 + 6",
            "Answer": 23,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 18 * 15 * 19 + 12 + 0",
            "Answer": 66702,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 7 * 18 * 1 + 18 + 16",
            "Answer": 790,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 1 * 17 * 12 + 11 + 9",
            "Answer": 2468,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 13 * 17 * 13 + 4 + 11",
            "Answer": 51729,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 0 * 6 * 4 + 19 + 8",
            "Answer": 27,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 17 * 2 * 12 + 17 + 18",
            "Answer": 5339,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 5 * 13 * 2 + 8 + 15",
            "Answer": 2103,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 8 * 18 * 6 + 18 + 16",
            "Answer": 3490,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 10 * 18 * 3 + 1 + 12",
            "Answer": 5953,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 9 * 1 * 5 + 8 + 6",
            "Answer": 824,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 15 * 1 * 5 + 4 + 18",
            "Answer": 547,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 16 * 8 * 17 + 18 + 9",
            "Answer": 30491,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 10 * 2 * 12 + 6 + 14",
            "Answer": 980,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 13 * 0 * 1 + 2 + 9",
            "Answer": 11,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 5 * 6 * 1 + 19 + 12",
            "Answer": 361,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 12 * 0 * 4 + 11 + 12",
            "Answer": 23,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 16 * 11 * 16 + 18 + 2",
            "Answer": 16916,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 5 * 16 * 17 + 14 + 12",
            "Answer": 20426,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 13 * 11 * 17 + 13 + 8",
            "Answer": 19469,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 17 * 19 * 1 + 17 + 16",
            "Answer": 3586,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 1 * 6 * 13 + 11 + 10",
            "Answer": 177,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 2 * 3 * 19 + 19 + 8",
            "Answer": 1281,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 14 * 7 * 3 + 0 + 18",
            "Answer": 900,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 5 * 16 * 2 + 6 + 11",
            "Answer": 1137,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 0 * 17 * 10 + 18 + 9",
            "Answer": 27,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 19 * 8 * 7 + 2 + 17",
            "Answer": 18107,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 13 * 2 * 11 + 8 + 13",
            "Answer": 1451,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + #"
        }
    ],
    "# * # * # + # + # * #": [
        {
            "Question": "12 * 18 * 12 + 13 + 19 * 17",
            "Answer": 2928,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 18 * 6 + 15 + 12 * 17",
            "Answer": 1947,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 8 * 7 + 9 + 13 * 3",
            "Answer": 888,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 10 * 9 + 7 + 0 * 14",
            "Answer": 187,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 11 * 17 + 12 + 2 * 12",
            "Answer": 223,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 13 * 6 + 5 + 15 * 19",
            "Answer": 1148,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 4 * 8 + 9 + 5 * 0",
            "Answer": 41,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 3 * 0 + 9 + 9 * 17",
            "Answer": 162,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 16 * 2 + 11 + 12 * 1",
            "Answer": 599,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 1 * 1 + 0 + 9 * 4",
            "Answer": 45,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 11 * 10 + 19 + 5 * 6",
            "Answer": 489,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 11 * 5 + 3 + 4 * 0",
            "Answer": 278,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 7 * 10 + 7 + 6 * 1",
            "Answer": 223,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 10 * 15 + 4 + 0 * 10",
            "Answer": 1504,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 11 * 18 + 10 + 6 * 9",
            "Answer": 658,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 10 * 15 + 9 + 0 * 13",
            "Answer": 159,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 18 * 3 + 8 + 3 * 14",
            "Answer": 590,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 9 * 18 + 19 + 8 * 15",
            "Answer": 1273,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 19 * 6 + 7 + 11 * 7",
            "Answer": 312,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 10 * 2 + 0 + 18 * 3",
            "Answer": 134,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 16 * 10 + 18 + 13 * 12",
            "Answer": 494,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 3 * 5 + 14 + 8 * 16",
            "Answer": 412,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 13 * 0 + 3 + 4 * 16",
            "Answer": 67,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 17 * 17 + 2 + 9 * 9",
            "Answer": 1817,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 12 * 13 + 14 + 7 * 17",
            "Answer": 3097,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 3 * 15 + 18 + 7 * 11",
            "Answer": 455,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 7 * 12 + 1 + 5 * 9",
            "Answer": 382,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 15 * 2 + 11 + 6 * 16",
            "Answer": 467,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 12 * 3 + 0 + 17 * 16",
            "Answer": 308,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 2 * 12 + 16 + 13 * 17",
            "Answer": 549,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 8 * 12 + 11 + 18 * 6",
            "Answer": 407,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 1 * 0 + 5 + 13 * 0",
            "Answer": 5,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 7 * 14 + 2 + 12 * 16",
            "Answer": 1076,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 3 * 17 + 1 + 9 * 15",
            "Answer": 544,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 9 * 17 + 17 + 13 * 4",
            "Answer": 1599,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 9 * 8 + 12 + 6 * 14",
            "Answer": 1176,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 11 * 12 + 2 + 5 * 3",
            "Answer": 1073,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 5 * 14 + 12 + 5 * 10",
            "Answer": 552,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 3 * 8 + 5 + 11 * 11",
            "Answer": 222,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 13 * 2 + 18 + 5 * 9",
            "Answer": 375,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 9 * 3 + 15 + 1 * 13",
            "Answer": 325,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 2 * 14 + 14 + 6 * 15",
            "Answer": 160,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 0 * 4 + 3 + 9 * 4",
            "Answer": 39,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 10 * 19 + 7 + 4 * 16",
            "Answer": 1781,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 3 * 8 + 11 + 3 * 16",
            "Answer": 227,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 14 * 9 + 15 + 11 * 9",
            "Answer": 1500,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 13 * 6 + 17 + 0 * 3",
            "Answer": 1031,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 8 * 17 + 4 + 17 * 16",
            "Answer": 2180,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 12 * 3 + 12 + 13 * 15",
            "Answer": 747,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 13 * 0 + 14 + 1 * 16",
            "Answer": 30,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 16 * 15 + 5 + 7 * 19",
            "Answer": 2538,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 17 * 12 + 18 + 16 * 5",
            "Answer": 3770,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 1 * 4 + 11 + 8 * 15",
            "Answer": 159,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 13 * 5 + 10 + 1 * 7",
            "Answer": 1122,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 15 * 18 + 4 + 1 * 14",
            "Answer": 288,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 17 * 16 + 8 + 16 * 11",
            "Answer": 2360,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 17 * 1 + 14 + 13 * 9",
            "Answer": 233,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 5 * 19 + 6 + 7 * 10",
            "Answer": 551,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 6 * 1 + 15 + 13 * 13",
            "Answer": 208,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 2 * 1 + 14 + 19 * 10",
            "Answer": 210,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 6 * 7 + 15 + 6 * 12",
            "Answer": 591,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 10 * 5 + 4 + 1 * 4",
            "Answer": 908,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 4 * 19 + 2 + 11 * 13",
            "Answer": 1209,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 5 * 1 + 16 + 14 * 13",
            "Answer": 233,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 4 * 2 + 6 + 11 * 10",
            "Answer": 260,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 11 * 15 + 1 + 4 * 18",
            "Answer": 3208,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 0 * 8 + 14 + 8 * 9",
            "Answer": 86,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 19 * 19 + 15 + 18 * 11",
            "Answer": 5267,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 17 * 13 + 10 + 11 * 5",
            "Answer": 2054,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 15 * 12 + 15 + 3 * 15",
            "Answer": 2400,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 7 * 12 + 12 + 1 * 16",
            "Answer": 1456,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 9 * 16 + 4 + 2 * 7",
            "Answer": 2754,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 16 * 10 + 6 + 13 * 9",
            "Answer": 1243,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 19 * 13 + 1 + 8 * 14",
            "Answer": 2830,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 10 * 13 + 13 + 1 * 19",
            "Answer": 422,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 13 * 10 + 2 + 19 * 13",
            "Answer": 2459,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 8 * 18 + 16 + 8 * 4",
            "Answer": 2496,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 4 * 2 + 18 + 17 * 7",
            "Answer": 249,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 3 * 13 + 18 + 14 * 6",
            "Answer": 570,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 8 * 3 + 7 + 1 * 2",
            "Answer": 273,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 14 * 5 + 11 + 19 * 14",
            "Answer": 1607,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 18 * 6 + 17 + 4 * 1",
            "Answer": 1317,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 7 * 10 + 16 + 10 * 5",
            "Answer": 1256,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 18 * 17 + 3 + 5 * 10",
            "Answer": 4949,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 16 * 16 + 6 + 7 * 13",
            "Answer": 609,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 16 * 18 + 11 + 1 * 9",
            "Answer": 308,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 4 * 7 + 0 + 18 * 15",
            "Answer": 606,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 17 * 1 + 9 + 17 * 12",
            "Answer": 264,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 13 * 12 + 19 + 0 * 14",
            "Answer": 1267,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 19 * 0 + 14 + 18 * 17",
            "Answer": 320,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 18 * 0 + 10 + 2 * 13",
            "Answer": 36,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 2 * 14 + 11 + 17 * 16",
            "Answer": 815,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 3 * 10 + 18 + 5 * 19",
            "Answer": 593,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 1 * 18 + 17 + 18 * 8",
            "Answer": 395,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 3 * 18 + 5 + 18 * 4",
            "Answer": 77,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 9 * 10 + 15 + 15 * 1",
            "Answer": 300,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 11 * 16 + 14 + 13 * 18",
            "Answer": 1304,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 4 * 3 + 15 + 6 * 15",
            "Answer": 201,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 7 * 4 + 0 + 8 * 15",
            "Answer": 204,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 4 * 10 + 7 + 19 * 15",
            "Answer": 972,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * #"
        }
    ],
    "# + # * # + # * # + #": [
        {
            "Question": "2 + 2 * 15 + 10 * 8 + 9",
            "Answer": 121,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 9 * 10 + 13 * 0 + 3",
            "Answer": 105,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 8 * 15 + 1 * 3 + 16",
            "Answer": 157,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 9 * 2 + 1 * 4 + 2",
            "Answer": 25,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 7 * 1 + 1 * 14 + 7",
            "Answer": 31,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 18 * 11 + 4 * 6 + 9",
            "Answer": 237,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 10 * 13 + 15 * 13 + 15",
            "Answer": 347,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 10 * 17 + 1 * 7 + 1",
            "Answer": 184,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 7 * 8 + 13 * 7 + 6",
            "Answer": 161,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 11 * 15 + 9 * 8 + 5",
            "Answer": 252,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 4 * 4 + 15 * 1 + 15",
            "Answer": 57,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 17 * 8 + 0 * 16 + 18",
            "Answer": 164,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 15 * 8 + 12 * 1 + 2",
            "Answer": 143,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 10 * 7 + 5 * 16 + 7",
            "Answer": 167,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 2 * 13 + 1 * 6 + 16",
            "Answer": 60,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 18 * 17 + 5 * 16 + 16",
            "Answer": 416,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 8 * 0 + 15 * 14 + 3",
            "Answer": 222,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 1 * 15 + 0 * 3 + 0",
            "Answer": 15,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 8 * 3 + 9 * 16 + 18",
            "Answer": 196,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 14 * 17 + 17 * 14 + 1",
            "Answer": 482,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 16 * 12 + 9 * 15 + 3",
            "Answer": 337,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 19 * 9 + 16 * 0 + 7",
            "Answer": 179,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 2 * 4 + 0 * 0 + 5",
            "Answer": 18,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 13 * 9 + 10 * 17 + 1",
            "Answer": 289,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 13 * 5 + 0 * 8 + 12",
            "Answer": 88,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 15 * 11 + 7 * 9 + 5",
            "Answer": 243,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 12 * 5 + 15 * 6 + 2",
            "Answer": 158,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 14 * 11 + 1 * 10 + 15",
            "Answer": 192,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 2 * 1 + 16 * 12 + 7",
            "Answer": 209,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 7 * 16 + 9 * 15 + 13",
            "Answer": 277,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 4 * 9 + 1 * 10 + 2",
            "Answer": 57,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 8 * 13 + 12 * 8 + 5",
            "Answer": 217,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 19 * 16 + 2 * 11 + 8",
            "Answer": 342,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 19 * 5 + 10 * 1 + 1",
            "Answer": 119,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 2 * 1 + 0 * 19 + 18",
            "Answer": 21,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 5 * 2 + 18 * 1 + 0",
            "Answer": 38,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 9 * 9 + 1 * 5 + 13",
            "Answer": 115,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 6 * 11 + 8 * 12 + 9",
            "Answer": 184,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 11 * 0 + 8 * 6 + 9",
            "Answer": 69,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 0 * 2 + 10 * 1 + 17",
            "Answer": 33,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 3 * 13 + 1 * 1 + 19",
            "Answer": 64,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 15 * 14 + 0 * 1 + 2",
            "Answer": 231,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 7 * 9 + 7 * 7 + 4",
            "Answer": 125,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 4 * 10 + 15 * 11 + 3",
            "Answer": 208,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 12 * 5 + 14 * 2 + 3",
            "Answer": 107,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 5 * 19 + 16 * 5 + 12",
            "Answer": 190,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 6 * 7 + 4 * 8 + 12",
            "Answer": 91,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 7 * 16 + 7 * 17 + 11",
            "Answer": 253,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 11 * 3 + 14 * 14 + 9",
            "Answer": 243,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 10 * 4 + 4 * 3 + 19",
            "Answer": 76,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 13 * 2 + 0 * 0 + 8",
            "Answer": 46,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 6 * 9 + 12 * 0 + 0",
            "Answer": 64,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 13 * 12 + 5 * 13 + 14",
            "Answer": 253,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 14 * 14 + 15 * 13 + 0",
            "Answer": 404,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 2 * 8 + 10 * 3 + 1",
            "Answer": 57,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 13 * 13 + 8 * 11 + 1",
            "Answer": 274,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 3 * 14 + 5 * 9 + 2",
            "Answer": 102,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 17 * 10 + 10 * 7 + 5",
            "Answer": 264,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 14 * 19 + 14 * 12 + 18",
            "Answer": 461,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 11 * 10 + 4 * 5 + 17",
            "Answer": 148,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 11 * 18 + 13 * 7 + 6",
            "Answer": 301,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 10 * 0 + 14 * 5 + 6",
            "Answer": 84,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 1 * 5 + 2 * 16 + 10",
            "Answer": 53,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 3 * 5 + 9 * 16 + 2",
            "Answer": 177,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 14 * 4 + 7 * 3 + 13",
            "Answer": 103,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 19 * 8 + 16 * 9 + 19",
            "Answer": 330,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 14 * 15 + 11 * 18 + 15",
            "Answer": 424,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 12 * 14 + 13 * 1 + 19",
            "Answer": 205,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 18 * 13 + 12 * 8 + 4",
            "Answer": 348,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 6 * 16 + 5 * 13 + 13",
            "Answer": 181,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 2 * 7 + 2 * 7 + 9",
            "Answer": 38,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 4 * 3 + 15 * 0 + 8",
            "Answer": 28,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 10 * 6 + 2 * 8 + 4",
            "Answer": 96,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 16 * 2 + 0 * 2 + 3",
            "Answer": 47,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 16 * 2 + 3 * 4 + 10",
            "Answer": 72,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 14 * 11 + 14 * 5 + 2",
            "Answer": 230,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 5 * 10 + 1 * 5 + 9",
            "Answer": 74,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 12 * 9 + 2 * 12 + 18",
            "Answer": 165,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 2 * 3 + 12 * 1 + 8",
            "Answer": 27,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 5 * 6 + 13 * 17 + 4",
            "Answer": 266,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 12 * 15 + 6 * 7 + 7",
            "Answer": 232,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 1 * 10 + 7 * 7 + 10",
            "Answer": 73,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 5 * 11 + 15 * 1 + 9",
            "Answer": 79,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 8 * 8 + 5 * 8 + 0",
            "Answer": 121,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 1 * 11 + 4 * 2 + 14",
            "Answer": 51,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 15 * 4 + 3 * 13 + 12",
            "Answer": 123,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 19 * 10 + 18 * 17 + 2",
            "Answer": 508,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 14 * 4 + 7 * 1 + 6",
            "Answer": 70,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 19 * 19 + 7 * 18 + 19",
            "Answer": 510,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 12 * 10 + 1 * 7 + 5",
            "Answer": 149,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 18 * 19 + 15 * 9 + 17",
            "Answer": 510,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 15 * 5 + 9 * 3 + 17",
            "Answer": 137,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 19 * 3 + 1 * 2 + 1",
            "Answer": 63,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 7 * 4 + 17 * 11 + 0",
            "Answer": 234,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 7 * 1 + 13 * 17 + 2",
            "Answer": 236,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 10 * 0 + 0 * 2 + 15",
            "Answer": 32,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 0 * 17 + 12 * 0 + 9",
            "Answer": 22,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 11 * 3 + 2 * 9 + 11",
            "Answer": 75,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 13 * 13 + 15 * 3 + 14",
            "Answer": 244,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 10 * 17 + 10 * 18 + 5",
            "Answer": 357,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + #"
        }
    ],
    "# + # + # * # + # * #": [
        {
            "Question": "8 + 1 + 3 * 19 + 19 * 0",
            "Answer": 66,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 18 + 0 * 4 + 19 * 14",
            "Answer": 291,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 4 + 9 * 19 + 15 * 6",
            "Answer": 284,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 1 + 18 * 10 + 18 * 4",
            "Answer": 255,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 0 + 10 * 13 + 9 * 8",
            "Answer": 208,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 7 + 7 * 17 + 9 * 17",
            "Answer": 286,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 15 + 0 * 16 + 9 * 1",
            "Answer": 29,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 10 + 17 * 0 + 6 * 16",
            "Answer": 123,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 11 + 2 * 17 + 11 * 18",
            "Answer": 246,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 12 + 12 * 13 + 19 * 12",
            "Answer": 396,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 18 + 3 * 4 + 2 * 18",
            "Answer": 78,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 7 + 18 * 7 + 3 * 6",
            "Answer": 166,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 9 + 18 * 19 + 5 * 11",
            "Answer": 408,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 18 + 18 * 6 + 19 * 16",
            "Answer": 448,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 6 + 6 * 3 + 16 * 5",
            "Answer": 117,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 17 + 11 * 1 + 0 * 2",
            "Answer": 28,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 19 + 2 * 1 + 12 * 5",
            "Answer": 90,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 8 + 4 * 7 + 14 * 9",
            "Answer": 169,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 17 + 6 * 17 + 10 * 18",
            "Answer": 311,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 19 + 13 * 0 + 14 * 3",
            "Answer": 71,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 17 + 14 * 0 + 16 * 17",
            "Answer": 307,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 10 + 16 * 2 + 14 * 4",
            "Answer": 117,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 18 + 11 * 14 + 18 * 16",
            "Answer": 474,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 11 + 2 * 16 + 17 * 19",
            "Answer": 382,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 19 + 0 * 17 + 7 * 3",
            "Answer": 43,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 5 + 16 * 4 + 1 * 3",
            "Answer": 85,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 10 + 4 * 10 + 9 * 2",
            "Answer": 74,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 5 + 19 * 6 + 5 * 11",
            "Answer": 176,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 10 + 4 * 17 + 2 * 17",
            "Answer": 117,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 12 + 14 * 12 + 8 * 8",
            "Answer": 257,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 17 + 3 * 5 + 14 * 7",
            "Answer": 140,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 17 + 3 * 10 + 14 * 12",
            "Answer": 218,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 5 + 14 * 0 + 19 * 2",
            "Answer": 58,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 5 + 7 * 15 + 18 * 6",
            "Answer": 225,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 10 + 19 * 17 + 2 * 11",
            "Answer": 363,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 6 + 2 * 12 + 14 * 13",
            "Answer": 217,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 12 + 17 * 11 + 1 * 18",
            "Answer": 229,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 7 + 6 * 4 + 15 * 12",
            "Answer": 214,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 13 + 4 * 2 + 9 * 11",
            "Answer": 131,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 6 + 18 * 17 + 3 * 14",
            "Answer": 364,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 3 + 8 * 3 + 9 * 9",
            "Answer": 112,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 9 + 3 * 7 + 7 * 14",
            "Answer": 135,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 1 + 18 * 16 + 1 * 16",
            "Answer": 306,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 17 + 12 * 17 + 10 * 7",
            "Answer": 297,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 8 + 15 * 14 + 6 * 15",
            "Answer": 311,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 10 + 5 * 2 + 13 * 10",
            "Answer": 168,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 0 + 16 * 15 + 14 * 6",
            "Answer": 337,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 8 + 14 * 17 + 0 * 3",
            "Answer": 261,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 17 + 2 * 6 + 17 * 9",
            "Answer": 193,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 12 + 2 * 8 + 11 * 8",
            "Answer": 118,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 8 + 15 * 10 + 10 * 13",
            "Answer": 302,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 7 + 14 * 2 + 8 * 2",
            "Answer": 59,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 17 + 9 * 12 + 9 * 1",
            "Answer": 134,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 17 + 12 * 7 + 15 * 13",
            "Answer": 308,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 5 + 15 * 3 + 13 * 13",
            "Answer": 225,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 0 + 15 * 2 + 1 * 2",
            "Answer": 33,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 11 + 15 * 14 + 2 * 10",
            "Answer": 254,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 0 + 5 * 13 + 13 * 4",
            "Answer": 135,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 8 + 15 * 9 + 7 * 4",
            "Answer": 174,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 9 + 6 * 3 + 15 * 4",
            "Answer": 87,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 16 + 8 * 12 + 13 * 19",
            "Answer": 376,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 15 + 8 * 10 + 17 * 7",
            "Answer": 217,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 11 + 17 * 8 + 6 * 18",
            "Answer": 272,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 15 + 17 * 3 + 5 * 15",
            "Answer": 141,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 9 + 17 * 5 + 11 * 18",
            "Answer": 301,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 10 + 10 * 18 + 7 * 10",
            "Answer": 275,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 3 + 19 * 13 + 4 * 11",
            "Answer": 311,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 12 + 9 * 2 + 18 * 11",
            "Answer": 234,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 7 + 10 * 1 + 19 * 4",
            "Answer": 102,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 6 + 12 * 12 + 3 * 12",
            "Answer": 204,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 0 + 7 * 16 + 11 * 12",
            "Answer": 253,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 18 + 14 * 15 + 1 * 3",
            "Answer": 240,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 1 + 14 * 13 + 17 * 8",
            "Answer": 332,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 6 + 11 * 16 + 8 * 12",
            "Answer": 283,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 13 + 1 * 16 + 2 * 3",
            "Answer": 49,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 14 + 3 * 10 + 12 * 5",
            "Answer": 122,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 12 + 18 * 17 + 0 * 10",
            "Answer": 318,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 16 + 10 * 9 + 0 * 14",
            "Answer": 113,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 14 + 7 * 10 + 13 * 1",
            "Answer": 106,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 14 + 12 * 10 + 6 * 12",
            "Answer": 209,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 1 + 18 * 11 + 9 * 10",
            "Answer": 308,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 6 + 15 * 15 + 18 * 9",
            "Answer": 401,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 9 + 15 * 7 + 14 * 13",
            "Answer": 301,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 19 + 13 * 17 + 15 * 5",
            "Answer": 326,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 14 + 12 * 14 + 7 * 7",
            "Answer": 240,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 5 + 1 * 1 + 0 * 1",
            "Answer": 19,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 14 + 19 * 12 + 10 * 14",
            "Answer": 401,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 2 + 0 * 3 + 2 * 2",
            "Answer": 17,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 16 + 4 * 16 + 9 * 10",
            "Answer": 179,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 8 + 8 * 1 + 15 * 8",
            "Answer": 155,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 8 + 2 * 3 + 18 * 5",
            "Answer": 118,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 14 + 8 * 10 + 5 * 10",
            "Answer": 153,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 11 + 1 * 5 + 1 * 8",
            "Answer": 41,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 10 + 10 * 10 + 15 * 1",
            "Answer": 136,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 7 + 3 * 19 + 13 * 19",
            "Answer": 320,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 13 + 16 * 18 + 16 * 10",
            "Answer": 471,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 2 + 14 * 10 + 7 * 6",
            "Answer": 201,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 11 + 7 * 8 + 17 * 13",
            "Answer": 291,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 18 + 17 * 9 + 7 * 8",
            "Answer": 230,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 13 + 11 * 4 + 0 * 13",
            "Answer": 64,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * #"
        }
    ],
    "# + # + # * # * # * #": [
        {
            "Question": "7 + 1 + 4 * 1 * 15 * 8",
            "Answer": 488,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 15 + 0 * 10 * 19 * 13",
            "Answer": 20,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 10 + 14 * 10 * 15 * 13",
            "Answer": 27314,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 15 + 13 * 6 * 12 * 15",
            "Answer": 14072,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 13 + 8 * 4 * 14 * 14",
            "Answer": 6286,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 14 + 11 * 3 * 5 * 19",
            "Answer": 3154,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 17 + 6 * 19 * 7 * 2",
            "Answer": 1624,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 11 + 12 * 0 * 12 * 2",
            "Answer": 17,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 4 + 9 * 3 * 0 * 2",
            "Answer": 17,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 7 + 14 * 18 * 4 * 0",
            "Answer": 10,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 16 + 14 * 1 * 19 * 9",
            "Answer": 2419,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 0 + 15 * 14 * 12 * 8",
            "Answer": 20166,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 18 + 5 * 7 * 14 * 12",
            "Answer": 5916,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 4 + 13 * 7 * 18 * 17",
            "Answer": 27852,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 6 + 19 * 3 * 11 * 4",
            "Answer": 2531,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 14 + 12 * 0 * 4 * 0",
            "Answer": 26,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 8 + 0 * 0 * 17 * 7",
            "Answer": 11,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 15 + 6 * 13 * 18 * 4",
            "Answer": 5631,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 13 + 10 * 2 * 19 * 17",
            "Answer": 6479,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 0 + 13 * 16 * 3 * 3",
            "Answer": 1878,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 4 + 8 * 4 * 6 * 0",
            "Answer": 11,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 10 + 7 * 10 * 14 * 16",
            "Answer": 15709,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 18 + 17 * 7 * 9 * 11",
            "Answer": 11801,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 19 + 14 * 12 * 11 * 13",
            "Answer": 24051,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 12 + 5 * 10 * 15 * 16",
            "Answer": 12028,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 3 + 18 * 1 * 19 * 17",
            "Answer": 5835,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 6 + 9 * 1 * 15 * 16",
            "Answer": 2168,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 12 + 15 * 4 * 12 * 1",
            "Answer": 751,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 18 + 18 * 4 * 7 * 2",
            "Answer": 1040,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 6 + 2 * 8 * 16 * 17",
            "Answer": 4365,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 16 + 18 * 11 * 14 * 12",
            "Answer": 33287,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 11 + 12 * 3 * 2 * 15",
            "Answer": 1109,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 19 + 5 * 17 * 3 * 17",
            "Answer": 4364,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 0 + 2 * 6 * 4 * 15",
            "Answer": 723,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 6 + 6 * 5 * 4 * 8",
            "Answer": 973,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 12 + 15 * 17 * 10 * 5",
            "Answer": 12769,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 13 + 6 * 16 * 7 * 8",
            "Answer": 5402,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 12 + 0 * 9 * 9 * 5",
            "Answer": 22,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 0 + 17 * 16 * 8 * 15",
            "Answer": 32652,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 11 + 10 * 4 * 17 * 0",
            "Answer": 17,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 6 + 0 * 17 * 7 * 9",
            "Answer": 9,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 8 + 15 * 10 * 1 * 11",
            "Answer": 1676,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 11 + 6 * 18 * 9 * 7",
            "Answer": 6828,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 19 + 11 * 4 * 10 * 14",
            "Answer": 6191,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 10 + 14 * 1 * 6 * 5",
            "Answer": 432,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 14 + 19 * 9 * 10 * 16",
            "Answer": 27389,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 6 + 1 * 18 * 16 * 3",
            "Answer": 875,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 15 + 0 * 11 * 10 * 2",
            "Answer": 24,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 13 + 9 * 10 * 0 * 4",
            "Answer": 29,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 8 + 15 * 9 * 8 * 5",
            "Answer": 5410,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 5 + 6 * 12 * 9 * 14",
            "Answer": 9084,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 16 + 10 * 15 * 9 * 12",
            "Answer": 16225,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 7 + 2 * 17 * 4 * 8",
            "Answer": 1112,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 13 + 18 * 0 * 8 * 5",
            "Answer": 19,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 15 + 3 * 10 * 15 * 11",
            "Answer": 4978,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 1 + 16 * 4 * 18 * 19",
            "Answer": 21902,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 3 + 19 * 11 * 5 * 9",
            "Answer": 9420,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 14 + 11 * 19 * 12 * 2",
            "Answer": 5030,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 4 + 19 * 16 * 5 * 19",
            "Answer": 28899,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 14 + 13 * 3 * 19 * 13",
            "Answer": 9663,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 11 + 19 * 18 * 18 * 11",
            "Answer": 67738,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 17 + 18 * 10 * 19 * 9",
            "Answer": 30816,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 5 + 5 * 3 * 7 * 14",
            "Answer": 1490,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 2 + 16 * 7 * 17 * 2",
            "Answer": 3827,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 15 + 7 * 7 * 10 * 13",
            "Answer": 6400,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 14 + 3 * 14 * 2 * 7",
            "Answer": 604,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 15 + 5 * 4 * 19 * 11",
            "Answer": 4205,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 3 + 14 * 11 * 12 * 14",
            "Answer": 25889,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 14 + 2 * 3 * 13 * 16",
            "Answer": 1266,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 14 + 0 * 17 * 10 * 10",
            "Answer": 26,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 19 + 14 * 11 * 12 * 16",
            "Answer": 29604,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 11 + 19 * 11 * 13 * 12",
            "Answer": 32618,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 13 + 2 * 12 * 4 * 19",
            "Answer": 1837,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 15 + 15 * 17 * 19 * 14",
            "Answer": 67852,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 8 + 13 * 11 * 15 * 9",
            "Answer": 19329,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 3 + 12 * 4 * 13 * 6",
            "Answer": 3758,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 4 + 17 * 11 * 10 * 12",
            "Answer": 22462,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 12 + 11 * 13 * 12 * 13",
            "Answer": 22323,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 11 + 6 * 7 * 7 * 7",
            "Answer": 2085,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 12 + 9 * 13 * 18 * 6",
            "Answer": 12654,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 16 + 7 * 14 * 9 * 8",
            "Answer": 7073,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 18 + 3 * 17 * 4 * 13",
            "Answer": 2673,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 6 + 1 * 2 * 17 * 4",
            "Answer": 151,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 0 + 9 * 16 * 4 * 14",
            "Answer": 8070,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 16 + 11 * 3 * 2 * 10",
            "Answer": 681,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 2 + 1 * 5 * 11 * 12",
            "Answer": 663,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 9 + 19 * 0 * 16 * 18",
            "Answer": 11,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 15 + 12 * 6 * 7 * 7",
            "Answer": 3554,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 2 + 14 * 12 * 12 * 11",
            "Answer": 22186,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 12 + 14 * 14 * 8 * 17",
            "Answer": 26682,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 17 + 6 * 7 * 14 * 15",
            "Answer": 8837,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 5 + 0 * 0 * 6 * 9",
            "Answer": 18,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 13 + 6 * 16 * 17 * 2",
            "Answer": 3286,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 13 + 9 * 11 * 9 * 3",
            "Answer": 2688,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 6 + 8 * 5 * 5 * 0",
            "Answer": 9,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 9 + 3 * 0 * 5 * 1",
            "Answer": 11,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 6 + 9 * 9 * 8 * 12",
            "Answer": 7797,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 7 + 15 * 3 * 4 * 0",
            "Answer": 7,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 8 + 16 * 18 * 14 * 17",
            "Answer": 68560,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 19 + 5 * 10 * 8 * 9",
            "Answer": 3619,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * #"
        }
    ],
    "# * # * # * # + # * #": [
        {
            "Question": "2 * 12 * 11 * 3 + 9 * 2",
            "Answer": 810,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 10 * 15 * 18 + 11 * 16",
            "Answer": 13676,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 4 * 12 * 6 + 13 * 15",
            "Answer": 195,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 6 * 7 * 19 + 1 * 7",
            "Answer": 805,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 8 * 17 * 3 + 7 * 4",
            "Answer": 6556,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 8 * 16 * 16 + 6 * 6",
            "Answer": 6180,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 5 * 10 * 9 + 12 * 12",
            "Answer": 4194,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 8 * 17 * 9 + 6 * 7",
            "Answer": 18402,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 0 * 9 * 14 + 13 * 13",
            "Answer": 169,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 15 * 12 * 16 + 5 * 13",
            "Answer": 8705,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 4 * 8 * 6 + 7 * 17",
            "Answer": 2423,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 5 * 3 * 4 + 13 * 7",
            "Answer": 1051,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 2 * 0 * 2 + 19 * 13",
            "Answer": 247,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 17 * 12 * 7 + 17 * 0",
            "Answer": 7140,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 6 * 6 * 1 + 18 * 7",
            "Answer": 378,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 18 * 12 * 17 + 8 * 0",
            "Answer": 66096,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 7 * 10 * 15 + 17 * 10",
            "Answer": 11720,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 3 * 16 * 11 + 2 * 15",
            "Answer": 10062,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 15 * 0 * 11 + 3 * 9",
            "Answer": 27,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 16 * 12 * 12 + 11 * 8",
            "Answer": 23128,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 13 * 8 * 15 + 2 * 18",
            "Answer": 6276,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 2 * 16 * 18 + 8 * 7",
            "Answer": 56,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 15 * 0 * 17 + 7 * 18",
            "Answer": 126,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 19 * 10 * 16 + 17 * 4",
            "Answer": 68,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 9 * 3 * 0 + 16 * 16",
            "Answer": 256,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 17 * 14 * 3 + 9 * 16",
            "Answer": 6570,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 6 * 15 * 15 + 0 * 15",
            "Answer": 9450,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 1 * 1 * 0 + 3 * 9",
            "Answer": 27,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 5 * 5 * 15 + 9 * 4",
            "Answer": 7161,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 14 * 17 * 8 + 17 * 16",
            "Answer": 13600,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 13 * 19 * 13 + 6 * 5",
            "Answer": 32140,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 3 * 9 * 19 + 5 * 2",
            "Answer": 8218,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 5 * 9 * 18 + 1 * 9",
            "Answer": 1629,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 6 * 10 * 7 + 0 * 0",
            "Answer": 7140,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 8 * 19 * 12 + 11 * 3",
            "Answer": 12801,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 19 * 16 * 0 + 10 * 12",
            "Answer": 120,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 17 * 12 * 7 + 10 * 2",
            "Answer": 1448,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 6 * 14 * 11 + 16 * 13",
            "Answer": 5752,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 11 * 17 * 8 + 14 * 4",
            "Answer": 15016,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 16 * 15 * 18 + 3 * 14",
            "Answer": 21642,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 16 * 15 * 19 + 2 * 18",
            "Answer": 59316,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 19 * 14 * 2 + 7 * 5",
            "Answer": 9079,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 3 * 18 * 19 + 3 * 10",
            "Answer": 9264,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 11 * 1 * 7 + 1 * 0",
            "Answer": 1463,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 15 * 18 * 18 + 7 * 18",
            "Answer": 9846,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 19 * 14 * 0 + 13 * 7",
            "Answer": 91,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 5 * 19 * 0 + 18 * 10",
            "Answer": 180,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 15 * 2 * 3 + 11 * 5",
            "Answer": 1765,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 10 * 15 * 18 + 1 * 13",
            "Answer": 16213,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 1 * 6 * 19 + 18 * 3",
            "Answer": 738,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 13 * 7 * 12 + 10 * 17",
            "Answer": 15458,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 3 * 7 * 10 + 16 * 9",
            "Answer": 3924,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 9 * 7 * 3 + 17 * 7",
            "Answer": 1253,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 11 * 16 * 15 + 16 * 10",
            "Answer": 10720,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 17 * 12 * 11 + 1 * 5",
            "Answer": 6737,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 3 * 2 * 18 + 1 * 9",
            "Answer": 1197,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 11 * 17 * 18 + 15 * 6",
            "Answer": 47214,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 5 * 2 * 2 + 15 * 7",
            "Answer": 485,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 19 * 17 * 15 + 3 * 6",
            "Answer": 48468,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 10 * 1 * 6 + 9 * 16",
            "Answer": 264,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 3 * 12 * 5 + 17 * 12",
            "Answer": 1104,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 19 * 8 * 15 + 1 * 15",
            "Answer": 27375,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 3 * 18 * 5 + 0 * 13",
            "Answer": 810,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 2 * 0 * 5 + 5 * 15",
            "Answer": 75,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 13 * 0 * 19 + 17 * 2",
            "Answer": 34,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 6 * 19 * 8 + 16 * 12",
            "Answer": 17520,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 19 * 6 * 18 + 10 * 0",
            "Answer": 8208,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 14 * 15 * 6 + 0 * 10",
            "Answer": 2520,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 19 * 4 * 6 + 11 * 7",
            "Answer": 6917,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 19 * 10 * 8 + 2 * 8",
            "Answer": 6096,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 12 * 17 * 16 + 5 * 5",
            "Answer": 9817,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 11 * 18 * 15 + 3 * 5",
            "Answer": 38625,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 0 * 0 * 17 + 9 * 17",
            "Answer": 153,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 2 * 2 * 14 + 0 * 3",
            "Answer": 168,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 11 * 2 * 6 + 11 * 15",
            "Answer": 1485,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 3 * 7 * 18 + 10 * 1",
            "Answer": 766,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 13 * 3 * 11 + 19 * 13",
            "Answer": 676,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 9 * 0 * 9 + 17 * 11",
            "Answer": 187,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 13 * 9 * 7 + 3 * 18",
            "Answer": 3330,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 10 * 3 * 19 + 12 * 10",
            "Answer": 7530,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 9 * 10 * 1 + 7 * 6",
            "Answer": 132,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 19 * 17 * 14 + 19 * 17",
            "Answer": 36499,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 17 * 17 * 9 + 16 * 18",
            "Answer": 36702,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 15 * 3 * 18 + 16 * 12",
            "Answer": 6672,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 1 * 10 * 0 + 18 * 11",
            "Answer": 198,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 16 * 6 * 15 + 7 * 16",
            "Answer": 10192,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 6 * 17 * 3 + 3 * 16",
            "Answer": 1272,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 9 * 19 * 9 + 17 * 8",
            "Answer": 12448,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 16 * 2 * 5 + 11 * 18",
            "Answer": 1158,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 6 * 11 * 18 + 2 * 2",
            "Answer": 3568,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 1 * 4 * 5 + 7 * 12",
            "Answer": 444,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 14 * 9 * 17 + 1 * 11",
            "Answer": 19289,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 8 * 1 * 18 + 16 * 7",
            "Answer": 112,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 7 * 2 * 0 + 12 * 2",
            "Answer": 24,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 2 * 3 * 4 + 17 * 5",
            "Answer": 325,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 19 * 15 * 14 + 12 * 10",
            "Answer": 59970,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 15 * 2 * 14 + 0 * 6",
            "Answer": 6300,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 8 * 0 * 10 + 6 * 3",
            "Answer": 18,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 5 * 5 * 5 + 18 * 14",
            "Answer": 377,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 4 * 16 * 16 + 18 * 15",
            "Answer": 18702,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * #"
        }
    ],
    "# + # * # + # * # * #": [
        {
            "Question": "19 + 0 * 9 + 1 * 15 * 6",
            "Answer": 109,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 14 * 19 + 3 * 17 * 10",
            "Answer": 780,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 0 * 7 + 4 * 10 * 4",
            "Answer": 163,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 11 * 6 + 6 * 10 * 17",
            "Answer": 1087,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 4 * 13 + 1 * 1 * 10",
            "Answer": 71,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 18 * 2 + 3 * 9 * 15",
            "Answer": 441,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 19 * 4 + 0 * 18 * 12",
            "Answer": 85,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 14 * 17 + 12 * 19 * 6",
            "Answer": 1613,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 3 * 15 + 8 * 9 * 14",
            "Answer": 1063,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 14 * 1 + 16 * 17 * 16",
            "Answer": 4367,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 14 * 2 + 4 * 18 * 14",
            "Answer": 1039,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 11 * 13 + 2 * 18 * 6",
            "Answer": 371,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 10 * 11 + 1 * 14 * 15",
            "Answer": 335,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 8 * 7 + 12 * 3 * 9",
            "Answer": 387,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 0 * 9 + 10 * 3 * 4",
            "Answer": 127,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 15 * 0 + 10 * 9 * 9",
            "Answer": 824,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 13 * 6 + 2 * 9 * 12",
            "Answer": 305,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 0 * 10 + 8 * 16 * 7",
            "Answer": 906,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 13 * 19 + 11 * 6 * 3",
            "Answer": 454,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 15 * 5 + 2 * 17 * 0",
            "Answer": 75,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 14 * 17 + 10 * 14 * 5",
            "Answer": 954,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 10 * 5 + 4 * 13 * 14",
            "Answer": 791,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 3 * 2 + 19 * 17 * 16",
            "Answer": 5186,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 3 * 14 + 10 * 7 * 4",
            "Answer": 327,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 4 * 2 + 3 * 12 * 6",
            "Answer": 232,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 9 * 3 + 11 * 6 * 5",
            "Answer": 367,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 4 * 15 + 13 * 19 * 5",
            "Answer": 1311,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 14 * 14 + 10 * 10 * 5",
            "Answer": 706,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 8 * 13 + 19 * 18 * 12",
            "Answer": 4226,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 8 * 18 + 19 * 1 * 4",
            "Answer": 235,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 17 * 11 + 13 * 8 * 9",
            "Answer": 1141,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 10 * 7 + 5 * 6 * 18",
            "Answer": 629,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 15 * 8 + 1 * 8 * 2",
            "Answer": 139,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 19 * 14 + 9 * 19 * 11",
            "Answer": 2157,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 11 * 5 + 11 * 13 * 6",
            "Answer": 923,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 15 * 9 + 14 * 3 * 4",
            "Answer": 311,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 13 * 12 + 9 * 0 * 8",
            "Answer": 172,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 10 * 16 + 8 * 16 * 2",
            "Answer": 418,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 0 * 12 + 8 * 6 * 14",
            "Answer": 679,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 8 * 8 + 11 * 13 * 15",
            "Answer": 2214,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 19 * 6 + 11 * 11 * 10",
            "Answer": 1326,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 12 * 10 + 5 * 17 * 13",
            "Answer": 1244,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 18 * 12 + 4 * 11 * 6",
            "Answer": 496,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 11 * 14 + 11 * 10 * 11",
            "Answer": 1376,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 18 * 8 + 2 * 11 * 9",
            "Answer": 355,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 8 * 14 + 17 * 17 * 0",
            "Answer": 114,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 10 * 4 + 19 * 11 * 19",
            "Answer": 4013,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 14 * 2 + 11 * 18 * 7",
            "Answer": 1420,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 9 * 15 + 3 * 7 * 7",
            "Answer": 294,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 16 * 8 + 4 * 18 * 3",
            "Answer": 353,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 5 * 19 + 10 * 5 * 14",
            "Answer": 805,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 5 * 12 + 8 * 7 * 14",
            "Answer": 859,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 1 * 4 + 17 * 9 * 15",
            "Answer": 2306,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 16 * 8 + 12 * 2 * 17",
            "Answer": 543,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 16 * 10 + 3 * 10 * 16",
            "Answer": 659,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 5 * 13 + 1 * 0 * 13",
            "Answer": 81,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 9 * 16 + 5 * 17 * 13",
            "Answer": 1250,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 18 * 0 + 6 * 6 * 1",
            "Answer": 37,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 13 * 12 + 3 * 12 * 3",
            "Answer": 271,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 13 * 9 + 10 * 7 * 7",
            "Answer": 613,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 1 * 17 + 17 * 14 * 12",
            "Answer": 2877,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 1 * 14 + 13 * 18 * 2",
            "Answer": 498,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 3 * 13 + 13 * 3 * 19",
            "Answer": 784,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 6 * 1 + 9 * 10 * 13",
            "Answer": 1187,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 8 * 4 + 8 * 18 * 14",
            "Answer": 2053,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 17 * 2 + 17 * 13 * 5",
            "Answer": 1147,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 7 * 2 + 5 * 12 * 8",
            "Answer": 495,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 0 * 8 + 6 * 3 * 14",
            "Answer": 258,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 6 * 10 + 1 * 8 * 17",
            "Answer": 202,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 4 * 11 + 15 * 3 * 19",
            "Answer": 900,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 5 * 17 + 12 * 15 * 8",
            "Answer": 1541,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 7 * 14 + 3 * 8 * 17",
            "Answer": 517,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 9 * 3 + 6 * 10 * 6",
            "Answer": 395,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 19 * 0 + 14 * 7 * 19",
            "Answer": 1866,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 12 * 0 + 10 * 8 * 1",
            "Answer": 81,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 1 * 17 + 7 * 10 * 11",
            "Answer": 795,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 10 * 19 + 11 * 0 * 6",
            "Answer": 209,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 0 * 11 + 1 * 14 * 7",
            "Answer": 111,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 16 * 4 + 17 * 9 * 14",
            "Answer": 2220,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 9 * 2 + 6 * 9 * 13",
            "Answer": 724,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 2 * 6 + 16 * 15 * 1",
            "Answer": 265,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 10 * 0 + 10 * 0 * 13",
            "Answer": 12,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 4 * 14 + 15 * 3 * 7",
            "Answer": 387,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 3 * 12 + 13 * 7 * 14",
            "Answer": 1326,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 12 * 15 + 2 * 16 * 16",
            "Answer": 703,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 9 * 13 + 9 * 18 * 9",
            "Answer": 1588,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 15 * 12 + 15 * 19 * 4",
            "Answer": 1335,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 3 * 9 + 15 * 18 * 8",
            "Answer": 2195,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 16 * 11 + 5 * 12 * 9",
            "Answer": 727,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 2 * 16 + 12 * 1 * 14",
            "Answer": 209,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 6 * 16 + 18 * 17 * 5",
            "Answer": 1642,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 4 * 10 + 18 * 15 * 16",
            "Answer": 4364,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 9 * 11 + 0 * 0 * 0",
            "Answer": 103,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 12 * 6 + 4 * 7 * 17",
            "Answer": 560,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 1 * 18 + 13 * 1 * 13",
            "Answer": 200,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 11 * 18 + 16 * 16 * 2",
            "Answer": 712,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 1 * 9 + 2 * 10 * 13",
            "Answer": 282,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 11 * 18 + 15 * 5 * 1",
            "Answer": 292,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 6 * 19 + 1 * 3 * 7",
            "Answer": 139,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 0 * 8 + 1 * 14 * 4",
            "Answer": 63,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * #"
        }
    ],
    "# * # + # + # * # * #": [
        {
            "Question": "13 * 11 + 9 + 3 * 13 * 1",
            "Answer": 191,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 8 + 18 + 3 * 7 * 15",
            "Answer": 381,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 13 + 11 + 3 * 19 * 3",
            "Answer": 351,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 11 + 7 + 18 * 19 * 5",
            "Answer": 1761,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 1 + 6 + 9 * 19 * 8",
            "Answer": 1374,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 2 + 12 + 15 * 13 * 15",
            "Answer": 2947,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 3 + 0 + 18 * 7 * 2",
            "Answer": 303,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 14 + 7 + 19 * 1 * 15",
            "Answer": 488,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 4 + 4 + 0 * 8 * 0",
            "Answer": 60,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 13 + 7 + 6 * 7 * 8",
            "Answer": 369,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 9 + 7 + 11 * 2 * 13",
            "Answer": 311,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 12 + 16 + 11 * 10 * 11",
            "Answer": 1310,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 11 + 19 + 16 * 9 * 18",
            "Answer": 2611,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 10 + 14 + 16 * 5 * 7",
            "Answer": 644,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 18 + 3 + 10 * 2 * 0",
            "Answer": 93,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 2 + 7 + 19 * 8 * 17",
            "Answer": 2625,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 13 + 4 + 10 * 1 * 6",
            "Answer": 259,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 1 + 9 + 1 * 6 * 17",
            "Answer": 130,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 14 + 9 + 3 * 18 * 1",
            "Answer": 189,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 19 + 13 + 16 * 7 * 18",
            "Answer": 2200,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 16 + 12 + 4 * 10 * 9",
            "Answer": 564,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 14 + 1 + 7 * 5 * 8",
            "Answer": 309,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 3 + 17 + 19 * 1 * 10",
            "Answer": 246,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 12 + 17 + 0 * 12 * 4",
            "Answer": 173,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 8 + 19 + 16 * 19 * 17",
            "Answer": 5235,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 9 + 17 + 3 * 4 * 19",
            "Answer": 362,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 2 + 10 + 8 * 17 * 2",
            "Answer": 304,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 18 + 4 + 8 * 16 * 3",
            "Answer": 514,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 3 + 0 + 0 * 17 * 12",
            "Answer": 21,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 0 + 10 + 19 * 16 * 13",
            "Answer": 3962,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 6 + 10 + 11 * 18 * 11",
            "Answer": 2278,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 14 + 15 + 10 * 1 * 3",
            "Answer": 185,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 6 + 18 + 5 * 5 * 2",
            "Answer": 164,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 13 + 12 + 1 * 4 * 18",
            "Answer": 175,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 2 + 10 + 13 * 12 * 15",
            "Answer": 2384,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 14 + 8 + 3 * 11 * 13",
            "Answer": 535,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 2 + 12 + 9 * 0 * 6",
            "Answer": 32,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 15 + 9 + 8 * 6 * 8",
            "Answer": 483,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 6 + 1 + 7 * 18 * 12",
            "Answer": 1561,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 4 + 7 + 12 * 1 * 17",
            "Answer": 271,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 9 + 6 + 14 * 12 * 0",
            "Answer": 150,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 6 + 7 + 10 * 3 * 6",
            "Answer": 289,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 10 + 17 + 19 * 14 * 11",
            "Answer": 3073,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 2 + 4 + 14 * 7 * 17",
            "Answer": 1694,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 1 + 6 + 7 * 3 * 2",
            "Answer": 67,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 10 + 5 + 9 * 6 * 14",
            "Answer": 851,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 0 + 11 + 3 * 15 * 0",
            "Answer": 11,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 16 + 3 + 6 * 2 * 9",
            "Answer": 191,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 14 + 3 + 12 * 0 * 11",
            "Answer": 185,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 9 + 5 + 15 * 6 * 16",
            "Answer": 1490,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 17 + 15 + 5 * 15 * 9",
            "Answer": 792,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 0 + 9 + 13 * 11 * 0",
            "Answer": 9,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 17 + 16 + 17 * 16 * 3",
            "Answer": 1036,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 16 + 12 + 1 * 0 * 8",
            "Answer": 12,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 10 + 4 + 12 * 8 * 13",
            "Answer": 1412,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 15 + 5 + 16 * 3 * 3",
            "Answer": 299,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 6 + 6 + 18 * 11 * 18",
            "Answer": 3612,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 6 + 19 + 10 * 8 * 12",
            "Answer": 991,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 14 + 19 + 2 * 12 * 1",
            "Answer": 197,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 4 + 8 + 15 * 16 * 11",
            "Answer": 2704,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 10 + 5 + 11 * 17 * 13",
            "Answer": 2536,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 17 + 19 + 3 * 18 * 16",
            "Answer": 1087,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 1 + 6 + 13 * 19 * 1",
            "Answer": 269,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 15 + 11 + 16 * 7 * 6",
            "Answer": 968,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 6 + 14 + 0 * 12 * 1",
            "Answer": 14,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 8 + 1 + 19 * 3 * 15",
            "Answer": 960,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 14 + 6 + 0 * 7 * 11",
            "Answer": 48,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 6 + 16 + 11 * 16 * 4",
            "Answer": 792,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 15 + 7 + 16 * 18 * 0",
            "Answer": 232,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 18 + 5 + 9 * 7 * 10",
            "Answer": 977,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 15 + 10 + 9 * 15 * 5",
            "Answer": 940,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 7 + 12 + 0 * 11 * 0",
            "Answer": 131,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 12 + 11 + 19 * 10 * 10",
            "Answer": 1923,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 12 + 14 + 13 * 2 * 4",
            "Answer": 226,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 18 + 14 + 2 * 3 * 11",
            "Answer": 386,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 16 + 11 + 19 * 10 * 11",
            "Answer": 2261,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 8 + 8 + 7 * 7 * 11",
            "Answer": 691,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 12 + 16 + 5 * 18 * 18",
            "Answer": 1816,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 13 + 4 + 17 * 16 * 2",
            "Answer": 795,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 18 + 7 + 18 * 5 * 0",
            "Answer": 97,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 9 + 5 + 11 * 2 * 13",
            "Answer": 426,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 3 + 4 + 13 * 6 * 12",
            "Answer": 973,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 0 + 9 + 13 * 14 * 14",
            "Answer": 2557,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 4 + 8 + 8 * 18 * 10",
            "Answer": 1460,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 0 + 14 + 1 * 12 * 17",
            "Answer": 218,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 10 + 7 + 6 * 5 * 0",
            "Answer": 107,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 4 + 7 + 17 * 17 * 16",
            "Answer": 4691,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 2 + 19 + 10 * 17 * 14",
            "Answer": 2421,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 5 + 7 + 2 * 0 * 15",
            "Answer": 87,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 6 + 6 + 12 * 10 * 15",
            "Answer": 1896,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 2 + 19 + 7 * 0 * 6",
            "Answer": 51,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 17 + 18 + 8 * 8 * 3",
            "Answer": 448,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 15 + 11 + 8 * 2 * 17",
            "Answer": 403,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 14 + 4 + 2 * 9 * 14",
            "Answer": 522,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 7 + 18 + 16 * 8 * 11",
            "Answer": 1489,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 16 + 1 + 3 * 15 * 10",
            "Answer": 595,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 18 + 11 + 7 * 15 * 7",
            "Answer": 818,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 3 + 16 + 9 * 10 * 8",
            "Answer": 736,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 14 + 7 + 7 * 5 * 0",
            "Answer": 161,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 11 + 2 + 2 * 4 * 14",
            "Answer": 312,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * #"
        }
    ],
    "# + # + # * # * # + #": [
        {
            "Question": "16 + 4 + 18 * 5 * 0 + 15",
            "Answer": 35,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 16 + 16 * 15 * 13 + 7",
            "Answer": 3158,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 0 + 8 * 8 * 4 + 19",
            "Answer": 277,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 2 + 6 * 5 * 12 + 15",
            "Answer": 390,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 10 + 16 * 2 * 3 + 6",
            "Answer": 120,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 10 + 7 * 0 * 0 + 18",
            "Answer": 38,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 17 + 4 * 12 * 16 + 16",
            "Answer": 820,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 14 + 13 * 4 * 8 + 15",
            "Answer": 462,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 8 + 12 * 16 * 10 + 17",
            "Answer": 1954,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 16 + 13 * 6 * 12 + 1",
            "Answer": 970,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 3 + 4 * 14 * 0 + 15",
            "Answer": 26,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 15 + 13 * 10 * 15 + 11",
            "Answer": 1985,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 2 + 0 * 0 * 2 + 18",
            "Answer": 27,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 15 + 4 * 16 * 6 + 2",
            "Answer": 404,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 1 + 2 * 4 * 14 + 8",
            "Answer": 137,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 7 + 4 * 13 * 2 + 9",
            "Answer": 138,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 7 + 9 * 12 * 0 + 2",
            "Answer": 22,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 10 + 10 * 9 * 1 + 12",
            "Answer": 112,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 7 + 10 * 6 * 12 + 5",
            "Answer": 732,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 1 + 6 * 6 * 0 + 3",
            "Answer": 10,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 5 + 8 * 14 * 11 + 14",
            "Answer": 1253,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 2 + 13 * 7 * 15 + 13",
            "Answer": 1392,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 12 + 1 * 7 * 4 + 8",
            "Answer": 58,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 2 + 1 * 14 * 19 + 10",
            "Answer": 296,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 14 + 11 * 2 * 2 + 2",
            "Answer": 61,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 2 + 11 * 17 * 16 + 5",
            "Answer": 3018,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 14 + 7 * 19 * 17 + 15",
            "Answer": 2299,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 19 + 6 * 19 * 12 + 18",
            "Answer": 1409,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 5 + 7 * 19 * 10 + 13",
            "Answer": 1361,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 10 + 2 * 15 * 18 + 17",
            "Answer": 575,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 11 + 2 * 11 * 16 + 15",
            "Answer": 386,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 5 + 15 * 5 * 1 + 15",
            "Answer": 96,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 0 + 18 * 2 * 5 + 9",
            "Answer": 205,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 15 + 1 * 14 * 13 + 18",
            "Answer": 229,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 3 + 0 * 2 * 13 + 12",
            "Answer": 31,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 9 + 18 * 5 * 10 + 16",
            "Answer": 926,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 12 + 12 * 7 * 14 + 1",
            "Answer": 1199,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 14 + 11 * 19 * 4 + 16",
            "Answer": 875,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 8 + 4 * 15 * 0 + 11",
            "Answer": 32,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 0 + 10 * 9 * 11 + 6",
            "Answer": 1005,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 12 + 2 * 19 * 11 + 15",
            "Answer": 462,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 4 + 5 * 16 * 15 + 2",
            "Answer": 1211,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 19 + 2 * 13 * 17 + 12",
            "Answer": 473,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 10 + 12 * 0 * 11 + 4",
            "Answer": 17,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 7 + 11 * 17 * 13 + 16",
            "Answer": 2460,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 6 + 8 * 8 * 15 + 11",
            "Answer": 994,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 1 + 10 * 6 * 16 + 15",
            "Answer": 993,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 3 + 10 * 6 * 3 + 19",
            "Answer": 208,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 13 + 1 * 6 * 15 + 1",
            "Answer": 111,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 17 + 1 * 17 * 7 + 3",
            "Answer": 146,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 9 + 11 * 7 * 15 + 6",
            "Answer": 1181,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 6 + 13 * 0 * 7 + 16",
            "Answer": 33,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 16 + 0 * 8 * 1 + 9",
            "Answer": 35,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 8 + 3 * 3 * 14 + 19",
            "Answer": 159,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 18 + 3 * 18 * 12 + 17",
            "Answer": 692,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 5 + 18 * 13 * 19 + 18",
            "Answer": 4473,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 5 + 9 * 16 * 3 + 3",
            "Answer": 455,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 12 + 3 * 3 * 4 + 9",
            "Answer": 62,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 3 + 1 * 15 * 18 + 1",
            "Answer": 284,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 17 + 1 * 18 * 9 + 11",
            "Answer": 207,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 14 + 7 * 14 * 7 + 7",
            "Answer": 713,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 12 + 8 * 5 * 0 + 13",
            "Answer": 30,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 12 + 18 * 2 * 15 + 15",
            "Answer": 586,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 15 + 1 * 14 * 19 + 7",
            "Answer": 296,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 12 + 14 * 16 * 7 + 19",
            "Answer": 1613,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 2 + 6 * 2 * 15 + 1",
            "Answer": 192,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 0 + 19 * 14 * 11 + 1",
            "Answer": 2942,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 18 + 2 * 14 * 1 + 11",
            "Answer": 62,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 14 + 15 * 16 * 14 + 17",
            "Answer": 3408,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 19 + 16 * 18 * 5 + 5",
            "Answer": 1464,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 15 + 13 * 5 * 14 + 0",
            "Answer": 925,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 17 + 15 * 13 * 6 + 6",
            "Answer": 1208,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 0 + 17 * 9 * 8 + 13",
            "Answer": 1256,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 14 + 3 * 11 * 3 + 15",
            "Answer": 129,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 4 + 18 * 12 * 12 + 9",
            "Answer": 2607,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 7 + 9 * 18 * 9 + 0",
            "Answer": 1466,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 14 + 10 * 14 * 8 + 17",
            "Answer": 1153,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 9 + 10 * 19 * 14 + 11",
            "Answer": 2684,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 11 + 7 * 8 * 4 + 1",
            "Answer": 255,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 13 + 15 * 8 * 4 + 3",
            "Answer": 507,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 2 + 1 * 5 * 7 + 6",
            "Answer": 54,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 16 + 5 * 18 * 16 + 3",
            "Answer": 1466,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 5 + 13 * 4 * 12 + 9",
            "Answer": 641,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 7 + 2 * 5 * 4 + 17",
            "Answer": 65,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 13 + 13 * 4 * 18 + 3",
            "Answer": 968,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 12 + 8 * 10 * 13 + 5",
            "Answer": 1063,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 2 + 5 * 13 * 9 + 9",
            "Answer": 599,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 3 + 1 * 2 * 9 + 17",
            "Answer": 41,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 3 + 11 * 19 * 19 + 3",
            "Answer": 3994,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 0 + 14 * 2 * 2 + 14",
            "Answer": 81,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 18 + 2 * 0 * 3 + 7",
            "Answer": 42,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 0 + 6 * 13 * 1 + 14",
            "Answer": 103,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 9 + 5 * 7 * 7 + 12",
            "Answer": 283,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 0 + 2 * 15 * 3 + 2",
            "Answer": 92,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 15 + 9 * 0 * 0 + 8",
            "Answer": 32,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 14 + 8 * 5 * 18 + 4",
            "Answer": 740,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 3 + 6 * 14 * 16 + 11",
            "Answer": 1374,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 9 + 18 * 0 * 16 + 18",
            "Answer": 33,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 4 + 10 * 3 * 4 + 15",
            "Answer": 158,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 14 + 19 * 6 * 0 + 7",
            "Answer": 31,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + #"
        }
    ],
    "# * # * # * # * # * #": [
        {
            "Question": "17 * 18 * 1 * 16 * 17 * 10",
            "Answer": 832320,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 2 * 6 * 12 * 19 * 17",
            "Answer": 744192,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 16 * 18 * 15 * 11 * 14",
            "Answer": 1330560,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 14 * 1 * 18 * 6 * 2",
            "Answer": 48384,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 3 * 8 * 17 * 8 * 12",
            "Answer": 274176,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 4 * 11 * 14 * 2 * 17",
            "Answer": 376992,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 4 * 14 * 19 * 12 * 12",
            "Answer": 1838592,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 12 * 10 * 14 * 5 * 18",
            "Answer": 1058400,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 4 * 5 * 0 * 6 * 5",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 4 * 1 * 17 * 19 * 7",
            "Answer": 36176,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 9 * 3 * 8 * 13 * 18",
            "Answer": 657072,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 4 * 2 * 12 * 9 * 13",
            "Answer": 202176,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 5 * 18 * 19 * 14 * 16",
            "Answer": 1915200,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 10 * 18 * 14 * 3 * 0",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 3 * 16 * 12 * 1 * 1",
            "Answer": 6912,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 18 * 19 * 4 * 3 * 5",
            "Answer": 389880,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 14 * 16 * 2 * 14 * 4",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 0 * 10 * 7 * 6 * 13",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 6 * 5 * 6 * 14 * 12",
            "Answer": 362880,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 8 * 2 * 1 * 6 * 12",
            "Answer": 8064,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 8 * 7 * 7 * 5 * 13",
            "Answer": 331240,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 9 * 7 * 10 * 12 * 1",
            "Answer": 15120,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 9 * 7 * 8 * 3 * 3",
            "Answer": 45360,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 11 * 12 * 13 * 19 * 9",
            "Answer": 3227796,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 9 * 12 * 17 * 18 * 0",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 8 * 11 * 5 * 19 * 4",
            "Answer": 501600,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 10 * 14 * 16 * 13 * 3",
            "Answer": 1397760,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 12 * 10 * 0 * 2 * 5",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 12 * 17 * 2 * 5 * 8",
            "Answer": 195840,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 19 * 16 * 0 * 2 * 11",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 15 * 15 * 7 * 1 * 3",
            "Answer": 61425,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 11 * 5 * 4 * 16 * 19",
            "Answer": 1003200,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 9 * 16 * 4 * 6 * 8",
            "Answer": 497664,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 7 * 12 * 8 * 14 * 12",
            "Answer": 564480,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 10 * 14 * 10 * 18 * 19",
            "Answer": 2394000,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 4 * 19 * 7 * 8 * 7",
            "Answer": 506464,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 1 * 0 * 7 * 18 * 11",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 17 * 0 * 1 * 3 * 17",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 14 * 14 * 19 * 7 * 18",
            "Answer": 8915256,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 18 * 4 * 2 * 8 * 1",
            "Answer": 11520,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 11 * 17 * 6 * 18 * 15",
            "Answer": 2120580,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 5 * 3 * 0 * 16 * 1",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 4 * 4 * 13 * 3 * 11",
            "Answer": 54912,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 0 * 2 * 17 * 11 * 5",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 11 * 6 * 15 * 10 * 9",
            "Answer": 801900,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 6 * 3 * 10 * 6 * 1",
            "Answer": 6480,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 3 * 4 * 14 * 7 * 8",
            "Answer": 56448,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 8 * 18 * 3 * 4 * 12",
            "Answer": 145152,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 10 * 6 * 10 * 19 * 12",
            "Answer": 2325600,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 13 * 6 * 7 * 8 * 15",
            "Answer": 786240,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 14 * 14 * 15 * 3 * 3",
            "Answer": 105840,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 17 * 1 * 19 * 0 * 11",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 13 * 8 * 19 * 8 * 7",
            "Answer": 1770496,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 13 * 18 * 7 * 10 * 8",
            "Answer": 1965600,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 19 * 12 * 15 * 0 * 14",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 13 * 8 * 7 * 19 * 1",
            "Answer": 55328,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 13 * 1 * 13 * 6 * 3",
            "Answer": 15210,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 15 * 0 * 2 * 6 * 11",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 18 * 13 * 19 * 19 * 19",
            "Answer": 11235042,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 10 * 14 * 10 * 10 * 13",
            "Answer": 2366000,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 9 * 17 * 7 * 9 * 9",
            "Answer": 607257,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 9 * 19 * 10 * 5 * 7",
            "Answer": 299250,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 4 * 12 * 2 * 5 * 2",
            "Answer": 18240,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 9 * 8 * 19 * 14 * 8",
            "Answer": 2451456,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 8 * 19 * 9 * 1 * 18",
            "Answer": 172368,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 16 * 4 * 18 * 1 * 8",
            "Answer": 73728,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 8 * 18 * 13 * 15 * 0",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 0 * 3 * 12 * 4 * 10",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 4 * 4 * 12 * 0 * 11",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 0 * 17 * 7 * 13 * 11",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 1 * 11 * 3 * 18 * 18",
            "Answer": 128304,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 10 * 7 * 12 * 6 * 1",
            "Answer": 75600,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 12 * 18 * 2 * 8 * 13",
            "Answer": 494208,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 7 * 3 * 10 * 14 * 13",
            "Answer": 726180,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 12 * 9 * 18 * 2 * 16",
            "Answer": 435456,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 10 * 6 * 10 * 16 * 7",
            "Answer": 1209600,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 16 * 3 * 4 * 5 * 0",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 10 * 11 * 12 * 11 * 16",
            "Answer": 3484800,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 10 * 19 * 0 * 6 * 4",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 3 * 18 * 3 * 7 * 11",
            "Answer": 74844,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 4 * 8 * 17 * 8 * 9",
            "Answer": 470016,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 0 * 1 * 12 * 7 * 0",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 5 * 14 * 0 * 19 * 0",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 11 * 4 * 5 * 10 * 12",
            "Answer": 264000,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 16 * 0 * 3 * 19 * 13",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 13 * 17 * 15 * 2 * 17",
            "Answer": 901680,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 19 * 14 * 2 * 8 * 1",
            "Answer": 12768,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 5 * 13 * 19 * 8 * 17",
            "Answer": 3191240,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 3 * 13 * 7 * 3 * 10",
            "Answer": 16380,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 19 * 4 * 10 * 18 * 17",
            "Answer": 930240,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 8 * 2 * 14 * 8 * 17",
            "Answer": 121856,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 12 * 3 * 8 * 0 * 14",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 19 * 6 * 0 * 9 * 15",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 16 * 8 * 4 * 2 * 3",
            "Answer": 55296,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 19 * 7 * 13 * 18 * 4",
            "Answer": 248976,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 8 * 16 * 10 * 16 * 19",
            "Answer": 2723840,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 7 * 15 * 17 * 5 * 14",
            "Answer": 999600,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 17 * 1 * 16 * 16 * 16",
            "Answer": 696320,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 4 * 14 * 19 * 1 * 15",
            "Answer": 95760,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 12 * 3 * 1 * 8 * 16",
            "Answer": 82944,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * #"
        }
    ],
    "# + # * # * # * # * #": [
        {
            "Question": "19 + 12 * 18 * 0 * 1 * 16",
            "Answer": 19,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 11 * 6 * 12 * 6 * 6",
            "Answer": 28527,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 12 * 5 * 9 * 10 * 2",
            "Answer": 10809,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 10 * 5 * 2 * 0 * 18",
            "Answer": 4,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 7 * 3 * 3 * 6 * 15",
            "Answer": 5683,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 4 * 19 * 4 * 9 * 10",
            "Answer": 27365,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 7 * 11 * 19 * 14 * 8",
            "Answer": 163861,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 10 * 15 * 4 * 10 * 12",
            "Answer": 72005,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 10 * 1 * 15 * 4 * 18",
            "Answer": 10806,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 7 * 12 * 6 * 9 * 10",
            "Answer": 45371,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 13 * 18 * 14 * 17 * 9",
            "Answer": 501239,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 16 * 1 * 14 * 8 * 11",
            "Answer": 19731,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 16 * 17 * 3 * 1 * 18",
            "Answer": 14692,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 18 * 2 * 8 * 14 * 13",
            "Answer": 52428,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 17 * 3 * 18 * 6 * 3",
            "Answer": 16537,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 16 * 16 * 0 * 5 * 5",
            "Answer": 15,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 4 * 1 * 9 * 9 * 13",
            "Answer": 4214,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 13 * 2 * 5 * 15 * 2",
            "Answer": 3900,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 5 * 12 * 19 * 15 * 16",
            "Answer": 273614,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 7 * 11 * 0 * 18 * 14",
            "Answer": 7,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 7 * 7 * 9 * 6 * 3",
            "Answer": 7944,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 18 * 3 * 13 * 14 * 4",
            "Answer": 39313,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 5 * 3 * 18 * 4 * 0",
            "Answer": 10,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 7 * 12 * 11 * 2 * 7",
            "Answer": 12949,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 16 * 2 * 5 * 8 * 14",
            "Answer": 17926,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 12 * 19 * 15 * 6 * 0",
            "Answer": 13,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 5 * 18 * 6 * 18 * 13",
            "Answer": 126361,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 10 * 3 * 4 * 8 * 7",
            "Answer": 6727,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 10 * 9 * 6 * 10 * 18",
            "Answer": 97208,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 15 * 12 * 18 * 16 * 8",
            "Answer": 414734,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 16 * 13 * 15 * 11 * 18",
            "Answer": 617769,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 9 * 8 * 5 * 5 * 4",
            "Answer": 7219,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 2 * 8 * 16 * 19 * 11",
            "Answer": 53521,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 1 * 0 * 12 * 1 * 7",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 14 * 19 * 13 * 3 * 18",
            "Answer": 186749,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 12 * 15 * 1 * 9 * 5",
            "Answer": 8107,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 0 * 3 * 11 * 8 * 14",
            "Answer": 19,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 6 * 10 * 9 * 12 * 14",
            "Answer": 90732,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 9 * 2 * 9 * 3 * 19",
            "Answer": 9238,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 11 * 18 * 1 * 11 * 18",
            "Answer": 39219,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 1 * 0 * 17 * 9 * 13",
            "Answer": 8,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 6 * 18 * 13 * 8 * 13",
            "Answer": 146029,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 14 * 17 * 17 * 7 * 14",
            "Answer": 396517,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 8 * 15 * 13 * 16 * 8",
            "Answer": 199695,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 18 * 6 * 18 * 18 * 0",
            "Answer": 10,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 2 * 6 * 13 * 16 * 3",
            "Answer": 7491,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 19 * 1 * 2 * 9 * 8",
            "Answer": 2737,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 12 * 6 * 12 * 12 * 5",
            "Answer": 51852,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 9 * 19 * 6 * 1 * 8",
            "Answer": 8216,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 4 * 5 * 6 * 11 * 7",
            "Answer": 9249,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 3 * 9 * 9 * 10 * 19",
            "Answer": 46184,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 15 * 11 * 14 * 2 * 8",
            "Answer": 36977,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 12 * 15 * 11 * 13 * 13",
            "Answer": 334631,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 10 * 2 * 10 * 4 * 14",
            "Answer": 11216,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 19 * 7 * 12 * 6 * 6",
            "Answer": 57466,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 17 * 5 * 12 * 8 * 8",
            "Answer": 65294,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 4 * 11 * 13 * 17 * 9",
            "Answer": 87534,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 12 * 15 * 12 * 12 * 17",
            "Answer": 440655,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 6 * 11 * 10 * 14 * 9",
            "Answer": 83165,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 14 * 15 * 9 * 17 * 14",
            "Answer": 449830,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 5 * 1 * 14 * 1 * 3",
            "Answer": 220,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 9 * 16 * 15 * 10 * 16",
            "Answer": 345603,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 9 * 3 * 15 * 9 * 9",
            "Answer": 32817,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 7 * 11 * 5 * 3 * 2",
            "Answer": 2322,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 18 * 5 * 13 * 1 * 3",
            "Answer": 3512,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 4 * 11 * 13 * 15 * 12",
            "Answer": 102978,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 19 * 19 * 16 * 9 * 5",
            "Answer": 259926,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 11 * 8 * 11 * 13 * 12",
            "Answer": 151025,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 8 * 16 * 4 * 4 * 5",
            "Answer": 10240,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 0 * 12 * 18 * 17 * 10",
            "Answer": 17,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 16 * 0 * 6 * 10 * 9",
            "Answer": 13,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 3 * 14 * 8 * 16 * 16",
            "Answer": 86019,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 14 * 10 * 1 * 16 * 10",
            "Answer": 22419,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 7 * 9 * 17 * 16 * 2",
            "Answer": 34278,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 16 * 9 * 14 * 1 * 7",
            "Answer": 14125,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 8 * 9 * 2 * 4 * 10",
            "Answer": 5771,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 11 * 0 * 8 * 4 * 1",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 11 * 4 * 8 * 14 * 15",
            "Answer": 73922,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 9 * 12 * 15 * 10 * 5",
            "Answer": 81008,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 13 * 9 * 2 * 14 * 10",
            "Answer": 32761,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 0 * 9 * 15 * 17 * 1",
            "Answer": 14,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 16 * 14 * 16 * 9 * 10",
            "Answer": 322575,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 1 * 11 * 0 * 15 * 15",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 16 * 10 * 8 * 4 * 18",
            "Answer": 92160,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 12 * 11 * 11 * 6 * 10",
            "Answer": 87130,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 6 * 15 * 6 * 15 * 7",
            "Answer": 56713,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 9 * 9 * 19 * 10 * 0",
            "Answer": 10,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 5 * 10 * 15 * 9 * 14",
            "Answer": 94508,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 11 * 11 * 6 * 10 * 1",
            "Answer": 7260,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 14 * 16 * 7 * 18 * 5",
            "Answer": 141121,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 4 * 16 * 0 * 14 * 6",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 15 * 1 * 7 * 2 * 19",
            "Answer": 3999,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 5 * 19 * 5 * 0 * 11",
            "Answer": 14,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 15 * 7 * 8 * 18 * 8",
            "Answer": 120968,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 11 * 14 * 3 * 16 * 4",
            "Answer": 29582,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 16 * 8 * 11 * 13 * 11",
            "Answer": 201354,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 2 * 4 * 2 * 13 * 14",
            "Answer": 2916,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 17 * 0 * 2 * 7 * 17",
            "Answer": 15,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 15 * 18 * 6 * 18 * 1",
            "Answer": 29174,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 4 * 2 * 7 * 18 * 4",
            "Answer": 4043,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * #"
        }
    ],
    "# + # + # + # + # + #": [
        {
            "Question": "16 + 18 + 1 + 19 + 17 + 0",
            "Answer": 71,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 12 + 12 + 17 + 6 + 1",
            "Answer": 50,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 4 + 12 + 10 + 8 + 9",
            "Answer": 51,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 4 + 5 + 15 + 19 + 9",
            "Answer": 66,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 5 + 9 + 16 + 8 + 7",
            "Answer": 57,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 13 + 19 + 12 + 14 + 18",
            "Answer": 78,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 4 + 9 + 7 + 14 + 12",
            "Answer": 57,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 9 + 17 + 11 + 18 + 14",
            "Answer": 74,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 18 + 2 + 14 + 8 + 17",
            "Answer": 75,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 0 + 3 + 1 + 12 + 15",
            "Answer": 38,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 16 + 12 + 0 + 0 + 10",
            "Answer": 54,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 15 + 7 + 6 + 11 + 12",
            "Answer": 64,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 6 + 3 + 7 + 8 + 12",
            "Answer": 55,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 19 + 4 + 1 + 10 + 14",
            "Answer": 50,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 7 + 7 + 5 + 12 + 5",
            "Answer": 51,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 10 + 13 + 13 + 1 + 14",
            "Answer": 62,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 7 + 18 + 15 + 5 + 0",
            "Answer": 58,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 5 + 3 + 5 + 12 + 4",
            "Answer": 33,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 5 + 1 + 10 + 0 + 14",
            "Answer": 48,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 12 + 9 + 6 + 10 + 15",
            "Answer": 66,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 9 + 3 + 9 + 12 + 16",
            "Answer": 60,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 3 + 5 + 9 + 7 + 3",
            "Answer": 43,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 7 + 10 + 18 + 13 + 6",
            "Answer": 73,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 2 + 7 + 5 + 10 + 13",
            "Answer": 38,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 8 + 13 + 9 + 3 + 2",
            "Answer": 39,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 4 + 14 + 7 + 14 + 12",
            "Answer": 67,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 1 + 14 + 11 + 15 + 14",
            "Answer": 61,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 3 + 7 + 0 + 19 + 1",
            "Answer": 37,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 11 + 3 + 14 + 11 + 16",
            "Answer": 72,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 9 + 16 + 12 + 17 + 14",
            "Answer": 85,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 19 + 4 + 6 + 14 + 11",
            "Answer": 71,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 0 + 18 + 0 + 17 + 0",
            "Answer": 49,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 19 + 15 + 15 + 7 + 10",
            "Answer": 72,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 2 + 1 + 7 + 9 + 8",
            "Answer": 34,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 0 + 6 + 11 + 4 + 6",
            "Answer": 46,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 0 + 0 + 16 + 8 + 2",
            "Answer": 39,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 19 + 3 + 18 + 10 + 7",
            "Answer": 57,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 19 + 14 + 17 + 19 + 1",
            "Answer": 89,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 2 + 0 + 10 + 3 + 0",
            "Answer": 26,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 18 + 10 + 0 + 0 + 19",
            "Answer": 51,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 8 + 19 + 9 + 5 + 13",
            "Answer": 58,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 12 + 12 + 0 + 13 + 5",
            "Answer": 50,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 19 + 18 + 8 + 9 + 7",
            "Answer": 65,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 3 + 10 + 2 + 3 + 5",
            "Answer": 26,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 9 + 4 + 16 + 4 + 9",
            "Answer": 43,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 16 + 4 + 12 + 1 + 11",
            "Answer": 52,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 4 + 6 + 1 + 9 + 10",
            "Answer": 36,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 5 + 17 + 5 + 19 + 9",
            "Answer": 68,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 18 + 11 + 7 + 11 + 6",
            "Answer": 62,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 14 + 18 + 19 + 0 + 12",
            "Answer": 69,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 9 + 2 + 6 + 7 + 3",
            "Answer": 27,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 2 + 2 + 13 + 9 + 2",
            "Answer": 31,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 19 + 2 + 0 + 7 + 16",
            "Answer": 58,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 11 + 16 + 19 + 17 + 5",
            "Answer": 86,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 11 + 19 + 18 + 11 + 8",
            "Answer": 85,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 13 + 16 + 17 + 2 + 14",
            "Answer": 77,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 6 + 5 + 13 + 13 + 19",
            "Answer": 57,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 5 + 13 + 0 + 3 + 10",
            "Answer": 40,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 0 + 2 + 2 + 3 + 9",
            "Answer": 18,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 7 + 11 + 14 + 10 + 15",
            "Answer": 74,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 13 + 5 + 4 + 17 + 7",
            "Answer": 50,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 11 + 13 + 13 + 8 + 4",
            "Answer": 64,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 3 + 14 + 15 + 1 + 0",
            "Answer": 47,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 15 + 13 + 10 + 18 + 8",
            "Answer": 75,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 10 + 8 + 5 + 14 + 3",
            "Answer": 46,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 13 + 4 + 9 + 13 + 0",
            "Answer": 51,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 6 + 10 + 6 + 10 + 11",
            "Answer": 53,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 10 + 1 + 17 + 5 + 3",
            "Answer": 42,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 0 + 2 + 17 + 11 + 13",
            "Answer": 50,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 16 + 5 + 17 + 8 + 11",
            "Answer": 63,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 15 + 15 + 7 + 16 + 8",
            "Answer": 79,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 6 + 6 + 11 + 2 + 4",
            "Answer": 31,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 13 + 7 + 16 + 13 + 5",
            "Answer": 67,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 2 + 11 + 14 + 9 + 0",
            "Answer": 40,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 7 + 13 + 11 + 6 + 14",
            "Answer": 56,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 17 + 15 + 0 + 17 + 5",
            "Answer": 64,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 14 + 13 + 5 + 7 + 4",
            "Answer": 53,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 3 + 14 + 8 + 10 + 13",
            "Answer": 67,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 14 + 19 + 5 + 10 + 3",
            "Answer": 59,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 7 + 1 + 3 + 9 + 4",
            "Answer": 39,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 15 + 16 + 12 + 4 + 11",
            "Answer": 75,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 3 + 14 + 9 + 17 + 1",
            "Answer": 49,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 9 + 0 + 5 + 18 + 15",
            "Answer": 47,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 6 + 14 + 8 + 15 + 0",
            "Answer": 43,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 17 + 1 + 12 + 5 + 1",
            "Answer": 40,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 10 + 18 + 4 + 2 + 19",
            "Answer": 60,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 12 + 11 + 16 + 17 + 10",
            "Answer": 76,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 6 + 6 + 14 + 6 + 16",
            "Answer": 63,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 6 + 7 + 10 + 1 + 10",
            "Answer": 48,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 1 + 0 + 14 + 4 + 13",
            "Answer": 44,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 1 + 0 + 4 + 18 + 19",
            "Answer": 57,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 13 + 2 + 15 + 16 + 18",
            "Answer": 82,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 2 + 0 + 17 + 4 + 15",
            "Answer": 46,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 5 + 19 + 12 + 14 + 1",
            "Answer": 58,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 11 + 12 + 16 + 16 + 14",
            "Answer": 74,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 14 + 5 + 17 + 7 + 17",
            "Answer": 66,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 7 + 11 + 14 + 3 + 9",
            "Answer": 48,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 12 + 16 + 6 + 17 + 10",
            "Answer": 70,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 13 + 11 + 14 + 14 + 12",
            "Answer": 64,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 18 + 19 + 14 + 8 + 3",
            "Answer": 64,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + #"
        }
    ],
    "# + # * # * # + # * #": [
        {
            "Question": "12 + 4 * 3 * 2 + 8 * 2",
            "Answer": 52,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 10 * 14 * 10 + 14 * 19",
            "Answer": 1666,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 9 * 18 * 12 + 15 * 15",
            "Answer": 2188,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 4 * 7 * 15 + 3 * 1",
            "Answer": 428,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 7 * 9 * 18 + 13 * 5",
            "Answer": 1204,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 19 * 0 * 0 + 14 * 5",
            "Answer": 79,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 3 * 5 * 8 + 8 * 5",
            "Answer": 167,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 17 * 0 * 19 + 5 * 4",
            "Answer": 29,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 2 * 9 * 3 + 0 * 9",
            "Answer": 72,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 12 * 2 * 17 + 3 * 13",
            "Answer": 451,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 3 * 2 * 0 + 5 * 14",
            "Answer": 74,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 1 * 18 * 6 + 17 * 19",
            "Answer": 435,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 3 * 7 * 17 + 17 * 0",
            "Answer": 374,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 1 * 11 * 11 + 19 * 5",
            "Answer": 234,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 19 * 12 * 7 + 9 * 12",
            "Answer": 1722,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 17 * 6 * 19 + 19 * 16",
            "Answer": 2261,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 2 * 12 * 7 + 7 * 2",
            "Answer": 191,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 11 * 12 * 4 + 10 * 3",
            "Answer": 562,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 12 * 13 * 1 + 15 * 3",
            "Answer": 220,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 6 * 7 * 18 + 15 * 9",
            "Answer": 905,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 5 * 0 * 10 + 19 * 16",
            "Answer": 321,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 7 * 7 * 0 + 7 * 13",
            "Answer": 109,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 4 * 13 * 4 + 19 * 5",
            "Answer": 304,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 7 * 6 * 5 + 2 * 1",
            "Answer": 217,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 19 * 12 * 3 + 12 * 4",
            "Answer": 749,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 11 * 16 * 6 + 9 * 15",
            "Answer": 1205,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 11 * 11 * 19 + 0 * 14",
            "Answer": 2299,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 13 * 10 * 19 + 13 * 2",
            "Answer": 2497,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 19 * 19 * 0 + 11 * 0",
            "Answer": 12,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 1 * 15 * 5 + 4 * 5",
            "Answer": 102,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 9 * 1 * 15 + 15 * 19",
            "Answer": 432,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 5 * 16 * 5 + 6 * 5",
            "Answer": 431,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 12 * 16 * 12 + 11 * 5",
            "Answer": 2366,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 5 * 17 * 11 + 10 * 18",
            "Answer": 1129,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 10 * 9 * 12 + 0 * 2",
            "Answer": 1092,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 4 * 18 * 9 + 17 * 6",
            "Answer": 765,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 18 * 2 * 8 + 6 * 11",
            "Answer": 362,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 10 * 2 * 3 + 5 * 18",
            "Answer": 155,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 12 * 1 * 9 + 5 * 7",
            "Answer": 153,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 2 * 9 * 6 + 12 * 15",
            "Answer": 291,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 5 * 17 * 17 + 6 * 3",
            "Answer": 1465,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 11 * 1 * 7 + 4 * 7",
            "Answer": 115,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 1 * 17 * 8 + 2 * 1",
            "Answer": 150,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 19 * 18 * 13 + 18 * 2",
            "Answer": 4491,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 10 * 1 * 2 + 16 * 19",
            "Answer": 339,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 9 * 18 * 10 + 13 * 5",
            "Answer": 1693,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 6 * 5 * 16 + 5 * 17",
            "Answer": 568,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 16 * 13 * 3 + 1 * 6",
            "Answer": 646,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 15 * 16 * 19 + 10 * 6",
            "Answer": 4623,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 4 * 17 * 4 + 1 * 10",
            "Answer": 299,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 15 * 17 * 11 + 5 * 3",
            "Answer": 2823,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 10 * 6 * 7 + 0 * 7",
            "Answer": 422,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 4 * 3 * 3 + 16 * 15",
            "Answer": 278,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 13 * 17 * 15 + 14 * 0",
            "Answer": 3334,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 10 * 16 * 18 + 6 * 19",
            "Answer": 3004,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 19 * 12 * 2 + 5 * 4",
            "Answer": 493,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 10 * 6 * 0 + 5 * 9",
            "Answer": 62,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 4 * 13 * 15 + 10 * 10",
            "Answer": 880,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 10 * 13 * 16 + 3 * 6",
            "Answer": 2108,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 15 * 7 * 18 + 14 * 15",
            "Answer": 2112,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 14 * 13 * 8 + 2 * 17",
            "Answer": 1494,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 19 * 16 * 0 + 1 * 11",
            "Answer": 16,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 1 * 3 * 9 + 3 * 2",
            "Answer": 41,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 13 * 16 * 16 + 16 * 10",
            "Answer": 3494,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 6 * 19 * 19 + 6 * 15",
            "Answer": 2274,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 1 * 5 * 17 + 11 * 18",
            "Answer": 296,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 13 * 2 * 17 + 7 * 10",
            "Answer": 529,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 7 * 0 * 18 + 8 * 19",
            "Answer": 154,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 0 * 5 * 8 + 12 * 15",
            "Answer": 194,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 5 * 0 * 1 + 4 * 14",
            "Answer": 63,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 8 * 11 * 10 + 7 * 8",
            "Answer": 938,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 2 * 11 * 12 + 12 * 12",
            "Answer": 425,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 5 * 0 * 15 + 2 * 6",
            "Answer": 21,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 5 * 14 * 6 + 13 * 12",
            "Answer": 594,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 8 * 3 * 3 + 19 * 0",
            "Answer": 75,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 19 * 3 * 14 + 19 * 17",
            "Answer": 1139,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 5 * 5 * 12 + 10 * 16",
            "Answer": 478,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 5 * 19 * 11 + 13 * 10",
            "Answer": 1187,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 7 * 4 * 18 + 18 * 16",
            "Answer": 811,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 11 * 15 * 8 + 14 * 9",
            "Answer": 1458,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 9 * 6 * 10 + 0 * 13",
            "Answer": 547,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 2 * 2 * 4 + 15 * 0",
            "Answer": 19,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 12 * 15 * 15 + 8 * 17",
            "Answer": 2840,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 8 * 18 * 9 + 11 * 10",
            "Answer": 1413,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 11 * 16 * 14 + 9 * 1",
            "Answer": 2473,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 0 * 18 * 9 + 2 * 12",
            "Answer": 43,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 12 * 13 * 3 + 17 * 13",
            "Answer": 691,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 15 * 6 * 1 + 9 * 5",
            "Answer": 138,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 8 * 0 * 16 + 12 * 14",
            "Answer": 185,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 10 * 3 * 19 + 14 * 13",
            "Answer": 757,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 17 * 14 * 0 + 9 * 7",
            "Answer": 68,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 12 * 7 * 1 + 4 * 19",
            "Answer": 179,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 15 * 15 * 11 + 2 * 19",
            "Answer": 2530,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 10 * 10 * 19 + 2 * 9",
            "Answer": 1922,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 2 * 3 * 9 + 9 * 13",
            "Answer": 171,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 15 * 5 * 10 + 3 * 17",
            "Answer": 815,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 15 * 4 * 9 + 15 * 3",
            "Answer": 597,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 18 * 13 * 19 + 15 * 3",
            "Answer": 4503,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 5 * 5 * 1 + 6 * 0",
            "Answer": 37,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 11 * 12 * 6 + 14 * 18",
            "Answer": 1059,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * #"
        }
    ],
    "# * # + # * # * # * #": [
        {
            "Question": "19 * 8 + 19 * 0 * 15 * 7",
            "Answer": 152,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 9 + 16 * 18 * 11 * 3",
            "Answer": 9666,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 2 + 8 * 12 * 8 * 6",
            "Answer": 4608,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 10 + 1 * 18 * 8 * 10",
            "Answer": 1450,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 10 + 17 * 4 * 4 * 1",
            "Answer": 322,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 7 + 11 * 15 * 7 * 14",
            "Answer": 16240,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 0 + 15 * 19 * 8 * 13",
            "Answer": 29640,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 11 + 9 * 9 * 9 * 10",
            "Answer": 7378,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 14 + 15 * 0 * 9 * 1",
            "Answer": 168,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 6 + 7 * 18 * 17 * 5",
            "Answer": 10782,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 17 + 11 * 6 * 0 * 2",
            "Answer": 204,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 13 + 18 * 0 * 17 * 16",
            "Answer": 39,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 11 + 13 * 19 * 15 * 19",
            "Answer": 70483,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 8 + 9 * 3 * 17 * 4",
            "Answer": 1852,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 17 + 2 * 14 * 4 * 19",
            "Answer": 2315,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 5 + 0 * 15 * 4 * 16",
            "Answer": 65,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 9 + 2 * 17 * 7 * 11",
            "Answer": 2681,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 3 + 3 * 1 * 14 * 16",
            "Answer": 693,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 4 + 16 * 7 * 12 * 12",
            "Answer": 16192,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 4 + 2 * 19 * 10 * 9",
            "Answer": 3440,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 19 + 6 * 4 * 19 * 0",
            "Answer": 57,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 8 + 18 * 10 * 4 * 0",
            "Answer": 48,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 18 + 0 * 0 * 14 * 14",
            "Answer": 342,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 10 + 3 * 9 * 3 * 19",
            "Answer": 1679,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 6 + 14 * 10 * 9 * 1",
            "Answer": 1296,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 5 + 15 * 8 * 7 * 2",
            "Answer": 1720,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 19 + 17 * 4 * 8 * 6",
            "Answer": 3587,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 18 + 13 * 14 * 9 * 1",
            "Answer": 1800,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 3 + 8 * 6 * 0 * 12",
            "Answer": 39,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 1 + 18 * 5 * 15 * 13",
            "Answer": 17557,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 17 + 5 * 19 * 15 * 16",
            "Answer": 22987,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 10 + 9 * 18 * 6 * 19",
            "Answer": 18508,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 3 + 10 * 11 * 2 * 9",
            "Answer": 2028,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 12 + 15 * 18 * 1 * 1",
            "Answer": 378,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 5 + 2 * 3 * 18 * 19",
            "Answer": 2112,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 10 + 15 * 17 * 12 * 18",
            "Answer": 55170,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 19 + 15 * 16 * 13 * 14",
            "Answer": 43946,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 0 + 13 * 1 * 10 * 8",
            "Answer": 1040,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 18 + 0 * 4 * 2 * 1",
            "Answer": 198,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 16 + 12 * 14 * 3 * 18",
            "Answer": 9136,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 18 + 10 * 4 * 9 * 16",
            "Answer": 5778,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 16 + 3 * 14 * 18 * 0",
            "Answer": 176,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 14 + 3 * 3 * 5 * 17",
            "Answer": 989,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 7 + 4 * 12 * 17 * 11",
            "Answer": 9102,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 11 + 17 * 10 * 2 * 13",
            "Answer": 4519,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 11 + 8 * 14 * 12 * 8",
            "Answer": 10939,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 12 + 16 * 5 * 7 * 11",
            "Answer": 6364,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 16 + 3 * 2 * 18 * 0",
            "Answer": 256,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 6 + 0 * 9 * 19 * 17",
            "Answer": 66,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 13 + 0 * 5 * 11 * 2",
            "Answer": 52,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 12 + 12 * 15 * 9 * 1",
            "Answer": 1848,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 0 + 17 * 5 * 0 * 19",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 1 + 15 * 11 * 19 * 13",
            "Answer": 40772,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 4 + 15 * 10 * 0 * 17",
            "Answer": 4,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 4 + 15 * 15 * 2 * 12",
            "Answer": 5432,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 3 + 16 * 15 * 1 * 4",
            "Answer": 984,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 1 + 17 * 1 * 2 * 19",
            "Answer": 655,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 7 + 14 * 18 * 13 * 14",
            "Answer": 45906,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 14 + 4 * 5 * 18 * 15",
            "Answer": 5610,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 4 + 17 * 4 * 1 * 19",
            "Answer": 1300,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 19 + 7 * 4 * 8 * 9",
            "Answer": 2339,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 3 + 0 * 18 * 9 * 15",
            "Answer": 12,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 18 + 3 * 8 * 10 * 12",
            "Answer": 2934,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 5 + 5 * 6 * 17 * 19",
            "Answer": 9785,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 1 + 10 * 9 * 7 * 18",
            "Answer": 11341,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 12 + 19 * 2 * 9 * 0",
            "Answer": 132,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 15 + 16 * 3 * 0 * 1",
            "Answer": 135,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 16 + 14 * 5 * 13 * 18",
            "Answer": 16540,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 10 + 19 * 1 * 3 * 6",
            "Answer": 452,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 11 + 5 * 5 * 10 * 8",
            "Answer": 2110,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 11 + 0 * 11 * 13 * 9",
            "Answer": 198,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 17 + 16 * 10 * 7 * 17",
            "Answer": 19210,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 3 + 5 * 0 * 15 * 3",
            "Answer": 30,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 6 + 8 * 3 * 12 * 15",
            "Answer": 4344,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 8 + 4 * 3 * 1 * 10",
            "Answer": 248,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 17 + 15 * 8 * 17 * 18",
            "Answer": 36873,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 16 + 10 * 18 * 11 * 12",
            "Answer": 24016,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 10 + 8 * 11 * 4 * 10",
            "Answer": 3660,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 5 + 1 * 15 * 3 * 15",
            "Answer": 730,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 19 + 9 * 6 * 1 * 7",
            "Answer": 473,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 18 + 5 * 2 * 15 * 18",
            "Answer": 2700,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 17 + 4 * 19 * 9 * 7",
            "Answer": 4839,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 17 + 13 * 13 * 3 * 11",
            "Answer": 5611,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 3 + 10 * 10 * 18 * 3",
            "Answer": 5406,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 9 + 15 * 4 * 5 * 13",
            "Answer": 3981,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 7 + 6 * 11 * 11 * 8",
            "Answer": 5829,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 18 + 18 * 17 * 16 * 6",
            "Answer": 29430,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 5 + 12 * 19 * 7 * 14",
            "Answer": 22404,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 15 + 0 * 2 * 10 * 4",
            "Answer": 255,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 13 + 17 * 17 * 4 * 6",
            "Answer": 7157,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 10 + 7 * 19 * 18 * 11",
            "Answer": 26464,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 6 + 12 * 9 * 15 * 10",
            "Answer": 16260,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 2 + 18 * 12 * 5 * 1",
            "Answer": 1088,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 2 + 0 * 1 * 11 * 14",
            "Answer": 20,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 14 + 6 * 6 * 6 * 7",
            "Answer": 1750,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 18 + 13 * 7 * 3 * 11",
            "Answer": 3021,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 10 + 18 * 11 * 9 * 18",
            "Answer": 32116,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 10 + 5 * 10 * 10 * 13",
            "Answer": 6550,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 0 + 19 * 14 * 1 * 17",
            "Answer": 4522,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 15 + 3 * 8 * 12 * 11",
            "Answer": 3228,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * #"
        }
    ],
    "# + # + # + # * # * #": [
        {
            "Question": "5 + 19 + 4 + 14 * 18 * 15",
            "Answer": 3808,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 12 + 11 + 15 * 8 * 16",
            "Answer": 1961,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 11 + 4 + 14 * 17 * 15",
            "Answer": 3591,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 8 + 6 + 0 * 13 * 13",
            "Answer": 32,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 12 + 8 + 9 * 7 * 19",
            "Answer": 1231,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 5 + 12 + 8 * 17 * 15",
            "Answer": 2076,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 2 + 17 + 16 * 19 * 19",
            "Answer": 5805,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 16 + 7 + 13 * 10 * 1",
            "Answer": 158,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 9 + 3 + 16 * 15 * 7",
            "Answer": 1707,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 11 + 3 + 7 * 0 * 1",
            "Answer": 27,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 5 + 2 + 19 * 16 * 7",
            "Answer": 2144,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 18 + 12 + 7 * 19 * 18",
            "Answer": 2426,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 12 + 3 + 3 * 0 * 11",
            "Answer": 25,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 8 + 15 + 9 * 1 * 15",
            "Answer": 174,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 3 + 6 + 14 * 0 * 13",
            "Answer": 16,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 6 + 12 + 12 * 15 * 12",
            "Answer": 2187,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 16 + 14 + 17 * 4 * 19",
            "Answer": 1341,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 12 + 0 + 18 * 19 * 16",
            "Answer": 5491,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 12 + 6 + 17 * 4 * 9",
            "Answer": 647,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 18 + 13 + 17 * 18 * 14",
            "Answer": 4319,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 6 + 4 + 16 * 3 * 4",
            "Answer": 213,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 1 + 13 + 9 * 16 * 14",
            "Answer": 2045,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 9 + 7 + 16 * 17 * 7",
            "Answer": 1932,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 10 + 18 + 10 * 6 * 0",
            "Answer": 47,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 12 + 19 + 1 * 2 * 19",
            "Answer": 85,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 14 + 7 + 16 * 11 * 13",
            "Answer": 2316,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 0 + 7 + 6 * 13 * 8",
            "Answer": 650,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 17 + 15 + 6 * 16 * 12",
            "Answer": 1195,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 9 + 17 + 18 * 13 * 16",
            "Answer": 3778,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 3 + 10 + 4 * 1 * 11",
            "Answer": 61,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 11 + 8 + 9 * 12 * 0",
            "Answer": 30,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 15 + 11 + 15 * 15 * 10",
            "Answer": 2290,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 9 + 17 + 12 * 11 * 12",
            "Answer": 1615,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 3 + 14 + 7 * 4 * 1",
            "Answer": 55,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 8 + 14 + 5 * 1 * 1",
            "Answer": 40,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 8 + 3 + 15 * 18 * 13",
            "Answer": 3539,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 11 + 0 + 5 * 15 * 2",
            "Answer": 175,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 8 + 18 + 10 * 2 * 13",
            "Answer": 300,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 1 + 12 + 13 * 16 * 13",
            "Answer": 2731,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 16 + 3 + 17 * 13 * 7",
            "Answer": 1577,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 9 + 18 + 15 * 10 * 19",
            "Answer": 2894,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 3 + 4 + 16 * 2 * 17",
            "Answer": 559,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 15 + 2 + 14 * 12 * 11",
            "Answer": 1867,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 19 + 12 + 8 * 0 * 7",
            "Answer": 31,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 6 + 1 + 6 * 11 * 4",
            "Answer": 285,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 11 + 1 + 8 * 16 * 19",
            "Answer": 2463,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 19 + 17 + 14 * 17 * 10",
            "Answer": 2418,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 6 + 2 + 2 * 12 * 13",
            "Answer": 336,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 19 + 18 + 6 * 6 * 9",
            "Answer": 380,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 11 + 16 + 5 * 12 * 18",
            "Answer": 1109,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 18 + 9 + 4 * 0 * 18",
            "Answer": 39,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 10 + 9 + 13 * 18 * 15",
            "Answer": 3543,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 0 + 5 + 5 * 15 * 8",
            "Answer": 610,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 5 + 7 + 18 * 11 * 12",
            "Answer": 2399,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 3 + 6 + 1 * 19 * 18",
            "Answer": 366,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 10 + 11 + 16 * 0 * 4",
            "Answer": 29,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 9 + 17 + 9 * 5 * 7",
            "Answer": 347,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 3 + 17 + 7 * 5 * 15",
            "Answer": 561,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 10 + 11 + 8 * 6 * 6",
            "Answer": 315,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 9 + 16 + 5 * 12 * 15",
            "Answer": 941,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 19 + 0 + 5 * 12 * 1",
            "Answer": 82,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 7 + 16 + 7 * 8 * 4",
            "Answer": 257,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 11 + 16 + 5 * 11 * 14",
            "Answer": 804,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 12 + 19 + 10 * 3 * 9",
            "Answer": 318,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 14 + 0 + 8 * 8 * 7",
            "Answer": 466,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 4 + 10 + 7 * 14 * 16",
            "Answer": 1585,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 12 + 5 + 11 * 6 * 19",
            "Answer": 1281,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 8 + 11 + 13 * 2 * 5",
            "Answer": 167,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 0 + 5 + 10 * 0 * 18",
            "Answer": 24,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 10 + 0 + 19 * 15 * 16",
            "Answer": 4583,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 15 + 11 + 14 * 16 * 8",
            "Answer": 1827,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 14 + 18 + 18 * 6 * 5",
            "Answer": 589,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 5 + 6 + 8 * 6 * 4",
            "Answer": 211,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 5 + 11 + 0 * 12 * 0",
            "Answer": 28,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 4 + 0 + 11 * 13 * 3",
            "Answer": 443,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 16 + 14 + 1 * 9 * 1",
            "Answer": 52,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 0 + 9 + 5 * 1 * 9",
            "Answer": 56,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 11 + 19 + 14 * 9 * 9",
            "Answer": 1167,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 10 + 14 + 5 * 14 * 4",
            "Answer": 310,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 13 + 6 + 4 * 17 * 10",
            "Answer": 712,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 16 + 4 + 18 * 16 * 3",
            "Answer": 889,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 0 + 19 + 16 * 15 * 6",
            "Answer": 1473,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 6 + 11 + 15 * 2 * 12",
            "Answer": 383,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 8 + 11 + 12 * 12 * 15",
            "Answer": 2181,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 6 + 6 + 12 * 13 * 14",
            "Answer": 2214,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 19 + 5 + 4 * 9 * 11",
            "Answer": 433,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 10 + 11 + 5 * 18 * 4",
            "Answer": 388,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 15 + 1 + 7 * 0 * 4",
            "Answer": 19,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 3 + 5 + 16 * 0 * 14",
            "Answer": 18,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 13 + 9 + 4 * 1 * 11",
            "Answer": 83,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 13 + 14 + 15 * 5 * 16",
            "Answer": 1246,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 7 + 16 + 18 * 8 * 6",
            "Answer": 899,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 6 + 8 + 7 * 8 * 8",
            "Answer": 462,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 16 + 7 + 6 * 7 * 12",
            "Answer": 535,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 9 + 7 + 10 * 0 * 2",
            "Answer": 18,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 16 + 11 + 16 * 8 * 5",
            "Answer": 671,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 17 + 2 + 12 * 5 * 2",
            "Answer": 158,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 15 + 6 + 6 * 8 * 16",
            "Answer": 803,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 17 + 19 + 15 * 1 * 7",
            "Answer": 157,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 2 + 14 + 15 * 16 * 8",
            "Answer": 1955,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * #"
        }
    ],
    "# + # * # * # + # + #": [
        {
            "Question": "17 + 1 * 2 * 14 + 9 + 10",
            "Answer": 64,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 10 * 7 * 17 + 1 + 12",
            "Answer": 1207,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 13 * 11 * 6 + 8 + 14",
            "Answer": 887,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 16 * 18 * 17 + 4 + 4",
            "Answer": 4904,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 1 * 0 * 0 + 18 + 10",
            "Answer": 47,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 19 * 15 * 13 + 3 + 17",
            "Answer": 3734,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 10 * 19 * 6 + 12 + 15",
            "Answer": 1181,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 12 * 8 * 2 + 4 + 17",
            "Answer": 231,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 15 * 0 * 16 + 9 + 10",
            "Answer": 32,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 5 * 13 * 18 + 15 + 18",
            "Answer": 1216,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 8 * 10 * 0 + 8 + 8",
            "Answer": 27,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 8 * 7 * 13 + 14 + 10",
            "Answer": 763,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 18 * 18 * 15 + 1 + 15",
            "Answer": 4891,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 6 * 14 * 8 + 19 + 13",
            "Answer": 710,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 4 * 8 * 19 + 13 + 13",
            "Answer": 651,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 12 * 19 * 16 + 11 + 14",
            "Answer": 3683,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 13 * 11 * 14 + 15 + 3",
            "Answer": 2039,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 16 * 17 * 3 + 12 + 7",
            "Answer": 840,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 1 * 9 * 16 + 3 + 2",
            "Answer": 151,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 0 * 6 * 10 + 19 + 9",
            "Answer": 37,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 8 * 1 * 19 + 14 + 14",
            "Answer": 190,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 1 * 17 * 17 + 10 + 17",
            "Answer": 333,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 18 * 14 * 2 + 12 + 19",
            "Answer": 544,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 0 * 13 * 8 + 16 + 19",
            "Answer": 44,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 9 * 18 * 19 + 3 + 11",
            "Answer": 3103,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 9 * 16 * 10 + 4 + 14",
            "Answer": 1472,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 13 * 17 * 17 + 16 + 7",
            "Answer": 3781,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 8 * 6 * 6 + 6 + 11",
            "Answer": 310,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 17 * 3 * 7 + 17 + 3",
            "Answer": 382,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 3 * 7 * 19 + 11 + 0",
            "Answer": 414,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 11 * 16 * 4 + 1 + 12",
            "Answer": 726,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 8 * 7 * 14 + 10 + 3",
            "Answer": 797,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 10 * 12 * 10 + 14 + 15",
            "Answer": 1237,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 1 * 1 * 19 + 4 + 8",
            "Answer": 41,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 14 * 5 * 0 + 8 + 0",
            "Answer": 9,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 0 * 15 * 0 + 6 + 14",
            "Answer": 36,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 19 * 6 * 15 + 17 + 18",
            "Answer": 1752,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 7 * 10 * 12 + 7 + 13",
            "Answer": 861,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 15 * 1 * 0 + 18 + 8",
            "Answer": 36,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 13 * 16 * 15 + 0 + 3",
            "Answer": 3127,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 8 * 15 * 12 + 14 + 18",
            "Answer": 1472,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 15 * 12 * 6 + 15 + 3",
            "Answer": 1109,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 17 * 9 * 15 + 15 + 6",
            "Answer": 2317,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 3 * 0 * 7 + 13 + 8",
            "Answer": 35,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 9 * 19 * 11 + 10 + 18",
            "Answer": 1924,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 16 * 3 * 13 + 6 + 18",
            "Answer": 651,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 18 * 3 * 12 + 6 + 18",
            "Answer": 674,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 4 * 4 * 1 + 14 + 8",
            "Answer": 51,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 5 * 15 * 8 + 4 + 10",
            "Answer": 628,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 0 * 14 * 6 + 5 + 12",
            "Answer": 17,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 4 * 10 * 12 + 5 + 8",
            "Answer": 506,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 15 * 19 * 2 + 16 + 5",
            "Answer": 601,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 17 * 8 * 3 + 16 + 10",
            "Answer": 451,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 8 * 8 * 14 + 9 + 15",
            "Answer": 939,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 8 * 10 * 5 + 18 + 12",
            "Answer": 441,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 7 * 7 * 4 + 10 + 8",
            "Answer": 226,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 6 * 14 * 9 + 5 + 9",
            "Answer": 779,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 13 * 3 * 3 + 9 + 18",
            "Answer": 155,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 8 * 1 * 7 + 12 + 6",
            "Answer": 79,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 6 * 8 * 8 + 8 + 7",
            "Answer": 414,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 15 * 19 * 3 + 15 + 7",
            "Answer": 881,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 7 * 18 * 13 + 1 + 0",
            "Answer": 1652,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 16 * 11 * 5 + 9 + 17",
            "Answer": 919,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 0 * 7 * 13 + 7 + 13",
            "Answer": 27,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 14 * 6 * 5 + 3 + 5",
            "Answer": 432,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 2 * 11 * 6 + 10 + 14",
            "Answer": 166,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 19 * 1 * 10 + 15 + 3",
            "Answer": 218,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 18 * 9 * 2 + 16 + 16",
            "Answer": 370,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 1 * 2 * 8 + 10 + 15",
            "Answer": 43,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 13 * 12 * 14 + 14 + 4",
            "Answer": 2206,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 18 * 8 * 4 + 16 + 8",
            "Answer": 615,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 11 * 1 * 9 + 18 + 19",
            "Answer": 137,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 2 * 19 * 16 + 16 + 8",
            "Answer": 634,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 17 * 10 * 16 + 19 + 5",
            "Answer": 2755,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 11 * 12 * 10 + 17 + 7",
            "Answer": 1358,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 14 * 1 * 5 + 19 + 0",
            "Answer": 101,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 14 * 7 * 11 + 6 + 13",
            "Answer": 1106,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 3 * 12 * 16 + 16 + 12",
            "Answer": 605,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 1 * 7 * 13 + 15 + 3",
            "Answer": 110,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 5 * 12 * 12 + 8 + 11",
            "Answer": 756,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 14 * 16 * 2 + 6 + 11",
            "Answer": 467,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 13 * 10 * 9 + 11 + 17",
            "Answer": 1212,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 19 * 4 * 9 + 5 + 16",
            "Answer": 719,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 13 * 0 * 2 + 15 + 13",
            "Answer": 43,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 5 * 19 * 8 + 5 + 10",
            "Answer": 793,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 9 * 12 * 15 + 14 + 14",
            "Answer": 1649,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 18 * 4 * 14 + 0 + 3",
            "Answer": 1030,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 2 * 8 * 12 + 19 + 7",
            "Answer": 227,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 9 * 11 * 6 + 12 + 5",
            "Answer": 611,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 0 * 8 * 18 + 8 + 4",
            "Answer": 19,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 9 * 4 * 13 + 19 + 13",
            "Answer": 502,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 11 * 10 * 9 + 0 + 11",
            "Answer": 1014,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 11 * 2 * 0 + 12 + 16",
            "Answer": 44,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 10 * 4 * 13 + 15 + 19",
            "Answer": 562,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 3 * 7 * 6 + 10 + 8",
            "Answer": 148,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 18 * 18 * 0 + 2 + 8",
            "Answer": 18,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 1 * 13 * 15 + 2 + 19",
            "Answer": 216,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 12 * 15 * 2 + 18 + 14",
            "Answer": 392,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 11 * 16 * 6 + 5 + 12",
            "Answer": 1080,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 9 * 15 * 2 + 2 + 4",
            "Answer": 277,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + #"
        }
    ],
    "# * # + # + # + # + #": [
        {
            "Question": "18 * 11 + 17 + 16 + 3 + 7",
            "Answer": 241,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 12 + 10 + 6 + 2 + 18",
            "Answer": 204,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 12 + 17 + 6 + 16 + 16",
            "Answer": 127,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 13 + 19 + 6 + 17 + 8",
            "Answer": 50,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 7 + 10 + 15 + 9 + 0",
            "Answer": 167,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 14 + 18 + 6 + 7 + 0",
            "Answer": 59,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 2 + 3 + 15 + 3 + 16",
            "Answer": 53,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 9 + 19 + 14 + 19 + 19",
            "Answer": 80,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 9 + 7 + 16 + 9 + 15",
            "Answer": 56,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 19 + 19 + 6 + 10 + 14",
            "Answer": 353,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 12 + 0 + 5 + 0 + 1",
            "Answer": 234,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 0 + 15 + 6 + 8 + 1",
            "Answer": 30,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 11 + 9 + 13 + 1 + 3",
            "Answer": 92,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 12 + 8 + 11 + 18 + 9",
            "Answer": 58,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 18 + 13 + 13 + 14 + 17",
            "Answer": 255,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 10 + 13 + 17 + 2 + 3",
            "Answer": 45,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 6 + 7 + 10 + 0 + 2",
            "Answer": 19,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 1 + 13 + 6 + 16 + 15",
            "Answer": 51,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 11 + 15 + 9 + 17 + 10",
            "Answer": 172,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 1 + 19 + 7 + 9 + 7",
            "Answer": 46,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 3 + 9 + 12 + 10 + 0",
            "Answer": 76,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 9 + 1 + 11 + 0 + 11",
            "Answer": 131,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 8 + 15 + 2 + 8 + 7",
            "Answer": 56,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 16 + 4 + 4 + 1 + 16",
            "Answer": 41,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 9 + 14 + 13 + 16 + 8",
            "Answer": 123,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 6 + 11 + 2 + 6 + 12",
            "Answer": 103,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 16 + 6 + 11 + 7 + 16",
            "Answer": 312,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 16 + 11 + 16 + 2 + 13",
            "Answer": 298,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 1 + 7 + 8 + 14 + 3",
            "Answer": 34,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 3 + 13 + 10 + 1 + 14",
            "Answer": 68,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 17 + 1 + 16 + 10 + 8",
            "Answer": 103,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 15 + 18 + 2 + 11 + 11",
            "Answer": 207,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 15 + 10 + 15 + 1 + 2",
            "Answer": 163,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 18 + 15 + 12 + 7 + 17",
            "Answer": 375,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 12 + 9 + 6 + 14 + 6",
            "Answer": 143,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 10 + 11 + 5 + 0 + 7",
            "Answer": 23,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 8 + 5 + 17 + 2 + 14",
            "Answer": 158,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 3 + 19 + 7 + 17 + 6",
            "Answer": 79,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 10 + 0 + 8 + 3 + 4",
            "Answer": 85,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 8 + 7 + 13 + 0 + 6",
            "Answer": 66,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 12 + 7 + 1 + 5 + 14",
            "Answer": 231,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 11 + 13 + 14 + 19 + 17",
            "Answer": 151,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 15 + 3 + 9 + 12 + 4",
            "Answer": 178,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 3 + 16 + 12 + 14 + 17",
            "Answer": 113,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 4 + 16 + 6 + 17 + 14",
            "Answer": 101,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 3 + 1 + 16 + 5 + 4",
            "Answer": 44,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 15 + 14 + 1 + 13 + 6",
            "Answer": 124,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 10 + 3 + 13 + 5 + 7",
            "Answer": 218,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 14 + 14 + 9 + 15 + 17",
            "Answer": 153,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 11 + 4 + 9 + 6 + 7",
            "Answer": 169,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 2 + 1 + 18 + 13 + 17",
            "Answer": 85,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 13 + 8 + 5 + 13 + 11",
            "Answer": 284,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 15 + 13 + 2 + 9 + 16",
            "Answer": 250,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 10 + 12 + 13 + 1 + 13",
            "Answer": 99,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 13 + 3 + 11 + 5 + 4",
            "Answer": 231,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 11 + 9 + 6 + 2 + 2",
            "Answer": 206,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 5 + 18 + 9 + 0 + 17",
            "Answer": 119,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 15 + 4 + 17 + 12 + 4",
            "Answer": 217,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 11 + 3 + 13 + 8 + 3",
            "Answer": 203,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 17 + 11 + 8 + 8 + 19",
            "Answer": 114,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 10 + 0 + 10 + 11 + 1",
            "Answer": 82,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 9 + 9 + 5 + 18 + 6",
            "Answer": 38,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 11 + 7 + 2 + 0 + 12",
            "Answer": 76,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 0 + 3 + 16 + 9 + 9",
            "Answer": 37,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 11 + 6 + 15 + 19 + 16",
            "Answer": 199,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 16 + 14 + 9 + 0 + 3",
            "Answer": 170,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 19 + 12 + 17 + 10 + 6",
            "Answer": 368,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 17 + 13 + 10 + 4 + 5",
            "Answer": 134,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 16 + 17 + 4 + 0 + 11",
            "Answer": 192,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 16 + 7 + 15 + 19 + 13",
            "Answer": 182,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 0 + 12 + 1 + 12 + 19",
            "Answer": 44,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 9 + 3 + 18 + 5 + 7",
            "Answer": 204,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 17 + 14 + 11 + 15 + 8",
            "Answer": 354,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 1 + 10 + 9 + 10 + 17",
            "Answer": 50,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 3 + 17 + 17 + 5 + 19",
            "Answer": 58,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 12 + 9 + 10 + 3 + 4",
            "Answer": 146,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 19 + 9 + 17 + 2 + 9",
            "Answer": 170,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 17 + 16 + 12 + 2 + 3",
            "Answer": 288,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 7 + 16 + 8 + 14 + 1",
            "Answer": 53,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 5 + 18 + 1 + 7 + 4",
            "Answer": 70,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 5 + 8 + 5 + 13 + 19",
            "Answer": 125,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 5 + 5 + 6 + 9 + 6",
            "Answer": 41,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 6 + 3 + 6 + 7 + 19",
            "Answer": 89,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 13 + 9 + 2 + 15 + 12",
            "Answer": 246,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 18 + 5 + 5 + 17 + 2",
            "Answer": 119,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 15 + 4 + 2 + 15 + 14",
            "Answer": 110,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 11 + 17 + 17 + 5 + 15",
            "Answer": 54,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 17 + 18 + 8 + 13 + 0",
            "Answer": 311,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 7 + 6 + 1 + 3 + 6",
            "Answer": 44,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 6 + 12 + 2 + 12 + 18",
            "Answer": 68,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 4 + 10 + 13 + 5 + 4",
            "Answer": 48,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 15 + 0 + 9 + 3 + 7",
            "Answer": 124,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 2 + 18 + 11 + 3 + 18",
            "Answer": 50,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 14 + 5 + 11 + 18 + 16",
            "Answer": 92,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 11 + 0 + 16 + 0 + 18",
            "Answer": 199,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 0 + 0 + 4 + 17 + 16",
            "Answer": 37,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 12 + 6 + 15 + 8 + 10",
            "Answer": 159,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 19 + 10 + 16 + 10 + 17",
            "Answer": 148,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 4 + 7 + 4 + 17 + 0",
            "Answer": 40,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 16 + 15 + 11 + 10 + 13",
            "Answer": 241,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + #"
        }
    ],
    "# + # + # + # + # * #": [
        {
            "Question": "7 + 3 + 15 + 3 + 16 * 11",
            "Answer": 204,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 18 + 1 + 5 + 17 * 3",
            "Answer": 81,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 19 + 1 + 13 + 8 * 18",
            "Answer": 189,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 4 + 3 + 0 + 11 * 6",
            "Answer": 89,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 16 + 6 + 12 + 13 * 17",
            "Answer": 267,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 6 + 19 + 2 + 1 * 0",
            "Answer": 27,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 17 + 11 + 1 + 11 * 9",
            "Answer": 145,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 6 + 2 + 19 + 7 * 16",
            "Answer": 149,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 12 + 11 + 16 + 4 * 6",
            "Answer": 69,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 13 + 4 + 4 + 19 * 15",
            "Answer": 321,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 3 + 3 + 2 + 5 * 11",
            "Answer": 78,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 3 + 10 + 14 + 0 * 6",
            "Answer": 35,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 3 + 2 + 6 + 1 * 18",
            "Answer": 36,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 10 + 4 + 1 + 5 * 3",
            "Answer": 34,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 4 + 9 + 8 + 14 * 10",
            "Answer": 175,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 17 + 1 + 7 + 4 * 17",
            "Answer": 107,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 6 + 7 + 1 + 5 * 13",
            "Answer": 94,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 3 + 18 + 11 + 17 * 2",
            "Answer": 85,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 3 + 13 + 11 + 5 * 2",
            "Answer": 43,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 4 + 11 + 1 + 12 * 18",
            "Answer": 243,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 10 + 14 + 7 + 2 * 5",
            "Answer": 56,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 13 + 18 + 10 + 10 * 3",
            "Answer": 80,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 13 + 8 + 10 + 10 * 2",
            "Answer": 61,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 14 + 10 + 3 + 10 * 19",
            "Answer": 223,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 8 + 2 + 11 + 5 * 5",
            "Answer": 57,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 7 + 19 + 3 + 12 * 14",
            "Answer": 198,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 19 + 16 + 5 + 7 * 11",
            "Answer": 128,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 7 + 19 + 2 + 10 * 10",
            "Answer": 147,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 16 + 2 + 2 + 5 * 16",
            "Answer": 118,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 5 + 19 + 10 + 13 * 0",
            "Answer": 48,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 5 + 15 + 6 + 2 * 8",
            "Answer": 61,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 6 + 1 + 11 + 9 * 11",
            "Answer": 125,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 8 + 5 + 5 + 8 * 1",
            "Answer": 30,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 15 + 11 + 4 + 19 * 14",
            "Answer": 302,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 6 + 17 + 7 + 7 * 4",
            "Answer": 73,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 19 + 8 + 15 + 10 * 3",
            "Answer": 84,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 6 + 2 + 2 + 17 * 15",
            "Answer": 268,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 4 + 6 + 1 + 12 * 17",
            "Answer": 227,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 11 + 15 + 17 + 9 * 14",
            "Answer": 184,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 19 + 16 + 7 + 9 * 5",
            "Answer": 89,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 19 + 15 + 4 + 9 * 6",
            "Answer": 98,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 14 + 13 + 8 + 5 * 17",
            "Answer": 120,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 0 + 8 + 13 + 1 * 13",
            "Answer": 40,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 2 + 6 + 18 + 5 * 19",
            "Answer": 126,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 15 + 16 + 13 + 17 * 14",
            "Answer": 290,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 18 + 14 + 0 + 14 * 16",
            "Answer": 274,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 18 + 4 + 17 + 1 * 13",
            "Answer": 59,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 1 + 6 + 0 + 6 * 14",
            "Answer": 101,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 0 + 1 + 14 + 19 * 11",
            "Answer": 238,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 12 + 7 + 15 + 10 * 13",
            "Answer": 181,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 5 + 9 + 12 + 5 * 3",
            "Answer": 51,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 12 + 6 + 6 + 0 * 12",
            "Answer": 33,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 5 + 3 + 19 + 4 * 2",
            "Answer": 52,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 15 + 5 + 5 + 8 * 11",
            "Answer": 118,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 11 + 4 + 15 + 8 * 10",
            "Answer": 127,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 15 + 16 + 19 + 9 * 12",
            "Answer": 176,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 8 + 5 + 15 + 6 * 11",
            "Answer": 105,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 16 + 15 + 7 + 3 * 2",
            "Answer": 59,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 2 + 14 + 15 + 14 * 5",
            "Answer": 105,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 18 + 4 + 11 + 1 * 10",
            "Answer": 57,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 12 + 14 + 14 + 15 * 7",
            "Answer": 150,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 2 + 15 + 17 + 6 * 6",
            "Answer": 87,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 10 + 12 + 7 + 14 * 10",
            "Answer": 185,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 10 + 10 + 3 + 19 * 9",
            "Answer": 204,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 10 + 2 + 0 + 0 * 13",
            "Answer": 27,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 12 + 10 + 9 + 16 * 5",
            "Answer": 113,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 13 + 13 + 16 + 4 * 6",
            "Answer": 79,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 17 + 17 + 1 + 16 * 8",
            "Answer": 165,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 0 + 12 + 10 + 4 * 3",
            "Answer": 44,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 16 + 19 + 0 + 1 * 0",
            "Answer": 36,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 11 + 13 + 2 + 17 * 18",
            "Answer": 350,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 15 + 5 + 16 + 19 * 16",
            "Answer": 355,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 4 + 8 + 9 + 1 * 13",
            "Answer": 39,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 6 + 13 + 12 + 2 * 2",
            "Answer": 50,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 5 + 0 + 2 + 12 * 3",
            "Answer": 57,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 9 + 6 + 18 + 15 * 19",
            "Answer": 324,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 19 + 16 + 13 + 9 * 6",
            "Answer": 113,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 8 + 6 + 11 + 2 * 15",
            "Answer": 63,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 17 + 13 + 16 + 6 * 10",
            "Answer": 112,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 13 + 19 + 4 + 16 * 8",
            "Answer": 171,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 2 + 18 + 16 + 3 * 12",
            "Answer": 79,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 14 + 1 + 19 + 6 * 3",
            "Answer": 65,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 2 + 1 + 16 + 18 * 18",
            "Answer": 359,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 3 + 18 + 5 + 14 * 11",
            "Answer": 191,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 8 + 12 + 5 + 7 * 6",
            "Answer": 81,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 19 + 6 + 9 + 4 * 16",
            "Answer": 114,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 2 + 0 + 13 + 12 * 13",
            "Answer": 189,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 0 + 8 + 4 + 5 * 19",
            "Answer": 115,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 19 + 14 + 11 + 7 * 9",
            "Answer": 110,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 3 + 17 + 11 + 15 * 1",
            "Answer": 63,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 12 + 10 + 17 + 3 * 7",
            "Answer": 62,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 8 + 9 + 7 + 0 * 12",
            "Answer": 25,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 13 + 9 + 19 + 19 * 5",
            "Answer": 137,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 12 + 8 + 16 + 10 * 18",
            "Answer": 216,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 0 + 5 + 9 + 7 * 3",
            "Answer": 39,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 0 + 18 + 0 + 0 * 19",
            "Answer": 30,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 16 + 13 + 16 + 12 * 2",
            "Answer": 78,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 16 + 19 + 19 + 3 * 19",
            "Answer": 118,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 0 + 9 + 13 + 3 * 17",
            "Answer": 90,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 6 + 17 + 2 + 8 * 0",
            "Answer": 43,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * #"
        }
    ],
    "# * # + # * # * # + #": [
        {
            "Question": "18 * 7 + 0 * 16 * 7 + 9",
            "Answer": 135,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 8 + 13 * 11 * 13 + 12",
            "Answer": 2023,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 9 + 18 * 3 * 19 + 9",
            "Answer": 1125,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 13 + 9 * 12 * 10 + 19",
            "Answer": 1346,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 5 + 18 * 12 * 11 + 16",
            "Answer": 2472,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 4 + 7 * 16 * 1 + 12",
            "Answer": 128,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 13 + 18 * 8 * 14 + 2",
            "Answer": 2044,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 2 + 1 * 16 * 1 + 11",
            "Answer": 53,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 12 + 6 * 0 * 0 + 9",
            "Answer": 177,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 3 + 11 * 6 * 6 + 16",
            "Answer": 433,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 18 + 14 * 7 * 2 + 6",
            "Answer": 220,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 2 + 19 * 10 * 15 + 11",
            "Answer": 2887,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 15 + 5 * 0 * 12 + 11",
            "Answer": 296,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 2 + 7 * 6 * 7 + 14",
            "Answer": 322,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 10 + 3 * 10 * 0 + 3",
            "Answer": 183,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 18 + 17 * 14 * 14 + 15",
            "Answer": 3491,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 18 + 12 * 7 * 4 + 4",
            "Answer": 448,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 17 + 2 * 2 * 12 + 18",
            "Answer": 83,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 3 + 2 * 17 * 7 + 13",
            "Answer": 296,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 9 + 11 * 13 * 13 + 11",
            "Answer": 1942,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 16 + 18 * 7 * 11 + 19",
            "Answer": 1469,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 6 + 2 * 16 * 19 + 9",
            "Answer": 659,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 16 + 18 * 5 * 8 + 3",
            "Answer": 1011,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 13 + 3 * 11 * 0 + 6",
            "Answer": 214,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 4 + 12 * 7 * 11 + 0",
            "Answer": 928,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 8 + 4 * 7 * 5 + 5",
            "Answer": 145,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 1 + 2 * 5 * 19 + 12",
            "Answer": 212,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 8 + 9 * 6 * 4 + 0",
            "Answer": 304,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 14 + 14 * 7 * 12 + 9",
            "Answer": 1367,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 6 + 15 * 9 * 14 + 13",
            "Answer": 1939,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 16 + 18 * 9 * 10 + 10",
            "Answer": 1630,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 5 + 6 * 9 * 3 + 15",
            "Answer": 202,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 14 + 8 * 13 * 15 + 3",
            "Answer": 1745,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 18 + 9 * 7 * 18 + 15",
            "Answer": 1347,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 1 + 16 * 8 * 11 + 13",
            "Answer": 1422,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 17 + 12 * 8 * 12 + 2",
            "Answer": 1290,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 8 + 4 * 4 * 16 + 3",
            "Answer": 387,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 11 + 12 * 8 * 9 + 3",
            "Answer": 988,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 8 + 4 * 10 * 8 + 5",
            "Answer": 469,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 3 + 11 * 14 * 8 + 7",
            "Answer": 1275,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 10 + 12 * 15 * 18 + 5",
            "Answer": 3305,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 9 + 14 * 9 * 17 + 18",
            "Answer": 2232,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 17 + 1 * 7 * 3 + 9",
            "Answer": 64,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 0 + 4 * 1 * 9 + 17",
            "Answer": 53,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 6 + 11 * 15 * 11 + 3",
            "Answer": 1932,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 6 + 10 * 16 * 14 + 4",
            "Answer": 2358,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 10 + 15 * 13 * 3 + 1",
            "Answer": 586,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 17 + 18 * 14 * 12 + 8",
            "Answer": 3338,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 10 + 6 * 19 * 3 + 13",
            "Answer": 535,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 14 + 4 * 17 * 18 + 10",
            "Answer": 1248,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 9 + 10 * 5 * 10 + 17",
            "Answer": 643,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 3 + 7 * 19 * 6 + 7",
            "Answer": 814,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 6 + 9 * 4 * 11 + 7",
            "Answer": 433,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 13 + 11 * 8 * 12 + 19",
            "Answer": 1218,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 8 + 10 * 10 * 12 + 4",
            "Answer": 1284,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 8 + 17 * 12 * 14 + 2",
            "Answer": 2906,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 11 + 15 * 4 * 10 + 0",
            "Answer": 710,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 19 + 18 * 14 * 18 + 7",
            "Answer": 4771,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 5 + 5 * 10 * 16 + 15",
            "Answer": 835,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 14 + 1 * 14 * 11 + 18",
            "Answer": 256,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 1 + 15 * 5 * 15 + 8",
            "Answer": 1136,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 15 + 16 * 7 * 1 + 10",
            "Answer": 272,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 15 + 3 * 14 * 2 + 2",
            "Answer": 191,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 17 + 3 * 19 * 16 + 18",
            "Answer": 1100,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 15 + 3 * 5 * 13 + 0",
            "Answer": 420,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 5 + 3 * 13 * 9 + 11",
            "Answer": 397,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 0 + 6 * 1 * 16 + 14",
            "Answer": 110,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 2 + 17 * 19 * 18 + 5",
            "Answer": 5843,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 14 + 11 * 5 * 8 + 11",
            "Answer": 451,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 9 + 14 * 11 * 11 + 3",
            "Answer": 1823,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 13 + 7 * 16 * 5 + 16",
            "Answer": 628,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 0 + 16 * 3 * 6 + 18",
            "Answer": 306,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 4 + 7 * 9 * 12 + 14",
            "Answer": 830,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 17 + 8 * 3 * 15 + 14",
            "Answer": 629,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 4 + 8 * 18 * 11 + 11",
            "Answer": 1655,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 17 + 7 * 11 * 1 + 2",
            "Answer": 113,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 8 + 13 * 4 * 14 + 4",
            "Answer": 756,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 16 + 19 * 19 * 4 + 13",
            "Answer": 1649,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 15 + 18 * 0 * 15 + 5",
            "Answer": 20,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 7 + 3 * 1 * 17 + 3",
            "Answer": 117,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 9 + 6 * 4 * 3 + 10",
            "Answer": 154,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 17 + 15 * 17 * 6 + 19",
            "Answer": 1838,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 9 + 10 * 3 * 1 + 8",
            "Answer": 38,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 13 + 8 * 18 * 5 + 17",
            "Answer": 919,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 10 + 10 * 13 * 14 + 17",
            "Answer": 1927,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 19 + 1 * 17 * 5 + 9",
            "Answer": 303,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 17 + 18 * 7 * 6 + 0",
            "Answer": 926,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 15 + 9 * 7 * 9 + 9",
            "Answer": 651,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 13 + 11 * 10 * 3 + 17",
            "Answer": 594,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 17 + 8 * 15 * 11 + 10",
            "Answer": 1466,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 1 + 6 * 7 * 9 + 18",
            "Answer": 412,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 15 + 14 * 4 * 11 + 8",
            "Answer": 759,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 17 + 11 * 5 * 2 + 9",
            "Answer": 357,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 19 + 9 * 12 * 6 + 12",
            "Answer": 1002,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 0 + 3 * 2 * 2 + 15",
            "Answer": 27,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 17 + 9 * 12 * 14 + 14",
            "Answer": 1526,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 15 + 4 * 3 * 8 + 7",
            "Answer": 193,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 12 + 12 * 1 * 11 + 0",
            "Answer": 216,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 8 + 9 * 15 * 9 + 16",
            "Answer": 1231,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 0 + 12 * 16 * 10 + 2",
            "Answer": 1922,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + #"
        }
    ],
    "# * # + # + # * # + #": [
        {
            "Question": "1 * 18 + 11 + 8 * 5 + 0",
            "Answer": 69,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 14 + 16 + 1 * 9 + 17",
            "Answer": 294,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 11 + 8 + 0 * 8 + 9",
            "Answer": 193,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 3 + 14 + 11 * 19 + 17",
            "Answer": 258,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 13 + 9 + 19 * 13 + 17",
            "Answer": 416,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 17 + 9 + 7 * 11 + 15",
            "Answer": 407,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 18 + 4 + 4 * 7 + 10",
            "Answer": 204,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 15 + 0 + 10 * 16 + 0",
            "Answer": 400,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 5 + 12 + 4 * 13 + 1",
            "Answer": 115,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 5 + 17 + 6 * 19 + 19",
            "Answer": 210,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 5 + 18 + 13 * 10 + 8",
            "Answer": 236,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 19 + 2 + 16 * 19 + 16",
            "Answer": 531,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 14 + 17 + 5 * 3 + 9",
            "Answer": 251,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 6 + 1 + 2 * 17 + 19",
            "Answer": 90,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 11 + 16 + 9 * 5 + 0",
            "Answer": 116,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 14 + 13 + 16 * 10 + 11",
            "Answer": 212,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 2 + 19 + 9 * 17 + 13",
            "Answer": 217,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 8 + 5 + 13 * 7 + 7",
            "Answer": 215,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 17 + 17 + 13 * 10 + 10",
            "Answer": 242,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 13 + 11 + 8 * 0 + 6",
            "Answer": 30,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 12 + 6 + 1 * 9 + 10",
            "Answer": 181,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 9 + 9 + 4 * 17 + 5",
            "Answer": 217,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 9 + 11 + 4 * 3 + 12",
            "Answer": 80,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 6 + 3 + 9 * 19 + 14",
            "Answer": 200,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 12 + 9 + 2 * 16 + 6",
            "Answer": 215,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 8 + 6 + 12 * 5 + 18",
            "Answer": 172,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 3 + 6 + 16 * 5 + 8",
            "Answer": 115,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 19 + 6 + 8 * 3 + 15",
            "Answer": 406,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 19 + 0 + 15 * 5 + 8",
            "Answer": 368,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 4 + 16 + 7 * 6 + 17",
            "Answer": 99,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 3 + 15 + 19 * 10 + 6",
            "Answer": 223,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 3 + 4 + 5 * 8 + 2",
            "Answer": 76,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 11 + 18 + 0 * 6 + 18",
            "Answer": 69,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 1 + 10 + 4 * 0 + 7",
            "Answer": 21,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 18 + 1 + 3 * 19 + 16",
            "Answer": 380,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 3 + 0 + 8 * 11 + 5",
            "Answer": 138,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 1 + 1 + 7 * 11 + 1",
            "Answer": 96,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 8 + 11 + 19 * 13 + 11",
            "Answer": 373,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 12 + 17 + 2 * 7 + 14",
            "Answer": 141,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 7 + 12 + 11 * 6 + 13",
            "Answer": 224,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 11 + 12 + 8 * 0 + 12",
            "Answer": 57,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 15 + 2 + 12 * 19 + 6",
            "Answer": 416,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 16 + 10 + 10 * 2 + 3",
            "Answer": 113,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 8 + 9 + 11 * 1 + 0",
            "Answer": 100,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 18 + 3 + 14 * 14 + 3",
            "Answer": 472,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 6 + 10 + 5 * 7 + 18",
            "Answer": 105,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 10 + 16 + 1 * 16 + 5",
            "Answer": 227,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 16 + 3 + 7 * 16 + 4",
            "Answer": 391,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 10 + 9 + 6 * 11 + 7",
            "Answer": 142,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 9 + 15 + 15 * 6 + 16",
            "Answer": 130,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 13 + 15 + 17 * 12 + 7",
            "Answer": 421,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 5 + 3 + 11 * 15 + 4",
            "Answer": 267,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 16 + 1 + 8 * 18 + 12",
            "Answer": 445,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 12 + 15 + 17 * 16 + 18",
            "Answer": 401,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 11 + 8 + 2 * 19 + 15",
            "Answer": 72,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 7 + 0 + 17 * 1 + 2",
            "Answer": 124,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 19 + 17 + 15 * 13 + 5",
            "Answer": 350,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 16 + 14 + 12 * 15 + 0",
            "Answer": 322,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 16 + 4 + 13 * 0 + 18",
            "Answer": 294,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 13 + 16 + 7 * 16 + 12",
            "Answer": 361,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 11 + 12 + 4 * 18 + 2",
            "Answer": 174,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 7 + 13 + 16 * 0 + 0",
            "Answer": 41,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 17 + 16 + 18 * 11 + 10",
            "Answer": 513,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 8 + 5 + 7 * 19 + 13",
            "Answer": 271,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 9 + 2 + 0 * 9 + 3",
            "Answer": 14,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 19 + 4 + 5 * 18 + 19",
            "Answer": 227,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 13 + 14 + 19 * 16 + 9",
            "Answer": 418,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 13 + 10 + 12 * 19 + 15",
            "Answer": 487,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 19 + 13 + 18 * 13 + 3",
            "Answer": 535,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 15 + 6 + 6 * 2 + 18",
            "Answer": 96,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 8 + 12 + 2 * 0 + 3",
            "Answer": 143,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 8 + 5 + 11 * 16 + 5",
            "Answer": 194,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 9 + 12 + 13 * 9 + 13",
            "Answer": 277,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 7 + 11 + 10 * 14 + 9",
            "Answer": 293,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 8 + 18 + 11 * 3 + 1",
            "Answer": 116,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 9 + 10 + 10 * 2 + 19",
            "Answer": 76,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 14 + 5 + 12 * 9 + 6",
            "Answer": 329,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 1 + 12 + 17 * 14 + 12",
            "Answer": 278,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 1 + 2 + 19 * 13 + 13",
            "Answer": 281,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 13 + 0 + 2 * 5 + 3",
            "Answer": 169,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 8 + 15 + 12 * 17 + 10",
            "Answer": 381,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 19 + 17 + 17 * 5 + 14",
            "Answer": 458,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 7 + 4 + 6 * 12 + 7",
            "Answer": 153,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 1 + 6 + 12 * 18 + 16",
            "Answer": 246,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 1 + 2 + 16 * 1 + 13",
            "Answer": 49,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 4 + 9 + 4 * 15 + 18",
            "Answer": 107,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 3 + 4 + 17 * 7 + 17",
            "Answer": 158,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 18 + 17 + 9 * 6 + 13",
            "Answer": 102,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 14 + 19 + 19 * 11 + 15",
            "Answer": 397,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 0 + 12 + 12 * 10 + 11",
            "Answer": 143,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 17 + 12 + 12 * 3 + 15",
            "Answer": 131,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 3 + 16 + 11 * 10 + 0",
            "Answer": 162,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 1 + 11 + 16 * 8 + 19",
            "Answer": 166,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 2 + 3 + 16 * 11 + 9",
            "Answer": 202,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 18 + 2 + 14 * 15 + 1",
            "Answer": 447,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 18 + 11 + 17 * 19 + 13",
            "Answer": 653,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 14 + 11 + 6 * 16 + 11",
            "Answer": 314,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 10 + 8 + 1 * 1 + 5",
            "Answer": 184,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 4 + 9 + 11 * 11 + 4",
            "Answer": 174,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 2 + 3 + 19 * 17 + 16",
            "Answer": 374,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + #"
        }
    ],
    "# * # + # + # + # * #": [
        {
            "Question": "8 * 16 + 5 + 6 + 3 * 15",
            "Answer": 184,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 8 + 17 + 10 + 9 * 2",
            "Answer": 141,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 16 + 8 + 19 + 12 * 1",
            "Answer": 71,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 11 + 7 + 3 + 3 * 6",
            "Answer": 204,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 7 + 6 + 11 + 17 * 7",
            "Answer": 192,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 17 + 4 + 8 + 2 * 5",
            "Answer": 158,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 10 + 13 + 15 + 17 * 9",
            "Answer": 281,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 12 + 3 + 5 + 8 * 16",
            "Answer": 316,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 4 + 19 + 13 + 16 * 10",
            "Answer": 240,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 17 + 5 + 5 + 10 * 1",
            "Answer": 275,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 5 + 15 + 15 + 17 * 18",
            "Answer": 386,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 10 + 15 + 12 + 1 * 4",
            "Answer": 71,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 7 + 12 + 17 + 8 * 7",
            "Answer": 99,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 9 + 7 + 15 + 5 * 15",
            "Answer": 259,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 17 + 8 + 17 + 1 * 0",
            "Answer": 314,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 2 + 3 + 2 + 9 * 3",
            "Answer": 40,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 2 + 13 + 3 + 17 * 15",
            "Answer": 277,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 16 + 3 + 0 + 6 * 11",
            "Answer": 373,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 5 + 4 + 9 + 15 * 10",
            "Answer": 168,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 18 + 17 + 8 + 19 * 5",
            "Answer": 174,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 1 + 18 + 17 + 0 * 4",
            "Answer": 38,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 5 + 19 + 15 + 0 * 4",
            "Answer": 44,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 10 + 10 + 0 + 12 * 17",
            "Answer": 354,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 15 + 4 + 1 + 14 * 18",
            "Answer": 437,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 3 + 13 + 10 + 9 * 19",
            "Answer": 248,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 17 + 5 + 1 + 7 * 9",
            "Answer": 103,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 19 + 2 + 8 + 6 * 5",
            "Answer": 116,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 0 + 7 + 18 + 3 * 6",
            "Answer": 43,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 16 + 6 + 12 + 10 * 17",
            "Answer": 476,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 11 + 12 + 3 + 1 * 17",
            "Answer": 164,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 8 + 12 + 9 + 11 * 1",
            "Answer": 128,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 11 + 6 + 2 + 0 * 17",
            "Answer": 19,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 15 + 18 + 8 + 8 * 12",
            "Answer": 287,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 19 + 3 + 2 + 1 * 13",
            "Answer": 94,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 13 + 0 + 11 + 19 * 0",
            "Answer": 193,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 10 + 14 + 4 + 2 * 18",
            "Answer": 164,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 15 + 6 + 18 + 4 * 8",
            "Answer": 86,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 1 + 0 + 9 + 9 * 14",
            "Answer": 147,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 12 + 0 + 6 + 19 * 7",
            "Answer": 271,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 3 + 0 + 4 + 1 * 2",
            "Answer": 18,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 6 + 11 + 1 + 12 * 19",
            "Answer": 264,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 9 + 5 + 5 + 10 * 0",
            "Answer": 46,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 10 + 0 + 8 + 16 * 14",
            "Answer": 382,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 12 + 8 + 14 + 3 * 11",
            "Answer": 67,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 9 + 11 + 3 + 12 * 7",
            "Answer": 116,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 8 + 13 + 17 + 3 * 11",
            "Answer": 63,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 3 + 9 + 4 + 9 * 1",
            "Answer": 70,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 18 + 19 + 14 + 2 * 8",
            "Answer": 139,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 9 + 4 + 16 + 19 * 9",
            "Answer": 200,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 17 + 10 + 10 + 1 * 15",
            "Answer": 341,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 3 + 5 + 12 + 4 * 6",
            "Answer": 68,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 11 + 1 + 18 + 13 * 9",
            "Answer": 147,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 10 + 9 + 13 + 2 * 9",
            "Answer": 170,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 8 + 12 + 12 + 0 * 5",
            "Answer": 152,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 17 + 4 + 9 + 2 * 14",
            "Answer": 160,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 8 + 13 + 12 + 2 * 15",
            "Answer": 183,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 7 + 0 + 13 + 16 * 13",
            "Answer": 228,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 1 + 8 + 18 + 9 * 13",
            "Answer": 148,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 1 + 17 + 14 + 5 * 12",
            "Answer": 95,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 10 + 6 + 6 + 3 * 5",
            "Answer": 27,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 12 + 4 + 7 + 8 * 3",
            "Answer": 107,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 5 + 2 + 2 + 1 * 7",
            "Answer": 21,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 10 + 0 + 17 + 8 * 9",
            "Answer": 189,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 6 + 8 + 4 + 4 * 16",
            "Answer": 154,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 2 + 10 + 11 + 5 * 9",
            "Answer": 66,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 10 + 11 + 0 + 9 * 8",
            "Answer": 273,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 4 + 5 + 7 + 18 * 5",
            "Answer": 178,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 5 + 3 + 3 + 3 * 6",
            "Answer": 49,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 2 + 10 + 2 + 3 * 8",
            "Answer": 50,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 1 + 6 + 2 + 12 * 7",
            "Answer": 99,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 11 + 15 + 1 + 17 * 8",
            "Answer": 240,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 1 + 16 + 0 + 17 * 10",
            "Answer": 200,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 2 + 13 + 0 + 19 * 0",
            "Answer": 39,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 19 + 2 + 5 + 4 * 6",
            "Answer": 297,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 18 + 10 + 7 + 17 * 16",
            "Answer": 595,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 18 + 7 + 12 + 18 * 4",
            "Answer": 253,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 16 + 7 + 11 + 19 * 6",
            "Answer": 276,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 2 + 17 + 9 + 8 * 11",
            "Answer": 118,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 16 + 5 + 0 + 14 * 18",
            "Answer": 289,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 5 + 14 + 9 + 12 * 1",
            "Answer": 90,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 15 + 9 + 19 + 16 * 4",
            "Answer": 92,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 1 + 10 + 10 + 14 * 13",
            "Answer": 215,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 7 + 0 + 1 + 7 * 12",
            "Answer": 92,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 18 + 11 + 0 + 18 * 8",
            "Answer": 209,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 10 + 10 + 19 + 7 * 12",
            "Answer": 113,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 3 + 14 + 8 + 19 * 12",
            "Answer": 265,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 19 + 14 + 6 + 3 * 4",
            "Answer": 355,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 10 + 7 + 0 + 3 * 11",
            "Answer": 70,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 7 + 4 + 16 + 14 * 3",
            "Answer": 118,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 5 + 11 + 8 + 14 * 19",
            "Answer": 295,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 18 + 7 + 12 + 0 * 6",
            "Answer": 217,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 11 + 2 + 13 + 2 * 19",
            "Answer": 218,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 6 + 12 + 12 + 17 * 0",
            "Answer": 114,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 15 + 10 + 13 + 13 * 1",
            "Answer": 96,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 11 + 9 + 16 + 15 * 19",
            "Answer": 387,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 14 + 1 + 6 + 18 * 17",
            "Answer": 355,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 11 + 4 + 13 + 15 * 4",
            "Answer": 220,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 13 + 4 + 16 + 4 * 3",
            "Answer": 253,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 4 + 5 + 4 + 11 * 1",
            "Answer": 28,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 14 + 8 + 6 + 7 * 16",
            "Answer": 322,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * #"
        }
    ],
    "# * # + # * # + # + #": [
        {
            "Question": "5 * 19 + 10 * 17 + 4 + 4",
            "Answer": 273,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 9 + 13 * 19 + 15 + 1",
            "Answer": 281,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 14 + 14 * 8 + 5 + 14",
            "Answer": 285,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 15 + 8 * 7 + 6 + 5",
            "Answer": 202,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 7 + 14 * 18 + 16 + 19",
            "Answer": 301,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 19 + 13 * 2 + 9 + 19",
            "Answer": 92,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 5 + 9 * 6 + 13 + 4",
            "Answer": 91,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 1 + 3 * 10 + 6 + 15",
            "Answer": 57,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 14 + 1 * 15 + 6 + 5",
            "Answer": 54,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 17 + 14 * 3 + 5 + 4",
            "Answer": 119,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 11 + 14 * 9 + 8 + 0",
            "Answer": 233,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 17 + 9 * 12 + 4 + 2",
            "Answer": 182,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 3 + 19 * 5 + 17 + 10",
            "Answer": 125,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 1 + 9 * 12 + 10 + 3",
            "Answer": 124,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 2 + 14 * 4 + 1 + 0",
            "Answer": 77,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 10 + 1 * 14 + 11 + 5",
            "Answer": 90,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 1 + 8 * 8 + 12 + 6",
            "Answer": 87,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 7 + 15 * 15 + 15 + 13",
            "Answer": 386,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 6 + 0 * 1 + 1 + 10",
            "Answer": 95,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 16 + 3 * 19 + 18 + 16",
            "Answer": 267,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 2 + 7 * 17 + 5 + 16",
            "Answer": 170,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 14 + 1 * 3 + 14 + 14",
            "Answer": 59,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 10 + 9 * 7 + 19 + 9",
            "Answer": 121,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 14 + 8 * 18 + 17 + 7",
            "Answer": 364,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 7 + 19 * 11 + 9 + 9",
            "Answer": 311,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 8 + 8 * 7 + 6 + 17",
            "Answer": 111,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 5 + 0 * 17 + 13 + 3",
            "Answer": 31,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 17 + 14 * 11 + 15 + 5",
            "Answer": 344,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 4 + 3 * 3 + 3 + 12",
            "Answer": 84,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 3 + 4 * 15 + 16 + 13",
            "Answer": 137,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 7 + 9 * 10 + 14 + 19",
            "Answer": 123,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 9 + 11 * 3 + 0 + 10",
            "Answer": 214,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 7 + 6 * 6 + 15 + 3",
            "Answer": 180,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 10 + 9 * 7 + 17 + 3",
            "Answer": 163,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 7 + 6 * 15 + 11 + 8",
            "Answer": 228,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 14 + 3 * 17 + 11 + 12",
            "Answer": 74,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 16 + 6 * 1 + 1 + 9",
            "Answer": 224,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 7 + 8 * 19 + 17 + 8",
            "Answer": 184,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 17 + 5 * 10 + 3 + 14",
            "Answer": 288,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 16 + 16 * 16 + 12 + 1",
            "Answer": 557,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 11 + 6 * 18 + 11 + 1",
            "Answer": 241,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 7 + 10 * 13 + 4 + 3",
            "Answer": 193,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 4 + 15 * 4 + 4 + 6",
            "Answer": 134,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 15 + 3 * 16 + 19 + 0",
            "Answer": 172,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 19 + 17 * 4 + 6 + 11",
            "Answer": 142,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 17 + 18 * 18 + 12 + 12",
            "Answer": 603,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 18 + 9 * 5 + 4 + 12",
            "Answer": 385,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 4 + 7 * 17 + 12 + 15",
            "Answer": 146,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 13 + 19 * 19 + 5 + 12",
            "Answer": 547,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 15 + 4 * 14 + 11 + 4",
            "Answer": 296,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 4 + 15 * 18 + 6 + 8",
            "Answer": 288,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 15 + 15 * 19 + 3 + 3",
            "Answer": 366,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 13 + 16 * 18 + 13 + 7",
            "Answer": 516,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 8 + 15 * 1 + 5 + 18",
            "Answer": 38,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 6 + 18 * 16 + 2 + 19",
            "Answer": 417,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 9 + 19 * 4 + 9 + 0",
            "Answer": 193,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 10 + 16 * 10 + 15 + 1",
            "Answer": 316,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 12 + 8 * 7 + 10 + 3",
            "Answer": 81,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 19 + 0 * 9 + 5 + 1",
            "Answer": 329,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 18 + 16 * 13 + 0 + 15",
            "Answer": 367,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 8 + 11 * 4 + 5 + 14",
            "Answer": 79,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 19 + 15 * 2 + 6 + 12",
            "Answer": 67,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 12 + 1 * 12 + 19 + 6",
            "Answer": 169,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 15 + 15 * 10 + 8 + 13",
            "Answer": 216,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 1 + 6 * 10 + 19 + 4",
            "Answer": 95,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 8 + 14 * 9 + 4 + 6",
            "Answer": 248,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 2 + 19 * 9 + 2 + 3",
            "Answer": 186,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 9 + 9 * 5 + 17 + 19",
            "Answer": 198,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 15 + 11 * 16 + 16 + 11",
            "Answer": 398,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 9 + 5 * 15 + 14 + 4",
            "Answer": 111,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 11 + 17 * 19 + 11 + 14",
            "Answer": 392,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 4 + 17 * 7 + 18 + 11",
            "Answer": 180,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 7 + 18 * 15 + 15 + 3",
            "Answer": 302,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 6 + 9 * 9 + 11 + 14",
            "Answer": 118,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 1 + 9 * 16 + 0 + 18",
            "Answer": 163,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 7 + 12 * 19 + 8 + 17",
            "Answer": 288,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 9 + 17 * 11 + 12 + 18",
            "Answer": 235,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 16 + 11 * 13 + 16 + 16",
            "Answer": 447,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 1 + 8 * 11 + 19 + 1",
            "Answer": 119,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 0 + 4 * 18 + 1 + 8",
            "Answer": 81,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 3 + 5 * 2 + 10 + 16",
            "Answer": 39,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 19 + 7 * 2 + 2 + 14",
            "Answer": 334,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 14 + 10 * 0 + 14 + 3",
            "Answer": 227,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 7 + 14 * 0 + 6 + 13",
            "Answer": 103,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 0 + 14 * 19 + 1 + 4",
            "Answer": 271,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 2 + 5 * 7 + 17 + 3",
            "Answer": 55,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 19 + 18 * 0 + 19 + 19",
            "Answer": 361,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 13 + 13 * 18 + 7 + 15",
            "Answer": 464,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 10 + 19 * 3 + 8 + 16",
            "Answer": 141,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 18 + 6 * 16 + 7 + 7",
            "Answer": 308,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 4 + 1 * 5 + 14 + 7",
            "Answer": 62,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 18 + 3 * 16 + 10 + 16",
            "Answer": 398,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 14 + 7 * 4 + 10 + 18",
            "Answer": 252,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 4 + 7 * 0 + 19 + 15",
            "Answer": 38,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 7 + 6 * 13 + 8 + 7",
            "Answer": 114,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 16 + 18 * 6 + 12 + 11",
            "Answer": 355,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 19 + 9 * 14 + 5 + 7",
            "Answer": 366,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 10 + 8 * 10 + 4 + 5",
            "Answer": 149,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 16 + 3 * 17 + 4 + 10",
            "Answer": 273,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 0 + 6 * 13 + 18 + 4",
            "Answer": 100,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + #"
        }
    ],
    "# + # * # + # + # + #": [
        {
            "Question": "13 + 3 * 0 + 7 + 10 + 12",
            "Answer": 42,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 13 * 10 + 5 + 4 + 9",
            "Answer": 152,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 0 * 13 + 9 + 16 + 10",
            "Answer": 40,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 2 * 11 + 3 + 1 + 6",
            "Answer": 35,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 16 * 19 + 5 + 7 + 13",
            "Answer": 338,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 6 * 19 + 2 + 9 + 4",
            "Answer": 142,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 3 * 2 + 5 + 3 + 6",
            "Answer": 28,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 13 * 14 + 1 + 19 + 12",
            "Answer": 229,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 12 * 2 + 7 + 2 + 14",
            "Answer": 58,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 16 * 11 + 17 + 12 + 15",
            "Answer": 233,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 13 * 9 + 19 + 16 + 0",
            "Answer": 171,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 11 * 1 + 18 + 0 + 4",
            "Answer": 35,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 3 * 11 + 7 + 18 + 18",
            "Answer": 77,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 10 * 0 + 0 + 7 + 9",
            "Answer": 24,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 12 * 8 + 7 + 10 + 5",
            "Answer": 131,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 19 * 5 + 15 + 2 + 10",
            "Answer": 122,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 19 * 8 + 18 + 1 + 0",
            "Answer": 181,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 13 * 13 + 0 + 13 + 3",
            "Answer": 190,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 12 * 4 + 8 + 8 + 0",
            "Answer": 82,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 15 * 7 + 2 + 14 + 8",
            "Answer": 130,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 14 * 17 + 6 + 18 + 1",
            "Answer": 279,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 10 * 4 + 2 + 6 + 11",
            "Answer": 59,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 9 * 12 + 9 + 2 + 10",
            "Answer": 131,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 9 * 1 + 0 + 15 + 12",
            "Answer": 51,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 13 * 12 + 6 + 7 + 16",
            "Answer": 185,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 16 * 11 + 10 + 12 + 4",
            "Answer": 208,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 11 * 10 + 2 + 3 + 17",
            "Answer": 133,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 4 * 6 + 7 + 2 + 8",
            "Answer": 53,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 4 * 15 + 8 + 11 + 8",
            "Answer": 96,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 3 * 11 + 3 + 9 + 1",
            "Answer": 49,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 7 * 2 + 17 + 19 + 8",
            "Answer": 58,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 13 * 13 + 10 + 4 + 2",
            "Answer": 191,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 17 * 13 + 0 + 12 + 11",
            "Answer": 257,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 15 * 15 + 10 + 3 + 1",
            "Answer": 245,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 4 * 1 + 3 + 12 + 19",
            "Answer": 47,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 5 * 15 + 3 + 5 + 1",
            "Answer": 92,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 3 * 1 + 17 + 0 + 15",
            "Answer": 45,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 11 * 4 + 15 + 14 + 7",
            "Answer": 96,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 16 * 17 + 8 + 9 + 15",
            "Answer": 315,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 7 * 13 + 0 + 2 + 8",
            "Answer": 116,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 14 * 0 + 15 + 8 + 1",
            "Answer": 39,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 11 * 1 + 0 + 2 + 9",
            "Answer": 39,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 16 * 10 + 1 + 13 + 6",
            "Answer": 195,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 14 * 14 + 5 + 15 + 1",
            "Answer": 235,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 4 * 8 + 14 + 12 + 19",
            "Answer": 87,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 13 * 8 + 5 + 1 + 14",
            "Answer": 140,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 1 * 12 + 2 + 12 + 11",
            "Answer": 39,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 5 * 5 + 8 + 8 + 6",
            "Answer": 49,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 12 * 13 + 7 + 6 + 10",
            "Answer": 186,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 2 * 12 + 8 + 14 + 18",
            "Answer": 69,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 0 * 6 + 1 + 17 + 16",
            "Answer": 35,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 17 * 19 + 15 + 7 + 13",
            "Answer": 362,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 2 * 9 + 13 + 4 + 15",
            "Answer": 53,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 2 * 16 + 14 + 12 + 17",
            "Answer": 87,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 12 * 12 + 1 + 3 + 19",
            "Answer": 177,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 11 * 1 + 18 + 13 + 9",
            "Answer": 66,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 12 * 18 + 11 + 1 + 10",
            "Answer": 252,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 16 * 11 + 12 + 15 + 6",
            "Answer": 217,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 7 * 19 + 14 + 0 + 1",
            "Answer": 157,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 6 * 4 + 0 + 1 + 15",
            "Answer": 41,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 16 * 14 + 3 + 9 + 15",
            "Answer": 267,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 14 * 16 + 18 + 0 + 0",
            "Answer": 248,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 14 * 14 + 19 + 3 + 6",
            "Answer": 228,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 13 * 11 + 18 + 1 + 4",
            "Answer": 184,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 3 * 15 + 19 + 12 + 3",
            "Answer": 95,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 14 * 11 + 4 + 18 + 12",
            "Answer": 190,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 15 * 11 + 15 + 13 + 5",
            "Answer": 200,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 1 * 1 + 14 + 0 + 13",
            "Answer": 29,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 2 * 4 + 18 + 11 + 5",
            "Answer": 54,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 1 * 13 + 9 + 14 + 5",
            "Answer": 42,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 9 * 14 + 4 + 2 + 1",
            "Answer": 152,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 1 * 8 + 12 + 4 + 18",
            "Answer": 50,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 7 * 8 + 9 + 11 + 2",
            "Answer": 86,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 0 * 2 + 8 + 0 + 19",
            "Answer": 39,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 11 * 6 + 7 + 2 + 11",
            "Answer": 87,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 3 * 17 + 9 + 4 + 18",
            "Answer": 85,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 3 * 9 + 5 + 6 + 10",
            "Answer": 54,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 0 * 18 + 4 + 9 + 10",
            "Answer": 28,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 13 * 9 + 19 + 5 + 18",
            "Answer": 178,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 11 * 15 + 3 + 1 + 8",
            "Answer": 177,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 1 * 14 + 19 + 18 + 18",
            "Answer": 81,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 2 * 14 + 16 + 18 + 18",
            "Answer": 95,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 3 * 3 + 13 + 14 + 15",
            "Answer": 70,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 10 * 17 + 15 + 14 + 5",
            "Answer": 207,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 14 * 4 + 14 + 3 + 10",
            "Answer": 83,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 15 * 16 + 3 + 6 + 8",
            "Answer": 261,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 15 * 19 + 14 + 3 + 10",
            "Answer": 322,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 9 * 16 + 6 + 18 + 2",
            "Answer": 171,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 6 * 8 + 3 + 17 + 16",
            "Answer": 92,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 3 * 15 + 9 + 1 + 17",
            "Answer": 75,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 17 * 13 + 6 + 3 + 6",
            "Answer": 251,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 14 * 7 + 16 + 12 + 2",
            "Answer": 138,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 13 * 16 + 9 + 0 + 16",
            "Answer": 250,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 19 * 7 + 11 + 2 + 13",
            "Answer": 175,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 0 * 3 + 19 + 3 + 1",
            "Answer": 37,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 0 * 13 + 7 + 5 + 1",
            "Answer": 22,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 10 * 12 + 16 + 10 + 7",
            "Answer": 167,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 11 * 1 + 1 + 11 + 11",
            "Answer": 34,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 5 * 13 + 8 + 3 + 16",
            "Answer": 103,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 17 * 5 + 12 + 10 + 14",
            "Answer": 133,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + #"
        }
    ],
    "# * # * # + # + # + #": [
        {
            "Question": "6 * 7 * 8 + 0 + 0 + 4",
            "Answer": 340,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 0 * 9 + 0 + 6 + 9",
            "Answer": 15,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 17 * 10 + 5 + 5 + 9",
            "Answer": 3249,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 9 * 2 + 2 + 9 + 13",
            "Answer": 132,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 9 * 0 + 5 + 1 + 11",
            "Answer": 17,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 3 * 14 + 3 + 11 + 1",
            "Answer": 477,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 19 * 9 + 7 + 12 + 3",
            "Answer": 2587,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 11 * 9 + 5 + 4 + 14",
            "Answer": 1211,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 17 * 8 + 6 + 6 + 14",
            "Answer": 2202,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 0 * 13 + 18 + 12 + 0",
            "Answer": 30,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 14 * 19 + 9 + 1 + 14",
            "Answer": 4280,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 3 * 18 + 4 + 9 + 11",
            "Answer": 1050,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 16 * 17 + 9 + 4 + 9",
            "Answer": 838,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 5 * 13 + 12 + 3 + 19",
            "Answer": 1139,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 13 * 2 + 18 + 18 + 12",
            "Answer": 438,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 4 * 18 + 18 + 13 + 19",
            "Answer": 266,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 6 * 9 + 10 + 7 + 16",
            "Answer": 1005,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 13 * 13 + 1 + 2 + 6",
            "Answer": 2882,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 0 * 10 + 11 + 17 + 19",
            "Answer": 47,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 7 * 17 + 0 + 12 + 15",
            "Answer": 2169,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 12 * 5 + 19 + 15 + 11",
            "Answer": 825,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 16 * 17 + 9 + 13 + 1",
            "Answer": 2743,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 13 * 16 + 5 + 18 + 8",
            "Answer": 3359,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 5 * 3 + 15 + 16 + 18",
            "Answer": 319,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 19 * 12 + 6 + 12 + 16",
            "Answer": 490,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 15 * 6 + 17 + 7 + 19",
            "Answer": 493,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 15 * 19 + 11 + 10 + 0",
            "Answer": 1446,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 1 * 4 + 0 + 3 + 11",
            "Answer": 82,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 13 * 0 + 2 + 4 + 16",
            "Answer": 22,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 3 * 18 + 10 + 10 + 8",
            "Answer": 622,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 16 * 11 + 5 + 1 + 17",
            "Answer": 23,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 5 * 2 + 8 + 8 + 2",
            "Answer": 198,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 17 * 5 + 8 + 5 + 3",
            "Answer": 1461,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 3 * 15 + 15 + 10 + 6",
            "Answer": 481,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 8 * 18 + 8 + 15 + 14",
            "Answer": 757,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 16 * 7 + 5 + 6 + 17",
            "Answer": 588,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 1 * 17 + 9 + 3 + 18",
            "Answer": 217,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 16 * 5 + 12 + 12 + 8",
            "Answer": 112,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 12 * 6 + 1 + 6 + 7",
            "Answer": 590,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 1 * 7 + 6 + 6 + 2",
            "Answer": 14,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 3 * 13 + 4 + 19 + 6",
            "Answer": 653,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 16 * 15 + 18 + 2 + 13",
            "Answer": 3633,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 9 * 16 + 8 + 12 + 11",
            "Answer": 2479,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 10 * 16 + 0 + 1 + 0",
            "Answer": 1601,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 2 * 3 + 17 + 8 + 19",
            "Answer": 128,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 5 * 0 + 0 + 1 + 13",
            "Answer": 14,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 12 * 13 + 16 + 16 + 5",
            "Answer": 1909,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 17 * 15 + 5 + 3 + 9",
            "Answer": 272,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 7 * 16 + 9 + 16 + 5",
            "Answer": 478,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 3 * 18 + 15 + 15 + 4",
            "Answer": 1060,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 7 * 16 + 12 + 7 + 10",
            "Answer": 1485,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 9 * 15 + 3 + 19 + 13",
            "Answer": 2060,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 9 * 1 + 18 + 8 + 18",
            "Answer": 206,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 13 * 3 + 9 + 4 + 8",
            "Answer": 528,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 12 * 2 + 9 + 17 + 5",
            "Answer": 463,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 7 * 19 + 15 + 5 + 2",
            "Answer": 1086,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 16 * 9 + 18 + 6 + 1",
            "Answer": 745,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 18 * 8 + 17 + 17 + 1",
            "Answer": 1043,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 8 * 18 + 9 + 8 + 8",
            "Answer": 601,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 17 * 8 + 7 + 14 + 12",
            "Answer": 2345,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 19 * 17 + 17 + 2 + 3",
            "Answer": 1637,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 15 * 8 + 17 + 11 + 2",
            "Answer": 30,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 4 * 15 + 6 + 7 + 17",
            "Answer": 150,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 13 * 7 + 7 + 15 + 1",
            "Answer": 751,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 13 * 12 + 6 + 10 + 15",
            "Answer": 2995,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 0 * 19 + 7 + 15 + 0",
            "Answer": 22,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 13 * 5 + 14 + 18 + 15",
            "Answer": 1282,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 18 * 19 + 7 + 2 + 0",
            "Answer": 5823,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 7 * 9 + 4 + 11 + 7",
            "Answer": 1030,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 9 * 0 + 9 + 18 + 4",
            "Answer": 31,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 2 * 19 + 10 + 14 + 14",
            "Answer": 760,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 16 * 2 + 12 + 16 + 7",
            "Answer": 547,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 13 * 14 + 5 + 5 + 9",
            "Answer": 383,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 15 * 5 + 1 + 10 + 15",
            "Answer": 476,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 16 * 19 + 15 + 7 + 3",
            "Answer": 3673,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 9 * 6 + 16 + 0 + 2",
            "Answer": 342,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 14 * 4 + 8 + 14 + 8",
            "Answer": 254,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 14 * 4 + 18 + 17 + 9",
            "Answer": 492,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 11 * 18 + 19 + 11 + 16",
            "Answer": 3610,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 0 * 10 + 18 + 5 + 4",
            "Answer": 27,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 12 * 8 + 13 + 17 + 9",
            "Answer": 999,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 3 * 17 + 15 + 19 + 4",
            "Answer": 89,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 17 * 13 + 1 + 12 + 16",
            "Answer": 1576,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 12 * 18 + 7 + 14 + 5",
            "Answer": 3482,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 5 * 2 + 4 + 17 + 1",
            "Answer": 22,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 0 * 16 + 13 + 19 + 3",
            "Answer": 35,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 5 * 5 + 9 + 19 + 11",
            "Answer": 389,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 6 * 1 + 18 + 5 + 2",
            "Answer": 121,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 1 * 13 + 9 + 14 + 13",
            "Answer": 179,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 12 * 16 + 5 + 17 + 1",
            "Answer": 2135,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 7 * 12 + 19 + 14 + 17",
            "Answer": 1646,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 9 * 11 + 7 + 11 + 1",
            "Answer": 514,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 12 * 9 + 12 + 10 + 4",
            "Answer": 350,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 19 * 11 + 11 + 12 + 19",
            "Answer": 3386,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 10 * 13 + 10 + 13 + 16",
            "Answer": 2509,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 12 * 19 + 2 + 18 + 9",
            "Answer": 3905,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 3 * 5 + 1 + 11 + 12",
            "Answer": 309,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 4 * 14 + 12 + 0 + 8",
            "Answer": 804,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 7 * 11 + 14 + 5 + 7",
            "Answer": 796,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 14 * 3 + 17 + 17 + 12",
            "Answer": 508,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + #"
        }
    ],
    "# * # * # * # * # * # * #": [
        {
            "Question": "5 * 17 * 9 * 15 * 16 * 1 * 16",
            "Answer": 2937600,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 4 * 2 * 3 * 9 * 8 * 9",
            "Answer": 233280,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 17 * 11 * 13 * 9 * 14 * 11",
            "Answer": 33693660,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 5 * 19 * 18 * 18 * 2 * 18",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 0 * 5 * 13 * 8 * 16 * 5",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 4 * 6 * 4 * 3 * 14 * 14",
            "Answer": 620928,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 14 * 6 * 2 * 0 * 18 * 7",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 3 * 3 * 14 * 11 * 1 * 17",
            "Answer": 447678,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 16 * 13 * 8 * 16 * 17 * 4",
            "Answer": 21725184,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 8 * 5 * 3 * 8 * 18 * 15",
            "Answer": 4147200,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 9 * 10 * 4 * 19 * 9 * 1",
            "Answer": 738720,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 17 * 12 * 12 * 5 * 5 * 11",
            "Answer": 4039200,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 8 * 14 * 3 * 10 * 1 * 15",
            "Answer": 957600,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 5 * 0 * 14 * 0 * 15 * 15",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 10 * 6 * 13 * 8 * 0 * 4",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 10 * 17 * 6 * 0 * 2 * 18",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 0 * 2 * 5 * 16 * 18 * 12",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 4 * 7 * 0 * 1 * 14 * 1",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 8 * 2 * 1 * 19 * 6 * 19",
            "Answer": 554496,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 13 * 0 * 1 * 11 * 9 * 5",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 2 * 15 * 8 * 3 * 2 * 9",
            "Answer": 207360,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 14 * 8 * 15 * 15 * 2 * 12",
            "Answer": 11491200,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 19 * 5 * 16 * 1 * 3 * 0",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 11 * 12 * 13 * 14 * 19 * 2",
            "Answer": 10954944,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 6 * 14 * 6 * 17 * 15 * 13",
            "Answer": 1670760,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 5 * 1 * 5 * 18 * 0 * 11",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 7 * 6 * 11 * 11 * 17 * 6",
            "Answer": 4665276,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 7 * 12 * 3 * 0 * 13 * 5",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 16 * 16 * 4 * 15 * 17 * 4",
            "Answer": 16711680,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 12 * 14 * 10 * 10 * 7 * 10",
            "Answer": 8232000,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 12 * 9 * 13 * 1 * 12 * 4",
            "Answer": 741312,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 15 * 0 * 6 * 4 * 8 * 3",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 0 * 8 * 0 * 14 * 16 * 13",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 18 * 10 * 7 * 8 * 16 * 4",
            "Answer": 12257280,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 14 * 9 * 3 * 2 * 19 * 14",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 15 * 16 * 13 * 2 * 12 * 0",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 15 * 6 * 0 * 2 * 0 * 9",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 11 * 8 * 10 * 14 * 10 * 3",
            "Answer": 739200,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 0 * 0 * 14 * 1 * 3 * 0",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 17 * 1 * 7 * 17 * 19 * 13",
            "Answer": 4497129,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 12 * 7 * 19 * 8 * 9 * 1",
            "Answer": 459648,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 11 * 12 * 3 * 6 * 6 * 8",
            "Answer": 456192,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 13 * 9 * 13 * 14 * 3 * 9",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 9 * 14 * 2 * 3 * 9 * 3",
            "Answer": 224532,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 6 * 16 * 19 * 9 * 15 * 5",
            "Answer": 14774400,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 0 * 9 * 11 * 14 * 0 * 15",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 7 * 15 * 16 * 9 * 5 * 18",
            "Answer": 21772800,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 1 * 14 * 18 * 9 * 1 * 3",
            "Answer": 122472,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 0 * 19 * 15 * 6 * 4 * 3",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 18 * 6 * 13 * 11 * 3 * 11",
            "Answer": 7644780,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 3 * 14 * 16 * 0 * 17 * 12",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 9 * 15 * 15 * 14 * 6 * 6",
            "Answer": 2041200,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 4 * 0 * 13 * 6 * 9 * 8",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 6 * 16 * 11 * 8 * 10 * 11",
            "Answer": 5575680,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 2 * 2 * 7 * 4 * 5 * 9",
            "Answer": 65520,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 1 * 18 * 2 * 18 * 9 * 13",
            "Answer": 75816,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 7 * 18 * 0 * 3 * 3 * 19",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 0 * 6 * 8 * 16 * 8 * 12",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 7 * 7 * 12 * 1 * 14 * 13",
            "Answer": 1284192,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 9 * 4 * 4 * 17 * 8 * 13",
            "Answer": 2036736,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 14 * 6 * 6 * 13 * 8 * 19",
            "Answer": 6971328,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 10 * 17 * 5 * 13 * 18 * 14",
            "Answer": 30630600,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 15 * 16 * 0 * 18 * 18 * 11",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 3 * 7 * 16 * 12 * 13 * 16",
            "Answer": 838656,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 9 * 17 * 6 * 1 * 4 * 5",
            "Answer": 91800,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 7 * 5 * 14 * 16 * 7 * 13",
            "Answer": 13555360,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 15 * 4 * 12 * 16 * 4 * 9",
            "Answer": 7464960,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 8 * 11 * 19 * 13 * 2 * 4",
            "Answer": 1738880,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 19 * 1 * 2 * 7 * 5 * 18",
            "Answer": 191520,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 1 * 2 * 15 * 12 * 1 * 6",
            "Answer": 36720,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 15 * 10 * 11 * 8 * 7 * 8",
            "Answer": 10348800,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 12 * 16 * 3 * 18 * 14 * 11",
            "Answer": 17563392,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 4 * 9 * 14 * 10 * 12 * 18",
            "Answer": 11975040,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 14 * 6 * 15 * 5 * 6 * 15",
            "Answer": 5670000,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 2 * 15 * 11 * 19 * 1 * 0",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 8 * 2 * 17 * 17 * 4 * 1",
            "Answer": 18496,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 17 * 11 * 6 * 15 * 6 * 4",
            "Answer": 6866640,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 14 * 3 * 9 * 15 * 0 * 9",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 10 * 19 * 1 * 17 * 16 * 16",
            "Answer": 15710720,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 12 * 13 * 16 * 18 * 13 * 6",
            "Answer": 21026304,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 13 * 11 * 15 * 10 * 15 * 14",
            "Answer": 9009000,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 2 * 15 * 2 * 14 * 18 * 4",
            "Answer": 786240,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 15 * 0 * 15 * 12 * 13 * 12",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 11 * 18 * 7 * 4 * 7 * 7",
            "Answer": 4618152,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 13 * 1 * 7 * 2 * 16 * 1",
            "Answer": 34944,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 19 * 14 * 18 * 12 * 17 * 12",
            "Answer": 117210240,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 4 * 16 * 19 * 3 * 3 * 6",
            "Answer": 590976,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 7 * 3 * 9 * 1 * 1 * 6",
            "Answer": 4536,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 18 * 2 * 3 * 19 * 17 * 1",
            "Answer": 558144,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 4 * 7 * 17 * 8 * 1 * 15",
            "Answer": 57120,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 7 * 13 * 16 * 10 * 7 * 6",
            "Answer": 9172800,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 11 * 11 * 8 * 14 * 16 * 3",
            "Answer": 4553472,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 3 * 16 * 4 * 5 * 16 * 11",
            "Answer": 506880,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 17 * 16 * 4 * 2 * 12 * 17",
            "Answer": 3107328,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 5 * 17 * 3 * 16 * 13 * 4",
            "Answer": 1697280,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 5 * 6 * 13 * 4 * 18 * 16",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 1 * 11 * 11 * 2 * 19 * 14",
            "Answer": 257488,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 6 * 9 * 8 * 5 * 14 * 11",
            "Answer": 4324320,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 11 * 5 * 13 * 1 * 6 * 8",
            "Answer": 274560,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 9 * 5 * 19 * 14 * 5 * 12",
            "Answer": 10773000,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # * #"
        }
    ],
    "# * # * # + # * # * # * #": [
        {
            "Question": "9 * 3 * 10 + 15 * 16 * 3 * 6",
            "Answer": 4590,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 14 * 9 + 19 * 2 * 16 * 6",
            "Answer": 4404,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 15 * 10 + 5 * 0 * 5 * 6",
            "Answer": 2550,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 2 * 7 + 6 * 12 * 10 * 19",
            "Answer": 13876,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 19 * 8 + 16 * 3 * 14 * 14",
            "Answer": 11232,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 19 * 12 + 19 * 0 * 0 * 18",
            "Answer": 4332,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 12 * 8 + 18 * 6 * 10 * 3",
            "Answer": 3240,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 19 * 7 + 16 * 10 * 15 * 2",
            "Answer": 4933,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 15 * 2 + 5 * 5 * 8 * 10",
            "Answer": 2090,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 2 * 15 + 13 * 17 * 5 * 14",
            "Answer": 15920,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 15 * 13 + 17 * 0 * 18 * 11",
            "Answer": 390,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 18 * 13 + 11 * 16 * 2 * 10",
            "Answer": 5392,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 9 * 11 + 17 * 5 * 7 * 4",
            "Answer": 4261,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 8 * 17 + 15 * 9 * 19 * 10",
            "Answer": 26330,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 13 * 19 + 8 * 14 * 12 * 8",
            "Answer": 12975,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 18 * 0 + 3 * 9 * 2 * 10",
            "Answer": 540,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 9 * 4 + 15 * 15 * 6 * 12",
            "Answer": 16884,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 9 * 5 + 5 * 6 * 2 * 3",
            "Answer": 675,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 3 * 13 + 9 * 10 * 11 * 11",
            "Answer": 11007,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 4 * 19 + 17 * 8 * 4 * 5",
            "Answer": 3860,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 1 * 16 + 18 * 16 * 13 * 7",
            "Answer": 26304,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 18 * 9 + 4 * 7 * 18 * 4",
            "Answer": 4608,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 3 * 1 + 16 * 14 * 12 * 4",
            "Answer": 10761,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 3 * 11 + 8 * 0 * 10 * 15",
            "Answer": 33,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 3 * 4 + 9 * 2 * 9 * 16",
            "Answer": 2652,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 8 * 3 + 6 * 3 * 18 * 15",
            "Answer": 5028,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 15 * 16 + 18 * 3 * 17 * 2",
            "Answer": 6396,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 0 * 16 + 11 * 10 * 17 * 9",
            "Answer": 16830,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 5 * 10 + 19 * 8 * 2 * 1",
            "Answer": 504,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 4 * 10 + 9 * 14 * 9 * 12",
            "Answer": 13728,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 0 * 14 + 6 * 14 * 19 * 5",
            "Answer": 7980,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 9 * 14 + 6 * 3 * 7 * 10",
            "Answer": 1512,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 13 * 11 + 19 * 18 * 2 * 2",
            "Answer": 1797,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 15 * 5 + 16 * 8 * 0 * 0",
            "Answer": 825,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 7 * 7 + 6 * 2 * 8 * 13",
            "Answer": 2130,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 0 * 1 + 10 * 2 * 19 * 3",
            "Answer": 1140,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 0 * 3 + 4 * 16 * 17 * 9",
            "Answer": 9792,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 11 * 0 + 14 * 17 * 14 * 9",
            "Answer": 29988,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 11 * 4 + 10 * 9 * 8 * 15",
            "Answer": 11416,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 0 * 19 + 3 * 18 * 11 * 0",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 7 * 0 + 13 * 8 * 6 * 3",
            "Answer": 1872,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 3 * 8 + 5 * 16 * 8 * 15",
            "Answer": 9816,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 10 * 17 + 9 * 13 * 7 * 8",
            "Answer": 7232,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 6 * 2 + 10 * 16 * 19 * 10",
            "Answer": 30400,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 8 * 18 + 4 * 9 * 5 * 15",
            "Answer": 2700,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 11 * 19 + 10 * 12 * 10 * 17",
            "Answer": 21445,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 1 * 8 + 4 * 10 * 7 * 9",
            "Answer": 2552,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 7 * 5 + 4 * 17 * 2 * 2",
            "Answer": 762,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 18 * 9 + 0 * 18 * 15 * 14",
            "Answer": 2268,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 6 * 17 + 14 * 8 * 13 * 0",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 0 * 15 + 12 * 13 * 5 * 17",
            "Answer": 13260,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 2 * 4 + 5 * 4 * 10 * 0",
            "Answer": 136,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 10 * 2 + 12 * 6 * 11 * 2",
            "Answer": 1844,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 14 * 12 + 9 * 8 * 1 * 9",
            "Answer": 984,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 1 * 2 + 13 * 9 * 10 * 0",
            "Answer": 16,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 19 * 4 + 2 * 6 * 18 * 10",
            "Answer": 3376,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 9 * 2 + 5 * 0 * 11 * 1",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 10 * 14 + 6 * 7 * 4 * 8",
            "Answer": 3584,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 16 * 0 + 4 * 1 * 15 * 11",
            "Answer": 660,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 18 * 11 + 13 * 4 * 13 * 17",
            "Answer": 15254,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 16 * 9 + 11 * 17 * 5 * 4",
            "Answer": 4748,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 19 * 3 + 6 * 5 * 11 * 14",
            "Answer": 5247,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 2 * 17 + 10 * 17 * 18 * 13",
            "Answer": 40188,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 3 * 19 + 11 * 11 * 19 * 6",
            "Answer": 14763,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 13 * 13 + 15 * 13 * 9 * 10",
            "Answer": 19916,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 19 * 18 + 19 * 19 * 8 * 3",
            "Answer": 10032,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 2 * 1 + 14 * 9 * 15 * 17",
            "Answer": 32142,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 9 * 18 + 15 * 0 * 15 * 1",
            "Answer": 1296,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 1 * 13 + 7 * 2 * 17 * 3",
            "Answer": 948,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 17 * 0 + 12 * 14 * 15 * 16",
            "Answer": 40320,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 1 * 1 + 16 * 9 * 5 * 3",
            "Answer": 2165,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 6 * 3 + 5 * 13 * 0 * 18",
            "Answer": 54,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 6 * 10 + 9 * 4 * 15 * 13",
            "Answer": 7980,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 8 * 18 + 3 * 1 * 10 * 19",
            "Answer": 1722,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 15 * 14 + 7 * 13 * 8 * 6",
            "Answer": 5208,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 8 * 17 + 19 * 10 * 18 * 10",
            "Answer": 36376,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 4 * 11 + 0 * 8 * 8 * 19",
            "Answer": 220,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 2 * 6 + 18 * 16 * 12 * 1",
            "Answer": 3540,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 10 * 15 + 10 * 18 * 11 * 5",
            "Answer": 11850,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 12 * 7 + 8 * 10 * 5 * 8",
            "Answer": 4712,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 0 * 12 + 7 * 9 * 17 * 6",
            "Answer": 6426,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 19 * 19 + 6 * 2 * 13 * 0",
            "Answer": 3610,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 14 * 1 + 14 * 3 * 5 * 12",
            "Answer": 2674,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 16 * 16 + 16 * 2 * 7 * 18",
            "Answer": 8384,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 11 * 7 + 4 * 5 * 6 * 0",
            "Answer": 770,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 17 * 7 + 3 * 9 * 17 * 8",
            "Answer": 5219,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 12 * 11 + 5 * 11 * 4 * 8",
            "Answer": 2024,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 9 * 6 + 12 * 14 * 17 * 7",
            "Answer": 20100,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 10 * 4 + 19 * 12 * 12 * 19",
            "Answer": 52424,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 11 * 10 + 12 * 2 * 8 * 3",
            "Answer": 1676,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 13 * 0 + 10 * 12 * 7 * 9",
            "Answer": 7560,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 5 * 8 + 9 * 18 * 11 * 15",
            "Answer": 27210,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 15 * 7 + 19 * 1 * 9 * 13",
            "Answer": 3378,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 1 * 17 + 13 * 2 * 18 * 11",
            "Answer": 5335,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 1 * 1 + 4 * 6 * 13 * 0",
            "Answer": 17,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 0 * 7 + 2 * 7 * 15 * 11",
            "Answer": 2310,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 16 * 9 + 5 * 19 * 0 * 14",
            "Answer": 2448,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 0 * 12 + 10 * 4 * 19 * 11",
            "Answer": 8360,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 11 * 14 + 14 * 16 * 15 * 19",
            "Answer": 65534,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 6 * 2 + 2 * 17 * 8 * 1",
            "Answer": 356,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # * #"
        }
    ],
    "# + # * # * # * # * # + #": [
        {
            "Question": "8 + 10 * 3 * 3 * 15 * 18 + 1",
            "Answer": 24309,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 8 * 11 * 5 * 14 * 10 + 10",
            "Answer": 61623,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 17 * 15 * 15 * 4 * 1 + 17",
            "Answer": 15326,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 8 * 1 * 11 * 11 * 5 + 1",
            "Answer": 4856,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 5 * 6 * 1 * 11 * 3 + 13",
            "Answer": 1021,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 19 * 0 * 6 * 6 * 14 + 0",
            "Answer": 4,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 2 * 18 * 6 * 16 * 7 + 14",
            "Answer": 24213,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 0 * 8 * 6 * 4 * 1 + 10",
            "Answer": 16,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 2 * 2 * 0 * 8 * 10 + 14",
            "Answer": 14,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 9 * 17 * 19 * 6 * 2 + 18",
            "Answer": 34917,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 17 * 17 * 1 * 9 * 3 + 1",
            "Answer": 7804,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 3 * 18 * 4 * 6 * 3 + 14",
            "Answer": 3912,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 14 * 10 * 19 * 1 * 6 + 13",
            "Answer": 15988,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 5 * 14 * 7 * 5 * 16 + 12",
            "Answer": 39221,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 17 * 17 * 9 * 10 * 19 + 1",
            "Answer": 494193,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 19 * 15 * 14 * 1 * 9 + 15",
            "Answer": 35926,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 16 * 16 * 15 * 16 * 2 + 5",
            "Answer": 122897,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 15 * 8 * 5 * 0 * 15 + 4",
            "Answer": 7,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 19 * 15 * 0 * 9 * 15 + 19",
            "Answer": 29,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 4 * 6 * 0 * 8 * 12 + 11",
            "Answer": 19,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 8 * 2 * 11 * 3 * 14 + 19",
            "Answer": 7420,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 6 * 15 * 1 * 7 * 1 + 2",
            "Answer": 650,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 5 * 10 * 13 * 3 * 4 + 14",
            "Answer": 7821,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 16 * 19 * 5 * 18 * 13 + 3",
            "Answer": 355694,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 6 * 11 * 12 * 16 * 13 + 19",
            "Answer": 164770,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 0 * 3 * 7 * 4 * 18 + 13",
            "Answer": 23,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 14 * 8 * 2 * 13 * 13 + 2",
            "Answer": 37869,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 10 * 12 * 7 * 7 * 11 + 11",
            "Answer": 64701,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 8 * 8 * 16 * 11 * 9 + 2",
            "Answer": 101393,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 4 * 8 * 11 * 5 * 5 + 5",
            "Answer": 8807,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 16 * 4 * 13 * 11 * 4 + 5",
            "Answer": 36625,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 6 * 4 * 18 * 17 * 19 + 8",
            "Answer": 139559,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 2 * 17 * 18 * 8 * 16 + 9",
            "Answer": 78346,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 15 * 2 * 14 * 15 * 12 + 1",
            "Answer": 75610,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 0 * 3 * 3 * 13 * 12 + 18",
            "Answer": 35,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 15 * 10 * 9 * 8 * 12 + 3",
            "Answer": 129615,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 12 * 2 * 14 * 1 * 16 + 8",
            "Answer": 5389,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 12 * 5 * 8 * 5 * 9 + 2",
            "Answer": 21613,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 14 * 8 * 5 * 15 * 16 + 13",
            "Answer": 134416,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 1 * 15 * 1 * 7 * 18 + 13",
            "Answer": 1905,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 11 * 10 * 5 * 0 * 8 + 10",
            "Answer": 29,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 0 * 7 * 8 * 9 * 1 + 11",
            "Answer": 19,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 19 * 18 * 13 * 3 * 18 + 0",
            "Answer": 240090,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 7 * 17 * 8 * 10 * 13 + 0",
            "Answer": 123778,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 2 * 6 * 11 * 7 * 19 + 15",
            "Answer": 17571,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 1 * 15 * 14 * 16 * 5 + 16",
            "Answer": 16825,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 1 * 11 * 1 * 8 * 18 + 7",
            "Answer": 1600,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 17 * 12 * 13 * 4 * 0 + 10",
            "Answer": 29,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 9 * 5 * 7 * 7 * 12 + 14",
            "Answer": 26487,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 5 * 14 * 6 * 9 * 2 + 7",
            "Answer": 7572,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 12 * 1 * 10 * 1 * 7 + 3",
            "Answer": 855,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 11 * 3 * 0 * 4 * 2 + 10",
            "Answer": 10,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 18 * 6 * 5 * 16 * 9 + 15",
            "Answer": 77786,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 11 * 2 * 2 * 0 * 13 + 19",
            "Answer": 34,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 9 * 10 * 18 * 9 * 2 + 7",
            "Answer": 29174,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 9 * 11 * 0 * 14 * 10 + 15",
            "Answer": 31,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 17 * 9 * 8 * 9 * 2 + 18",
            "Answer": 22066,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 10 * 13 * 3 * 14 * 10 + 3",
            "Answer": 54604,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 6 * 4 * 16 * 17 * 1 + 18",
            "Answer": 6555,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 4 * 5 * 13 * 9 * 15 + 9",
            "Answer": 35109,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 5 * 10 * 8 * 8 * 18 + 8",
            "Answer": 57620,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 6 * 15 * 9 * 19 * 18 + 5",
            "Answer": 277033,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 11 * 1 * 11 * 7 * 7 + 10",
            "Answer": 5958,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 8 * 8 * 15 * 15 * 3 + 4",
            "Answer": 43221,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 7 * 4 * 4 * 13 * 0 + 16",
            "Answer": 24,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 4 * 11 * 17 * 7 * 3 + 1",
            "Answer": 15724,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 16 * 18 * 0 * 4 * 17 + 14",
            "Answer": 18,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 18 * 5 * 5 * 19 * 9 + 2",
            "Answer": 76954,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 6 * 14 * 16 * 3 * 12 + 19",
            "Answer": 48407,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 5 * 2 * 17 * 12 * 10 + 16",
            "Answer": 20421,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 1 * 9 * 10 * 11 * 5 + 1",
            "Answer": 4968,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 5 * 8 * 8 * 16 * 3 + 19",
            "Answer": 15397,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 7 * 5 * 9 * 3 * 9 + 7",
            "Answer": 8517,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 3 * 8 * 7 * 9 * 7 + 6",
            "Answer": 10597,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 5 * 19 * 10 * 9 * 6 + 18",
            "Answer": 51329,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 15 * 4 * 1 * 10 * 18 + 18",
            "Answer": 10834,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 7 * 16 * 0 * 9 * 11 + 10",
            "Answer": 27,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 8 * 2 * 14 * 0 * 19 + 6",
            "Answer": 10,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 5 * 0 * 9 * 9 * 3 + 6",
            "Answer": 16,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 3 * 12 * 8 * 13 * 12 + 12",
            "Answer": 44945,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 9 * 17 * 9 * 19 * 9 + 16",
            "Answer": 235488,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 12 * 13 * 5 * 10 * 8 + 11",
            "Answer": 62415,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 10 * 16 * 12 * 11 * 16 + 5",
            "Answer": 337939,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 13 * 11 * 8 * 4 * 9 + 17",
            "Answer": 41202,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 7 * 5 * 18 * 12 * 18 + 10",
            "Answer": 136099,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 4 * 6 * 17 * 13 * 8 + 15",
            "Answer": 42449,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 10 * 3 * 6 * 6 * 1 + 5",
            "Answer": 1086,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 4 * 16 * 9 * 15 * 1 + 3",
            "Answer": 8657,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 3 * 12 * 19 * 5 * 7 + 7",
            "Answer": 23949,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 2 * 4 * 7 * 9 * 1 + 11",
            "Answer": 521,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 3 * 11 * 14 * 10 * 5 + 0",
            "Answer": 23112,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 11 * 15 * 14 * 5 * 15 + 5",
            "Answer": 173267,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 12 * 11 * 18 * 4 * 5 + 14",
            "Answer": 47540,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 3 * 16 * 12 * 12 * 14 + 2",
            "Answer": 96787,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 18 * 12 * 4 * 13 * 16 + 19",
            "Answer": 179735,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 3 * 7 * 19 * 16 * 5 + 10",
            "Answer": 31935,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 1 * 11 * 14 * 9 * 6 + 15",
            "Answer": 8343,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 12 * 18 * 7 * 9 * 12 + 7",
            "Answer": 163315,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 10 * 14 * 2 * 13 * 7 + 14",
            "Answer": 25502,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 6 * 2 * 4 * 7 * 19 + 1",
            "Answer": 6402,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # + #"
        }
    ],
    "# * # + # + # * # * # * #": [
        {
            "Question": "4 * 5 + 10 + 9 * 12 * 0 * 16",
            "Answer": 30,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 5 + 6 + 7 * 1 * 4 * 8",
            "Answer": 325,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 1 + 10 + 0 * 10 * 7 * 3",
            "Answer": 23,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 5 + 4 + 13 * 14 * 10 * 16",
            "Answer": 29214,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 12 + 10 + 8 * 2 * 2 * 8",
            "Answer": 458,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 19 + 3 + 4 * 8 * 15 * 17",
            "Answer": 8391,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 10 + 0 + 19 * 12 * 18 * 16",
            "Answer": 65704,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 15 + 14 + 14 * 19 * 8 * 12",
            "Answer": 25625,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 9 + 5 + 15 * 1 * 3 * 9",
            "Answer": 509,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 4 + 7 + 4 * 11 * 10 * 13",
            "Answer": 5747,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 6 + 18 + 19 * 15 * 3 * 14",
            "Answer": 12006,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 3 + 13 + 17 * 4 * 6 * 2",
            "Answer": 841,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 7 + 5 + 11 * 1 * 11 * 18",
            "Answer": 2232,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 19 + 13 + 10 * 13 * 17 * 16",
            "Answer": 35506,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 11 + 11 + 15 * 8 * 17 * 10",
            "Answer": 20411,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 19 + 7 + 2 * 7 * 14 * 14",
            "Answer": 2751,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 18 + 16 + 3 * 4 * 6 * 16",
            "Answer": 1222,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 8 + 8 + 4 * 6 * 6 * 1",
            "Answer": 232,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 18 + 19 + 17 * 5 * 9 * 1",
            "Answer": 784,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 11 + 15 + 9 * 4 * 19 * 12",
            "Answer": 8245,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 2 + 0 + 16 * 1 * 16 * 19",
            "Answer": 4868,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 12 + 8 + 14 * 6 * 15 * 8",
            "Answer": 10100,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 7 + 9 + 4 * 9 * 7 * 0",
            "Answer": 121,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 9 + 0 + 13 * 10 * 8 * 18",
            "Answer": 18891,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 16 + 15 + 3 * 19 * 7 * 1",
            "Answer": 606,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 6 + 13 + 5 * 13 * 11 * 13",
            "Answer": 9368,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 11 + 7 + 13 * 2 * 14 * 1",
            "Answer": 404,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 8 + 9 + 12 * 7 * 18 * 15",
            "Answer": 22785,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 9 + 15 + 12 * 14 * 17 * 13",
            "Answer": 37179,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 3 + 10 + 3 * 7 * 5 * 18",
            "Answer": 1951,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 2 + 13 + 18 * 10 * 14 * 3",
            "Answer": 7599,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 10 + 15 + 14 * 0 * 7 * 18",
            "Answer": 85,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 18 + 11 + 15 * 13 * 10 * 5",
            "Answer": 9779,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 9 + 19 + 10 * 7 * 3 * 10",
            "Answer": 2272,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 6 + 18 + 18 * 1 * 14 * 5",
            "Answer": 1392,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 5 + 2 + 9 * 17 * 3 * 15",
            "Answer": 6897,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 15 + 14 + 17 * 10 * 0 * 8",
            "Answer": 149,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 6 + 11 + 9 * 2 * 17 * 9",
            "Answer": 2765,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 12 + 2 + 16 * 17 * 15 * 0",
            "Answer": 98,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 19 + 10 + 4 * 15 * 3 * 15",
            "Answer": 2805,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 9 + 1 + 8 * 1 * 9 * 9",
            "Answer": 721,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 15 + 10 + 0 * 17 * 5 * 10",
            "Answer": 55,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 13 + 12 + 1 * 5 * 14 * 14",
            "Answer": 992,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 12 + 13 + 4 * 19 * 5 * 5",
            "Answer": 1913,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 13 + 10 + 16 * 2 * 1 * 19",
            "Answer": 631,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 12 + 9 + 3 * 4 * 7 * 0",
            "Answer": 105,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 13 + 8 + 12 * 0 * 18 * 17",
            "Answer": 73,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 11 + 5 + 8 * 15 * 5 * 19",
            "Answer": 11416,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 4 + 1 + 16 * 9 * 11 * 6",
            "Answer": 9545,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 4 + 13 + 19 * 2 * 7 * 16",
            "Answer": 4321,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 6 + 2 + 6 * 10 * 0 * 14",
            "Answer": 62,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 16 + 12 + 10 * 6 * 8 * 17",
            "Answer": 8220,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 3 + 14 + 15 * 15 * 0 * 5",
            "Answer": 50,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 18 + 14 + 11 * 9 * 2 * 9",
            "Answer": 1994,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 19 + 15 + 11 * 2 * 19 * 11",
            "Answer": 4955,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 17 + 1 + 7 * 15 * 17 * 0",
            "Answer": 188,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 13 + 16 + 9 * 15 * 19 * 10",
            "Answer": 25718,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 16 + 2 + 5 * 17 * 7 * 7",
            "Answer": 4183,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 2 + 8 + 9 * 7 * 8 * 13",
            "Answer": 6576,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 11 + 10 + 15 * 6 * 19 * 8",
            "Answer": 13701,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 2 + 13 + 0 * 18 * 13 * 5",
            "Answer": 43,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 4 + 7 + 5 * 6 * 11 * 13",
            "Answer": 4317,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 7 + 14 + 8 * 18 * 19 * 10",
            "Answer": 27381,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 1 + 8 + 8 * 13 * 9 * 16",
            "Answer": 14990,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 7 + 17 + 7 * 7 * 10 * 5",
            "Answer": 2502,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 3 + 9 + 7 * 4 * 8 * 2",
            "Answer": 457,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 9 + 15 + 18 * 16 * 18 * 9",
            "Answer": 46698,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 19 + 8 + 1 * 8 * 15 * 9",
            "Answer": 1411,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 12 + 19 + 5 * 15 * 17 * 6",
            "Answer": 7789,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 16 + 14 + 8 * 4 * 6 * 9",
            "Answer": 1950,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 11 + 2 + 16 * 11 * 2 * 16",
            "Answer": 5744,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 3 + 7 + 11 * 2 * 4 * 19",
            "Answer": 1697,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 12 + 12 + 13 * 13 * 9 * 12",
            "Answer": 18336,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 4 + 15 + 9 * 3 * 14 * 12",
            "Answer": 4599,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 3 + 17 + 6 * 1 * 6 * 1",
            "Answer": 56,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 6 + 6 + 15 * 7 * 15 * 5",
            "Answer": 7917,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 8 + 2 + 0 * 10 * 9 * 17",
            "Answer": 18,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 14 + 8 + 0 * 12 * 16 * 0",
            "Answer": 106,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 10 + 9 + 2 * 14 * 4 * 10",
            "Answer": 1149,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 10 + 14 + 7 * 13 * 0 * 14",
            "Answer": 104,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 5 + 2 + 16 * 5 * 5 * 15",
            "Answer": 6002,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 12 + 19 + 5 * 9 * 12 * 4",
            "Answer": 2275,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 10 + 12 + 3 * 11 * 0 * 5",
            "Answer": 32,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 2 + 11 + 18 * 0 * 9 * 0",
            "Answer": 31,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 5 + 12 + 5 * 1 * 13 * 12",
            "Answer": 792,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 19 + 13 + 1 * 5 * 14 * 11",
            "Answer": 954,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 11 + 5 + 8 * 17 * 7 * 3",
            "Answer": 3048,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 8 + 1 + 16 * 7 * 7 * 2",
            "Answer": 1601,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 10 + 16 + 11 * 8 * 18 * 2",
            "Answer": 3354,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 2 + 7 + 19 * 12 * 18 * 16",
            "Answer": 65697,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 12 + 1 + 18 * 5 * 3 * 4",
            "Answer": 1285,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 15 + 4 + 16 * 6 * 17 * 15",
            "Answer": 24619,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 1 + 3 + 0 * 4 * 3 * 4",
            "Answer": 9,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 6 + 0 + 0 * 4 * 6 * 10",
            "Answer": 48,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 9 + 10 + 16 * 2 * 5 * 11",
            "Answer": 1860,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 8 + 7 + 7 * 9 * 7 * 11",
            "Answer": 4882,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 11 + 8 + 17 * 3 * 13 * 3",
            "Answer": 2063,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 17 + 0 + 10 * 8 * 17 * 16",
            "Answer": 21879,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 1 + 7 + 5 * 1 * 17 * 18",
            "Answer": 1537,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 17 + 3 + 0 * 10 * 15 * 2",
            "Answer": 105,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # * #"
        }
    ],
    "# * # + # + # + # + # * #": [
        {
            "Question": "6 * 1 + 16 + 13 + 14 + 17 * 14",
            "Answer": 287,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 10 + 16 + 14 + 13 + 3 * 7",
            "Answer": 174,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 5 + 5 + 16 + 8 + 11 * 4",
            "Answer": 143,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 13 + 16 + 13 + 16 + 11 * 12",
            "Answer": 281,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 16 + 0 + 12 + 9 + 0 * 19",
            "Answer": 277,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 7 + 0 + 7 + 13 + 7 * 14",
            "Answer": 181,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 7 + 16 + 16 + 14 + 19 * 13",
            "Answer": 335,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 16 + 3 + 1 + 18 + 8 * 16",
            "Answer": 166,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 9 + 13 + 11 + 1 + 16 * 16",
            "Answer": 290,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 11 + 7 + 4 + 0 + 7 * 16",
            "Answer": 321,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 18 + 16 + 10 + 10 + 5 * 14",
            "Answer": 196,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 8 + 19 + 18 + 6 + 3 * 3",
            "Answer": 188,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 9 + 6 + 15 + 0 + 12 * 10",
            "Answer": 285,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 4 + 1 + 0 + 5 + 14 * 11",
            "Answer": 180,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 2 + 16 + 15 + 12 + 16 * 14",
            "Answer": 295,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 10 + 17 + 2 + 5 + 18 * 0",
            "Answer": 144,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 10 + 16 + 9 + 15 + 10 * 8",
            "Answer": 160,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 12 + 19 + 15 + 8 + 3 * 15",
            "Answer": 123,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 18 + 17 + 18 + 1 + 9 * 4",
            "Answer": 342,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 9 + 17 + 12 + 5 + 12 * 4",
            "Answer": 226,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 6 + 13 + 9 + 3 + 17 * 0",
            "Answer": 79,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 17 + 2 + 6 + 5 + 4 * 0",
            "Answer": 47,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 0 + 10 + 2 + 12 + 18 * 15",
            "Answer": 294,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 6 + 7 + 14 + 0 + 4 * 2",
            "Answer": 125,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 8 + 1 + 14 + 16 + 3 * 15",
            "Answer": 188,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 7 + 11 + 2 + 12 + 0 * 3",
            "Answer": 46,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 10 + 16 + 11 + 19 + 19 * 4",
            "Answer": 272,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 6 + 0 + 6 + 8 + 18 * 17",
            "Answer": 374,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 17 + 10 + 8 + 13 + 9 * 15",
            "Answer": 472,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 17 + 12 + 17 + 6 + 7 * 0",
            "Answer": 307,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 3 + 2 + 11 + 6 + 7 * 13",
            "Answer": 161,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 19 + 4 + 1 + 16 + 17 * 1",
            "Answer": 76,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 17 + 2 + 17 + 6 + 14 * 0",
            "Answer": 263,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 12 + 0 + 1 + 1 + 3 * 12",
            "Answer": 182,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 0 + 15 + 18 + 14 + 2 * 10",
            "Answer": 67,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 19 + 17 + 9 + 4 + 16 * 16",
            "Answer": 324,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 1 + 11 + 10 + 5 + 8 * 11",
            "Answer": 117,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 8 + 11 + 14 + 6 + 3 * 6",
            "Answer": 129,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 0 + 4 + 7 + 8 + 15 * 9",
            "Answer": 154,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 11 + 0 + 2 + 0 + 12 * 2",
            "Answer": 158,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 19 + 17 + 8 + 11 + 17 * 7",
            "Answer": 250,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 5 + 5 + 18 + 5 + 4 * 3",
            "Answer": 45,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 13 + 4 + 0 + 4 + 14 * 3",
            "Answer": 89,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 15 + 5 + 3 + 11 + 1 * 2",
            "Answer": 111,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 13 + 0 + 4 + 15 + 19 * 9",
            "Answer": 255,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 19 + 7 + 6 + 7 + 13 * 0",
            "Answer": 20,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 11 + 2 + 4 + 12 + 17 * 18",
            "Answer": 324,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 6 + 1 + 9 + 11 + 5 * 0",
            "Answer": 75,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 15 + 7 + 11 + 16 + 11 * 4",
            "Answer": 333,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 2 + 19 + 6 + 7 + 17 * 19",
            "Answer": 367,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 10 + 12 + 13 + 12 + 16 * 14",
            "Answer": 351,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 6 + 14 + 5 + 0 + 11 * 4",
            "Answer": 177,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 9 + 16 + 0 + 3 + 12 * 1",
            "Answer": 58,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 19 + 1 + 9 + 4 + 8 * 4",
            "Answer": 179,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 9 + 17 + 11 + 5 + 16 * 13",
            "Answer": 322,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 16 + 9 + 14 + 18 + 0 * 11",
            "Answer": 73,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 1 + 1 + 17 + 13 + 1 * 16",
            "Answer": 47,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 17 + 8 + 2 + 4 + 13 * 11",
            "Answer": 310,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 5 + 19 + 11 + 8 + 8 * 9",
            "Answer": 140,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 12 + 0 + 18 + 14 + 19 * 6",
            "Answer": 326,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 4 + 17 + 9 + 9 + 12 * 12",
            "Answer": 215,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 8 + 10 + 3 + 16 + 5 * 11",
            "Answer": 220,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 17 + 13 + 9 + 11 + 18 * 3",
            "Answer": 189,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 17 + 16 + 18 + 2 + 3 * 13",
            "Answer": 279,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 9 + 9 + 6 + 5 + 0 * 8",
            "Answer": 119,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 16 + 10 + 2 + 1 + 7 * 19",
            "Answer": 450,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 2 + 2 + 12 + 17 + 17 * 16",
            "Answer": 331,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 12 + 10 + 19 + 11 + 17 * 16",
            "Answer": 480,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 7 + 1 + 9 + 10 + 6 * 3",
            "Answer": 66,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 9 + 10 + 16 + 15 + 11 * 10",
            "Answer": 232,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 6 + 17 + 18 + 19 + 11 * 7",
            "Answer": 239,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 4 + 16 + 19 + 18 + 12 * 17",
            "Answer": 265,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 12 + 1 + 0 + 4 + 1 * 11",
            "Answer": 244,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 7 + 18 + 3 + 11 + 16 * 5",
            "Answer": 140,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 13 + 18 + 3 + 9 + 7 * 18",
            "Answer": 364,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 4 + 2 + 13 + 9 + 9 * 19",
            "Answer": 231,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 13 + 15 + 6 + 4 + 10 * 19",
            "Answer": 293,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 2 + 13 + 7 + 8 + 19 * 10",
            "Answer": 256,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 10 + 17 + 10 + 7 + 1 * 5",
            "Answer": 219,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 10 + 8 + 12 + 10 + 18 * 2",
            "Answer": 166,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 10 + 1 + 10 + 18 + 17 * 5",
            "Answer": 214,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 4 + 11 + 14 + 19 + 12 * 2",
            "Answer": 128,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 17 + 2 + 5 + 11 + 9 * 7",
            "Answer": 302,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 11 + 0 + 5 + 15 + 9 * 17",
            "Answer": 250,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 18 + 18 + 11 + 16 + 10 * 9",
            "Answer": 441,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 5 + 11 + 13 + 13 + 4 * 18",
            "Answer": 184,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 17 + 16 + 19 + 3 + 12 * 18",
            "Answer": 560,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 19 + 18 + 5 + 6 + 18 * 10",
            "Answer": 456,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 2 + 2 + 0 + 3 + 7 * 10",
            "Answer": 93,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 9 + 0 + 18 + 10 + 9 * 11",
            "Answer": 208,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 1 + 4 + 2 + 1 + 8 * 8",
            "Answer": 89,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 16 + 15 + 18 + 9 + 1 * 4",
            "Answer": 62,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 3 + 11 + 11 + 2 + 1 * 0",
            "Answer": 45,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 19 + 0 + 16 + 19 + 14 * 1",
            "Answer": 391,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 7 + 0 + 19 + 8 + 17 * 11",
            "Answer": 221,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 6 + 0 + 1 + 3 + 0 * 13",
            "Answer": 76,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 9 + 1 + 10 + 3 + 11 * 5",
            "Answer": 177,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 10 + 5 + 17 + 1 + 2 * 19",
            "Answer": 171,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 16 + 3 + 17 + 4 + 19 * 1",
            "Answer": 267,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 19 + 13 + 1 + 16 + 5 * 10",
            "Answer": 118,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # * #"
        }
    ],
    "# + # + # * # + # + # * #": [
        {
            "Question": "1 + 8 + 8 * 18 + 14 + 19 * 6",
            "Answer": 281,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 14 + 1 * 19 + 16 + 6 * 14",
            "Answer": 146,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 7 + 12 * 0 + 1 + 2 * 15",
            "Answer": 56,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 5 + 16 * 12 + 1 + 9 * 3",
            "Answer": 241,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 16 + 14 * 15 + 16 + 10 * 7",
            "Answer": 327,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 14 + 3 * 15 + 2 + 5 * 2",
            "Answer": 72,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 17 + 6 * 5 + 4 + 1 * 13",
            "Answer": 72,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 1 + 5 * 4 + 17 + 1 * 14",
            "Answer": 66,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 8 + 13 * 0 + 12 + 11 * 16",
            "Answer": 201,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 8 + 16 * 2 + 9 + 5 * 4",
            "Answer": 80,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 2 + 18 * 10 + 15 + 9 * 2",
            "Answer": 232,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 2 + 14 * 14 + 10 + 6 * 12",
            "Answer": 288,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 5 + 19 * 16 + 19 + 18 * 11",
            "Answer": 541,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 0 + 10 * 11 + 3 + 18 * 6",
            "Answer": 239,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 17 + 9 * 2 + 5 + 2 * 13",
            "Answer": 68,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 15 + 17 * 2 + 18 + 8 * 7",
            "Answer": 128,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 7 + 2 * 18 + 3 + 1 * 19",
            "Answer": 83,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 17 + 11 * 11 + 16 + 10 * 14",
            "Answer": 308,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 13 + 18 * 6 + 17 + 16 * 2",
            "Answer": 182,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 7 + 14 * 13 + 7 + 13 * 8",
            "Answer": 301,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 6 + 9 * 10 + 13 + 12 * 8",
            "Answer": 211,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 9 + 17 * 12 + 3 + 9 * 9",
            "Answer": 305,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 16 + 4 * 11 + 10 + 1 * 17",
            "Answer": 88,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 19 + 8 * 14 + 4 + 13 * 13",
            "Answer": 312,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 12 + 0 * 5 + 1 + 14 * 3",
            "Answer": 61,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 12 + 14 * 19 + 18 + 9 * 5",
            "Answer": 360,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 3 + 1 * 6 + 10 + 7 * 18",
            "Answer": 160,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 11 + 15 * 17 + 7 + 0 * 18",
            "Answer": 289,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 18 + 5 * 17 + 17 + 4 * 11",
            "Answer": 182,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 0 + 14 * 5 + 18 + 10 * 19",
            "Answer": 294,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 5 + 17 * 9 + 0 + 15 * 18",
            "Answer": 445,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 10 + 16 * 17 + 17 + 18 * 9",
            "Answer": 479,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 9 + 19 * 0 + 11 + 10 * 8",
            "Answer": 111,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 14 + 19 * 10 + 14 + 8 * 7",
            "Answer": 282,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 11 + 11 * 0 + 2 + 13 * 17",
            "Answer": 238,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 17 + 14 * 17 + 7 + 16 * 0",
            "Answer": 279,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 4 + 5 * 11 + 9 + 10 * 12",
            "Answer": 198,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 9 + 8 * 12 + 4 + 4 * 10",
            "Answer": 166,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 16 + 4 * 16 + 3 + 15 * 0",
            "Answer": 85,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 15 + 3 * 0 + 0 + 9 * 8",
            "Answer": 92,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 3 + 16 * 7 + 8 + 7 * 3",
            "Answer": 144,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 9 + 18 * 12 + 13 + 17 * 17",
            "Answer": 530,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 6 + 18 * 19 + 2 + 15 * 3",
            "Answer": 395,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 7 + 16 * 2 + 12 + 13 * 17",
            "Answer": 285,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 18 + 9 * 6 + 19 + 7 * 18",
            "Answer": 234,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 2 + 19 * 5 + 3 + 13 * 1",
            "Answer": 127,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 0 + 5 * 3 + 0 + 19 * 1",
            "Answer": 41,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 5 + 3 * 6 + 15 + 7 * 4",
            "Answer": 66,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 13 + 8 * 6 + 15 + 10 * 6",
            "Answer": 141,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 16 + 11 * 14 + 1 + 3 * 6",
            "Answer": 189,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 6 + 15 * 17 + 19 + 2 * 5",
            "Answer": 296,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 7 + 5 * 0 + 8 + 17 * 0",
            "Answer": 23,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 18 + 3 * 0 + 8 + 13 * 2",
            "Answer": 54,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 14 + 3 * 14 + 4 + 5 * 11",
            "Answer": 118,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 6 + 2 * 4 + 9 + 1 * 12",
            "Answer": 40,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 15 + 3 * 14 + 3 + 19 * 8",
            "Answer": 218,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 7 + 16 * 14 + 15 + 11 * 19",
            "Answer": 468,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 8 + 3 * 16 + 12 + 6 * 10",
            "Answer": 132,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 0 + 5 * 11 + 12 + 0 * 15",
            "Answer": 74,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 12 + 3 * 3 + 16 + 17 * 1",
            "Answer": 54,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 0 + 12 * 11 + 8 + 4 * 1",
            "Answer": 158,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 13 + 13 * 5 + 14 + 19 * 4",
            "Answer": 170,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 17 + 17 * 4 + 16 + 3 * 7",
            "Answer": 139,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 17 + 11 * 7 + 0 + 12 * 11",
            "Answer": 226,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 12 + 10 * 5 + 7 + 7 * 4",
            "Answer": 116,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 11 + 3 * 9 + 12 + 10 * 1",
            "Answer": 79,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 16 + 4 * 12 + 6 + 16 * 13",
            "Answer": 286,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 6 + 7 * 5 + 19 + 13 * 7",
            "Answer": 152,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 6 + 12 * 1 + 2 + 0 * 6",
            "Answer": 31,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 8 + 7 * 6 + 16 + 10 * 16",
            "Answer": 230,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 16 + 0 * 5 + 12 + 7 * 3",
            "Answer": 65,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 15 + 7 * 14 + 0 + 13 * 16",
            "Answer": 329,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 16 + 6 * 2 + 13 + 2 * 2",
            "Answer": 53,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 18 + 18 * 10 + 18 + 10 * 4",
            "Answer": 271,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 18 + 14 * 10 + 12 + 9 * 5",
            "Answer": 227,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 19 + 17 * 10 + 10 + 18 * 8",
            "Answer": 357,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 2 + 5 * 14 + 14 + 15 * 13",
            "Answer": 290,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 4 + 6 * 6 + 6 + 9 * 0",
            "Answer": 48,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 13 + 10 * 7 + 14 + 2 * 16",
            "Answer": 132,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 6 + 0 * 9 + 6 + 0 * 3",
            "Answer": 12,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 7 + 18 * 2 + 0 + 7 * 15",
            "Answer": 160,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 12 + 11 * 14 + 0 + 4 * 3",
            "Answer": 182,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 10 + 4 * 7 + 16 + 15 * 18",
            "Answer": 331,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 19 + 18 * 4 + 14 + 11 * 14",
            "Answer": 262,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 16 + 14 * 2 + 11 + 10 * 6",
            "Answer": 131,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 16 + 3 * 6 + 11 + 6 * 8",
            "Answer": 104,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 9 + 2 * 7 + 9 + 1 * 13",
            "Answer": 61,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 5 + 15 * 16 + 19 + 9 * 17",
            "Answer": 424,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 12 + 3 * 11 + 17 + 6 * 15",
            "Answer": 154,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 13 + 11 * 1 + 0 + 15 * 10",
            "Answer": 192,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 0 + 8 * 8 + 10 + 13 * 5",
            "Answer": 148,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 10 + 0 * 3 + 7 + 6 * 11",
            "Answer": 86,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 18 + 8 * 1 + 16 + 7 * 4",
            "Answer": 80,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 11 + 5 * 13 + 1 + 7 * 1",
            "Answer": 87,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 18 + 6 * 4 + 18 + 8 * 15",
            "Answer": 198,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 12 + 9 * 8 + 11 + 18 * 18",
            "Answer": 438,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 13 + 16 * 4 + 13 + 13 * 18",
            "Answer": 336,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 3 + 15 * 0 + 12 + 17 * 18",
            "Answer": 332,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 3 + 15 * 1 + 2 + 6 * 11",
            "Answer": 98,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 6 + 6 * 9 + 7 + 4 * 4",
            "Answer": 91,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # * #"
        }
    ],
    "# * # * # * # * # + # * #": [
        {
            "Question": "19 * 1 * 0 * 17 * 17 + 16 * 19",
            "Answer": 304,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 8 * 9 * 2 * 7 + 19 * 18",
            "Answer": 6390,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 14 * 6 * 13 * 0 + 8 * 14",
            "Answer": 112,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 1 * 18 * 2 * 4 + 5 * 3",
            "Answer": 1311,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 10 * 3 * 5 * 19 + 8 * 1",
            "Answer": 11408,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 8 * 15 * 15 * 0 + 1 * 17",
            "Answer": 17,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 14 * 19 * 7 * 4 + 7 * 14",
            "Answer": 98,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 16 * 17 * 3 * 5 + 7 * 17",
            "Answer": 119,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 11 * 14 * 10 * 10 + 6 * 10",
            "Answer": 15460,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 5 * 12 * 19 * 16 + 17 * 2",
            "Answer": 91234,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 9 * 3 * 14 * 7 + 1 * 11",
            "Answer": 13241,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 10 * 17 * 9 * 16 + 12 * 14",
            "Answer": 342888,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 16 * 15 * 4 * 5 + 18 * 19",
            "Answer": 77142,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 1 * 19 * 1 * 14 + 10 * 12",
            "Answer": 5174,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 3 * 4 * 4 * 4 + 8 * 17",
            "Answer": 3784,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 17 * 1 * 17 * 8 + 12 * 0",
            "Answer": 41616,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 12 * 2 * 2 * 10 + 5 * 14",
            "Answer": 550,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 17 * 3 * 0 * 11 + 17 * 2",
            "Answer": 34,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 5 * 3 * 5 * 13 + 0 * 12",
            "Answer": 9750,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 4 * 5 * 14 * 7 + 10 * 9",
            "Answer": 5970,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 0 * 17 * 0 * 1 + 3 * 0",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 5 * 2 * 7 * 17 + 7 * 1",
            "Answer": 8337,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 7 * 15 * 11 * 2 + 7 * 10",
            "Answer": 39340,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 18 * 2 * 4 * 8 + 11 * 5",
            "Answer": 20791,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 19 * 4 * 5 * 15 + 8 * 12",
            "Answer": 62796,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 5 * 5 * 8 * 15 + 9 * 1",
            "Answer": 45009,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 16 * 4 * 2 * 3 + 1 * 2",
            "Answer": 4226,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 15 * 5 * 2 * 2 + 5 * 14",
            "Answer": 1870,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 4 * 14 * 11 * 17 + 17 * 9",
            "Answer": 153,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 2 * 10 * 19 * 1 + 0 * 1",
            "Answer": 4180,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 10 * 13 * 11 * 10 + 6 * 1",
            "Answer": 6,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 17 * 8 * 8 * 13 + 3 * 3",
            "Answer": 212169,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 1 * 15 * 2 * 4 + 10 * 18",
            "Answer": 1860,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 8 * 14 * 6 * 5 + 6 * 2",
            "Answer": 40332,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 4 * 19 * 3 * 6 + 11 * 3",
            "Answer": 2769,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 5 * 17 * 5 * 4 + 18 * 12",
            "Answer": 27416,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 9 * 11 * 13 * 19 + 18 * 3",
            "Answer": 415755,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 16 * 7 * 2 * 17 + 13 * 0",
            "Answer": 57120,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 19 * 7 * 4 * 3 + 15 * 1",
            "Answer": 1611,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 0 * 5 * 2 * 3 + 7 * 3",
            "Answer": 21,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 9 * 16 * 18 * 11 + 18 * 1",
            "Answer": 18,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 8 * 6 * 7 * 14 + 3 * 9",
            "Answer": 56475,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 1 * 1 * 5 * 10 + 13 * 11",
            "Answer": 943,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 12 * 10 * 16 * 1 + 12 * 15",
            "Answer": 32820,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 14 * 0 * 2 * 4 + 16 * 12",
            "Answer": 192,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 1 * 0 * 8 * 10 + 0 * 11",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 15 * 3 * 17 * 16 + 11 * 15",
            "Answer": 12405,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 12 * 8 * 12 * 13 + 0 * 16",
            "Answer": 104832,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 7 * 1 * 16 * 5 + 18 * 13",
            "Answer": 8074,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 11 * 17 * 17 * 14 + 13 * 2",
            "Answer": 26,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 5 * 11 * 4 * 0 + 8 * 2",
            "Answer": 16,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 9 * 16 * 15 * 14 + 0 * 4",
            "Answer": 241920,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 18 * 9 * 18 * 5 + 10 * 14",
            "Answer": 87620,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 16 * 13 * 14 * 14 + 17 * 19",
            "Answer": 204163,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 2 * 12 * 13 * 13 + 15 * 5",
            "Answer": 44691,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 0 * 18 * 3 * 9 + 0 * 15",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 18 * 19 * 4 * 10 + 19 * 5",
            "Answer": 260015,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 3 * 10 * 17 * 7 + 17 * 14",
            "Answer": 53788,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 6 * 3 * 12 * 18 + 7 * 4",
            "Answer": 62236,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 9 * 6 * 17 * 19 + 15 * 16",
            "Answer": 192102,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 14 * 17 * 15 * 17 + 1 * 3",
            "Answer": 485523,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 11 * 15 * 18 * 10 + 14 * 6",
            "Answer": 59484,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 5 * 4 * 8 * 14 + 0 * 12",
            "Answer": 11200,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 10 * 6 * 11 * 13 + 13 * 18",
            "Answer": 103194,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 18 * 12 * 3 * 1 + 1 * 14",
            "Answer": 5198,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 15 * 16 * 8 * 2 + 8 * 17",
            "Answer": 23176,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 18 * 10 * 2 * 6 + 1 * 5",
            "Answer": 17285,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 13 * 10 * 5 * 12 + 1 * 11",
            "Answer": 70211,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 6 * 18 * 2 * 9 + 10 * 13",
            "Answer": 4018,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 13 * 9 * 4 * 19 + 8 * 3",
            "Answer": 53376,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 13 * 9 * 6 * 0 + 12 * 8",
            "Answer": 96,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 8 * 14 * 19 * 14 + 13 * 6",
            "Answer": 566126,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 2 * 2 * 15 * 18 + 12 * 11",
            "Answer": 9852,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 18 * 6 * 15 * 0 + 6 * 15",
            "Answer": 90,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 5 * 10 * 11 * 1 + 18 * 13",
            "Answer": 5184,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 14 * 11 * 10 * 16 + 8 * 16",
            "Answer": 24768,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 7 * 15 * 7 * 19 + 11 * 12",
            "Answer": 55992,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 8 * 18 * 1 * 16 + 9 * 0",
            "Answer": 11520,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 3 * 2 * 4 * 19 + 11 * 3",
            "Answer": 7785,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 16 * 9 * 14 * 3 + 17 * 17",
            "Answer": 78913,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 14 * 12 * 4 * 16 + 6 * 17",
            "Answer": 53862,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 2 * 16 * 0 * 10 + 11 * 9",
            "Answer": 99,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 11 * 10 * 0 * 12 + 13 * 2",
            "Answer": 26,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 15 * 13 * 11 * 1 + 16 * 4",
            "Answer": 27949,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 2 * 9 * 14 * 10 + 19 * 5",
            "Answer": 2615,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 0 * 4 * 4 * 2 + 14 * 2",
            "Answer": 28,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 5 * 0 * 6 * 1 + 14 * 8",
            "Answer": 112,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 12 * 2 * 15 * 6 + 9 * 19",
            "Answer": 26091,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 5 * 6 * 7 * 6 + 15 * 14",
            "Answer": 22890,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 18 * 6 * 13 * 19 + 12 * 18",
            "Answer": 320328,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 9 * 1 * 8 * 6 + 7 * 18",
            "Answer": 3150,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 15 * 3 * 19 * 2 + 2 * 12",
            "Answer": 24,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 17 * 13 * 4 * 15 + 19 * 1",
            "Answer": 145879,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 18 * 17 * 11 * 6 + 0 * 16",
            "Answer": 302940,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 3 * 2 * 12 * 13 + 1 * 12",
            "Answer": 6564,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 4 * 18 * 17 * 7 + 16 * 3",
            "Answer": 48,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 13 * 11 * 15 * 10 + 12 * 17",
            "Answer": 150354,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 4 * 11 * 8 * 9 + 10 * 9",
            "Answer": 44442,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 3 * 2 * 15 * 17 + 9 * 8",
            "Answer": 9252,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 18 * 0 * 18 * 5 + 13 * 2",
            "Answer": 26,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # * #"
        }
    ],
    "# + # + # + # * # + # * #": [
        {
            "Question": "8 + 18 + 13 + 13 * 15 + 3 * 16",
            "Answer": 282,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 16 + 7 + 15 * 10 + 16 * 6",
            "Answer": 287,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 16 + 5 + 2 * 7 + 5 * 7",
            "Answer": 75,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 9 + 14 + 7 * 16 + 14 * 1",
            "Answer": 149,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 19 + 0 + 19 * 7 + 13 * 0",
            "Answer": 154,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 8 + 19 + 16 * 9 + 5 * 10",
            "Answer": 225,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 14 + 5 + 0 * 15 + 10 * 3",
            "Answer": 59,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 12 + 7 + 7 * 5 + 6 * 1",
            "Answer": 75,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 3 + 4 + 17 * 17 + 12 * 3",
            "Answer": 350,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 11 + 3 + 11 * 4 + 17 * 2",
            "Answer": 95,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 16 + 17 + 0 * 17 + 5 * 4",
            "Answer": 69,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 15 + 9 + 0 * 11 + 17 * 10",
            "Answer": 195,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 12 + 9 + 9 * 4 + 10 * 3",
            "Answer": 91,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 2 + 16 + 15 * 4 + 16 * 0",
            "Answer": 79,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 6 + 12 + 13 * 8 + 13 * 11",
            "Answer": 278,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 3 + 15 + 14 * 14 + 13 * 16",
            "Answer": 441,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 18 + 9 + 14 * 0 + 8 * 15",
            "Answer": 158,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 9 + 12 + 18 * 7 + 11 * 3",
            "Answer": 186,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 16 + 15 + 18 * 6 + 8 * 12",
            "Answer": 241,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 12 + 16 + 4 * 18 + 7 * 9",
            "Answer": 174,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 10 + 10 + 15 * 7 + 3 * 19",
            "Answer": 198,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 6 + 1 + 12 * 0 + 11 * 6",
            "Answer": 78,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 9 + 11 + 9 * 10 + 3 * 3",
            "Answer": 128,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 9 + 12 + 10 * 15 + 18 * 1",
            "Answer": 198,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 9 + 1 + 14 * 4 + 6 * 13",
            "Answer": 150,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 3 + 7 + 8 * 2 + 18 * 10",
            "Answer": 220,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 0 + 17 + 3 * 6 + 14 * 5",
            "Answer": 116,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 17 + 11 + 16 * 15 + 11 * 11",
            "Answer": 398,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 6 + 17 + 10 * 16 + 17 * 4",
            "Answer": 255,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 15 + 8 + 2 * 4 + 16 * 5",
            "Answer": 120,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 15 + 12 + 10 * 9 + 15 * 17",
            "Answer": 382,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 18 + 15 + 1 * 11 + 2 * 18",
            "Answer": 94,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 7 + 7 + 2 * 10 + 14 * 5",
            "Answer": 119,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 7 + 9 + 10 * 4 + 19 * 12",
            "Answer": 299,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 3 + 4 + 7 * 8 + 11 * 0",
            "Answer": 66,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 18 + 4 + 6 * 18 + 6 * 19",
            "Answer": 251,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 1 + 6 + 2 * 6 + 8 * 19",
            "Answer": 178,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 16 + 14 + 1 * 1 + 3 * 6",
            "Answer": 65,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 8 + 9 + 18 * 7 + 3 * 6",
            "Answer": 169,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 10 + 8 + 10 * 2 + 4 * 0",
            "Answer": 41,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 16 + 7 + 11 * 18 + 4 * 17",
            "Answer": 303,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 14 + 7 + 11 * 3 + 8 * 2",
            "Answer": 89,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 7 + 13 + 8 * 17 + 7 * 13",
            "Answer": 252,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 19 + 11 + 1 * 16 + 5 * 13",
            "Answer": 127,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 3 + 9 + 17 * 18 + 8 * 19",
            "Answer": 473,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 2 + 0 + 1 * 16 + 9 * 7",
            "Answer": 90,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 14 + 14 + 6 * 14 + 10 * 11",
            "Answer": 233,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 2 + 14 + 8 * 9 + 4 * 19",
            "Answer": 172,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 5 + 1 + 13 * 6 + 4 * 16",
            "Answer": 148,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 2 + 10 + 0 * 12 + 14 * 11",
            "Answer": 172,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 7 + 15 + 9 * 12 + 2 * 16",
            "Answer": 164,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 18 + 19 + 3 * 4 + 2 * 12",
            "Answer": 89,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 9 + 4 + 0 * 12 + 7 * 10",
            "Answer": 88,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 9 + 6 + 2 * 9 + 10 * 12",
            "Answer": 162,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 0 + 19 + 0 * 17 + 4 * 14",
            "Answer": 87,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 12 + 16 + 15 * 18 + 17 * 1",
            "Answer": 318,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 1 + 15 + 12 * 1 + 9 * 7",
            "Answer": 107,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 3 + 16 + 15 * 7 + 2 * 12",
            "Answer": 167,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 10 + 17 + 17 * 10 + 19 * 6",
            "Answer": 316,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 14 + 16 + 7 * 0 + 6 * 16",
            "Answer": 143,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 5 + 2 + 8 * 11 + 19 * 8",
            "Answer": 266,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 9 + 0 + 13 * 15 + 19 * 7",
            "Answer": 356,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 0 + 19 + 5 * 3 + 2 * 5",
            "Answer": 56,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 15 + 2 + 0 * 11 + 13 * 18",
            "Answer": 256,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 15 + 10 + 15 * 19 + 1 * 14",
            "Answer": 339,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 4 + 14 + 0 * 10 + 17 * 12",
            "Answer": 239,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 1 + 8 + 14 * 12 + 19 * 13",
            "Answer": 426,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 10 + 10 + 10 * 10 + 7 * 2",
            "Answer": 147,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 3 + 17 + 2 * 5 + 10 * 4",
            "Answer": 70,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 1 + 2 + 13 * 19 + 14 * 19",
            "Answer": 520,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 16 + 13 + 2 * 10 + 9 * 5",
            "Answer": 112,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 2 + 13 + 10 * 13 + 6 * 18",
            "Answer": 256,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 15 + 3 + 9 * 18 + 15 * 19",
            "Answer": 483,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 14 + 14 + 12 * 6 + 17 * 3",
            "Answer": 164,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 0 + 0 + 16 * 17 + 10 * 14",
            "Answer": 422,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 15 + 15 + 7 * 0 + 13 * 7",
            "Answer": 135,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 9 + 13 + 12 * 1 + 4 * 5",
            "Answer": 58,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 6 + 3 + 5 * 9 + 8 * 19",
            "Answer": 208,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 8 + 0 + 4 * 11 + 18 * 6",
            "Answer": 167,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 16 + 16 + 13 * 18 + 16 * 15",
            "Answer": 516,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 17 + 14 + 9 * 6 + 5 * 5",
            "Answer": 124,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 10 + 18 + 15 * 11 + 2 * 17",
            "Answer": 229,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 14 + 14 + 3 * 10 + 6 * 6",
            "Answer": 108,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 18 + 16 + 7 * 8 + 12 * 13",
            "Answer": 248,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 13 + 19 + 18 * 13 + 7 * 14",
            "Answer": 375,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 8 + 3 + 17 * 3 + 15 * 18",
            "Answer": 344,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 14 + 5 + 0 * 0 + 12 * 17",
            "Answer": 236,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 9 + 17 + 1 * 15 + 18 * 4",
            "Answer": 117,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 12 + 4 + 16 * 8 + 4 * 4",
            "Answer": 169,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 12 + 1 + 16 * 7 + 8 * 3",
            "Answer": 163,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 7 + 3 + 10 * 8 + 10 * 19",
            "Answer": 292,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 19 + 11 + 17 * 6 + 17 * 0",
            "Answer": 149,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 14 + 14 + 15 * 4 + 19 * 5",
            "Answer": 192,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 12 + 19 + 6 * 5 + 19 * 1",
            "Answer": 84,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 18 + 14 + 6 * 8 + 14 * 9",
            "Answer": 210,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 5 + 13 + 14 * 3 + 11 * 18",
            "Answer": 263,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 16 + 16 + 16 * 6 + 4 * 1",
            "Answer": 141,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 19 + 7 + 8 * 19 + 1 * 8",
            "Answer": 199,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 14 + 9 + 12 * 4 + 10 * 5",
            "Answer": 128,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 11 + 6 + 17 * 8 + 18 * 11",
            "Answer": 367,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # * #"
        }
    ],
    "# * # + # * # + # * # * #": [
        {
            "Question": "9 * 5 + 12 * 11 + 13 * 2 * 0",
            "Answer": 177,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 5 + 12 * 16 + 10 * 10 * 1",
            "Answer": 387,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 11 + 3 * 14 + 15 * 16 * 5",
            "Answer": 1242,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 3 + 19 * 2 + 14 * 4 * 0",
            "Answer": 86,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 9 + 10 * 3 + 3 * 18 * 15",
            "Answer": 912,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 10 + 17 * 4 + 8 * 4 * 12",
            "Answer": 572,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 6 + 8 * 3 + 7 * 15 * 5",
            "Answer": 573,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 2 + 6 * 2 + 10 * 15 * 13",
            "Answer": 1994,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 6 + 0 * 1 + 15 * 0 * 6",
            "Answer": 30,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 6 + 13 * 4 + 11 * 14 * 12",
            "Answer": 1960,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 13 + 8 * 14 + 12 * 2 * 16",
            "Answer": 613,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 14 + 3 * 16 + 1 * 14 * 10",
            "Answer": 398,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 7 + 4 * 15 + 16 * 13 * 1",
            "Answer": 352,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 1 + 6 * 7 + 11 * 2 * 19",
            "Answer": 461,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 9 + 11 * 0 + 4 * 14 * 3",
            "Answer": 204,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 10 + 12 * 11 + 6 * 17 * 4",
            "Answer": 630,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 1 + 16 * 2 + 2 * 4 * 19",
            "Answer": 187,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 5 + 3 * 1 + 8 * 6 * 13",
            "Answer": 667,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 6 + 13 * 2 + 18 * 12 * 6",
            "Answer": 1412,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 5 + 19 * 15 + 8 * 3 * 4",
            "Answer": 386,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 10 + 12 * 14 + 10 * 2 * 18",
            "Answer": 648,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 2 + 2 * 17 + 17 * 18 * 5",
            "Answer": 1598,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 19 + 17 * 1 + 13 * 15 * 0",
            "Answer": 17,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 17 + 17 * 1 + 13 * 10 * 13",
            "Answer": 1775,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 10 + 0 * 2 + 12 * 5 * 8",
            "Answer": 520,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 15 + 5 * 7 + 13 * 12 * 1",
            "Answer": 326,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 0 + 15 * 10 + 18 * 5 * 5",
            "Answer": 600,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 16 + 15 * 16 + 18 * 14 * 7",
            "Answer": 2260,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 12 + 4 * 18 + 5 * 0 * 15",
            "Answer": 300,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 9 + 7 * 17 + 12 * 8 * 4",
            "Answer": 575,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 0 + 2 * 3 + 2 * 3 * 1",
            "Answer": 12,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 11 + 19 * 19 + 16 * 11 * 11",
            "Answer": 2440,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 12 + 7 * 7 + 14 * 19 * 14",
            "Answer": 3821,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 13 + 19 * 0 + 0 * 14 * 7",
            "Answer": 195,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 18 + 4 * 5 + 18 * 19 * 8",
            "Answer": 2864,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 3 + 4 * 2 + 4 * 13 * 1",
            "Answer": 114,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 19 + 5 * 5 + 10 * 19 * 19",
            "Answer": 3863,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 6 + 5 * 2 + 6 * 2 * 4",
            "Answer": 112,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 16 + 3 * 3 + 19 * 18 * 14",
            "Answer": 4973,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 18 + 9 * 16 + 0 * 5 * 5",
            "Answer": 306,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 10 + 10 * 3 + 1 * 11 * 8",
            "Answer": 248,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 5 + 14 * 12 + 16 * 19 * 1",
            "Answer": 547,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 18 + 12 * 5 + 19 * 14 * 10",
            "Answer": 2954,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 11 + 7 * 12 + 14 * 3 * 15",
            "Answer": 923,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 18 + 6 * 17 + 0 * 3 * 9",
            "Answer": 426,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 16 + 0 * 2 + 9 * 4 * 3",
            "Answer": 124,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 9 + 9 * 11 + 15 * 13 * 4",
            "Answer": 897,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 16 + 10 * 6 + 1 * 0 * 3",
            "Answer": 220,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 16 + 0 * 11 + 14 * 1 * 0",
            "Answer": 96,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 7 + 2 * 1 + 1 * 10 * 19",
            "Answer": 206,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 9 + 18 * 5 + 5 * 19 * 13",
            "Answer": 1424,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 9 + 13 * 8 + 6 * 9 * 13",
            "Answer": 815,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 9 + 0 * 0 + 11 * 7 * 1",
            "Answer": 176,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 8 + 0 * 2 + 1 * 0 * 15",
            "Answer": 80,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 5 + 4 * 6 + 15 * 5 * 15",
            "Answer": 1239,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 10 + 6 * 16 + 19 * 5 * 3",
            "Answer": 461,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 7 + 1 * 15 + 19 * 0 * 4",
            "Answer": 64,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 14 + 7 * 8 + 11 * 15 * 18",
            "Answer": 3194,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 2 + 4 * 10 + 8 * 3 * 2",
            "Answer": 120,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 4 + 16 * 5 + 4 * 19 * 19",
            "Answer": 1548,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 0 + 0 * 15 + 14 * 5 * 10",
            "Answer": 700,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 10 + 15 * 18 + 6 * 18 * 7",
            "Answer": 1036,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 4 + 9 * 12 + 3 * 9 * 13",
            "Answer": 483,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 7 + 17 * 18 + 5 * 15 * 11",
            "Answer": 1208,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 6 + 6 * 4 + 4 * 15 * 0",
            "Answer": 120,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 17 + 19 * 12 + 15 * 4 * 1",
            "Answer": 509,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 6 + 3 * 9 + 13 * 11 * 6",
            "Answer": 921,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 12 + 15 * 15 + 0 * 7 * 4",
            "Answer": 405,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 6 + 10 * 10 + 17 * 15 * 0",
            "Answer": 130,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 15 + 4 * 2 + 0 * 11 * 18",
            "Answer": 203,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 17 + 12 * 8 + 15 * 15 * 8",
            "Answer": 1930,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 10 + 4 * 11 + 4 * 16 * 1",
            "Answer": 188,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 18 + 13 * 0 + 11 * 4 * 3",
            "Answer": 276,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 17 + 4 * 16 + 5 * 0 * 1",
            "Answer": 132,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 3 + 0 * 17 + 8 * 15 * 10",
            "Answer": 1236,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 4 + 7 * 17 + 17 * 1 * 17",
            "Answer": 460,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 18 + 1 * 17 + 18 * 16 * 0",
            "Answer": 71,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 4 + 4 * 17 + 6 * 15 * 3",
            "Answer": 398,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 2 + 12 * 12 + 13 * 9 * 7",
            "Answer": 963,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 4 + 9 * 18 + 4 * 3 * 1",
            "Answer": 226,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 10 + 9 * 0 + 2 * 4 * 3",
            "Answer": 24,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 11 + 16 * 7 + 11 * 11 * 6",
            "Answer": 948,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 10 + 8 * 18 + 19 * 5 * 3",
            "Answer": 549,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 4 + 17 * 8 + 9 * 4 * 5",
            "Answer": 384,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 11 + 2 * 11 + 10 * 19 * 3",
            "Answer": 603,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 9 + 7 * 9 + 15 * 6 * 8",
            "Answer": 873,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 14 + 0 * 18 + 2 * 0 * 3",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 17 + 16 * 11 + 16 * 15 * 8",
            "Answer": 2232,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 13 + 18 * 19 + 14 * 19 * 3",
            "Answer": 1192,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 7 + 11 * 6 + 6 * 2 * 19",
            "Answer": 420,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 8 + 7 * 13 + 11 * 9 * 2",
            "Answer": 409,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 17 + 18 * 19 + 8 * 9 * 4",
            "Answer": 936,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 3 + 14 * 13 + 12 * 18 * 2",
            "Answer": 617,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 6 + 9 * 5 + 14 * 5 * 16",
            "Answer": 1189,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 11 + 8 * 12 + 5 * 18 * 18",
            "Answer": 1848,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 3 + 15 * 9 + 6 * 18 * 11",
            "Answer": 1356,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 15 + 5 * 14 + 4 * 2 * 5",
            "Answer": 365,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 0 + 15 * 1 + 5 * 18 * 11",
            "Answer": 1005,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 15 + 16 * 13 + 13 * 12 * 10",
            "Answer": 1783,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 15 + 16 * 6 + 14 * 15 * 10",
            "Answer": 2241,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # * #"
        }
    ],
    "# * # + # + # * # + # * #": [
        {
            "Question": "10 * 6 + 14 + 3 * 1 + 11 * 10",
            "Answer": 187,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 5 + 5 + 9 * 15 + 4 * 19",
            "Answer": 226,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 19 + 10 + 14 * 13 + 3 * 18",
            "Answer": 493,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 19 + 8 + 19 * 10 + 10 * 17",
            "Answer": 729,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 1 + 4 + 10 * 4 + 13 * 4",
            "Answer": 112,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 18 + 19 + 8 * 5 + 12 * 2",
            "Answer": 389,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 14 + 5 + 6 * 12 + 0 * 2",
            "Answer": 105,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 4 + 8 + 1 * 19 + 1 * 5",
            "Answer": 76,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 3 + 19 + 18 * 19 + 18 * 14",
            "Answer": 652,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 13 + 8 + 17 * 13 + 4 * 12",
            "Answer": 420,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 14 + 0 + 15 * 7 + 4 * 17",
            "Answer": 173,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 0 + 10 + 3 * 3 + 8 * 0",
            "Answer": 19,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 13 + 17 + 15 * 15 + 9 * 8",
            "Answer": 470,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 15 + 6 + 6 * 13 + 1 * 5",
            "Answer": 104,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 7 + 11 + 12 * 19 + 17 * 4",
            "Answer": 440,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 0 + 11 + 18 * 11 + 13 * 2",
            "Answer": 235,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 17 + 15 + 13 * 19 + 1 * 0",
            "Answer": 500,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 17 + 5 + 2 * 7 + 6 * 14",
            "Answer": 154,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 6 + 15 + 2 * 4 + 6 * 9",
            "Answer": 77,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 1 + 17 + 11 * 12 + 19 * 2",
            "Answer": 204,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 18 + 15 + 8 * 9 + 12 * 14",
            "Answer": 471,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 4 + 8 + 17 * 17 + 1 * 10",
            "Answer": 347,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 15 + 8 + 9 * 6 + 4 * 12",
            "Answer": 230,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 2 + 7 + 11 * 12 + 14 * 8",
            "Answer": 269,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 2 + 18 + 15 * 5 + 18 * 2",
            "Answer": 147,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 18 + 15 + 7 * 1 + 19 * 10",
            "Answer": 248,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 4 + 8 + 6 * 13 + 6 * 9",
            "Answer": 140,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 18 + 14 + 0 * 5 + 12 * 5",
            "Answer": 308,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 19 + 17 + 7 * 0 + 12 * 5",
            "Answer": 96,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 14 + 11 + 1 * 17 + 11 * 5",
            "Answer": 83,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 11 + 2 + 17 * 13 + 10 * 5",
            "Answer": 482,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 14 + 9 + 3 * 19 + 14 * 6",
            "Answer": 318,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 18 + 4 + 13 * 17 + 7 * 9",
            "Answer": 540,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 12 + 5 + 10 * 1 + 0 * 2",
            "Answer": 171,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 5 + 13 + 17 * 18 + 9 * 15",
            "Answer": 534,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 2 + 17 + 14 * 4 + 13 * 5",
            "Answer": 152,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 12 + 8 + 11 * 18 + 8 * 15",
            "Answer": 326,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 12 + 19 + 7 * 3 + 17 * 10",
            "Answer": 354,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 7 + 7 + 19 * 2 + 12 * 18",
            "Answer": 282,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 9 + 19 + 13 * 5 + 3 * 19",
            "Answer": 312,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 15 + 10 + 9 * 7 + 3 * 2",
            "Answer": 184,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 11 + 3 + 18 * 1 + 19 * 18",
            "Answer": 429,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 14 + 17 + 13 * 10 + 8 * 0",
            "Answer": 371,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 11 + 11 + 1 * 19 + 14 * 16",
            "Answer": 309,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 16 + 3 + 2 * 0 + 8 * 18",
            "Answer": 323,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 6 + 12 + 18 * 4 + 10 * 12",
            "Answer": 252,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 3 + 10 + 4 * 3 + 13 * 18",
            "Answer": 286,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 11 + 7 + 16 * 17 + 2 * 14",
            "Answer": 384,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 6 + 16 + 5 * 17 + 11 * 11",
            "Answer": 336,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 8 + 14 + 6 * 6 + 7 * 2",
            "Answer": 120,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 15 + 15 + 6 * 1 + 1 * 9",
            "Answer": 150,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 11 + 8 + 9 * 16 + 5 * 2",
            "Answer": 272,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 3 + 18 + 2 * 12 + 10 * 1",
            "Answer": 76,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 4 + 8 + 15 * 1 + 10 * 12",
            "Answer": 151,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 0 + 15 + 4 * 16 + 17 * 19",
            "Answer": 402,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 11 + 1 + 4 * 16 + 9 * 3",
            "Answer": 158,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 10 + 8 + 2 * 12 + 14 * 17",
            "Answer": 320,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 3 + 7 + 12 * 14 + 13 * 6",
            "Answer": 298,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 2 + 16 + 0 * 15 + 11 * 3",
            "Answer": 85,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 13 + 17 + 5 * 19 + 5 * 6",
            "Answer": 324,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 13 + 0 + 17 * 19 + 12 * 2",
            "Answer": 568,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 15 + 2 + 16 * 5 + 12 * 13",
            "Answer": 343,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 3 + 14 + 13 * 9 + 17 * 11",
            "Answer": 369,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 11 + 5 + 16 * 5 + 19 * 7",
            "Answer": 240,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 8 + 19 + 9 * 0 + 2 * 0",
            "Answer": 67,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 6 + 12 + 18 * 2 + 3 * 14",
            "Answer": 102,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 9 + 5 + 3 * 10 + 8 * 12",
            "Answer": 239,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 13 + 19 + 8 * 16 + 10 * 7",
            "Answer": 256,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 14 + 5 + 4 * 5 + 6 * 17",
            "Answer": 253,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 11 + 17 + 17 * 2 + 8 * 17",
            "Answer": 275,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 12 + 12 + 17 * 2 + 16 * 16",
            "Answer": 506,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 15 + 18 + 0 * 0 + 0 * 14",
            "Answer": 198,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 12 + 15 + 0 * 6 + 1 * 18",
            "Answer": 45,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 10 + 4 + 7 * 15 + 3 * 1",
            "Answer": 292,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 7 + 17 + 9 * 13 + 12 * 4",
            "Answer": 196,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 8 + 15 + 0 * 9 + 2 * 2",
            "Answer": 131,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 2 + 6 + 0 * 2 + 11 * 14",
            "Answer": 182,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 18 + 2 + 5 * 15 + 3 * 7",
            "Answer": 188,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 0 + 5 + 3 * 8 + 15 * 8",
            "Answer": 149,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 13 + 12 + 0 * 18 + 8 * 5",
            "Answer": 65,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 9 + 9 + 17 * 1 + 14 * 12",
            "Answer": 347,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 11 + 5 + 10 * 6 + 19 * 7",
            "Answer": 319,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 6 + 0 + 11 * 5 + 8 * 2",
            "Answer": 71,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 16 + 4 + 19 * 3 + 6 * 19",
            "Answer": 255,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 3 + 3 + 15 * 8 + 13 * 18",
            "Answer": 366,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 10 + 18 + 5 * 2 + 0 * 16",
            "Answer": 108,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 17 + 2 + 4 * 10 + 3 * 0",
            "Answer": 93,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 9 + 1 + 17 * 15 + 5 * 13",
            "Answer": 357,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 8 + 16 + 15 * 12 + 17 * 8",
            "Answer": 468,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 13 + 8 + 6 * 5 + 10 * 16",
            "Answer": 250,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 18 + 7 + 1 * 12 + 14 * 12",
            "Answer": 277,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 5 + 3 + 18 * 0 + 7 * 1",
            "Answer": 75,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 16 + 7 + 8 * 11 + 13 * 3",
            "Answer": 278,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 1 + 9 + 9 * 2 + 16 * 10",
            "Answer": 206,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 14 + 15 + 4 * 14 + 0 * 2",
            "Answer": 197,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 13 + 0 + 12 * 12 + 0 * 5",
            "Answer": 378,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 0 + 10 + 9 * 11 + 18 * 3",
            "Answer": 163,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 6 + 5 + 17 * 1 + 9 * 3",
            "Answer": 127,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 1 + 10 + 5 * 18 + 8 * 16",
            "Answer": 246,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 10 + 7 + 16 * 14 + 14 * 12",
            "Answer": 569,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # * #"
        }
    ],
    "# + # + # * # * # * # * #": [
        {
            "Question": "12 + 12 + 12 * 4 * 9 * 15 * 5",
            "Answer": 32424,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 4 + 0 * 2 * 6 * 1 * 7",
            "Answer": 14,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 4 + 19 * 4 * 15 * 3 * 1",
            "Answer": 3424,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 11 + 18 * 16 * 13 * 14 * 11",
            "Answer": 576603,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 8 + 13 * 2 * 1 * 11 * 11",
            "Answer": 3164,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 10 + 16 * 13 * 18 * 6 * 2",
            "Answer": 44940,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 17 + 5 * 6 * 14 * 1 * 18",
            "Answer": 7590,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 10 + 4 * 9 * 4 * 8 * 7",
            "Answer": 8089,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 10 + 18 * 18 * 6 * 10 * 4",
            "Answer": 77778,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 12 + 10 * 13 * 13 * 7 * 3",
            "Answer": 35515,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 7 + 4 * 14 * 12 * 14 * 18",
            "Answer": 169353,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 18 + 2 * 7 * 16 * 16 * 7",
            "Answer": 25114,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 7 + 6 * 11 * 16 * 3 * 8",
            "Answer": 25366,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 6 + 2 * 4 * 8 * 19 * 12",
            "Answer": 14602,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 5 + 12 * 14 * 12 * 7 * 10",
            "Answer": 141129,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 16 + 14 * 17 * 2 * 4 * 10",
            "Answer": 19056,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 2 + 3 * 13 * 1 * 11 * 6",
            "Answer": 2583,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 16 + 19 * 2 * 18 * 2 * 1",
            "Answer": 1392,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 2 + 17 * 2 * 14 * 2 * 1",
            "Answer": 956,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 9 + 10 * 10 * 9 * 2 * 3",
            "Answer": 5414,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 19 + 19 * 18 * 15 * 1 * 16",
            "Answer": 82116,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 14 + 0 * 7 * 18 * 16 * 10",
            "Answer": 14,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 0 + 6 * 10 * 11 * 1 * 18",
            "Answer": 11886,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 7 + 5 * 1 * 2 * 11 * 18",
            "Answer": 1996,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 15 + 5 * 8 * 10 * 9 * 17",
            "Answer": 61232,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 2 + 9 * 4 * 11 * 1 * 15",
            "Answer": 5948,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 8 + 17 * 18 * 4 * 18 * 6",
            "Answer": 132202,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 12 + 8 * 12 * 12 * 8 * 18",
            "Answer": 165915,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 17 + 6 * 19 * 12 * 7 * 12",
            "Answer": 114936,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 12 + 11 * 0 * 17 * 1 * 4",
            "Answer": 27,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 3 + 8 * 4 * 8 * 12 * 18",
            "Answer": 55313,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 7 + 12 * 2 * 10 * 10 * 5",
            "Answer": 12014,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 18 + 9 * 8 * 2 * 10 * 8",
            "Answer": 11545,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 5 + 16 * 19 * 8 * 5 * 0",
            "Answer": 7,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 14 + 13 * 14 * 5 * 7 * 18",
            "Answer": 114685,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 18 + 1 * 17 * 1 * 10 * 8",
            "Answer": 1395,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 11 + 4 * 17 * 3 * 17 * 16",
            "Answer": 55511,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 10 + 6 * 1 * 13 * 17 * 13",
            "Answer": 17256,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 6 + 14 * 19 * 1 * 6 * 11",
            "Answer": 17576,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 15 + 10 * 16 * 10 * 10 * 8",
            "Answer": 128017,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 0 + 18 * 0 * 10 * 19 * 1",
            "Answer": 8,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 1 + 5 * 3 * 12 * 9 * 9",
            "Answer": 14597,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 16 + 3 * 15 * 13 * 4 * 8",
            "Answer": 18745,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 17 + 3 * 13 * 16 * 18 * 19",
            "Answer": 213434,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 7 + 8 * 7 * 16 * 18 * 3",
            "Answer": 48408,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 15 + 11 * 13 * 7 * 3 * 5",
            "Answer": 15046,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 15 + 3 * 15 * 8 * 13 * 8",
            "Answer": 37460,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 8 + 11 * 4 * 19 * 4 * 10",
            "Answer": 33455,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 4 + 11 * 4 * 1 * 10 * 2",
            "Answer": 902,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 9 + 18 * 13 * 14 * 7 * 0",
            "Answer": 16,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 16 + 3 * 0 * 19 * 1 * 16",
            "Answer": 20,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 5 + 17 * 4 * 5 * 3 * 10",
            "Answer": 10220,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 8 + 3 * 17 * 14 * 16 * 0",
            "Answer": 16,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 5 + 14 * 17 * 1 * 16 * 2",
            "Answer": 7625,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 4 + 19 * 11 * 12 * 12 * 18",
            "Answer": 541740,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 19 + 14 * 9 * 1 * 6 * 6",
            "Answer": 4570,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 12 + 3 * 15 * 8 * 18 * 9",
            "Answer": 58345,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 13 + 6 * 10 * 7 * 6 * 8",
            "Answer": 20182,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 14 + 8 * 8 * 9 * 19 * 3",
            "Answer": 32847,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 10 + 7 * 1 * 9 * 8 * 17",
            "Answer": 8579,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 19 + 11 * 18 * 17 * 0 * 3",
            "Answer": 24,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 12 + 0 * 11 * 7 * 17 * 2",
            "Answer": 15,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 19 + 4 * 9 * 6 * 4 * 5",
            "Answer": 4344,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 19 + 15 * 16 * 14 * 17 * 16",
            "Answer": 913944,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 19 + 4 * 16 * 18 * 7 * 9",
            "Answer": 72599,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 5 + 18 * 16 * 5 * 1 * 7",
            "Answer": 10102,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 12 + 6 * 12 * 11 * 10 * 15",
            "Answer": 118828,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 5 + 0 * 18 * 15 * 5 * 10",
            "Answer": 11,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 3 + 9 * 12 * 13 * 13 * 9",
            "Answer": 164279,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 4 + 0 * 4 * 3 * 2 * 0",
            "Answer": 22,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 19 + 3 * 4 * 12 * 8 * 15",
            "Answer": 17311,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 6 + 10 * 0 * 5 * 11 * 6",
            "Answer": 25,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 1 + 13 * 15 * 0 * 19 * 15",
            "Answer": 13,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 8 + 13 * 2 * 6 * 14 * 0",
            "Answer": 22,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 16 + 4 * 10 * 6 * 11 * 17",
            "Answer": 44905,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 7 + 1 * 13 * 2 * 9 * 5",
            "Answer": 1180,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 3 + 5 * 13 * 14 * 18 * 1",
            "Answer": 16397,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 5 + 15 * 13 * 5 * 16 * 2",
            "Answer": 31224,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 1 + 18 * 13 * 4 * 18 * 1",
            "Answer": 16860,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 18 + 6 * 4 * 16 * 2 * 8",
            "Answer": 6173,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 4 + 13 * 18 * 2 * 1 * 8",
            "Answer": 3766,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 3 + 0 * 8 * 3 * 0 * 14",
            "Answer": 5,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 0 + 6 * 11 * 1 * 6 * 12",
            "Answer": 4763,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 9 + 12 * 13 * 9 * 1 * 0",
            "Answer": 14,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 19 + 16 * 6 * 12 * 5 * 7",
            "Answer": 40356,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 18 + 6 * 2 * 9 * 6 * 3",
            "Answer": 1969,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 14 + 8 * 0 * 0 * 12 * 9",
            "Answer": 31,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 18 + 9 * 14 * 4 * 9 * 0",
            "Answer": 32,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 13 + 4 * 3 * 17 * 14 * 2",
            "Answer": 5736,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 5 + 13 * 12 * 15 * 1 * 5",
            "Answer": 11723,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 8 + 19 * 11 * 10 * 1 * 8",
            "Answer": 16728,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 12 + 13 * 8 * 1 * 4 * 9",
            "Answer": 3775,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 5 + 14 * 13 * 9 * 3 * 18",
            "Answer": 88468,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 5 + 1 * 19 * 16 * 11 * 17",
            "Answer": 56871,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 17 + 2 * 7 * 0 * 0 * 17",
            "Answer": 19,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 13 + 4 * 19 * 5 * 1 * 8",
            "Answer": 3057,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 11 + 8 * 19 * 3 * 5 * 18",
            "Answer": 41069,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 5 + 5 * 18 * 11 * 5 * 19",
            "Answer": 94072,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 7 + 17 * 15 * 12 * 15 * 15",
            "Answer": 688520,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 17 + 6 * 4 * 9 * 2 * 17",
            "Answer": 7366,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # * #"
        }
    ],
    "# + # * # + # + # + # * #": [
        {
            "Question": "2 + 9 * 17 + 13 + 11 + 16 * 0",
            "Answer": 179,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 18 * 5 + 16 + 4 + 8 * 10",
            "Answer": 191,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 17 * 0 + 13 + 14 + 17 * 18",
            "Answer": 339,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 8 * 13 + 16 + 3 + 12 * 13",
            "Answer": 286,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 5 * 4 + 15 + 7 + 5 * 9",
            "Answer": 95,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 16 * 2 + 0 + 10 + 8 * 12",
            "Answer": 155,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 10 * 17 + 14 + 4 + 15 * 13",
            "Answer": 391,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 6 * 19 + 9 + 4 + 10 * 0",
            "Answer": 137,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 14 * 8 + 7 + 19 + 17 * 13",
            "Answer": 376,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 8 * 9 + 13 + 6 + 16 * 4",
            "Answer": 174,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 9 * 4 + 12 + 0 + 8 * 18",
            "Answer": 203,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 4 * 5 + 11 + 1 + 19 * 12",
            "Answer": 278,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 10 * 12 + 1 + 4 + 8 * 13",
            "Answer": 234,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 6 * 18 + 18 + 16 + 19 * 18",
            "Answer": 486,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 9 * 7 + 3 + 2 + 5 * 18",
            "Answer": 165,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 17 * 18 + 14 + 2 + 11 * 2",
            "Answer": 352,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 18 * 15 + 19 + 16 + 14 * 8",
            "Answer": 423,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 1 * 11 + 12 + 10 + 5 * 15",
            "Answer": 116,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 16 * 19 + 2 + 6 + 0 * 4",
            "Answer": 314,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 6 * 11 + 2 + 12 + 2 * 15",
            "Answer": 119,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 8 * 11 + 19 + 5 + 14 * 8",
            "Answer": 236,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 12 * 12 + 0 + 5 + 2 * 10",
            "Answer": 178,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 6 * 17 + 15 + 15 + 8 * 6",
            "Answer": 192,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 17 * 16 + 3 + 8 + 11 * 2",
            "Answer": 314,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 2 * 17 + 17 + 11 + 10 * 18",
            "Answer": 248,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 14 * 5 + 13 + 1 + 5 * 12",
            "Answer": 154,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 9 * 12 + 11 + 1 + 11 * 18",
            "Answer": 323,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 19 * 19 + 13 + 17 + 10 * 6",
            "Answer": 452,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 7 * 7 + 7 + 2 + 5 * 16",
            "Answer": 148,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 16 * 17 + 15 + 8 + 19 * 1",
            "Answer": 315,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 6 * 3 + 17 + 7 + 19 * 10",
            "Answer": 245,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 8 * 16 + 9 + 0 + 7 * 13",
            "Answer": 229,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 1 * 17 + 13 + 4 + 17 * 11",
            "Answer": 222,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 4 * 16 + 11 + 10 + 17 * 15",
            "Answer": 348,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 11 * 11 + 13 + 3 + 17 * 16",
            "Answer": 422,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 14 * 6 + 2 + 13 + 1 * 1",
            "Answer": 114,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 8 * 17 + 18 + 18 + 1 * 15",
            "Answer": 189,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 15 * 18 + 2 + 14 + 9 * 7",
            "Answer": 350,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 9 * 11 + 5 + 6 + 15 * 1",
            "Answer": 128,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 18 * 8 + 3 + 18 + 4 * 4",
            "Answer": 195,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 6 * 12 + 5 + 4 + 19 * 4",
            "Answer": 172,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 3 * 17 + 13 + 10 + 6 * 4",
            "Answer": 106,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 1 * 19 + 17 + 18 + 18 * 16",
            "Answer": 347,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 3 * 19 + 11 + 14 + 11 * 0",
            "Answer": 99,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 5 * 8 + 8 + 15 + 10 * 9",
            "Answer": 156,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 11 * 13 + 14 + 2 + 10 * 2",
            "Answer": 192,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 4 * 4 + 3 + 7 + 1 * 14",
            "Answer": 55,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 15 * 6 + 2 + 12 + 19 * 18",
            "Answer": 461,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 3 * 18 + 14 + 19 + 11 * 11",
            "Answer": 211,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 1 * 12 + 4 + 10 + 19 * 19",
            "Answer": 401,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 19 * 6 + 0 + 12 + 4 * 9",
            "Answer": 172,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 0 * 12 + 3 + 3 + 2 * 9",
            "Answer": 27,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 12 * 19 + 5 + 9 + 16 * 8",
            "Answer": 383,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 4 * 16 + 13 + 12 + 9 * 12",
            "Answer": 198,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 1 * 0 + 8 + 12 + 2 * 18",
            "Answer": 72,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 16 * 13 + 15 + 1 + 6 * 16",
            "Answer": 324,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 16 * 8 + 10 + 13 + 14 * 13",
            "Answer": 333,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 3 * 4 + 1 + 14 + 9 * 2",
            "Answer": 60,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 1 * 0 + 15 + 6 + 10 * 9",
            "Answer": 130,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 16 * 17 + 3 + 3 + 16 * 2",
            "Answer": 328,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 11 * 16 + 14 + 15 + 12 * 3",
            "Answer": 255,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 6 * 0 + 4 + 16 + 8 * 11",
            "Answer": 109,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 13 * 9 + 12 + 0 + 16 * 1",
            "Answer": 156,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 2 * 19 + 5 + 0 + 14 * 15",
            "Answer": 254,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 1 * 12 + 3 + 19 + 2 * 8",
            "Answer": 56,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 8 * 8 + 4 + 9 + 18 * 6",
            "Answer": 186,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 3 * 0 + 2 + 5 + 0 * 9",
            "Answer": 14,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 4 * 10 + 8 + 18 + 8 * 19",
            "Answer": 237,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 19 * 1 + 14 + 6 + 13 * 10",
            "Answer": 174,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 14 * 15 + 8 + 3 + 12 * 0",
            "Answer": 234,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 4 * 15 + 2 + 18 + 19 * 2",
            "Answer": 119,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 1 * 11 + 14 + 11 + 0 * 5",
            "Answer": 42,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 12 * 10 + 6 + 18 + 15 * 19",
            "Answer": 429,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 19 * 19 + 5 + 19 + 7 * 2",
            "Answer": 418,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 18 * 11 + 8 + 18 + 6 * 13",
            "Answer": 316,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 16 * 10 + 13 + 8 + 10 * 11",
            "Answer": 299,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 8 * 13 + 6 + 12 + 7 * 12",
            "Answer": 213,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 9 * 4 + 2 + 1 + 7 * 17",
            "Answer": 164,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 4 * 10 + 6 + 3 + 8 * 9",
            "Answer": 124,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 2 * 2 + 5 + 6 + 9 * 17",
            "Answer": 169,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 12 * 1 + 16 + 2 + 6 * 8",
            "Answer": 81,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 18 * 12 + 12 + 1 + 19 * 3",
            "Answer": 291,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 13 * 5 + 13 + 13 + 9 * 4",
            "Answer": 137,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 11 * 18 + 11 + 12 + 1 * 15",
            "Answer": 247,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 8 * 10 + 4 + 6 + 6 * 4",
            "Answer": 115,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 18 * 14 + 10 + 7 + 12 * 13",
            "Answer": 427,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 5 * 14 + 3 + 17 + 11 * 6",
            "Answer": 162,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 18 * 17 + 18 + 3 + 8 * 2",
            "Answer": 344,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 15 * 14 + 15 + 14 + 19 * 0",
            "Answer": 249,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 14 * 9 + 15 + 4 + 16 * 16",
            "Answer": 420,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 9 * 11 + 8 + 7 + 2 * 19",
            "Answer": 169,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 17 * 6 + 6 + 13 + 12 * 6",
            "Answer": 198,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 13 * 10 + 16 + 19 + 15 * 14",
            "Answer": 390,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 4 * 13 + 1 + 15 + 12 * 12",
            "Answer": 227,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 13 * 9 + 17 + 7 + 0 * 14",
            "Answer": 156,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 18 * 6 + 18 + 15 + 7 * 3",
            "Answer": 168,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 11 * 14 + 12 + 7 + 0 * 12",
            "Answer": 173,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 8 * 13 + 19 + 5 + 1 * 14",
            "Answer": 157,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 10 * 5 + 17 + 18 + 13 * 19",
            "Answer": 338,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 14 * 13 + 11 + 5 + 6 * 17",
            "Answer": 301,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # * #"
        }
    ],
    "# * # + # + # + # * # + #": [
        {
            "Question": "7 * 9 + 12 + 15 + 15 * 13 + 17",
            "Answer": 302,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 10 + 11 + 8 + 0 * 13 + 16",
            "Answer": 225,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 6 + 4 + 2 + 6 * 3 + 2",
            "Answer": 32,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 13 + 3 + 16 + 15 * 19 + 19",
            "Answer": 518,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 7 + 0 + 14 + 0 * 4 + 14",
            "Answer": 70,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 7 + 17 + 17 + 13 * 18 + 7",
            "Answer": 352,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 9 + 5 + 3 + 7 * 18 + 15",
            "Answer": 284,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 2 + 9 + 6 + 9 * 10 + 9",
            "Answer": 122,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 11 + 0 + 19 + 2 * 4 + 19",
            "Answer": 255,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 7 + 14 + 12 + 12 * 12 + 0",
            "Answer": 184,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 0 + 5 + 4 + 7 * 6 + 10",
            "Answer": 61,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 0 + 15 + 15 + 13 * 1 + 15",
            "Answer": 58,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 4 + 16 + 19 + 5 * 2 + 2",
            "Answer": 123,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 4 + 4 + 16 + 16 * 15 + 14",
            "Answer": 346,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 7 + 7 + 3 + 8 * 17 + 3",
            "Answer": 247,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 9 + 6 + 8 + 4 * 9 + 6",
            "Answer": 200,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 10 + 5 + 6 + 18 * 13 + 5",
            "Answer": 390,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 7 + 15 + 3 + 6 * 15 + 13",
            "Answer": 121,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 0 + 18 + 3 + 6 * 9 + 4",
            "Answer": 79,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 0 + 18 + 3 + 14 * 6 + 0",
            "Answer": 105,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 13 + 11 + 0 + 5 * 12 + 15",
            "Answer": 229,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 3 + 8 + 15 + 11 * 19 + 3",
            "Answer": 238,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 4 + 14 + 9 + 1 * 18 + 7",
            "Answer": 64,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 8 + 10 + 16 + 11 * 14 + 18",
            "Answer": 326,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 17 + 15 + 7 + 14 * 14 + 19",
            "Answer": 254,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 4 + 2 + 9 + 10 * 11 + 0",
            "Answer": 197,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 3 + 17 + 6 + 4 * 0 + 14",
            "Answer": 37,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 3 + 18 + 6 + 5 * 19 + 11",
            "Answer": 184,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 19 + 15 + 0 + 16 * 18 + 15",
            "Answer": 584,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 19 + 13 + 0 + 18 * 11 + 9",
            "Answer": 486,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 10 + 14 + 12 + 12 * 3 + 11",
            "Answer": 163,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 19 + 7 + 16 + 2 * 10 + 19",
            "Answer": 119,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 13 + 7 + 9 + 0 * 4 + 14",
            "Answer": 82,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 7 + 15 + 16 + 7 * 16 + 3",
            "Answer": 279,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 6 + 17 + 6 + 10 * 10 + 0",
            "Answer": 195,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 16 + 5 + 14 + 1 * 2 + 19",
            "Answer": 328,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 13 + 2 + 7 + 2 * 12 + 9",
            "Answer": 276,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 8 + 0 + 7 + 3 * 6 + 11",
            "Answer": 76,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 17 + 13 + 19 + 17 * 19 + 9",
            "Answer": 449,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 19 + 10 + 4 + 5 * 6 + 18",
            "Answer": 328,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 8 + 16 + 14 + 12 * 8 + 13",
            "Answer": 203,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 16 + 3 + 7 + 14 * 11 + 19",
            "Answer": 455,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 10 + 10 + 3 + 16 * 14 + 19",
            "Answer": 316,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 16 + 18 + 18 + 6 * 8 + 11",
            "Answer": 287,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 6 + 12 + 7 + 1 * 6 + 7",
            "Answer": 44,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 10 + 10 + 12 + 9 * 13 + 15",
            "Answer": 224,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 14 + 1 + 0 + 19 * 18 + 13",
            "Answer": 580,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 5 + 16 + 0 + 2 * 15 + 14",
            "Answer": 150,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 14 + 12 + 10 + 1 * 2 + 13",
            "Answer": 289,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 14 + 15 + 19 + 10 * 11 + 9",
            "Answer": 195,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 1 + 19 + 7 + 13 * 7 + 14",
            "Answer": 141,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 11 + 5 + 14 + 2 * 8 + 19",
            "Answer": 175,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 11 + 19 + 17 + 0 * 6 + 8",
            "Answer": 55,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 4 + 18 + 18 + 12 * 16 + 16",
            "Answer": 252,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 1 + 11 + 19 + 17 * 12 + 15",
            "Answer": 254,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 6 + 17 + 3 + 0 * 6 + 10",
            "Answer": 48,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 2 + 7 + 8 + 18 * 14 + 12",
            "Answer": 305,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 10 + 4 + 17 + 16 * 6 + 14",
            "Answer": 151,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 5 + 17 + 18 + 18 * 18 + 16",
            "Answer": 440,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 3 + 2 + 15 + 1 * 9 + 14",
            "Answer": 79,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 2 + 12 + 1 + 15 * 19 + 2",
            "Answer": 326,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 4 + 10 + 17 + 1 * 0 + 16",
            "Answer": 103,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 9 + 16 + 6 + 13 * 15 + 18",
            "Answer": 280,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 6 + 2 + 18 + 6 * 12 + 11",
            "Answer": 163,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 6 + 5 + 2 + 18 * 7 + 8",
            "Answer": 231,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 14 + 7 + 17 + 19 * 6 + 9",
            "Answer": 343,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 6 + 18 + 12 + 0 * 12 + 8",
            "Answer": 56,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 9 + 13 + 17 + 13 * 15 + 13",
            "Answer": 346,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 15 + 11 + 17 + 4 * 5 + 0",
            "Answer": 198,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 14 + 15 + 2 + 6 * 4 + 1",
            "Answer": 154,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 4 + 0 + 17 + 9 * 6 + 15",
            "Answer": 118,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 6 + 10 + 2 + 16 * 19 + 3",
            "Answer": 325,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 11 + 3 + 7 + 5 * 0 + 13",
            "Answer": 34,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 14 + 16 + 0 + 18 * 15 + 2",
            "Answer": 442,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 14 + 2 + 1 + 9 * 14 + 8",
            "Answer": 193,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 6 + 17 + 9 + 11 * 6 + 6",
            "Answer": 176,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 16 + 0 + 19 + 17 * 6 + 9",
            "Answer": 162,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 15 + 3 + 9 + 12 * 4 + 0",
            "Answer": 300,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 2 + 2 + 3 + 0 * 13 + 6",
            "Answer": 39,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 11 + 14 + 0 + 7 * 18 + 4",
            "Answer": 144,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 6 + 16 + 7 + 6 * 12 + 11",
            "Answer": 178,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 14 + 10 + 9 + 6 * 10 + 2",
            "Answer": 249,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 7 + 17 + 19 + 13 * 17 + 0",
            "Answer": 369,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 11 + 0 + 10 + 19 * 19 + 12",
            "Answer": 526,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 0 + 8 + 17 + 8 * 19 + 8",
            "Answer": 185,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 14 + 18 + 13 + 9 * 15 + 5",
            "Answer": 241,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 10 + 0 + 11 + 9 * 0 + 3",
            "Answer": 34,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 10 + 16 + 7 + 11 * 12 + 0",
            "Answer": 205,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 12 + 2 + 17 + 13 * 3 + 12",
            "Answer": 106,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 11 + 18 + 15 + 11 * 17 + 11",
            "Answer": 330,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 16 + 4 + 7 + 13 * 15 + 7",
            "Answer": 213,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 1 + 19 + 0 + 5 * 14 + 16",
            "Answer": 112,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 3 + 10 + 17 + 19 * 13 + 16",
            "Answer": 332,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 13 + 14 + 5 + 2 * 15 + 10",
            "Answer": 176,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 3 + 7 + 12 + 12 * 11 + 9",
            "Answer": 178,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 2 + 3 + 9 + 1 * 6 + 10",
            "Answer": 50,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 11 + 6 + 14 + 6 * 16 + 2",
            "Answer": 140,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 18 + 9 + 5 + 17 * 8 + 17",
            "Answer": 383,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 4 + 8 + 5 + 1 * 15 + 18",
            "Answer": 54,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 2 + 13 + 6 + 7 * 19 + 4",
            "Answer": 170,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # + #"
        }
    ],
    "# + # + # + # * # * # + #": [
        {
            "Question": "6 + 12 + 12 + 19 * 7 * 4 + 0",
            "Answer": 562,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 18 + 1 + 14 * 13 * 9 + 9",
            "Answer": 1680,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 17 + 2 + 13 * 3 * 4 + 8",
            "Answer": 197,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 8 + 0 + 2 * 7 * 2 + 19",
            "Answer": 64,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 7 + 8 + 0 * 15 * 9 + 2",
            "Answer": 27,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 16 + 19 + 3 * 10 * 12 + 0",
            "Answer": 403,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 15 + 9 + 16 * 10 * 14 + 3",
            "Answer": 2275,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 17 + 1 + 8 * 10 * 19 + 17",
            "Answer": 1570,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 19 + 18 + 0 * 8 * 10 + 4",
            "Answer": 41,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 15 + 9 + 9 * 5 * 5 + 13",
            "Answer": 262,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 3 + 14 + 2 * 17 * 12 + 13",
            "Answer": 449,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 10 + 13 + 12 * 13 * 16 + 13",
            "Answer": 2540,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 2 + 19 + 8 * 10 * 10 + 1",
            "Answer": 835,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 19 + 8 + 4 * 3 * 0 + 14",
            "Answer": 50,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 4 + 17 + 16 * 12 * 16 + 17",
            "Answer": 3125,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 6 + 14 + 2 * 13 * 10 + 5",
            "Answer": 302,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 5 + 18 + 1 * 18 * 6 + 6",
            "Answer": 153,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 15 + 13 + 19 * 17 * 14 + 15",
            "Answer": 4578,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 5 + 11 + 1 * 8 * 0 + 12",
            "Answer": 28,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 11 + 10 + 7 * 7 * 7 + 14",
            "Answer": 380,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 8 + 16 + 16 * 6 * 9 + 11",
            "Answer": 914,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 13 + 6 + 9 * 1 * 14 + 5",
            "Answer": 153,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 8 + 17 + 16 * 4 * 12 + 11",
            "Answer": 813,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 13 + 6 + 0 * 3 * 12 + 4",
            "Answer": 32,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 11 + 5 + 10 * 16 * 13 + 9",
            "Answer": 2106,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 13 + 4 + 6 * 12 * 19 + 8",
            "Answer": 1403,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 0 + 1 + 17 * 16 * 3 + 4",
            "Answer": 831,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 17 + 15 + 18 * 8 * 0 + 16",
            "Answer": 59,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 12 + 11 + 18 * 10 * 19 + 2",
            "Answer": 3462,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 4 + 17 + 10 * 3 * 18 + 3",
            "Answer": 571,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 8 + 5 + 14 * 4 * 2 + 4",
            "Answer": 138,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 6 + 2 + 9 * 3 * 18 + 2",
            "Answer": 503,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 11 + 0 + 17 * 13 * 19 + 16",
            "Answer": 4244,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 0 + 9 + 8 * 17 * 19 + 16",
            "Answer": 2619,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 4 + 0 + 0 * 17 * 12 + 15",
            "Answer": 28,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 2 + 8 + 16 * 2 * 12 + 9",
            "Answer": 414,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 12 + 17 + 0 * 11 * 18 + 5",
            "Answer": 38,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 7 + 11 + 13 * 12 * 3 + 7",
            "Answer": 493,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 5 + 17 + 5 * 1 * 6 + 5",
            "Answer": 70,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 8 + 4 + 8 * 3 * 13 + 3",
            "Answer": 328,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 13 + 18 + 5 * 14 * 17 + 14",
            "Answer": 1249,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 18 + 17 + 6 * 10 * 19 + 15",
            "Answer": 1194,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 2 + 19 + 11 * 6 * 3 + 0",
            "Answer": 227,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 8 + 16 + 14 * 8 * 5 + 3",
            "Answer": 588,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 17 + 11 + 8 * 18 * 15 + 5",
            "Answer": 2203,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 17 + 10 + 15 * 8 * 19 + 18",
            "Answer": 2328,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 15 + 1 + 4 * 6 * 6 + 3",
            "Answer": 178,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 4 + 2 + 14 * 16 * 16 + 10",
            "Answer": 3617,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 17 + 1 + 14 * 5 * 12 + 4",
            "Answer": 867,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 18 + 16 + 8 * 4 * 2 + 1",
            "Answer": 105,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 13 + 15 + 13 * 9 * 17 + 6",
            "Answer": 2026,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 17 + 3 + 7 * 8 * 10 + 19",
            "Answer": 614,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 14 + 3 + 17 * 12 * 1 + 18",
            "Answer": 251,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 12 + 0 + 1 * 13 * 15 + 9",
            "Answer": 220,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 0 + 17 + 19 * 13 * 18 + 19",
            "Answer": 4492,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 0 + 18 + 14 * 17 * 18 + 6",
            "Answer": 4310,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 18 + 19 + 13 * 13 * 17 + 16",
            "Answer": 2927,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 16 + 11 + 11 * 10 * 18 + 15",
            "Answer": 2041,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 16 + 6 + 12 * 15 * 0 + 1",
            "Answer": 32,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 9 + 4 + 3 * 10 * 6 + 19",
            "Answer": 214,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 2 + 18 + 13 * 4 * 15 + 7",
            "Answer": 807,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 14 + 1 + 1 * 10 * 12 + 0",
            "Answer": 139,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 8 + 5 + 7 * 3 * 7 + 9",
            "Answer": 184,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 16 + 16 + 0 * 13 * 18 + 18",
            "Answer": 59,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 0 + 8 + 19 * 2 * 8 + 8",
            "Answer": 335,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 16 + 3 + 7 * 7 * 18 + 0",
            "Answer": 910,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 17 + 6 + 9 * 16 * 14 + 4",
            "Answer": 2058,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 14 + 16 + 16 * 4 * 3 + 13",
            "Answer": 251,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 0 + 1 + 5 * 8 * 2 + 13",
            "Answer": 96,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 4 + 4 + 11 * 12 * 16 + 0",
            "Answer": 2125,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 12 + 16 + 5 * 8 * 18 + 11",
            "Answer": 769,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 1 + 8 + 1 * 0 * 6 + 3",
            "Answer": 14,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 8 + 4 + 6 * 10 * 6 + 6",
            "Answer": 396,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 13 + 2 + 10 * 14 * 14 + 7",
            "Answer": 2001,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 4 + 3 + 6 * 7 * 14 + 8",
            "Answer": 620,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 7 + 9 + 0 * 5 * 18 + 9",
            "Answer": 36,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 1 + 17 + 15 * 10 * 12 + 14",
            "Answer": 1838,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 12 + 18 + 11 * 12 * 8 + 9",
            "Answer": 1108,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 18 + 7 + 17 * 16 * 0 + 15",
            "Answer": 53,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 6 + 14 + 8 * 12 * 6 + 8",
            "Answer": 620,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 11 + 13 + 3 * 1 * 9 + 11",
            "Answer": 62,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 17 + 6 + 13 * 14 * 4 + 8",
            "Answer": 760,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 2 + 1 + 6 * 8 * 11 + 18",
            "Answer": 565,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 4 + 3 + 16 * 6 * 19 + 16",
            "Answer": 1852,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 0 + 11 + 13 * 2 * 15 + 9",
            "Answer": 428,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 1 + 17 + 9 * 11 * 5 + 14",
            "Answer": 532,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 18 + 15 + 7 * 3 * 11 + 8",
            "Answer": 277,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 14 + 6 + 6 * 14 * 2 + 16",
            "Answer": 210,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 13 + 11 + 2 * 16 * 16 + 12",
            "Answer": 548,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 19 + 10 + 17 * 13 * 1 + 18",
            "Answer": 283,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 7 + 1 + 19 * 11 * 5 + 3",
            "Answer": 1056,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 13 + 9 + 12 * 3 * 17 + 12",
            "Answer": 664,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 16 + 5 + 14 * 15 * 16 + 9",
            "Answer": 3390,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 15 + 8 + 11 * 7 * 12 + 9",
            "Answer": 974,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 18 + 0 + 17 * 14 * 5 + 2",
            "Answer": 1224,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 14 + 9 + 13 * 0 * 8 + 8",
            "Answer": 47,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 8 + 6 + 16 * 0 * 12 + 5",
            "Answer": 26,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 14 + 6 + 17 * 7 * 15 + 13",
            "Answer": 1818,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 10 + 4 + 19 * 17 * 0 + 17",
            "Answer": 42,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 17 + 9 + 16 * 13 * 2 + 11",
            "Answer": 458,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # + #"
        }
    ],
    "# * # * # + # * # * # + #": [
        {
            "Question": "18 * 3 * 0 + 15 * 9 * 7 + 5",
            "Answer": 950,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 8 * 0 + 16 * 19 * 19 + 3",
            "Answer": 5779,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 11 * 17 + 1 * 11 * 18 + 10",
            "Answer": 3013,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 15 * 11 + 4 * 17 * 7 + 10",
            "Answer": 2301,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 18 * 5 + 14 * 17 * 19 + 17",
            "Answer": 6159,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 13 * 17 + 1 * 11 * 0 + 11",
            "Answer": 674,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 18 * 7 + 8 * 9 * 17 + 2",
            "Answer": 3116,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 9 * 2 + 11 * 7 * 2 + 16",
            "Answer": 314,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 9 * 11 + 7 * 14 * 2 + 17",
            "Answer": 1302,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 9 * 8 + 6 * 0 * 19 + 15",
            "Answer": 1095,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 7 * 3 + 12 * 18 * 13 + 18",
            "Answer": 2868,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 7 * 9 + 10 * 8 * 18 + 6",
            "Answer": 1509,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 6 * 15 + 11 * 14 * 15 + 1",
            "Answer": 3211,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 14 * 7 + 5 * 16 * 5 + 10",
            "Answer": 508,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 14 * 12 + 19 * 10 * 17 + 4",
            "Answer": 4410,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 4 * 15 + 1 * 10 * 8 + 5",
            "Answer": 745,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 12 * 12 + 16 * 9 * 10 + 12",
            "Answer": 2316,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 10 * 11 + 14 * 10 * 7 + 1",
            "Answer": 2411,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 8 * 18 + 9 * 17 * 11 + 18",
            "Answer": 2421,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 0 * 1 + 0 * 3 * 13 + 1",
            "Answer": 1,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 14 * 15 + 8 * 11 * 6 + 3",
            "Answer": 3471,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 3 * 19 + 0 * 11 * 4 + 4",
            "Answer": 1087,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 6 * 18 + 6 * 2 * 12 + 5",
            "Answer": 905,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 18 * 6 + 16 * 10 * 2 + 17",
            "Answer": 1633,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 14 * 6 + 18 * 14 * 13 + 14",
            "Answer": 3626,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 16 * 4 + 15 * 10 * 13 + 15",
            "Answer": 2733,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 11 * 9 + 17 * 15 * 6 + 4",
            "Answer": 1633,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 14 * 7 + 2 * 0 * 11 + 15",
            "Answer": 701,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 17 * 9 + 0 * 13 * 13 + 2",
            "Answer": 2297,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 12 * 3 + 16 * 2 * 13 + 11",
            "Answer": 643,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 11 * 14 + 12 * 8 * 14 + 14",
            "Answer": 3514,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 18 * 3 + 2 * 13 * 15 + 2",
            "Answer": 1418,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 7 * 15 + 11 * 9 * 2 + 18",
            "Answer": 321,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 16 * 3 + 10 * 16 * 16 + 3",
            "Answer": 2707,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 11 * 8 + 1 * 17 * 4 + 10",
            "Answer": 782,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 6 * 10 + 3 * 6 * 5 + 17",
            "Answer": 1007,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 10 * 1 + 19 * 13 * 11 + 16",
            "Answer": 2873,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 9 * 10 + 7 * 15 * 17 + 7",
            "Answer": 3322,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 7 * 0 + 9 * 15 * 1 + 10",
            "Answer": 145,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 11 * 9 + 10 * 6 * 17 + 19",
            "Answer": 2920,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 12 * 7 + 11 * 8 * 13 + 5",
            "Answer": 2073,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 13 * 10 + 15 * 15 * 1 + 6",
            "Answer": 1271,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 8 * 13 + 13 * 18 * 8 + 18",
            "Answer": 1994,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 2 * 18 + 18 * 11 * 13 + 4",
            "Answer": 2866,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 11 * 13 + 9 * 14 * 7 + 13",
            "Answer": 1896,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 11 * 8 + 3 * 14 * 7 + 17",
            "Answer": 1367,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 4 * 1 + 5 * 14 * 3 + 4",
            "Answer": 234,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 17 * 15 + 12 * 15 * 10 + 0",
            "Answer": 4350,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 18 * 16 + 7 * 0 * 8 + 10",
            "Answer": 1738,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 8 * 13 + 14 * 4 * 5 + 12",
            "Answer": 1436,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 16 * 11 + 1 * 11 * 12 + 1",
            "Answer": 1365,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 2 * 17 + 11 * 6 * 14 + 0",
            "Answer": 1162,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 6 * 5 + 6 * 16 * 11 + 4",
            "Answer": 1480,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 14 * 0 + 10 * 4 * 15 + 8",
            "Answer": 608,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 19 * 19 + 1 * 19 * 12 + 1",
            "Answer": 7088,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 8 * 3 + 12 * 4 * 12 + 0",
            "Answer": 696,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 2 * 4 + 12 * 19 * 8 + 18",
            "Answer": 1906,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 14 * 9 + 6 * 1 * 11 + 16",
            "Answer": 2224,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 17 * 19 + 12 * 3 * 11 + 13",
            "Answer": 4285,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 4 * 4 + 16 * 3 * 0 + 17",
            "Answer": 161,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 13 * 18 + 13 * 1 * 6 + 0",
            "Answer": 2886,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 5 * 7 + 11 * 14 * 17 + 9",
            "Answer": 2872,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 11 * 10 + 18 * 0 * 3 + 5",
            "Answer": 1765,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 4 * 3 + 16 * 13 * 9 + 0",
            "Answer": 1932,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 5 * 4 + 3 * 19 * 5 + 11",
            "Answer": 296,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 19 * 7 + 0 * 5 * 6 + 10",
            "Answer": 1606,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 16 * 10 + 1 * 15 * 7 + 11",
            "Answer": 276,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 11 * 10 + 13 * 16 * 14 + 15",
            "Answer": 3697,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 10 * 4 + 5 * 11 * 6 + 10",
            "Answer": 860,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 7 * 14 + 10 * 16 * 15 + 13",
            "Answer": 2413,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 15 * 17 + 7 * 16 * 14 + 3",
            "Answer": 5651,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 16 * 17 + 9 * 11 * 7 + 18",
            "Answer": 3159,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 0 * 1 + 14 * 6 * 13 + 14",
            "Answer": 1106,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 4 * 2 + 1 * 1 * 7 + 1",
            "Answer": 88,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 7 * 9 + 8 * 18 * 0 + 2",
            "Answer": 1073,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 3 * 14 + 18 * 14 * 6 + 19",
            "Answer": 1867,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 10 * 2 + 6 * 10 * 10 + 19",
            "Answer": 839,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 0 * 7 + 11 * 10 * 17 + 3",
            "Answer": 1873,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 1 * 15 + 15 * 12 * 16 + 12",
            "Answer": 2937,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 8 * 18 + 18 * 7 * 4 + 10",
            "Answer": 802,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 0 * 8 + 3 * 13 * 16 + 9",
            "Answer": 633,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 0 * 17 + 15 * 0 * 18 + 15",
            "Answer": 15,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 1 * 12 + 15 * 15 * 16 + 15",
            "Answer": 3807,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 10 * 7 + 15 * 17 * 14 + 2",
            "Answer": 4412,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 0 * 9 + 8 * 8 * 9 + 7",
            "Answer": 583,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 18 * 8 + 6 * 1 * 13 + 2",
            "Answer": 2240,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 6 * 2 + 9 * 12 * 14 + 14",
            "Answer": 1598,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 0 * 12 + 16 * 11 * 17 + 5",
            "Answer": 2997,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 9 * 8 + 14 * 17 * 0 + 19",
            "Answer": 955,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 16 * 15 + 14 * 2 * 13 + 10",
            "Answer": 2534,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 5 * 0 + 9 * 11 * 18 + 4",
            "Answer": 1786,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 5 * 9 + 14 * 19 * 2 + 0",
            "Answer": 1207,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 16 * 4 + 6 * 6 * 19 + 19",
            "Answer": 1855,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 19 * 13 + 11 * 6 * 4 + 6",
            "Answer": 4716,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 5 * 17 + 18 * 3 * 12 + 6",
            "Answer": 1589,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 4 * 6 + 12 * 7 * 19 + 19",
            "Answer": 1687,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 14 * 0 + 6 * 16 * 7 + 13",
            "Answer": 685,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 6 * 6 + 11 * 3 * 8 + 17",
            "Answer": 605,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 19 * 16 + 17 * 4 * 1 + 10",
            "Answer": 1294,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 15 * 6 + 18 * 9 * 4 + 18",
            "Answer": 1566,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # * # + #"
        }
    ],
    "# * # * # * # * # * # + #": [
        {
            "Question": "3 * 8 * 3 * 19 * 17 * 17 + 16",
            "Answer": 395368,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 12 * 18 * 5 * 2 * 14 + 8",
            "Answer": 211688,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 19 * 11 * 19 * 18 * 5 + 7",
            "Answer": 2501737,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 13 * 18 * 13 * 7 * 16 + 4",
            "Answer": 681412,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 15 * 16 * 16 * 13 * 3 + 12",
            "Answer": 449292,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 0 * 7 * 3 * 17 * 1 + 7",
            "Answer": 7,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 11 * 10 * 4 * 19 * 14 + 15",
            "Answer": 585215,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 3 * 7 * 5 * 10 * 3 + 7",
            "Answer": 31507,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 18 * 7 * 2 * 10 * 4 + 6",
            "Answer": 181446,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 0 * 8 * 5 * 12 * 3 + 13",
            "Answer": 13,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 3 * 15 * 0 * 12 * 9 + 12",
            "Answer": 12,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 3 * 9 * 8 * 15 * 9 + 13",
            "Answer": 466573,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 8 * 12 * 4 * 17 * 10 + 6",
            "Answer": 130566,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 18 * 3 * 11 * 5 * 13 + 4",
            "Answer": 4,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 10 * 16 * 5 * 6 * 2 + 1",
            "Answer": 76801,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 19 * 3 * 2 * 17 * 0 + 7",
            "Answer": 7,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 10 * 18 * 9 * 12 * 19 + 12",
            "Answer": 5540412,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 18 * 5 * 0 * 6 * 19 + 12",
            "Answer": 12,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 14 * 12 * 4 * 10 * 8 + 11",
            "Answer": 967691,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 1 * 11 * 5 * 6 * 5 + 7",
            "Answer": 1657,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 5 * 3 * 16 * 4 * 6 + 12",
            "Answer": 34572,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 3 * 9 * 0 * 4 * 5 + 12",
            "Answer": 12,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 4 * 12 * 14 * 5 * 17 + 2",
            "Answer": 456962,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 18 * 11 * 6 * 2 * 16 + 6",
            "Answer": 684294,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 15 * 2 * 15 * 19 * 2 + 13",
            "Answer": 290713,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 4 * 19 * 3 * 9 * 17 + 16",
            "Answer": 662812,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 14 * 8 * 2 * 18 * 0 + 12",
            "Answer": 12,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 10 * 13 * 16 * 2 * 15 + 16",
            "Answer": 249616,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 6 * 6 * 7 * 7 * 14 + 18",
            "Answer": 395154,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 12 * 17 * 15 * 12 * 11 + 10",
            "Answer": 5250970,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 16 * 16 * 16 * 8 * 8 + 15",
            "Answer": 3932175,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 15 * 11 * 6 * 5 * 10 + 19",
            "Answer": 693019,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 9 * 18 * 10 * 11 * 18 + 7",
            "Answer": 5773687,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 0 * 10 * 9 * 8 * 3 + 1",
            "Answer": 1,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 17 * 4 * 8 * 14 * 17 + 1",
            "Answer": 2459969,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 19 * 8 * 13 * 18 * 6 + 6",
            "Answer": 3414534,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 13 * 7 * 11 * 12 * 9 + 19",
            "Answer": 1621639,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 8 * 16 * 18 * 15 * 3 + 8",
            "Answer": 933128,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 1 * 14 * 13 * 15 * 7 + 4",
            "Answer": 38224,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 9 * 1 * 1 * 9 * 0 + 2",
            "Answer": 2,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 12 * 10 * 19 * 12 * 12 + 4",
            "Answer": 4268164,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 9 * 7 * 16 * 18 * 9 + 6",
            "Answer": 2939334,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 2 * 10 * 13 * 7 * 15 + 16",
            "Answer": 109216,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 1 * 11 * 6 * 12 * 8 + 6",
            "Answer": 6,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 16 * 11 * 12 * 18 * 16 + 7",
            "Answer": 5474311,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 4 * 7 * 2 * 11 * 9 + 19",
            "Answer": 83179,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 6 * 5 * 17 * 14 * 18 + 12",
            "Answer": 128532,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 16 * 6 * 16 * 16 * 2 + 0",
            "Answer": 589824,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 14 * 10 * 8 * 17 * 6 + 9",
            "Answer": 1713609,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 1 * 9 * 5 * 6 * 7 + 14",
            "Answer": 20804,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 14 * 18 * 3 * 2 * 9 + 17",
            "Answer": 244961,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 13 * 18 * 10 * 12 * 9 + 6",
            "Answer": 2274486,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 2 * 8 * 10 * 15 * 2 + 4",
            "Answer": 14404,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 17 * 3 * 16 * 14 * 1 + 16",
            "Answer": 114256,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 9 * 14 * 5 * 6 * 16 + 2",
            "Answer": 241922,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 7 * 17 * 10 * 11 * 6 + 8",
            "Answer": 471248,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 1 * 8 * 14 * 5 * 15 + 0",
            "Answer": 8400,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 3 * 10 * 1 * 14 * 5 + 15",
            "Answer": 14715,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 4 * 6 * 19 * 19 * 6 + 3",
            "Answer": 779763,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 4 * 18 * 18 * 4 * 6 + 13",
            "Answer": 31117,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 5 * 19 * 8 * 7 * 12 + 9",
            "Answer": 1149129,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 6 * 19 * 11 * 5 * 8 + 13",
            "Answer": 13,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 5 * 2 * 12 * 8 * 19 + 15",
            "Answer": 291855,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 1 * 5 * 6 * 6 * 16 + 15",
            "Answer": 25935,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 7 * 17 * 13 * 10 * 12 + 19",
            "Answer": 1299499,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 2 * 13 * 13 * 11 * 19 + 19",
            "Answer": 494513,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 13 * 3 * 1 * 4 * 10 + 8",
            "Answer": 12488,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 1 * 17 * 0 * 8 * 11 + 4",
            "Answer": 4,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 14 * 12 * 15 * 0 * 6 + 6",
            "Answer": 6,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 2 * 11 * 15 * 19 * 0 + 16",
            "Answer": 16,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 11 * 2 * 19 * 1 * 11 + 11",
            "Answer": 9207,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 9 * 14 * 2 * 18 * 0 + 18",
            "Answer": 18,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 7 * 16 * 14 * 14 * 0 + 13",
            "Answer": 13,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 8 * 14 * 6 * 3 * 5 + 16",
            "Answer": 10096,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 16 * 3 * 14 * 18 * 10 + 14",
            "Answer": 725774,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 16 * 9 * 5 * 18 * 19 + 9",
            "Answer": 1231209,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 13 * 15 * 10 * 9 * 4 + 1",
            "Answer": 1193401,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 1 * 4 * 8 * 18 * 5 + 14",
            "Answer": 5774,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 14 * 16 * 10 * 14 * 16 + 9",
            "Answer": 6522889,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 13 * 19 * 5 * 12 * 17 + 12",
            "Answer": 4031052,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 17 * 4 * 1 * 19 * 12 + 1",
            "Answer": 248065,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 17 * 15 * 16 * 12 * 10 + 0",
            "Answer": 4896000,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 7 * 5 * 17 * 1 * 1 + 7",
            "Answer": 5957,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 8 * 8 * 16 * 14 * 17 + 2",
            "Answer": 1949698,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 14 * 19 * 1 * 9 * 7 + 12",
            "Answer": 184350,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 12 * 3 * 1 * 12 * 16 + 4",
            "Answer": 82948,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 14 * 14 * 0 * 14 * 5 + 19",
            "Answer": 19,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 11 * 17 * 2 * 18 * 15 + 4",
            "Answer": 807844,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 6 * 18 * 13 * 12 * 17 + 11",
            "Answer": 286427,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 11 * 3 * 4 * 19 * 8 + 3",
            "Answer": 140451,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 10 * 18 * 7 * 8 * 16 + 15",
            "Answer": 3064335,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 11 * 8 * 1 * 14 * 14 + 16",
            "Answer": 86256,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 14 * 17 * 13 * 0 * 16 + 12",
            "Answer": 12,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 1 * 11 * 11 * 18 * 4 + 7",
            "Answer": 95839,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 17 * 1 * 17 * 13 * 4 + 4",
            "Answer": 240452,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 4 * 8 * 14 * 18 * 12 + 3",
            "Answer": 3,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 14 * 19 * 7 * 16 * 11 + 11",
            "Answer": 2949419,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 17 * 11 * 3 * 5 * 4 + 3",
            "Answer": 134643,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 4 * 7 * 8 * 3 * 16 + 6",
            "Answer": 129030,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 7 * 4 * 19 * 12 * 6 + 12",
            "Answer": 306444,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # * # + #"
        }
    ],
    "# * # + # * # * # * # * #": [
        {
            "Question": "3 * 9 + 19 * 12 * 4 * 13 * 15",
            "Answer": 177867,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 13 + 5 * 10 * 2 * 6 * 13",
            "Answer": 7904,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 8 + 18 * 4 * 11 * 15 * 4",
            "Answer": 47600,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 14 + 0 * 5 * 13 * 9 * 19",
            "Answer": 238,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 0 + 2 * 11 * 9 * 7 * 10",
            "Answer": 13860,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 5 + 18 * 4 * 3 * 1 * 16",
            "Answer": 3531,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 12 + 15 * 14 * 5 * 5 * 9",
            "Answer": 47322,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 12 + 15 * 15 * 6 * 2 * 9",
            "Answer": 24456,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 10 + 3 * 17 * 12 * 10 * 17",
            "Answer": 104120,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 7 + 16 * 19 * 3 * 4 * 3",
            "Answer": 10965,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 9 + 7 * 10 * 7 * 9 * 7",
            "Answer": 30978,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 11 + 8 * 0 * 9 * 1 * 17",
            "Answer": 33,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 7 + 2 * 10 * 2 * 15 * 2",
            "Answer": 1312,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 16 + 2 * 4 * 11 * 6 * 9",
            "Answer": 4912,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 4 + 10 * 16 * 1 * 14 * 19",
            "Answer": 42572,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 5 + 10 * 1 * 7 * 1 * 12",
            "Answer": 840,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 15 + 4 * 10 * 3 * 18 * 14",
            "Answer": 30450,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 1 + 7 * 14 * 4 * 4 * 16",
            "Answer": 25104,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 17 + 3 * 17 * 5 * 14 * 11",
            "Answer": 39287,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 4 + 11 * 6 * 4 * 13 * 3",
            "Answer": 10364,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 0 + 18 * 13 * 11 * 9 * 5",
            "Answer": 115830,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 0 + 4 * 0 * 0 * 12 * 14",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 17 + 18 * 2 * 11 * 3 * 7",
            "Answer": 8486,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 17 + 6 * 9 * 1 * 5 * 6",
            "Answer": 1637,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 8 + 18 * 6 * 19 * 15 * 12",
            "Answer": 369472,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 13 + 1 * 15 * 9 * 19 * 2",
            "Answer": 5182,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 10 + 4 * 10 * 8 * 8 * 10",
            "Answer": 25730,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 15 + 11 * 3 * 12 * 9 * 18",
            "Answer": 64242,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 6 + 6 * 3 * 5 * 8 * 10",
            "Answer": 7278,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 6 + 14 * 18 * 17 * 12 * 8",
            "Answer": 411264,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 2 + 6 * 16 * 4 * 18 * 2",
            "Answer": 13850,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 19 + 9 * 8 * 12 * 13 * 6",
            "Answer": 67563,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 1 + 7 * 5 * 18 * 16 * 4",
            "Answer": 40335,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 2 + 5 * 15 * 12 * 15 * 0",
            "Answer": 10,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 7 + 17 * 17 * 16 * 6 * 11",
            "Answer": 305198,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 3 + 14 * 3 * 5 * 4 * 6",
            "Answer": 5046,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 17 + 13 * 3 * 0 * 1 * 8",
            "Answer": 255,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 11 + 13 * 6 * 11 * 2 * 15",
            "Answer": 25751,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 9 + 7 * 14 * 5 * 14 * 5",
            "Answer": 34363,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 13 + 9 * 7 * 4 * 7 * 7",
            "Answer": 12400,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 16 + 17 * 17 * 16 * 10 * 0",
            "Answer": 288,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 4 + 2 * 3 * 13 * 17 * 8",
            "Answer": 10624,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 9 + 16 * 7 * 8 * 15 * 17",
            "Answer": 228552,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 9 + 18 * 2 * 5 * 11 * 11",
            "Answer": 21924,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 7 + 1 * 13 * 13 * 0 * 10",
            "Answer": 133,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 15 + 19 * 3 * 4 * 18 * 17",
            "Answer": 69813,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 3 + 8 * 7 * 10 * 0 * 6",
            "Answer": 24,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 16 + 11 * 7 * 15 * 9 * 3",
            "Answer": 31345,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 19 + 19 * 6 * 9 * 5 * 18",
            "Answer": 92359,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 18 + 3 * 14 * 12 * 3 * 8",
            "Answer": 12366,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 4 + 3 * 3 * 15 * 11 * 15",
            "Answer": 22303,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 1 + 11 * 11 * 6 * 0 * 14",
            "Answer": 5,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 18 + 12 * 1 * 11 * 5 * 3",
            "Answer": 2052,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 6 + 8 * 14 * 5 * 10 * 8",
            "Answer": 44866,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 4 + 19 * 7 * 5 * 10 * 1",
            "Answer": 6670,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 7 + 11 * 7 * 1 * 3 * 2",
            "Answer": 560,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 9 + 7 * 1 * 9 * 7 * 14",
            "Answer": 6318,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 10 + 4 * 0 * 17 * 4 * 11",
            "Answer": 40,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 18 + 18 * 19 * 14 * 17 * 12",
            "Answer": 976806,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 8 + 9 * 7 * 17 * 3 * 18",
            "Answer": 57858,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 19 + 0 * 13 * 4 * 18 * 19",
            "Answer": 133,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 15 + 5 * 10 * 15 * 15 * 18",
            "Answer": 202665,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 11 + 6 * 5 * 10 * 11 * 1",
            "Answer": 3344,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 6 + 12 * 6 * 1 * 2 * 11",
            "Answer": 1584,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 16 + 4 * 14 * 0 * 18 * 1",
            "Answer": 64,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 18 + 19 * 16 * 9 * 1 * 0",
            "Answer": 324,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 14 + 12 * 19 * 0 * 15 * 8",
            "Answer": 70,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 14 + 7 * 12 * 16 * 1 * 12",
            "Answer": 16254,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 4 + 14 * 3 * 15 * 9 * 14",
            "Answer": 79404,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 2 + 8 * 1 * 11 * 1 * 6",
            "Answer": 556,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 10 + 16 * 6 * 9 * 3 * 8",
            "Answer": 20816,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 19 + 2 * 8 * 9 * 3 * 0",
            "Answer": 190,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 4 + 15 * 11 * 12 * 12 * 19",
            "Answer": 451504,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 13 + 9 * 2 * 0 * 8 * 4",
            "Answer": 104,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 0 + 10 * 1 * 19 * 18 * 19",
            "Answer": 64980,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 7 + 1 * 12 * 3 * 10 * 13",
            "Answer": 4715,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 13 + 6 * 5 * 7 * 9 * 9",
            "Answer": 17218,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 1 + 13 * 1 * 4 * 16 * 12",
            "Answer": 9992,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 7 + 15 * 17 * 4 * 10 * 14",
            "Answer": 142898,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 16 + 0 * 5 * 13 * 4 * 12",
            "Answer": 96,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 17 + 5 * 5 * 17 * 0 * 3",
            "Answer": 289,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 10 + 3 * 15 * 8 * 11 * 7",
            "Answer": 27790,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 16 + 11 * 19 * 8 * 15 * 0",
            "Answer": 96,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 18 + 0 * 9 * 14 * 10 * 8",
            "Answer": 288,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 12 + 18 * 3 * 10 * 11 * 8",
            "Answer": 47712,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 14 + 8 * 0 * 1 * 19 * 16",
            "Answer": 14,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 7 + 2 * 19 * 14 * 5 * 4",
            "Answer": 10654,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 16 + 19 * 12 * 9 * 16 * 10",
            "Answer": 328384,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 18 + 9 * 3 * 10 * 9 * 15",
            "Answer": 36630,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 3 + 10 * 3 * 11 * 2 * 18",
            "Answer": 11922,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 9 + 19 * 10 * 18 * 15 * 18",
            "Answer": 923445,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 11 + 17 * 13 * 13 * 7 * 14",
            "Answer": 281576,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 2 + 17 * 16 * 13 * 13 * 5",
            "Answer": 229860,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 11 + 18 * 5 * 3 * 2 * 3",
            "Answer": 1796,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 10 + 16 * 19 * 10 * 11 * 13",
            "Answer": 434760,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 1 + 15 * 0 * 1 * 16 * 12",
            "Answer": 5,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 6 + 3 * 9 * 13 * 10 * 17",
            "Answer": 59718,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 0 + 18 * 14 * 8 * 15 * 15",
            "Answer": 453600,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 3 + 16 * 8 * 14 * 19 * 14",
            "Answer": 476723,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 0 + 14 * 10 * 5 * 6 * 11",
            "Answer": 46200,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # * #"
        }
    ],
    "# + # + # + # + # * # + #": [
        {
            "Question": "18 + 13 + 8 + 18 + 7 * 6 + 18",
            "Answer": 117,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 6 + 9 + 12 + 8 * 15 + 14",
            "Answer": 180,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 2 + 14 + 13 + 0 * 10 + 5",
            "Answer": 53,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 17 + 12 + 10 + 13 * 1 + 13",
            "Answer": 68,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 18 + 5 + 13 + 2 * 3 + 8",
            "Answer": 62,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 7 + 3 + 10 + 2 * 6 + 14",
            "Answer": 58,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 10 + 8 + 6 + 16 * 2 + 19",
            "Answer": 83,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 3 + 6 + 11 + 14 * 14 + 8",
            "Answer": 231,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 15 + 15 + 4 + 13 * 10 + 6",
            "Answer": 186,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 11 + 5 + 16 + 5 * 2 + 9",
            "Answer": 69,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 17 + 12 + 12 + 16 * 18 + 16",
            "Answer": 352,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 18 + 0 + 1 + 9 * 12 + 2",
            "Answer": 144,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 16 + 4 + 2 + 12 * 7 + 10",
            "Answer": 118,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 7 + 15 + 6 + 12 * 10 + 12",
            "Answer": 166,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 2 + 13 + 3 + 16 * 19 + 5",
            "Answer": 331,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 19 + 10 + 10 + 13 * 16 + 12",
            "Answer": 274,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 11 + 12 + 8 + 10 * 4 + 7",
            "Answer": 78,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 19 + 15 + 11 + 11 * 13 + 9",
            "Answer": 214,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 13 + 1 + 15 + 12 * 8 + 15",
            "Answer": 143,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 11 + 19 + 10 + 16 * 0 + 7",
            "Answer": 47,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 16 + 12 + 0 + 16 * 13 + 18",
            "Answer": 264,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 14 + 13 + 4 + 18 * 14 + 17",
            "Answer": 301,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 17 + 6 + 16 + 6 * 6 + 1",
            "Answer": 94,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 0 + 10 + 11 + 13 * 0 + 0",
            "Answer": 24,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 4 + 6 + 7 + 1 * 12 + 13",
            "Answer": 50,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 5 + 15 + 3 + 10 * 5 + 9",
            "Answer": 94,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 9 + 14 + 11 + 19 * 18 + 4",
            "Answer": 386,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 5 + 16 + 4 + 9 * 15 + 12",
            "Answer": 174,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 12 + 18 + 9 + 6 * 14 + 6",
            "Answer": 145,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 2 + 3 + 15 + 6 * 13 + 2",
            "Answer": 102,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 2 + 10 + 19 + 13 * 3 + 5",
            "Answer": 80,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 10 + 1 + 2 + 7 * 10 + 19",
            "Answer": 105,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 16 + 6 + 8 + 8 * 7 + 19",
            "Answer": 120,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 5 + 19 + 4 + 9 * 14 + 15",
            "Answer": 188,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 9 + 13 + 6 + 8 * 19 + 18",
            "Answer": 215,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 17 + 4 + 16 + 0 * 10 + 14",
            "Answer": 52,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 6 + 15 + 15 + 6 * 19 + 18",
            "Answer": 175,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 8 + 18 + 8 + 1 * 9 + 4",
            "Answer": 65,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 12 + 18 + 7 + 7 * 19 + 7",
            "Answer": 190,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 19 + 17 + 7 + 5 * 11 + 12",
            "Answer": 127,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 14 + 17 + 0 + 10 * 12 + 18",
            "Answer": 176,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 9 + 8 + 6 + 6 * 12 + 19",
            "Answer": 132,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 0 + 13 + 0 + 6 * 1 + 4",
            "Answer": 34,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 16 + 16 + 17 + 17 * 11 + 0",
            "Answer": 245,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 13 + 12 + 9 + 15 * 2 + 12",
            "Answer": 92,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 10 + 19 + 19 + 12 * 16 + 1",
            "Answer": 244,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 16 + 4 + 11 + 8 * 5 + 1",
            "Answer": 89,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 16 + 2 + 11 + 0 * 14 + 9",
            "Answer": 52,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 11 + 9 + 8 + 17 * 19 + 2",
            "Answer": 355,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 17 + 2 + 9 + 8 * 12 + 11",
            "Answer": 154,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 2 + 15 + 15 + 14 * 6 + 5",
            "Answer": 124,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 0 + 19 + 5 + 18 * 15 + 7",
            "Answer": 306,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 18 + 1 + 19 + 3 * 10 + 18",
            "Answer": 98,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 19 + 3 + 9 + 16 * 3 + 1",
            "Answer": 82,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 17 + 11 + 7 + 0 * 6 + 1",
            "Answer": 44,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 9 + 17 + 2 + 9 * 3 + 2",
            "Answer": 62,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 7 + 1 + 5 + 8 * 4 + 14",
            "Answer": 60,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 13 + 0 + 11 + 17 * 4 + 3",
            "Answer": 104,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 17 + 13 + 1 + 10 * 12 + 10",
            "Answer": 169,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 8 + 3 + 10 + 2 * 1 + 8",
            "Answer": 35,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 14 + 18 + 1 + 9 * 11 + 15",
            "Answer": 164,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 17 + 12 + 8 + 16 * 15 + 15",
            "Answer": 310,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 14 + 18 + 10 + 4 * 2 + 10",
            "Answer": 73,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 4 + 5 + 1 + 16 * 12 + 2",
            "Answer": 204,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 13 + 15 + 18 + 7 * 0 + 8",
            "Answer": 57,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 18 + 1 + 11 + 18 * 6 + 9",
            "Answer": 151,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 12 + 11 + 17 + 17 * 16 + 1",
            "Answer": 325,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 3 + 1 + 6 + 5 * 16 + 17",
            "Answer": 109,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 2 + 5 + 4 + 6 * 5 + 17",
            "Answer": 70,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 10 + 11 + 15 + 11 * 19 + 13",
            "Answer": 264,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 12 + 2 + 8 + 18 * 12 + 7",
            "Answer": 251,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 11 + 15 + 6 + 19 * 7 + 4",
            "Answer": 173,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 3 + 0 + 11 + 10 * 8 + 3",
            "Answer": 98,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 2 + 6 + 8 + 10 * 5 + 2",
            "Answer": 76,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 10 + 8 + 17 + 7 * 4 + 10",
            "Answer": 80,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 13 + 8 + 11 + 19 * 11 + 3",
            "Answer": 252,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 17 + 18 + 1 + 3 * 5 + 18",
            "Answer": 72,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 13 + 1 + 6 + 10 * 9 + 19",
            "Answer": 132,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 11 + 4 + 13 + 7 * 11 + 12",
            "Answer": 119,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 1 + 1 + 19 + 7 * 14 + 17",
            "Answer": 143,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 9 + 5 + 3 + 17 * 18 + 19",
            "Answer": 349,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 19 + 4 + 2 + 4 * 17 + 17",
            "Answer": 127,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 6 + 2 + 12 + 18 * 14 + 19",
            "Answer": 306,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 1 + 10 + 8 + 2 * 12 + 15",
            "Answer": 76,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 14 + 0 + 9 + 4 * 5 + 13",
            "Answer": 62,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 11 + 9 + 14 + 15 * 2 + 13",
            "Answer": 87,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 15 + 2 + 2 + 11 * 18 + 12",
            "Answer": 240,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 8 + 7 + 8 + 6 * 15 + 7",
            "Answer": 123,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 16 + 5 + 13 + 10 * 1 + 9",
            "Answer": 66,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 1 + 18 + 17 + 19 * 15 + 17",
            "Answer": 357,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 5 + 18 + 16 + 9 * 2 + 13",
            "Answer": 70,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 19 + 1 + 4 + 14 * 11 + 7",
            "Answer": 200,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 4 + 5 + 8 + 1 * 1 + 17",
            "Answer": 40,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 17 + 13 + 15 + 8 * 4 + 18",
            "Answer": 101,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 2 + 3 + 15 + 8 * 8 + 1",
            "Answer": 99,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 17 + 1 + 0 + 1 * 12 + 13",
            "Answer": 60,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 4 + 4 + 4 + 7 * 15 + 0",
            "Answer": 134,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 16 + 7 + 4 + 7 * 9 + 12",
            "Answer": 119,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 17 + 11 + 11 + 9 * 15 + 18",
            "Answer": 209,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 17 + 14 + 13 + 17 * 4 + 17",
            "Answer": 144,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # + #"
        }
    ],
    "# * # * # + # + # + # * #": [
        {
            "Question": "19 * 3 * 9 + 0 + 5 + 1 * 13",
            "Answer": 531,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 10 * 3 + 6 + 8 + 16 * 9",
            "Answer": 728,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 10 * 18 + 9 + 14 + 6 * 11",
            "Answer": 3329,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 13 * 17 + 3 + 5 + 16 * 0",
            "Answer": 3102,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 17 * 2 + 16 + 9 + 1 * 19",
            "Answer": 520,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 6 * 8 + 13 + 15 + 15 * 14",
            "Answer": 574,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 14 * 12 + 13 + 14 + 9 * 7",
            "Answer": 1434,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 6 * 17 + 0 + 13 + 0 * 4",
            "Answer": 421,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 4 * 8 + 15 + 17 + 8 * 4",
            "Answer": 480,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 17 * 15 + 11 + 10 + 14 * 4",
            "Answer": 1607,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 14 * 7 + 14 + 14 + 14 * 10",
            "Answer": 364,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 14 * 13 + 18 + 2 + 8 * 19",
            "Answer": 2174,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 3 * 7 + 9 + 1 + 18 * 2",
            "Answer": 88,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 5 * 4 + 1 + 7 + 12 * 12",
            "Answer": 252,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 4 * 15 + 11 + 13 + 10 * 9",
            "Answer": 1074,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 9 * 0 + 8 + 5 + 19 * 2",
            "Answer": 51,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 1 * 18 + 4 + 7 + 7 * 11",
            "Answer": 232,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 12 * 7 + 15 + 8 + 11 * 8",
            "Answer": 363,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 17 * 0 + 18 + 11 + 18 * 11",
            "Answer": 227,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 0 * 4 + 17 + 0 + 19 * 3",
            "Answer": 74,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 13 * 4 + 14 + 19 + 15 * 19",
            "Answer": 630,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 9 * 4 + 18 + 16 + 12 * 1",
            "Answer": 694,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 2 * 16 + 15 + 10 + 16 * 17",
            "Answer": 841,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 9 * 0 + 15 + 1 + 15 * 13",
            "Answer": 211,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 5 * 10 + 1 + 2 + 8 * 17",
            "Answer": 739,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 10 * 5 + 4 + 2 + 15 * 8",
            "Answer": 1026,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 12 * 5 + 12 + 3 + 7 * 19",
            "Answer": 568,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 8 * 8 + 5 + 14 + 13 * 18",
            "Answer": 1469,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 18 * 2 + 7 + 11 + 16 * 18",
            "Answer": 414,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 6 * 7 + 1 + 17 + 1 * 1",
            "Answer": 61,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 12 * 0 + 4 + 19 + 19 * 9",
            "Answer": 194,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 10 * 18 + 10 + 10 + 15 * 11",
            "Answer": 3245,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 12 * 1 + 12 + 12 + 2 * 5",
            "Answer": 238,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 17 * 18 + 6 + 13 + 15 * 1",
            "Answer": 5848,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 5 * 13 + 1 + 15 + 1 * 16",
            "Answer": 97,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 17 * 1 + 17 + 15 + 1 * 16",
            "Answer": 269,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 4 * 14 + 11 + 11 + 5 * 2",
            "Answer": 928,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 17 * 2 + 5 + 14 + 8 * 9",
            "Answer": 261,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 13 * 14 + 6 + 5 + 4 * 3",
            "Answer": 3481,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 18 * 10 + 19 + 16 + 9 * 8",
            "Answer": 107,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 17 * 1 + 14 + 14 + 15 * 9",
            "Answer": 469,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 8 * 10 + 5 + 7 + 4 * 18",
            "Answer": 964,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 18 * 10 + 14 + 7 + 7 * 14",
            "Answer": 3539,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 13 * 10 + 11 + 4 + 18 * 13",
            "Answer": 379,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 16 * 15 + 5 + 16 + 11 * 16",
            "Answer": 2837,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 5 * 13 + 13 + 8 + 8 * 5",
            "Answer": 321,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 7 * 8 + 19 + 7 + 9 * 12",
            "Answer": 1198,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 2 * 19 + 9 + 10 + 2 * 1",
            "Answer": 743,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 7 * 3 + 13 + 6 + 13 * 19",
            "Answer": 602,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 0 * 11 + 5 + 11 + 1 * 9",
            "Answer": 25,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 1 * 7 + 14 + 10 + 14 * 8",
            "Answer": 185,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 9 * 5 + 17 + 2 + 14 * 19",
            "Answer": 375,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 15 * 3 + 3 + 8 + 3 * 3",
            "Answer": 290,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 15 * 7 + 16 + 8 + 13 * 16",
            "Answer": 1807,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 19 * 11 + 4 + 0 + 5 * 17",
            "Answer": 3015,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 18 * 3 + 15 + 14 + 14 * 2",
            "Answer": 921,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 17 * 8 + 5 + 14 + 5 * 11",
            "Answer": 2114,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 11 * 13 + 7 + 11 + 3 * 17",
            "Answer": 1785,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 4 * 15 + 0 + 2 + 15 * 14",
            "Answer": 632,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 5 * 6 + 13 + 6 + 4 * 15",
            "Answer": 79,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 17 * 0 + 16 + 18 + 0 * 9",
            "Answer": 34,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 10 * 5 + 9 + 4 + 11 * 18",
            "Answer": 361,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 19 * 13 + 11 + 1 + 4 * 8",
            "Answer": 291,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 18 * 5 + 12 + 4 + 16 * 12",
            "Answer": 388,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 15 * 10 + 13 + 3 + 12 * 10",
            "Answer": 736,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 2 * 19 + 13 + 14 + 6 * 16",
            "Answer": 237,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 12 * 12 + 16 + 16 + 1 * 7",
            "Answer": 471,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 4 * 6 + 6 + 9 + 8 * 9",
            "Answer": 495,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 16 * 14 + 17 + 5 + 9 * 16",
            "Answer": 3750,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 12 * 8 + 14 + 11 + 1 * 1",
            "Answer": 602,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 0 * 11 + 4 + 2 + 13 * 2",
            "Answer": 32,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 6 * 10 + 7 + 4 + 4 * 5",
            "Answer": 391,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 2 * 7 + 16 + 15 + 7 * 14",
            "Answer": 311,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 9 * 17 + 8 + 19 + 12 * 8",
            "Answer": 2877,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 12 * 13 + 12 + 15 + 18 * 18",
            "Answer": 2223,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 14 * 13 + 19 + 19 + 7 * 19",
            "Answer": 2355,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 14 * 0 + 16 + 8 + 19 * 14",
            "Answer": 290,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 12 * 19 + 8 + 18 + 9 * 13",
            "Answer": 2651,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 3 * 12 + 18 + 10 + 10 * 3",
            "Answer": 418,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 11 * 5 + 11 + 8 + 17 * 8",
            "Answer": 1145,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 4 * 6 + 19 + 13 + 15 * 19",
            "Answer": 341,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 7 * 0 + 19 + 19 + 15 * 2",
            "Answer": 68,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 14 * 15 + 14 + 9 + 11 * 5",
            "Answer": 2808,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 10 * 19 + 0 + 3 + 15 * 1",
            "Answer": 2868,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 19 * 14 + 15 + 18 + 0 * 7",
            "Answer": 4821,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 16 * 2 + 4 + 6 + 6 * 10",
            "Answer": 326,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 17 * 16 + 19 + 12 + 11 * 18",
            "Answer": 3765,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 15 * 10 + 17 + 15 + 6 * 7",
            "Answer": 2624,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 12 * 14 + 3 + 1 + 7 * 11",
            "Answer": 921,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 0 * 7 + 16 + 6 + 14 * 13",
            "Answer": 204,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 16 * 13 + 6 + 17 + 0 * 14",
            "Answer": 1479,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 14 * 2 + 6 + 9 + 13 * 11",
            "Answer": 438,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 3 * 17 + 7 + 13 + 5 * 2",
            "Answer": 591,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 11 * 18 + 18 + 11 + 11 * 6",
            "Answer": 2273,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 8 * 3 + 7 + 17 + 2 * 19",
            "Answer": 374,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 0 * 3 + 9 + 6 + 1 * 10",
            "Answer": 25,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 4 * 3 + 1 + 7 + 7 * 11",
            "Answer": 145,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 8 * 15 + 6 + 1 + 18 * 14",
            "Answer": 259,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 14 * 16 + 17 + 7 + 6 * 1",
            "Answer": 2718,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 6 * 1 + 12 + 5 + 2 * 2",
            "Answer": 123,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # * #"
        }
    ],
    "# * # * # + # + # * # * #": [
        {
            "Question": "16 * 2 * 8 + 15 + 4 * 11 * 14",
            "Answer": 887,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 19 * 2 + 14 + 16 * 5 * 6",
            "Answer": 570,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 10 * 3 + 2 + 14 * 19 * 3",
            "Answer": 800,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 10 * 0 + 8 + 15 * 2 * 6",
            "Answer": 188,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 12 * 6 + 2 + 4 * 19 * 9",
            "Answer": 686,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 14 * 8 + 2 + 8 * 15 * 1",
            "Answer": 1130,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 15 * 0 + 15 + 12 * 5 * 17",
            "Answer": 1035,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 13 * 3 + 19 + 10 * 0 * 9",
            "Answer": 682,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 1 * 7 + 17 + 9 * 6 * 2",
            "Answer": 202,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 14 * 2 + 10 + 12 * 3 * 9",
            "Answer": 782,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 12 * 9 + 13 + 11 * 4 * 5",
            "Answer": 1745,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 19 * 4 + 14 + 18 * 12 * 12",
            "Answer": 3974,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 10 * 6 + 11 + 13 * 12 * 18",
            "Answer": 2819,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 7 * 1 + 8 + 7 * 14 * 2",
            "Answer": 218,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 15 * 1 + 0 + 3 * 6 * 14",
            "Answer": 342,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 17 * 2 + 9 + 18 * 9 * 4",
            "Answer": 1133,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 1 * 6 + 6 + 18 * 1 * 1",
            "Answer": 90,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 18 * 11 + 3 + 17 * 16 * 3",
            "Answer": 3789,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 9 * 19 + 0 + 1 * 2 * 0",
            "Answer": 1368,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 9 * 8 + 8 + 15 * 1 * 10",
            "Answer": 878,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 10 * 13 + 8 + 7 * 6 * 19",
            "Answer": 1716,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 8 * 2 + 2 + 18 * 19 * 18",
            "Answer": 6398,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 17 * 10 + 7 + 18 * 8 * 14",
            "Answer": 4233,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 19 * 0 + 18 + 13 * 3 * 7",
            "Answer": 291,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 4 * 19 + 7 + 9 * 8 * 9",
            "Answer": 1871,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 11 * 1 + 12 + 18 * 4 * 4",
            "Answer": 399,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 5 * 14 + 12 + 12 * 0 * 7",
            "Answer": 502,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 2 * 9 + 18 + 11 * 16 * 18",
            "Answer": 3312,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 10 * 2 + 9 + 8 * 11 * 18",
            "Answer": 1973,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 12 * 13 + 3 + 15 * 5 * 4",
            "Answer": 303,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 7 * 14 + 2 + 16 * 13 * 11",
            "Answer": 2976,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 3 * 0 + 7 + 14 * 17 * 8",
            "Answer": 1911,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 0 * 2 + 7 + 16 * 14 * 14",
            "Answer": 3143,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 16 * 9 + 0 + 11 * 3 * 15",
            "Answer": 927,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 17 * 12 + 0 + 0 * 11 * 11",
            "Answer": 2448,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 16 * 14 + 13 + 0 * 13 * 7",
            "Answer": 2925,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 4 * 19 + 18 + 14 * 15 * 0",
            "Answer": 322,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 6 * 7 + 10 + 11 * 10 * 8",
            "Answer": 1100,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 17 * 19 + 4 + 19 * 3 * 19",
            "Answer": 1087,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 18 * 6 + 4 + 15 * 18 * 15",
            "Answer": 5782,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 10 * 8 + 4 + 15 * 0 * 17",
            "Answer": 724,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 10 * 1 + 18 + 4 * 4 * 16",
            "Answer": 374,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 18 * 11 + 6 + 1 * 3 * 17",
            "Answer": 3027,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 3 * 13 + 11 + 8 * 5 * 16",
            "Answer": 963,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 19 * 0 + 3 + 13 * 15 * 17",
            "Answer": 3318,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 9 * 2 + 5 + 11 * 9 * 0",
            "Answer": 185,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 5 * 10 + 6 + 5 * 1 * 3",
            "Answer": 371,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 15 * 15 + 4 + 6 * 13 * 14",
            "Answer": 2896,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 18 * 0 + 9 + 3 * 11 * 17",
            "Answer": 570,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 4 * 7 + 19 + 10 * 6 * 2",
            "Answer": 223,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 12 * 19 + 18 + 16 * 15 * 18",
            "Answer": 7986,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 0 * 19 + 13 + 9 * 1 * 8",
            "Answer": 85,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 17 * 12 + 3 + 7 * 3 * 9",
            "Answer": 2844,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 7 * 16 + 10 + 18 * 14 * 17",
            "Answer": 6310,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 8 * 12 + 5 + 8 * 8 * 6",
            "Answer": 1637,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 14 * 16 + 16 + 3 * 19 * 8",
            "Answer": 3160,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 8 * 6 + 5 + 3 * 6 * 12",
            "Answer": 749,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 13 * 12 + 3 + 1 * 6 * 17",
            "Answer": 729,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 18 * 13 + 12 + 10 * 1 * 8",
            "Answer": 2198,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 4 * 11 + 14 + 9 * 4 * 14",
            "Answer": 1266,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 3 * 3 + 0 + 6 * 2 * 2",
            "Answer": 87,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 16 * 12 + 13 + 15 * 1 * 2",
            "Answer": 2731,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 17 * 17 + 7 + 9 * 12 * 8",
            "Answer": 5784,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 6 * 15 + 13 + 5 * 5 * 15",
            "Answer": 1018,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 6 * 16 + 1 + 0 * 3 * 13",
            "Answer": 1729,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 11 * 0 + 8 + 17 * 6 * 18",
            "Answer": 1844,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 7 * 6 + 18 + 16 * 13 * 4",
            "Answer": 1228,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 0 * 2 + 15 + 17 * 9 * 18",
            "Answer": 2769,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 15 * 4 + 14 + 11 * 5 * 7",
            "Answer": 519,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 0 * 6 + 14 + 7 * 0 * 3",
            "Answer": 14,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 2 * 19 + 9 + 19 * 19 * 15",
            "Answer": 5880,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 6 * 3 + 18 + 1 * 17 * 7",
            "Answer": 227,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 14 * 8 + 6 + 7 * 15 * 4",
            "Answer": 762,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 14 * 17 + 17 + 14 * 0 * 2",
            "Answer": 2635,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 11 * 0 + 7 + 16 * 18 * 13",
            "Answer": 3751,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 10 * 5 + 19 + 1 * 19 * 4",
            "Answer": 795,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 10 * 6 + 19 + 15 * 2 * 8",
            "Answer": 1159,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 19 * 9 + 0 + 14 * 12 * 0",
            "Answer": 2907,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 4 * 4 + 11 + 9 * 17 * 5",
            "Answer": 984,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 17 * 1 + 12 + 12 * 9 * 8",
            "Answer": 1046,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 12 * 10 + 13 + 7 * 10 * 7",
            "Answer": 1343,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 17 * 15 + 16 + 16 * 19 * 2",
            "Answer": 4959,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 9 * 0 + 16 + 9 * 17 * 5",
            "Answer": 781,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 9 * 8 + 15 + 2 * 8 * 18",
            "Answer": 951,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 16 * 17 + 10 + 3 * 18 * 4",
            "Answer": 2130,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 4 * 10 + 9 + 6 * 17 * 16",
            "Answer": 2121,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 3 * 11 + 9 + 6 * 17 * 17",
            "Answer": 2304,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 9 * 8 + 14 + 3 * 18 * 4",
            "Answer": 878,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 18 * 2 + 7 + 6 * 19 * 12",
            "Answer": 1519,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 7 * 9 + 14 + 17 * 12 * 7",
            "Answer": 2135,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 11 * 8 + 6 + 3 * 5 * 8",
            "Answer": 830,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 1 * 10 + 18 + 5 * 18 * 16",
            "Answer": 1518,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 11 * 16 + 8 + 17 * 12 * 5",
            "Answer": 2260,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 12 * 13 + 15 + 9 * 0 * 7",
            "Answer": 1887,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 17 * 15 + 11 + 1 * 9 * 8",
            "Answer": 4418,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 10 * 0 + 0 + 16 * 9 * 13",
            "Answer": 1872,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 13 * 14 + 0 + 11 * 3 * 18",
            "Answer": 1504,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 13 * 6 + 0 + 9 * 9 * 15",
            "Answer": 2229,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 9 * 11 + 12 + 18 * 13 * 2",
            "Answer": 2262,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 2 * 1 + 9 + 8 * 1 * 3",
            "Answer": 47,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # * #"
        }
    ],
    "# * # + # + # + # * # * #": [
        {
            "Question": "6 * 7 + 9 + 9 + 1 * 18 * 4",
            "Answer": 132,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 4 + 7 + 16 + 3 * 6 * 0",
            "Answer": 99,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 2 + 18 + 13 + 5 * 13 * 9",
            "Answer": 616,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 14 + 13 + 16 + 2 * 16 * 5",
            "Answer": 371,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 12 + 6 + 12 + 19 * 9 * 15",
            "Answer": 2751,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 13 + 6 + 2 + 6 * 12 * 9",
            "Answer": 682,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 8 + 2 + 1 + 2 * 12 * 1",
            "Answer": 155,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 19 + 4 + 5 + 14 * 10 * 5",
            "Answer": 747,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 3 + 16 + 15 + 12 * 0 * 1",
            "Answer": 55,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 3 + 19 + 11 + 8 * 3 * 4",
            "Answer": 153,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 0 + 0 + 4 + 2 * 14 * 17",
            "Answer": 480,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 19 + 7 + 1 + 11 * 7 * 12",
            "Answer": 951,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 17 + 12 + 8 + 14 * 3 * 15",
            "Answer": 718,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 10 + 18 + 7 + 3 * 15 * 14",
            "Answer": 835,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 11 + 9 + 15 + 16 * 8 * 14",
            "Answer": 1816,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 14 + 18 + 17 + 12 * 6 * 16",
            "Answer": 1215,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 11 + 19 + 9 + 4 * 1 * 14",
            "Answer": 106,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 13 + 0 + 11 + 0 * 12 * 15",
            "Answer": 154,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 18 + 14 + 5 + 0 * 9 * 2",
            "Answer": 325,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 3 + 6 + 15 + 5 * 4 * 8",
            "Answer": 205,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 16 + 12 + 17 + 8 * 17 * 2",
            "Answer": 429,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 3 + 5 + 19 + 12 * 12 * 2",
            "Answer": 351,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 3 + 4 + 12 + 14 * 4 * 8",
            "Answer": 485,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 8 + 15 + 16 + 10 * 1 * 13",
            "Answer": 313,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 4 + 1 + 12 + 12 * 5 * 17",
            "Answer": 1065,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 3 + 5 + 16 + 9 * 12 * 19",
            "Answer": 2130,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 16 + 17 + 15 + 13 * 0 * 3",
            "Answer": 208,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 18 + 12 + 8 + 11 * 7 * 1",
            "Answer": 349,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 9 + 4 + 7 + 3 * 5 * 10",
            "Answer": 179,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 12 + 17 + 16 + 5 * 15 * 16",
            "Answer": 1233,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 17 + 19 + 1 + 7 * 18 * 4",
            "Answer": 762,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 9 + 10 + 17 + 2 * 18 * 19",
            "Answer": 855,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 17 + 1 + 11 + 4 * 10 * 6",
            "Answer": 541,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 7 + 7 + 7 + 14 * 4 * 0",
            "Answer": 126,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 19 + 7 + 0 + 19 * 5 * 3",
            "Answer": 653,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 2 + 11 + 4 + 16 * 13 * 18",
            "Answer": 3789,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 2 + 4 + 5 + 6 * 16 * 3",
            "Answer": 307,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 11 + 16 + 3 + 9 * 3 * 16",
            "Answer": 616,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 6 + 3 + 12 + 15 * 10 * 14",
            "Answer": 2199,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 11 + 0 + 4 + 18 * 6 * 16",
            "Answer": 1820,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 7 + 2 + 14 + 13 * 4 * 19",
            "Answer": 1025,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 13 + 4 + 19 + 13 * 5 * 19",
            "Answer": 1362,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 8 + 0 + 1 + 6 * 11 * 12",
            "Answer": 857,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 4 + 4 + 0 + 18 * 18 * 13",
            "Answer": 4220,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 11 + 2 + 3 + 9 * 16 * 1",
            "Answer": 237,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 12 + 4 + 8 + 12 * 9 * 5",
            "Answer": 696,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 0 + 5 + 0 + 1 * 17 * 10",
            "Answer": 175,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 12 + 14 + 5 + 6 * 6 * 17",
            "Answer": 667,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 6 + 19 + 15 + 14 * 1 * 0",
            "Answer": 106,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 0 + 4 + 12 + 2 * 17 * 10",
            "Answer": 356,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 3 + 13 + 6 + 14 * 8 * 10",
            "Answer": 1172,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 4 + 6 + 5 + 8 * 13 * 12",
            "Answer": 1331,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 12 + 18 + 6 + 9 * 4 * 12",
            "Answer": 636,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 15 + 10 + 7 + 4 * 6 * 13",
            "Answer": 509,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 15 + 9 + 2 + 16 * 16 * 0",
            "Answer": 221,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 4 + 2 + 19 + 5 * 17 * 19",
            "Answer": 1648,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 14 + 13 + 15 + 6 * 13 * 2",
            "Answer": 324,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 12 + 14 + 19 + 19 * 19 * 14",
            "Answer": 5171,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 10 + 15 + 4 + 10 * 15 * 18",
            "Answer": 2839,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 11 + 15 + 6 + 10 * 10 * 1",
            "Answer": 253,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 6 + 12 + 0 + 10 * 14 * 17",
            "Answer": 2404,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 18 + 2 + 0 + 2 * 8 * 19",
            "Answer": 504,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 2 + 11 + 9 + 6 * 6 * 12",
            "Answer": 488,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 11 + 1 + 1 + 17 * 16 * 17",
            "Answer": 4813,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 1 + 17 + 16 + 17 * 0 * 7",
            "Answer": 45,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 14 + 3 + 3 + 12 * 11 * 5",
            "Answer": 932,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 17 + 13 + 13 + 12 * 7 * 12",
            "Answer": 1340,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 4 + 3 + 0 + 2 * 2 * 17",
            "Answer": 147,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 1 + 4 + 3 + 1 * 3 * 6",
            "Answer": 44,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 10 + 5 + 0 + 18 * 11 * 1",
            "Answer": 253,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 7 + 7 + 3 + 9 * 4 * 19",
            "Answer": 799,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 14 + 5 + 3 + 8 * 7 * 19",
            "Answer": 1086,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 12 + 3 + 17 + 0 * 11 * 17",
            "Answer": 32,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 7 + 10 + 0 + 13 * 14 * 10",
            "Answer": 1942,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 14 + 13 + 17 + 5 * 1 * 2",
            "Answer": 236,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 10 + 2 + 4 + 17 * 2 * 1",
            "Answer": 130,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 13 + 18 + 18 + 1 * 15 * 4",
            "Answer": 187,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 2 + 1 + 15 + 19 * 4 * 3",
            "Answer": 252,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 0 + 4 + 7 + 0 * 11 * 8",
            "Answer": 11,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 8 + 7 + 10 + 12 * 1 * 5",
            "Answer": 85,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 13 + 18 + 18 + 10 * 17 * 5",
            "Answer": 1016,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 11 + 14 + 19 + 15 * 3 * 15",
            "Answer": 774,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 15 + 5 + 14 + 1 * 10 * 13",
            "Answer": 344,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 8 + 11 + 2 + 12 * 19 * 3",
            "Answer": 761,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 14 + 11 + 17 + 7 * 12 * 14",
            "Answer": 1428,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 0 + 1 + 12 + 14 * 15 * 1",
            "Answer": 223,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 9 + 5 + 10 + 9 * 15 * 14",
            "Answer": 1986,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 3 + 15 + 8 + 13 * 17 * 2",
            "Answer": 480,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 10 + 12 + 15 + 17 * 14 * 5",
            "Answer": 1247,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 6 + 18 + 5 + 10 * 18 * 4",
            "Answer": 743,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 17 + 14 + 12 + 15 * 12 * 5",
            "Answer": 977,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 15 + 0 + 5 + 15 * 7 * 14",
            "Answer": 1490,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 0 + 7 + 15 + 10 * 2 * 8",
            "Answer": 182,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 13 + 9 + 19 + 16 * 14 * 7",
            "Answer": 1700,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 6 + 19 + 1 + 5 * 4 * 9",
            "Answer": 296,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 11 + 4 + 3 + 3 * 10 * 16",
            "Answer": 564,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 11 + 2 + 19 + 5 * 1 * 10",
            "Answer": 137,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 14 + 18 + 15 + 4 * 16 * 5",
            "Answer": 381,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 7 + 0 + 10 + 17 * 14 * 19",
            "Answer": 4567,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 8 + 18 + 10 + 16 * 10 * 13",
            "Answer": 2180,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # * # * #"
        }
    ],
    "# + # + # + # + # + # + #": [
        {
            "Question": "14 + 17 + 14 + 16 + 3 + 10 + 0",
            "Answer": 74,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 15 + 18 + 19 + 6 + 1 + 1",
            "Answer": 67,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 12 + 3 + 6 + 16 + 14 + 15",
            "Answer": 84,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 14 + 15 + 13 + 10 + 13 + 15",
            "Answer": 85,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 12 + 7 + 9 + 9 + 15 + 1",
            "Answer": 68,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 19 + 2 + 15 + 11 + 1 + 2",
            "Answer": 59,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 0 + 6 + 11 + 13 + 8 + 5",
            "Answer": 52,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 4 + 2 + 9 + 15 + 6 + 8",
            "Answer": 55,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 6 + 15 + 9 + 19 + 18 + 19",
            "Answer": 92,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 0 + 9 + 12 + 17 + 17 + 18",
            "Answer": 85,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 9 + 15 + 2 + 4 + 2 + 17",
            "Answer": 67,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 2 + 18 + 6 + 6 + 6 + 7",
            "Answer": 52,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 9 + 11 + 4 + 5 + 0 + 7",
            "Answer": 42,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 18 + 7 + 17 + 19 + 2 + 16",
            "Answer": 84,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 16 + 3 + 3 + 14 + 3 + 19",
            "Answer": 77,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 4 + 4 + 15 + 12 + 15 + 17",
            "Answer": 85,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 4 + 5 + 13 + 5 + 16 + 3",
            "Answer": 58,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 16 + 18 + 0 + 5 + 16 + 18",
            "Answer": 80,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 11 + 10 + 13 + 13 + 14 + 14",
            "Answer": 85,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 11 + 15 + 18 + 4 + 18 + 0",
            "Answer": 79,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 19 + 10 + 1 + 11 + 17 + 8",
            "Answer": 81,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 0 + 6 + 9 + 2 + 7 + 4",
            "Answer": 36,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 17 + 10 + 18 + 4 + 0 + 7",
            "Answer": 57,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 13 + 18 + 0 + 7 + 14 + 8",
            "Answer": 77,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 3 + 11 + 7 + 3 + 8 + 12",
            "Answer": 61,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 14 + 19 + 8 + 18 + 10 + 14",
            "Answer": 97,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 19 + 0 + 10 + 12 + 16 + 9",
            "Answer": 78,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 10 + 6 + 8 + 17 + 19 + 7",
            "Answer": 79,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 11 + 19 + 0 + 8 + 17 + 16",
            "Answer": 89,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 2 + 3 + 4 + 9 + 14 + 18",
            "Answer": 60,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 10 + 3 + 9 + 18 + 0 + 14",
            "Answer": 66,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 4 + 19 + 0 + 10 + 3 + 4",
            "Answer": 42,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 5 + 15 + 0 + 9 + 17 + 10",
            "Answer": 71,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 5 + 6 + 0 + 13 + 9 + 0",
            "Answer": 46,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 12 + 3 + 8 + 11 + 16 + 0",
            "Answer": 52,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 16 + 9 + 2 + 16 + 7 + 17",
            "Answer": 81,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 4 + 16 + 10 + 12 + 18 + 1",
            "Answer": 72,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 15 + 11 + 5 + 16 + 15 + 6",
            "Answer": 85,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 12 + 4 + 10 + 0 + 17 + 13",
            "Answer": 56,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 11 + 9 + 14 + 3 + 4 + 10",
            "Answer": 61,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 19 + 19 + 14 + 8 + 10 + 9",
            "Answer": 93,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 6 + 18 + 9 + 7 + 15 + 0",
            "Answer": 62,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 16 + 6 + 13 + 13 + 12 + 6",
            "Answer": 78,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 3 + 5 + 10 + 4 + 17 + 19",
            "Answer": 74,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 13 + 14 + 4 + 10 + 14 + 15",
            "Answer": 76,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 11 + 12 + 12 + 11 + 18 + 11",
            "Answer": 84,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 7 + 5 + 14 + 4 + 15 + 16",
            "Answer": 65,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 3 + 4 + 4 + 0 + 4 + 5",
            "Answer": 39,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 14 + 8 + 18 + 2 + 7 + 0",
            "Answer": 62,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 10 + 14 + 4 + 19 + 6 + 16",
            "Answer": 70,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 13 + 19 + 4 + 0 + 6 + 5",
            "Answer": 57,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 11 + 13 + 0 + 3 + 7 + 9",
            "Answer": 51,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 8 + 11 + 6 + 18 + 15 + 5",
            "Answer": 79,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 11 + 14 + 3 + 13 + 19 + 9",
            "Answer": 87,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 15 + 9 + 16 + 9 + 14 + 6",
            "Answer": 83,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 17 + 2 + 15 + 12 + 18 + 19",
            "Answer": 95,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 6 + 18 + 18 + 12 + 10 + 19",
            "Answer": 88,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 19 + 12 + 5 + 15 + 7 + 17",
            "Answer": 80,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 1 + 1 + 12 + 15 + 4 + 8",
            "Answer": 46,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 12 + 1 + 4 + 1 + 14 + 17",
            "Answer": 52,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 4 + 5 + 5 + 9 + 11 + 9",
            "Answer": 50,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 6 + 18 + 3 + 10 + 18 + 16",
            "Answer": 71,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 4 + 12 + 8 + 12 + 2 + 6",
            "Answer": 54,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 7 + 15 + 2 + 12 + 2 + 10",
            "Answer": 60,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 19 + 16 + 15 + 16 + 6 + 15",
            "Answer": 97,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 3 + 10 + 1 + 11 + 19 + 6",
            "Answer": 62,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 17 + 5 + 8 + 1 + 5 + 3",
            "Answer": 52,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 4 + 11 + 1 + 10 + 13 + 12",
            "Answer": 58,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 7 + 11 + 19 + 5 + 15 + 2",
            "Answer": 61,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 19 + 13 + 18 + 14 + 7 + 3",
            "Answer": 92,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 7 + 4 + 5 + 10 + 12 + 2",
            "Answer": 41,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 18 + 14 + 11 + 10 + 19 + 9",
            "Answer": 86,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 14 + 2 + 6 + 1 + 17 + 5",
            "Answer": 63,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 5 + 14 + 18 + 12 + 13 + 19",
            "Answer": 89,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 13 + 19 + 8 + 15 + 10 + 10",
            "Answer": 91,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 14 + 15 + 11 + 15 + 0 + 13",
            "Answer": 84,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 11 + 14 + 1 + 11 + 6 + 0",
            "Answer": 47,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 7 + 12 + 17 + 13 + 18 + 14",
            "Answer": 86,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 9 + 14 + 2 + 13 + 1 + 11",
            "Answer": 58,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 16 + 14 + 1 + 10 + 1 + 1",
            "Answer": 57,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 16 + 10 + 5 + 16 + 13 + 15",
            "Answer": 90,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 9 + 12 + 6 + 6 + 18 + 7",
            "Answer": 68,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 4 + 4 + 16 + 7 + 3 + 12",
            "Answer": 47,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 5 + 17 + 6 + 10 + 0 + 7",
            "Answer": 46,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 17 + 0 + 0 + 1 + 5 + 2",
            "Answer": 34,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 15 + 9 + 17 + 5 + 15 + 4",
            "Answer": 76,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 15 + 2 + 2 + 18 + 4 + 3",
            "Answer": 54,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 11 + 8 + 16 + 11 + 7 + 1",
            "Answer": 70,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 2 + 14 + 11 + 10 + 2 + 11",
            "Answer": 61,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 14 + 14 + 1 + 1 + 11 + 18",
            "Answer": 76,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 2 + 15 + 7 + 2 + 0 + 4",
            "Answer": 43,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 1 + 16 + 19 + 0 + 16 + 13",
            "Answer": 70,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 6 + 15 + 13 + 13 + 8 + 15",
            "Answer": 85,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 16 + 0 + 14 + 10 + 11 + 9",
            "Answer": 72,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 3 + 16 + 8 + 14 + 10 + 2",
            "Answer": 65,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 2 + 10 + 3 + 15 + 16 + 7",
            "Answer": 70,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 1 + 16 + 9 + 12 + 1 + 9",
            "Answer": 48,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 12 + 13 + 11 + 7 + 2 + 16",
            "Answer": 72,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 9 + 0 + 10 + 18 + 0 + 1",
            "Answer": 54,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 10 + 14 + 5 + 16 + 12 + 1",
            "Answer": 69,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # + #"
        }
    ],
    "# + # * # * # + # + # * #": [
        {
            "Question": "7 + 17 * 2 * 8 + 3 + 14 * 4",
            "Answer": 338,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 15 * 4 * 13 + 2 + 19 * 17",
            "Answer": 1112,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 12 * 2 * 13 + 19 + 5 * 19",
            "Answer": 439,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 4 * 8 * 12 + 9 + 14 * 4",
            "Answer": 465,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 12 * 8 * 10 + 19 + 16 * 0",
            "Answer": 980,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 17 * 7 * 11 + 15 + 2 * 4",
            "Answer": 1336,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 13 * 13 * 19 + 12 + 3 * 5",
            "Answer": 3257,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 14 * 0 * 13 + 10 + 14 * 6",
            "Answer": 107,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 9 * 15 * 19 + 11 + 13 * 14",
            "Answer": 2760,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 17 * 4 * 4 + 3 + 8 * 0",
            "Answer": 289,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 14 * 4 * 7 + 4 + 7 * 0",
            "Answer": 415,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 1 * 13 * 11 + 3 + 11 * 3",
            "Answer": 188,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 18 * 10 * 1 + 5 + 18 * 6",
            "Answer": 311,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 16 * 14 * 14 + 10 + 6 * 10",
            "Answer": 3213,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 16 * 10 * 19 + 8 + 19 * 5",
            "Answer": 3155,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 0 * 2 * 9 + 5 + 17 * 4",
            "Answer": 85,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 14 * 10 * 10 + 16 + 6 * 16",
            "Answer": 1513,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 14 * 0 * 8 + 3 + 2 * 18",
            "Answer": 49,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 9 * 1 * 5 + 18 + 16 * 0",
            "Answer": 82,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 7 * 13 * 12 + 9 + 5 * 9",
            "Answer": 1152,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 1 * 17 * 13 + 6 + 0 * 4",
            "Answer": 242,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 9 * 16 * 0 + 3 + 4 * 3",
            "Answer": 32,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 15 * 2 * 9 + 18 + 3 * 7",
            "Answer": 324,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 8 * 5 * 19 + 12 + 5 * 18",
            "Answer": 874,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 7 * 9 * 7 + 5 + 5 * 4",
            "Answer": 466,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 12 * 17 * 17 + 7 + 4 * 1",
            "Answer": 3491,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 15 * 17 * 7 + 13 + 3 * 1",
            "Answer": 1818,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 3 * 8 * 17 + 3 + 16 * 8",
            "Answer": 542,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 14 * 10 * 6 + 1 + 3 * 8",
            "Answer": 878,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 19 * 14 * 7 + 7 + 6 * 6",
            "Answer": 1924,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 8 * 9 * 6 + 12 + 15 * 19",
            "Answer": 731,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 16 * 16 * 6 + 6 + 18 * 19",
            "Answer": 1893,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 14 * 18 * 18 + 12 + 1 * 2",
            "Answer": 4568,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 17 * 15 * 7 + 3 + 12 * 18",
            "Answer": 2006,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 11 * 15 * 15 + 5 + 2 * 14",
            "Answer": 2512,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 19 * 5 * 15 + 12 + 8 * 8",
            "Answer": 1502,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 6 * 17 * 12 + 9 + 5 * 10",
            "Answer": 1283,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 14 * 6 * 19 + 0 + 8 * 1",
            "Answer": 1619,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 16 * 9 * 4 + 0 + 17 * 17",
            "Answer": 872,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 17 * 11 * 3 + 18 + 7 * 19",
            "Answer": 725,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 7 * 5 * 3 + 8 + 5 * 15",
            "Answer": 194,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 0 * 13 * 3 + 1 + 11 * 9",
            "Answer": 118,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 5 * 9 * 4 + 18 + 16 * 16",
            "Answer": 472,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 16 * 2 * 2 + 16 + 3 * 15",
            "Answer": 134,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 15 * 16 * 1 + 4 + 19 * 8",
            "Answer": 415,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 9 * 5 * 17 + 5 + 16 * 2",
            "Answer": 818,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 13 * 18 * 3 + 8 + 13 * 4",
            "Answer": 773,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 10 * 8 * 5 + 12 + 19 * 3",
            "Answer": 479,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 8 * 3 * 2 + 3 + 6 * 2",
            "Answer": 65,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 5 * 9 * 17 + 5 + 15 * 14",
            "Answer": 982,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 19 * 17 * 3 + 1 + 6 * 0",
            "Answer": 971,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 14 * 2 * 19 + 1 + 12 * 2",
            "Answer": 562,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 0 * 18 * 12 + 17 + 7 * 8",
            "Answer": 80,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 0 * 15 * 14 + 3 + 12 * 1",
            "Answer": 28,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 9 * 8 * 7 + 1 + 19 * 14",
            "Answer": 790,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 2 * 11 * 8 + 11 + 19 * 17",
            "Answer": 516,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 7 * 7 * 14 + 0 + 3 * 17",
            "Answer": 746,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 5 * 3 * 14 + 7 + 10 * 6",
            "Answer": 278,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 18 * 7 * 16 + 13 + 2 * 17",
            "Answer": 2072,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 9 * 7 * 13 + 14 + 4 * 17",
            "Answer": 902,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 2 * 18 * 13 + 9 + 13 * 6",
            "Answer": 559,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 3 * 11 * 10 + 19 + 10 * 9",
            "Answer": 456,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 16 * 19 * 9 + 4 + 10 * 17",
            "Answer": 2910,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 16 * 0 * 4 + 11 + 3 * 7",
            "Answer": 40,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 1 * 14 * 6 + 15 + 18 * 2",
            "Answer": 136,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 11 * 15 * 10 + 9 + 6 * 7",
            "Answer": 1713,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 13 * 13 * 10 + 1 + 6 * 11",
            "Answer": 1768,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 5 * 3 * 7 + 0 + 8 * 7",
            "Answer": 174,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 11 * 19 * 1 + 19 + 16 * 8",
            "Answer": 364,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 16 * 13 * 3 + 16 + 13 * 1",
            "Answer": 661,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 17 * 2 * 15 + 17 + 16 * 7",
            "Answer": 652,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 15 * 11 * 0 + 1 + 16 * 18",
            "Answer": 299,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 2 * 19 * 11 + 0 + 12 * 14",
            "Answer": 596,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 17 * 4 * 4 + 4 + 6 * 10",
            "Answer": 338,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 2 * 2 * 11 + 14 + 7 * 18",
            "Answer": 184,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 10 * 19 * 6 + 19 + 7 * 12",
            "Answer": 1245,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 17 * 4 * 9 + 5 + 10 * 14",
            "Answer": 768,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 2 * 7 * 6 + 19 + 17 * 14",
            "Answer": 350,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 4 * 17 * 6 + 12 + 19 * 14",
            "Answer": 701,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 16 * 12 * 19 + 3 + 8 * 10",
            "Answer": 3742,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 2 * 8 * 10 + 3 + 6 * 19",
            "Answer": 286,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 13 * 17 * 9 + 11 + 19 * 18",
            "Answer": 2355,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 1 * 10 * 3 + 7 + 15 * 6",
            "Answer": 138,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 10 * 12 * 16 + 5 + 8 * 19",
            "Answer": 2078,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 1 * 8 * 19 + 3 + 19 * 0",
            "Answer": 162,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 3 * 11 * 19 + 15 + 19 * 18",
            "Answer": 990,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 5 * 18 * 19 + 19 + 14 * 10",
            "Answer": 1874,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 15 * 4 * 5 + 17 + 15 * 16",
            "Answer": 559,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 19 * 17 * 7 + 7 + 12 * 19",
            "Answer": 2507,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 4 * 17 * 8 + 3 + 8 * 19",
            "Answer": 699,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 4 * 6 * 17 + 19 + 9 * 18",
            "Answer": 594,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 10 * 9 * 18 + 3 + 4 * 2",
            "Answer": 1638,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 6 * 13 * 9 + 14 + 18 * 12",
            "Answer": 947,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 15 * 5 * 8 + 4 + 3 * 5",
            "Answer": 625,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 7 * 4 * 11 + 4 + 12 * 10",
            "Answer": 440,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 3 * 11 * 15 + 10 + 17 * 8",
            "Answer": 648,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 16 * 6 * 1 + 17 + 9 * 6",
            "Answer": 179,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 11 * 3 * 15 + 18 + 3 * 3",
            "Answer": 525,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 3 * 2 * 1 + 5 + 18 * 15",
            "Answer": 297,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 13 * 4 * 17 + 12 + 5 * 3",
            "Answer": 912,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # * #"
        }
    ],
    "# + # * # + # * # + # * #": [
        {
            "Question": "18 + 6 * 11 + 8 * 7 + 5 * 0",
            "Answer": 140,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 6 * 16 + 0 * 11 + 16 * 10",
            "Answer": 269,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 3 * 16 + 7 * 16 + 8 * 11",
            "Answer": 255,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 3 * 6 + 3 * 5 + 18 * 12",
            "Answer": 253,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 5 * 15 + 16 * 18 + 11 * 3",
            "Answer": 412,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 3 * 19 + 16 * 16 + 6 * 13",
            "Answer": 406,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 8 * 13 + 0 * 7 + 9 * 18",
            "Answer": 270,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 16 * 8 + 1 * 9 + 12 * 8",
            "Answer": 250,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 19 * 18 + 18 * 15 + 17 * 12",
            "Answer": 827,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 0 * 7 + 18 * 9 + 7 * 3",
            "Answer": 191,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 15 * 3 + 18 * 11 + 7 * 15",
            "Answer": 356,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 2 * 13 + 19 * 4 + 12 * 15",
            "Answer": 297,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 10 * 8 + 17 * 0 + 11 * 18",
            "Answer": 293,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 1 * 13 + 7 * 4 + 7 * 16",
            "Answer": 158,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 12 * 12 + 7 * 0 + 16 * 7",
            "Answer": 260,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 15 * 19 + 14 * 6 + 14 * 0",
            "Answer": 381,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 13 * 3 + 9 * 8 + 4 * 12",
            "Answer": 171,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 14 * 15 + 4 * 4 + 0 * 13",
            "Answer": 240,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 0 * 15 + 11 * 2 + 1 * 17",
            "Answer": 40,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 2 * 9 + 19 * 1 + 3 * 3",
            "Answer": 51,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 12 * 16 + 6 * 3 + 8 * 1",
            "Answer": 224,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 19 * 10 + 3 * 11 + 8 * 15",
            "Answer": 348,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 2 * 3 + 18 * 11 + 17 * 15",
            "Answer": 467,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 12 * 1 + 3 * 16 + 7 * 19",
            "Answer": 210,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 14 * 12 + 11 * 12 + 15 * 18",
            "Answer": 589,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 8 * 7 + 15 * 10 + 12 * 17",
            "Answer": 429,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 7 * 3 + 19 * 4 + 1 * 9",
            "Answer": 124,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 11 * 14 + 0 * 1 + 13 * 14",
            "Answer": 344,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 9 * 9 + 15 * 16 + 4 * 8",
            "Answer": 363,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 18 * 17 + 6 * 15 + 14 * 16",
            "Answer": 630,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 18 * 0 + 13 * 17 + 9 * 8",
            "Answer": 306,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 19 * 4 + 8 * 6 + 1 * 16",
            "Answer": 150,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 19 * 18 + 6 * 7 + 9 * 5",
            "Answer": 430,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 12 * 3 + 16 * 0 + 15 * 14",
            "Answer": 258,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 0 * 17 + 11 * 15 + 16 * 1",
            "Answer": 186,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 10 * 16 + 10 * 1 + 9 * 18",
            "Answer": 332,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 12 * 7 + 12 * 0 + 19 * 15",
            "Answer": 370,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 17 * 15 + 4 * 17 + 1 * 10",
            "Answer": 350,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 6 * 19 + 19 * 15 + 12 * 8",
            "Answer": 510,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 1 * 14 + 18 * 17 + 13 * 18",
            "Answer": 565,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 14 * 2 + 16 * 2 + 12 * 13",
            "Answer": 223,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 9 * 3 + 16 * 1 + 8 * 2",
            "Answer": 75,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 8 * 1 + 16 * 19 + 15 * 10",
            "Answer": 468,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 11 * 1 + 2 * 3 + 7 * 17",
            "Answer": 146,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 0 * 1 + 6 * 19 + 17 * 4",
            "Answer": 198,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 13 * 2 + 17 * 13 + 8 * 4",
            "Answer": 283,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 2 * 10 + 6 * 0 + 4 * 0",
            "Answer": 32,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 2 * 11 + 16 * 0 + 12 * 6",
            "Answer": 113,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 1 * 3 + 5 * 17 + 2 * 5",
            "Answer": 110,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 10 * 0 + 16 * 17 + 10 * 4",
            "Answer": 328,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 16 * 2 + 18 * 9 + 10 * 6",
            "Answer": 268,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 2 * 12 + 7 * 4 + 19 * 16",
            "Answer": 366,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 14 * 4 + 17 * 1 + 0 * 9",
            "Answer": 84,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 15 * 17 + 19 * 11 + 1 * 19",
            "Answer": 486,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 12 * 3 + 0 * 0 + 0 * 8",
            "Answer": 47,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 17 * 15 + 4 * 3 + 9 * 13",
            "Answer": 396,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 17 * 1 + 17 * 9 + 15 * 3",
            "Answer": 231,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 7 * 19 + 7 * 16 + 11 * 13",
            "Answer": 394,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 5 * 5 + 17 * 19 + 18 * 3",
            "Answer": 413,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 12 * 6 + 11 * 18 + 16 * 8",
            "Answer": 405,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 5 * 11 + 4 * 16 + 14 * 12",
            "Answer": 294,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 17 * 7 + 2 * 8 + 10 * 5",
            "Answer": 186,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 8 * 5 + 10 * 18 + 11 * 8",
            "Answer": 322,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 0 * 2 + 3 * 2 + 10 * 4",
            "Answer": 64,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 12 * 19 + 1 * 3 + 10 * 8",
            "Answer": 322,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 10 * 10 + 7 * 11 + 13 * 1",
            "Answer": 191,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 1 * 12 + 3 * 10 + 6 * 1",
            "Answer": 52,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 15 * 14 + 6 * 4 + 1 * 19",
            "Answer": 266,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 11 * 17 + 10 * 14 + 12 * 0",
            "Answer": 336,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 11 * 8 + 8 * 3 + 10 * 0",
            "Answer": 120,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 15 * 14 + 9 * 8 + 9 * 0",
            "Answer": 295,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 15 * 8 + 1 * 2 + 3 * 1",
            "Answer": 132,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 17 * 8 + 3 * 17 + 4 * 16",
            "Answer": 260,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 10 * 19 + 10 * 6 + 15 * 2",
            "Answer": 284,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 4 * 14 + 18 * 9 + 10 * 7",
            "Answer": 302,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 13 * 2 + 14 * 17 + 19 * 19",
            "Answer": 635,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 5 * 13 + 16 * 15 + 15 * 6",
            "Answer": 403,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 7 * 9 + 4 * 3 + 5 * 12",
            "Answer": 135,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 6 * 6 + 9 * 7 + 5 * 11",
            "Answer": 161,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 10 * 8 + 6 * 15 + 2 * 8",
            "Answer": 188,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 8 * 10 + 7 * 7 + 11 * 14",
            "Answer": 298,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 18 * 18 + 15 * 15 + 18 * 1",
            "Answer": 579,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 18 * 19 + 9 * 14 + 17 * 1",
            "Answer": 501,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 4 * 11 + 6 * 14 + 9 * 17",
            "Answer": 281,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 17 * 1 + 13 * 0 + 15 * 5",
            "Answer": 96,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 15 * 5 + 0 * 5 + 0 * 0",
            "Answer": 80,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 13 * 14 + 10 * 3 + 14 * 7",
            "Answer": 318,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 17 * 15 + 17 * 3 + 9 * 11",
            "Answer": 415,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 5 * 16 + 1 * 13 + 4 * 3",
            "Answer": 117,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 10 * 7 + 14 * 19 + 0 * 3",
            "Answer": 350,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 7 * 14 + 10 * 1 + 14 * 7",
            "Answer": 207,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 7 * 8 + 8 * 7 + 2 * 18",
            "Answer": 158,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 11 * 16 + 18 * 4 + 15 * 13",
            "Answer": 454,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 11 * 18 + 15 * 9 + 2 * 6",
            "Answer": 347,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 17 * 9 + 5 * 12 + 8 * 4",
            "Answer": 253,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 17 * 7 + 7 * 8 + 4 * 5",
            "Answer": 198,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 1 * 10 + 3 * 14 + 17 * 11",
            "Answer": 245,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 18 * 3 + 3 * 17 + 11 * 18",
            "Answer": 314,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 15 * 8 + 13 * 4 + 7 * 10",
            "Answer": 250,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 9 * 11 + 3 * 6 + 15 * 6",
            "Answer": 217,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # * #"
        }
    ],
    "# + # * # * # + # * # * #": [
        {
            "Question": "5 + 3 * 2 * 16 + 18 * 6 * 4",
            "Answer": 533,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 15 * 17 * 11 + 10 * 6 * 6",
            "Answer": 3166,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 1 * 18 * 10 + 8 * 18 * 12",
            "Answer": 1909,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 12 * 17 * 8 + 1 * 0 * 0",
            "Answer": 1634,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 1 * 13 * 13 + 4 * 1 * 16",
            "Answer": 242,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 13 * 15 * 17 + 12 * 12 * 9",
            "Answer": 4628,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 3 * 1 * 3 + 14 * 1 * 10",
            "Answer": 160,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 19 * 19 * 4 + 11 * 12 * 12",
            "Answer": 3031,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 14 * 1 * 13 + 10 * 1 * 6",
            "Answer": 255,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 19 * 5 * 11 + 0 * 15 * 8",
            "Answer": 1053,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 12 * 19 * 13 + 1 * 5 * 9",
            "Answer": 3024,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 18 * 18 * 17 + 4 * 13 * 14",
            "Answer": 6251,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 0 * 10 * 18 + 19 * 9 * 0",
            "Answer": 19,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 4 * 12 * 1 + 1 * 6 * 4",
            "Answer": 75,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 9 * 13 * 18 + 4 * 3 * 11",
            "Answer": 2250,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 0 * 6 * 3 + 10 * 14 * 17",
            "Answer": 2391,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 0 * 7 * 13 + 9 * 11 * 2",
            "Answer": 212,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 12 * 7 * 3 + 17 * 12 * 8",
            "Answer": 1885,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 2 * 5 * 12 + 1 * 2 * 6",
            "Answer": 149,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 9 * 18 * 14 + 19 * 13 * 9",
            "Answer": 4503,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 15 * 14 * 12 + 12 * 15 * 16",
            "Answer": 5418,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 4 * 12 * 2 + 2 * 5 * 7",
            "Answer": 166,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 17 * 16 * 11 + 1 * 12 * 10",
            "Answer": 3112,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 14 * 11 * 17 + 12 * 10 * 7",
            "Answer": 3471,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 0 * 11 * 8 + 8 * 13 * 17",
            "Answer": 1771,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 0 * 2 * 13 + 7 * 14 * 5",
            "Answer": 499,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 7 * 15 * 6 + 8 * 19 * 2",
            "Answer": 938,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 14 * 14 * 0 + 19 * 10 * 13",
            "Answer": 2476,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 16 * 2 * 6 + 8 * 0 * 1",
            "Answer": 196,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 7 * 1 * 7 + 2 * 1 * 11",
            "Answer": 88,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 12 * 18 * 7 + 7 * 5 * 2",
            "Answer": 1591,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 1 * 5 * 7 + 0 * 19 * 5",
            "Answer": 37,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 10 * 4 * 11 + 6 * 5 * 3",
            "Answer": 545,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 8 * 4 * 14 + 5 * 14 * 16",
            "Answer": 1586,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 4 * 6 * 0 + 15 * 8 * 0",
            "Answer": 12,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 12 * 10 * 12 + 9 * 8 * 0",
            "Answer": 1456,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 13 * 5 * 13 + 15 * 14 * 7",
            "Answer": 2329,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 1 * 0 * 6 + 1 * 4 * 19",
            "Answer": 87,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 3 * 14 * 14 + 8 * 0 * 2",
            "Answer": 589,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 14 * 18 * 13 + 18 * 6 * 8",
            "Answer": 4145,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 11 * 16 * 17 + 0 * 13 * 5",
            "Answer": 3010,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 0 * 10 * 0 + 0 * 14 * 6",
            "Answer": 2,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 12 * 0 * 8 + 11 * 4 * 1",
            "Answer": 48,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 16 * 11 * 4 + 2 * 9 * 14",
            "Answer": 970,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 14 * 16 * 15 + 16 * 0 * 14",
            "Answer": 3378,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 5 * 12 * 17 + 15 * 4 * 1",
            "Answer": 1099,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 14 * 9 * 13 + 13 * 16 * 18",
            "Answer": 5385,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 15 * 9 * 11 + 6 * 18 * 4",
            "Answer": 1920,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 12 * 1 * 0 + 6 * 14 * 13",
            "Answer": 1107,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 9 * 6 * 0 + 11 * 8 * 5",
            "Answer": 447,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 6 * 1 * 5 + 0 * 0 * 5",
            "Answer": 44,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 17 * 8 * 12 + 12 * 5 * 16",
            "Answer": 2599,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 5 * 11 * 15 + 3 * 7 * 0",
            "Answer": 834,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 2 * 5 * 0 + 12 * 9 * 18",
            "Answer": 1963,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 19 * 3 * 13 + 15 * 7 * 14",
            "Answer": 2217,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 13 * 11 * 8 + 15 * 18 * 5",
            "Answer": 2496,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 18 * 15 * 9 + 1 * 1 * 15",
            "Answer": 2453,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 9 * 3 * 2 + 11 * 13 * 16",
            "Answer": 2348,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 6 * 3 * 1 + 15 * 3 * 19",
            "Answer": 878,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 18 * 1 * 13 + 2 * 12 * 15",
            "Answer": 597,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 14 * 18 * 10 + 13 * 11 * 10",
            "Answer": 3954,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 1 * 16 * 3 + 15 * 16 * 7",
            "Answer": 1732,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 17 * 14 * 6 + 18 * 13 * 4",
            "Answer": 2369,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 14 * 9 * 18 + 0 * 10 * 13",
            "Answer": 2271,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 4 * 5 * 9 + 7 * 14 * 8",
            "Answer": 975,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 5 * 16 * 10 + 16 * 16 * 14",
            "Answer": 4395,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 17 * 19 * 13 + 18 * 14 * 0",
            "Answer": 4199,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 5 * 8 * 17 + 16 * 5 * 10",
            "Answer": 1497,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 8 * 8 * 1 + 2 * 18 * 6",
            "Answer": 288,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 8 * 10 * 8 + 1 * 1 * 2",
            "Answer": 654,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 0 * 16 * 14 + 6 * 15 * 9",
            "Answer": 823,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 8 * 0 * 17 + 15 * 15 * 9",
            "Answer": 2044,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 15 * 11 * 18 + 18 * 11 * 15",
            "Answer": 5945,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 17 * 14 * 8 + 10 * 13 * 2",
            "Answer": 2164,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 14 * 0 * 7 + 4 * 0 * 8",
            "Answer": 8,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 2 * 5 * 4 + 6 * 6 * 11",
            "Answer": 438,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 19 * 8 * 18 + 5 * 12 * 1",
            "Answer": 2814,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 11 * 4 * 4 + 4 * 14 * 1",
            "Answer": 233,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 7 * 0 * 12 + 7 * 5 * 19",
            "Answer": 680,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 15 * 10 * 1 + 13 * 15 * 1",
            "Answer": 347,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 7 * 17 * 8 + 12 * 8 * 5",
            "Answer": 1433,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 11 * 5 * 15 + 11 * 9 * 1",
            "Answer": 925,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 14 * 4 * 16 + 14 * 3 * 11",
            "Answer": 1363,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 8 * 0 * 14 + 18 * 14 * 7",
            "Answer": 1768,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 9 * 9 * 5 + 19 * 15 * 17",
            "Answer": 5250,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 11 * 5 * 16 + 5 * 8 * 13",
            "Answer": 1402,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 6 * 6 * 10 + 18 * 9 * 9",
            "Answer": 1819,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 2 * 19 * 1 + 14 * 6 * 8",
            "Answer": 718,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 19 * 17 * 19 + 19 * 3 * 6",
            "Answer": 6495,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 10 * 16 * 2 + 19 * 13 * 8",
            "Answer": 2311,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 18 * 12 * 4 + 4 * 16 * 1",
            "Answer": 934,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 1 * 9 * 3 + 4 * 11 * 12",
            "Answer": 572,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 18 * 18 * 2 + 0 * 8 * 9",
            "Answer": 658,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 14 * 10 * 2 + 1 * 5 * 3",
            "Answer": 314,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 5 * 8 * 17 + 17 * 10 * 15",
            "Answer": 3247,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 10 * 4 * 8 + 12 * 15 * 4",
            "Answer": 1042,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 14 * 6 * 15 + 11 * 18 * 8",
            "Answer": 2847,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 5 * 0 * 10 + 6 * 11 * 7",
            "Answer": 478,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 2 * 16 * 12 + 6 * 14 * 2",
            "Answer": 569,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 5 * 5 * 1 + 6 * 12 * 9",
            "Answer": 683,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # * #"
        }
    ],
    "# + # * # * # * # * # * #": [
        {
            "Question": "16 + 2 * 11 * 18 * 8 * 4 * 5",
            "Answer": 63376,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 3 * 8 * 6 * 9 * 14 * 6",
            "Answer": 108882,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 12 * 0 * 3 * 10 * 19 * 7",
            "Answer": 1,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 9 * 10 * 4 * 6 * 13 * 17",
            "Answer": 477366,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 6 * 11 * 5 * 1 * 19 * 19",
            "Answer": 119136,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 16 * 11 * 4 * 19 * 4 * 5",
            "Answer": 267521,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 13 * 4 * 16 * 2 * 17 * 1",
            "Answer": 28292,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 17 * 18 * 1 * 17 * 6 * 13",
            "Answer": 405757,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 14 * 12 * 13 * 0 * 6 * 8",
            "Answer": 17,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 12 * 10 * 5 * 8 * 2 * 10",
            "Answer": 96007,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 9 * 18 * 3 * 0 * 9 * 14",
            "Answer": 19,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 19 * 16 * 16 * 14 * 14 * 18",
            "Answer": 17160210,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 11 * 1 * 4 * 2 * 18 * 15",
            "Answer": 23772,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 1 * 12 * 14 * 16 * 14 * 8",
            "Answer": 301066,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 8 * 2 * 1 * 11 * 1 * 16",
            "Answer": 2818,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 13 * 2 * 5 * 13 * 17 * 6",
            "Answer": 172393,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 9 * 12 * 8 * 8 * 10 * 9",
            "Answer": 622088,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 11 * 17 * 0 * 2 * 4 * 1",
            "Answer": 2,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 0 * 3 * 0 * 17 * 14 * 6",
            "Answer": 6,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 8 * 16 * 15 * 5 * 0 * 13",
            "Answer": 14,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 6 * 10 * 7 * 2 * 12 * 9",
            "Answer": 90728,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 2 * 0 * 16 * 11 * 1 * 0",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 6 * 2 * 8 * 10 * 8 * 6",
            "Answer": 46091,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 17 * 17 * 19 * 15 * 12 * 0",
            "Answer": 11,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 2 * 11 * 6 * 4 * 7 * 2",
            "Answer": 7409,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 0 * 11 * 2 * 6 * 9 * 16",
            "Answer": 9,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 0 * 9 * 13 * 14 * 14 * 8",
            "Answer": 14,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 11 * 17 * 5 * 14 * 12 * 9",
            "Answer": 1413723,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 6 * 6 * 17 * 16 * 15 * 2",
            "Answer": 293760,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 9 * 15 * 11 * 13 * 19 * 2",
            "Answer": 733601,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 19 * 8 * 6 * 4 * 18 * 11",
            "Answer": 722323,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 9 * 0 * 6 * 1 * 8 * 15",
            "Answer": 11,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 14 * 3 * 1 * 4 * 17 * 14",
            "Answer": 39993,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 5 * 1 * 13 * 11 * 3 * 2",
            "Answer": 4302,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 13 * 13 * 18 * 12 * 0 * 9",
            "Answer": 16,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 8 * 16 * 8 * 14 * 15 * 11",
            "Answer": 2365446,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 8 * 9 * 6 * 9 * 11 * 16",
            "Answer": 684302,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 13 * 3 * 8 * 2 * 18 * 13",
            "Answer": 146024,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 13 * 9 * 15 * 6 * 4 * 5",
            "Answer": 210610,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 16 * 0 * 1 * 0 * 9 * 3",
            "Answer": 8,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 13 * 0 * 1 * 16 * 19 * 10",
            "Answer": 5,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 13 * 1 * 7 * 1 * 17 * 6",
            "Answer": 9283,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 19 * 17 * 6 * 0 * 17 * 5",
            "Answer": 14,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 13 * 19 * 2 * 10 * 18 * 0",
            "Answer": 3,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 14 * 2 * 10 * 2 * 18 * 0",
            "Answer": 8,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 13 * 6 * 6 * 5 * 17 * 14",
            "Answer": 556927,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 17 * 3 * 12 * 12 * 15 * 5",
            "Answer": 550804,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 0 * 19 * 0 * 2 * 9 * 19",
            "Answer": 15,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 15 * 19 * 9 * 9 * 12 * 2",
            "Answer": 554052,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 6 * 8 * 17 * 17 * 11 * 12",
            "Answer": 1831117,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 1 * 7 * 3 * 18 * 5 * 18",
            "Answer": 34026,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 10 * 7 * 11 * 19 * 17 * 9",
            "Answer": 2238403,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 11 * 9 * 17 * 5 * 7 * 0",
            "Answer": 14,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 2 * 0 * 15 * 10 * 15 * 15",
            "Answer": 10,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 14 * 10 * 2 * 19 * 19 * 15",
            "Answer": 1516209,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 9 * 11 * 12 * 19 * 8 * 1",
            "Answer": 180577,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 4 * 13 * 2 * 10 * 14 * 16",
            "Answer": 232964,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 9 * 12 * 9 * 4 * 16 * 16",
            "Answer": 995328,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 13 * 14 * 1 * 5 * 8 * 6",
            "Answer": 43687,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 4 * 10 * 3 * 0 * 0 * 5",
            "Answer": 16,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 15 * 8 * 19 * 3 * 19 * 1",
            "Answer": 129978,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 18 * 6 * 4 * 14 * 6 * 18",
            "Answer": 653199,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 15 * 16 * 14 * 10 * 17 * 10",
            "Answer": 5712000,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 19 * 18 * 3 * 3 * 16 * 13",
            "Answer": 640226,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 2 * 17 * 2 * 18 * 5 * 10",
            "Answer": 61202,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 5 * 14 * 14 * 13 * 1 * 7",
            "Answer": 89192,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 19 * 6 * 13 * 7 * 18 * 6",
            "Answer": 1120396,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 9 * 8 * 14 * 8 * 13 * 9",
            "Answer": 943492,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 13 * 2 * 12 * 9 * 8 * 10",
            "Answer": 224655,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 16 * 9 * 7 * 7 * 3 * 5",
            "Answer": 105849,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 16 * 19 * 2 * 4 * 18 * 17",
            "Answer": 744197,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 11 * 7 * 6 * 7 * 19 * 0",
            "Answer": 3,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 13 * 7 * 13 * 4 * 13 * 5",
            "Answer": 307598,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 7 * 17 * 0 * 16 * 18 * 4",
            "Answer": 6,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 8 * 7 * 4 * 16 * 11 * 6",
            "Answer": 236556,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 14 * 13 * 17 * 2 * 3 * 13",
            "Answer": 241345,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 3 * 9 * 3 * 16 * 4 * 1",
            "Answer": 5194,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 2 * 12 * 2 * 0 * 1 * 1",
            "Answer": 9,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 7 * 10 * 0 * 14 * 6 * 19",
            "Answer": 9,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 2 * 0 * 12 * 0 * 11 * 9",
            "Answer": 6,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 1 * 6 * 5 * 19 * 16 * 10",
            "Answer": 91216,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 14 * 6 * 12 * 14 * 5 * 8",
            "Answer": 564486,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 18 * 2 * 0 * 12 * 11 * 8",
            "Answer": 10,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 3 * 9 * 10 * 11 * 8 * 1",
            "Answer": 23766,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 6 * 6 * 2 * 3 * 11 * 17",
            "Answer": 40392,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 4 * 0 * 17 * 9 * 1 * 1",
            "Answer": 2,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 15 * 10 * 13 * 0 * 11 * 10",
            "Answer": 1,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 3 * 12 * 18 * 12 * 19 * 10",
            "Answer": 1477446,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 7 * 16 * 12 * 7 * 14 * 17",
            "Answer": 2239122,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 11 * 17 * 9 * 0 * 10 * 3",
            "Answer": 12,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 13 * 19 * 15 * 12 * 13 * 6",
            "Answer": 3467885,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 1 * 10 * 10 * 11 * 3 * 18",
            "Answer": 59400,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 1 * 11 * 10 * 18 * 9 * 11",
            "Answer": 196031,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 13 * 17 * 14 * 0 * 19 * 16",
            "Answer": 6,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 11 * 10 * 18 * 18 * 13 * 5",
            "Answer": 2316609,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 9 * 15 * 9 * 15 * 2 * 3",
            "Answer": 109358,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 5 * 15 * 12 * 3 * 14 * 9",
            "Answer": 340213,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 7 * 18 * 19 * 12 * 15 * 1",
            "Answer": 430926,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 11 * 10 * 1 * 2 * 10 * 14",
            "Answer": 30807,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 18 * 18 * 16 * 5 * 3 * 11",
            "Answer": 855376,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # * # * #"
        }
    ],
    "# + # + # * # * # * # + #": [
        {
            "Question": "8 + 1 + 0 * 11 * 8 * 14 + 12",
            "Answer": 21,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 7 + 5 * 2 * 6 * 18 + 1",
            "Answer": 1100,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 5 + 1 * 16 * 16 * 8 + 13",
            "Answer": 2078,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 3 + 15 * 2 * 1 * 0 + 13",
            "Answer": 26,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 7 + 15 * 6 * 19 * 16 + 18",
            "Answer": 27401,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 9 + 14 * 12 * 7 * 16 + 3",
            "Answer": 18834,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 8 + 9 * 16 * 8 * 15 + 17",
            "Answer": 17310,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 17 + 11 * 0 * 18 * 7 + 13",
            "Answer": 35,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 0 + 8 * 0 * 17 * 7 + 3",
            "Answer": 13,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 4 + 9 * 9 * 8 * 13 + 9",
            "Answer": 8440,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 6 + 19 * 1 * 6 * 4 + 19",
            "Answer": 492,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 9 + 18 * 0 * 8 * 1 + 2",
            "Answer": 25,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 7 + 6 * 4 * 10 * 4 + 10",
            "Answer": 981,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 0 + 18 * 1 * 16 * 19 + 17",
            "Answer": 5495,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 2 + 1 * 17 * 17 * 1 + 4",
            "Answer": 309,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 8 + 4 * 11 * 13 * 15 + 11",
            "Answer": 8617,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 1 + 1 * 15 * 3 * 15 + 14",
            "Answer": 693,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 0 + 14 * 4 * 17 * 8 + 16",
            "Answer": 7639,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 8 + 11 * 4 * 3 * 12 + 13",
            "Answer": 1613,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 5 + 2 * 5 * 16 * 17 + 17",
            "Answer": 2752,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 13 + 7 * 17 * 4 * 4 + 7",
            "Answer": 1939,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 4 + 13 * 5 * 1 * 8 + 5",
            "Answer": 533,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 2 + 7 * 4 * 0 * 5 + 19",
            "Answer": 21,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 12 + 17 * 11 * 17 * 4 + 15",
            "Answer": 12756,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 1 + 12 * 19 * 14 * 18 + 11",
            "Answer": 57480,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 12 + 5 * 12 * 5 * 0 + 13",
            "Answer": 36,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 9 + 9 * 18 * 12 * 10 + 8",
            "Answer": 19468,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 19 + 11 * 12 * 12 * 12 + 17",
            "Answer": 19045,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 4 + 10 * 11 * 1 * 7 + 5",
            "Answer": 784,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 9 + 17 * 18 * 9 * 17 + 16",
            "Answer": 46853,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 17 + 14 * 13 * 5 * 16 + 2",
            "Answer": 14582,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 18 + 5 * 11 * 14 * 11 + 2",
            "Answer": 8504,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 1 + 5 * 10 * 7 * 14 + 13",
            "Answer": 4931,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 4 + 5 * 19 * 3 * 2 + 14",
            "Answer": 603,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 3 + 5 * 2 * 12 * 1 + 14",
            "Answer": 146,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 17 + 18 * 13 * 4 * 18 + 13",
            "Answer": 16879,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 2 + 15 * 2 * 18 * 5 + 7",
            "Answer": 2719,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 1 + 18 * 17 * 17 * 14 + 10",
            "Answer": 72841,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 6 + 12 * 0 * 4 * 17 + 2",
            "Answer": 16,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 5 + 17 * 9 * 0 * 11 + 14",
            "Answer": 25,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 11 + 13 * 10 * 18 * 13 + 9",
            "Answer": 30441,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 10 + 7 * 18 * 16 * 17 + 8",
            "Answer": 34303,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 12 + 1 * 8 * 6 * 6 + 9",
            "Answer": 313,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 2 + 4 * 4 * 8 * 9 + 3",
            "Answer": 1170,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 19 + 5 * 6 * 7 * 12 + 16",
            "Answer": 2568,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 11 + 17 * 9 * 4 * 0 + 13",
            "Answer": 43,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 18 + 16 * 3 * 12 * 10 + 18",
            "Answer": 5806,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 6 + 1 * 15 * 7 * 1 + 10",
            "Answer": 133,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 14 + 7 * 5 * 15 * 17 + 5",
            "Answer": 8957,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 18 + 11 * 13 * 6 * 16 + 2",
            "Answer": 13748,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 12 + 5 * 15 * 16 * 18 + 0",
            "Answer": 21621,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 18 + 19 * 8 * 19 * 12 + 14",
            "Answer": 34703,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 15 + 16 * 19 * 11 * 17 + 12",
            "Answer": 56891,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 3 + 19 * 11 * 5 * 1 + 13",
            "Answer": 1067,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 9 + 0 * 9 * 2 * 12 + 2",
            "Answer": 12,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 2 + 4 * 9 * 18 * 19 + 15",
            "Answer": 12345,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 14 + 3 * 19 * 4 * 0 + 10",
            "Answer": 39,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 11 + 11 * 11 * 4 * 3 + 0",
            "Answer": 1474,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 0 + 11 * 1 * 5 * 12 + 4",
            "Answer": 677,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 14 + 4 * 13 * 4 * 13 + 5",
            "Answer": 2741,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 13 + 5 * 3 * 12 * 10 + 17",
            "Answer": 1837,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 1 + 17 * 10 * 17 * 14 + 2",
            "Answer": 40480,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 6 + 2 * 17 * 1 * 13 + 7",
            "Answer": 472,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 4 + 18 * 10 * 13 * 4 + 19",
            "Answer": 9402,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 13 + 12 * 12 * 17 * 2 + 0",
            "Answer": 4923,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 2 + 13 * 15 * 1 * 13 + 17",
            "Answer": 2555,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 6 + 2 * 17 * 11 * 2 + 0",
            "Answer": 759,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 17 + 12 * 16 * 5 * 5 + 7",
            "Answer": 4843,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 8 + 11 * 0 * 6 * 11 + 5",
            "Answer": 18,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 11 + 10 * 6 * 15 * 6 + 7",
            "Answer": 5430,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 7 + 16 * 15 * 13 * 2 + 2",
            "Answer": 6253,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 6 + 3 * 3 * 0 * 7 + 11",
            "Answer": 23,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 19 + 10 * 13 * 12 * 3 + 19",
            "Answer": 4722,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 12 + 9 * 5 * 4 * 12 + 12",
            "Answer": 2187,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 14 + 19 * 10 * 16 * 16 + 14",
            "Answer": 48679,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 4 + 1 * 3 * 6 * 11 + 12",
            "Answer": 216,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 1 + 1 * 12 * 5 * 8 + 19",
            "Answer": 501,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 10 + 12 * 7 * 19 * 10 + 11",
            "Answer": 15991,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 11 + 3 * 11 * 11 * 8 + 17",
            "Answer": 2947,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 6 + 3 * 17 * 6 * 4 + 16",
            "Answer": 1259,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 10 + 0 * 15 * 18 * 9 + 0",
            "Answer": 29,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 0 + 9 * 9 * 9 * 18 + 18",
            "Answer": 13157,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 12 + 14 * 9 * 17 * 7 + 12",
            "Answer": 15035,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 17 + 8 * 11 * 12 * 12 + 1",
            "Answer": 12700,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 16 + 13 * 11 * 19 * 10 + 0",
            "Answer": 27204,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 2 + 17 * 1 * 13 * 19 + 4",
            "Answer": 4208,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 8 + 10 * 6 * 7 * 13 + 12",
            "Answer": 5496,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 11 + 4 * 5 * 2 * 14 + 3",
            "Answer": 576,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 1 + 13 * 5 * 11 * 17 + 6",
            "Answer": 12178,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 5 + 1 * 14 * 10 * 16 + 14",
            "Answer": 2273,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 0 + 19 * 1 * 2 * 18 + 12",
            "Answer": 714,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 6 + 6 * 7 * 7 * 12 + 0",
            "Answer": 3546,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 4 + 17 * 0 * 12 * 1 + 12",
            "Answer": 25,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 1 + 7 * 6 * 16 * 13 + 18",
            "Answer": 8763,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 16 + 4 * 16 * 6 * 15 + 15",
            "Answer": 5795,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 2 + 11 * 3 * 10 * 5 + 1",
            "Answer": 1670,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 15 + 1 * 5 * 1 * 17 + 17",
            "Answer": 120,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 11 + 11 * 8 * 6 * 14 + 11",
            "Answer": 7422,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 9 + 15 * 1 * 6 * 6 + 17",
            "Answer": 581,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 4 + 10 * 16 * 17 * 19 + 14",
            "Answer": 51708,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # * # + #"
        }
    ],
    "# + # + # * # + # + # + #": [
        {
            "Question": "16 + 15 + 19 * 16 + 17 + 15 + 7",
            "Answer": 374,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 9 + 1 * 0 + 6 + 13 + 11",
            "Answer": 55,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 4 + 0 * 5 + 17 + 16 + 4",
            "Answer": 57,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 7 + 17 * 0 + 16 + 12 + 19",
            "Answer": 57,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 13 + 2 * 14 + 14 + 4 + 10",
            "Answer": 69,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 11 + 19 * 10 + 6 + 18 + 11",
            "Answer": 242,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 5 + 3 * 6 + 10 + 8 + 15",
            "Answer": 64,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 15 + 18 * 2 + 1 + 18 + 1",
            "Answer": 72,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 10 + 16 * 9 + 0 + 2 + 19",
            "Answer": 178,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 1 + 16 * 6 + 8 + 7 + 10",
            "Answer": 141,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 13 + 12 * 10 + 14 + 9 + 7",
            "Answer": 182,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 11 + 15 * 16 + 16 + 11 + 6",
            "Answer": 294,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 6 + 16 * 7 + 3 + 6 + 17",
            "Answer": 153,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 11 + 15 * 9 + 9 + 16 + 19",
            "Answer": 199,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 4 + 5 * 0 + 18 + 10 + 14",
            "Answer": 64,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 5 + 6 * 5 + 15 + 2 + 14",
            "Answer": 74,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 7 + 3 * 0 + 7 + 3 + 7",
            "Answer": 34,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 11 + 19 * 5 + 5 + 15 + 18",
            "Answer": 155,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 11 + 13 * 13 + 16 + 18 + 14",
            "Answer": 229,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 12 + 14 * 4 + 10 + 9 + 13",
            "Answer": 119,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 12 + 9 * 3 + 7 + 8 + 15",
            "Answer": 70,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 11 + 12 * 9 + 9 + 12 + 19",
            "Answer": 174,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 17 + 0 * 17 + 3 + 19 + 16",
            "Answer": 68,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 19 + 2 * 0 + 15 + 14 + 11",
            "Answer": 61,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 17 + 10 * 19 + 3 + 16 + 2",
            "Answer": 233,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 12 + 5 * 16 + 0 + 13 + 1",
            "Answer": 120,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 19 + 8 * 4 + 10 + 1 + 7",
            "Answer": 86,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 13 + 12 * 13 + 17 + 11 + 6",
            "Answer": 204,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 2 + 8 * 17 + 14 + 19 + 6",
            "Answer": 179,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 9 + 4 * 10 + 11 + 18 + 19",
            "Answer": 106,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 10 + 10 * 12 + 4 + 9 + 2",
            "Answer": 158,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 19 + 12 * 11 + 5 + 6 + 5",
            "Answer": 184,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 19 + 9 * 13 + 5 + 4 + 10",
            "Answer": 170,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 2 + 17 * 4 + 8 + 19 + 6",
            "Answer": 113,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 14 + 15 * 0 + 14 + 0 + 3",
            "Answer": 47,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 15 + 13 * 18 + 14 + 15 + 11",
            "Answer": 299,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 8 + 3 * 5 + 16 + 16 + 3",
            "Answer": 72,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 15 + 4 * 18 + 16 + 6 + 8",
            "Answer": 129,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 8 + 14 * 2 + 12 + 0 + 17",
            "Answer": 84,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 10 + 15 * 17 + 19 + 2 + 8",
            "Answer": 302,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 11 + 7 * 9 + 19 + 5 + 1",
            "Answer": 117,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 14 + 17 * 8 + 6 + 5 + 10",
            "Answer": 172,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 9 + 17 * 0 + 1 + 19 + 19",
            "Answer": 58,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 5 + 19 * 17 + 17 + 12 + 18",
            "Answer": 384,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 6 + 11 * 4 + 16 + 18 + 6",
            "Answer": 97,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 0 + 13 * 9 + 7 + 2 + 19",
            "Answer": 150,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 9 + 18 * 2 + 9 + 19 + 10",
            "Answer": 91,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 5 + 11 * 13 + 7 + 9 + 12",
            "Answer": 179,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 11 + 8 * 15 + 11 + 10 + 17",
            "Answer": 171,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 10 + 3 * 1 + 15 + 19 + 12",
            "Answer": 75,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 6 + 7 * 3 + 12 + 5 + 1",
            "Answer": 45,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 4 + 11 * 19 + 4 + 12 + 10",
            "Answer": 242,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 7 + 4 * 12 + 3 + 8 + 16",
            "Answer": 99,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 11 + 7 * 6 + 2 + 5 + 14",
            "Answer": 78,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 11 + 12 * 12 + 1 + 3 + 6",
            "Answer": 181,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 19 + 15 * 8 + 3 + 0 + 4",
            "Answer": 158,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 4 + 18 * 12 + 18 + 7 + 4",
            "Answer": 254,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 12 + 0 * 17 + 0 + 17 + 2",
            "Answer": 32,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 8 + 0 * 11 + 17 + 16 + 5",
            "Answer": 63,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 8 + 12 * 9 + 7 + 16 + 3",
            "Answer": 148,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 7 + 0 * 15 + 13 + 14 + 0",
            "Answer": 42,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 18 + 3 * 14 + 2 + 7 + 12",
            "Answer": 95,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 2 + 15 * 5 + 5 + 8 + 14",
            "Answer": 118,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 6 + 7 * 16 + 12 + 2 + 13",
            "Answer": 160,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 19 + 16 * 18 + 2 + 12 + 2",
            "Answer": 326,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 12 + 13 * 18 + 12 + 16 + 14",
            "Answer": 301,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 1 + 13 * 10 + 16 + 4 + 19",
            "Answer": 182,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 5 + 19 * 3 + 14 + 15 + 14",
            "Answer": 115,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 7 + 5 * 10 + 0 + 19 + 14",
            "Answer": 96,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 3 + 0 * 17 + 5 + 15 + 3",
            "Answer": 26,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 9 + 7 * 17 + 17 + 6 + 16",
            "Answer": 184,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 16 + 19 * 13 + 2 + 12 + 8",
            "Answer": 301,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 18 + 10 * 9 + 8 + 6 + 15",
            "Answer": 144,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 12 + 13 * 10 + 6 + 12 + 11",
            "Answer": 175,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 7 + 5 * 6 + 3 + 5 + 15",
            "Answer": 77,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 8 + 1 * 3 + 4 + 1 + 18",
            "Answer": 39,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 11 + 13 * 17 + 11 + 16 + 16",
            "Answer": 293,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 13 + 15 * 17 + 17 + 16 + 4",
            "Answer": 314,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 0 + 3 * 5 + 5 + 16 + 15",
            "Answer": 55,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 0 + 19 * 15 + 19 + 17 + 14",
            "Answer": 335,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 4 + 7 * 16 + 14 + 11 + 16",
            "Answer": 167,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 3 + 15 * 10 + 5 + 17 + 4",
            "Answer": 182,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 15 + 3 * 13 + 15 + 18 + 19",
            "Answer": 112,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 5 + 4 * 13 + 17 + 18 + 16",
            "Answer": 123,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 18 + 15 * 13 + 12 + 15 + 1",
            "Answer": 253,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 14 + 18 * 7 + 7 + 13 + 18",
            "Answer": 191,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 17 + 18 * 13 + 18 + 1 + 11",
            "Answer": 282,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 10 + 12 * 1 + 18 + 0 + 5",
            "Answer": 56,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 11 + 5 * 15 + 13 + 17 + 4",
            "Answer": 124,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 7 + 18 * 6 + 3 + 17 + 19",
            "Answer": 154,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 12 + 12 * 10 + 14 + 10 + 16",
            "Answer": 181,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 2 + 14 * 11 + 13 + 7 + 15",
            "Answer": 210,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 5 + 12 * 9 + 18 + 16 + 11",
            "Answer": 158,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 12 + 13 * 2 + 5 + 14 + 15",
            "Answer": 80,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 9 + 14 * 2 + 16 + 17 + 10",
            "Answer": 80,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 18 + 1 * 5 + 13 + 0 + 12",
            "Answer": 51,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 10 + 2 * 13 + 18 + 17 + 14",
            "Answer": 93,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 6 + 13 * 0 + 15 + 18 + 7",
            "Answer": 60,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 11 + 15 * 19 + 8 + 11 + 2",
            "Answer": 320,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 2 + 17 * 11 + 18 + 13 + 10",
            "Answer": 242,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # + # + #"
        }
    ],
    "# + # * # + # + # * # * #": [
        {
            "Question": "7 + 16 * 8 + 18 + 18 * 8 * 15",
            "Answer": 2313,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 1 * 5 + 16 + 11 * 12 * 16",
            "Answer": 2135,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 16 * 2 + 15 + 19 * 9 * 9",
            "Answer": 1601,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 16 * 4 + 1 + 10 * 11 * 16",
            "Answer": 1841,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 12 * 5 + 14 + 13 * 17 * 4",
            "Answer": 977,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 17 * 5 + 3 + 6 * 8 * 19",
            "Answer": 1010,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 7 * 18 + 5 + 6 * 13 * 7",
            "Answer": 690,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 7 * 10 + 11 + 8 * 8 * 0",
            "Answer": 87,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 15 * 5 + 3 + 3 * 3 * 13",
            "Answer": 206,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 0 * 11 + 10 + 7 * 9 * 11",
            "Answer": 714,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 9 * 6 + 8 + 7 * 10 * 2",
            "Answer": 204,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 16 * 8 + 9 + 18 * 13 * 11",
            "Answer": 2730,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 18 * 16 + 4 + 8 * 15 * 10",
            "Answer": 1505,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 9 * 10 + 5 + 2 * 13 * 18",
            "Answer": 580,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 15 * 15 + 2 + 12 * 13 * 18",
            "Answer": 3048,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 18 * 15 + 2 + 8 * 13 * 5",
            "Answer": 810,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 5 * 3 + 17 + 17 * 17 * 19",
            "Answer": 5526,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 2 * 12 + 16 + 9 * 16 * 11",
            "Answer": 1643,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 19 * 9 + 18 + 13 * 9 * 9",
            "Answer": 1245,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 10 * 0 + 4 + 3 * 18 * 1",
            "Answer": 62,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 6 * 16 + 13 + 9 * 6 * 11",
            "Answer": 709,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 9 * 11 + 18 + 6 * 18 * 0",
            "Answer": 124,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 3 * 12 + 6 + 5 * 3 * 18",
            "Answer": 312,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 9 * 11 + 14 + 8 * 17 * 15",
            "Answer": 2163,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 10 * 0 + 1 + 18 * 2 * 8",
            "Answer": 294,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 1 * 6 + 4 + 14 * 18 * 1",
            "Answer": 264,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 3 * 11 + 2 + 10 * 16 * 14",
            "Answer": 2275,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 9 * 1 + 13 + 4 * 15 * 0",
            "Answer": 38,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 7 * 10 + 0 + 0 * 0 * 5",
            "Answer": 89,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 14 * 5 + 2 + 17 * 7 * 10",
            "Answer": 1270,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 11 * 2 + 4 + 7 * 9 * 0",
            "Answer": 31,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 6 * 16 + 14 + 17 * 15 * 13",
            "Answer": 3437,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 14 * 9 + 9 + 2 * 10 * 6",
            "Answer": 274,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 19 * 2 + 19 + 12 * 18 * 11",
            "Answer": 2451,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 5 * 18 + 0 + 12 * 3 * 1",
            "Answer": 130,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 19 * 16 + 13 + 0 * 1 * 4",
            "Answer": 324,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 1 * 18 + 11 + 15 * 10 * 17",
            "Answer": 2592,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 18 * 6 + 2 + 17 * 10 * 9",
            "Answer": 1644,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 13 * 7 + 13 + 3 * 14 * 16",
            "Answer": 787,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 7 * 4 + 0 + 11 * 18 * 12",
            "Answer": 2416,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 6 * 18 + 8 + 12 * 6 * 15",
            "Answer": 1205,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 7 * 2 + 1 + 14 * 5 * 0",
            "Answer": 32,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 1 * 0 + 8 + 18 * 19 * 13",
            "Answer": 4454,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 2 * 9 + 17 + 5 * 19 * 14",
            "Answer": 1375,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 1 * 0 + 7 + 19 * 15 * 16",
            "Answer": 4567,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 8 * 17 + 17 + 18 * 16 * 11",
            "Answer": 3323,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 15 * 4 + 11 + 1 * 10 * 8",
            "Answer": 153,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 5 * 9 + 12 + 9 * 13 * 12",
            "Answer": 1470,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 2 * 13 + 16 + 5 * 15 * 7",
            "Answer": 586,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 16 * 10 + 3 + 13 * 9 * 14",
            "Answer": 1813,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 5 * 7 + 2 + 14 * 15 * 3",
            "Answer": 671,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 7 * 6 + 11 + 8 * 15 * 19",
            "Answer": 2343,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 9 * 19 + 1 + 14 * 15 * 4",
            "Answer": 1029,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 7 * 14 + 18 + 19 * 9 * 6",
            "Answer": 1160,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 17 * 2 + 2 + 2 * 17 * 18",
            "Answer": 653,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 4 * 4 + 4 + 17 * 13 * 14",
            "Answer": 3133,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 16 * 14 + 5 + 14 * 19 * 18",
            "Answer": 5022,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 7 * 18 + 1 + 4 * 4 * 11",
            "Answer": 313,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 5 * 3 + 7 + 17 * 7 * 4",
            "Answer": 505,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 14 * 15 + 13 + 12 * 8 * 5",
            "Answer": 704,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 12 * 0 + 3 + 7 * 13 * 10",
            "Answer": 922,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 4 * 3 + 16 + 0 * 17 * 8",
            "Answer": 36,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 17 * 0 + 6 + 0 * 12 * 0",
            "Answer": 12,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 1 * 18 + 18 + 8 * 18 * 18",
            "Answer": 2629,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 11 * 3 + 4 + 1 * 10 * 0",
            "Answer": 44,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 1 * 14 + 10 + 14 * 4 * 1",
            "Answer": 98,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 7 * 15 + 8 + 6 * 1 * 16",
            "Answer": 209,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 18 * 17 + 10 + 1 * 17 * 6",
            "Answer": 429,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 14 * 8 + 10 + 17 * 12 * 17",
            "Answer": 3590,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 10 * 19 + 19 + 12 * 16 * 3",
            "Answer": 788,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 15 * 14 + 14 + 17 * 0 * 19",
            "Answer": 225,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 14 * 4 + 17 + 16 * 6 * 13",
            "Answer": 1321,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 19 * 1 + 4 + 0 * 4 * 3",
            "Answer": 24,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 9 * 12 + 11 + 3 * 13 * 15",
            "Answer": 720,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 11 * 8 + 0 + 14 * 17 * 0",
            "Answer": 106,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 10 * 3 + 13 + 1 * 19 * 12",
            "Answer": 287,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 16 * 1 + 18 + 19 * 17 * 0",
            "Answer": 51,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 9 * 16 + 0 + 2 * 11 * 7",
            "Answer": 300,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 18 * 1 + 3 + 12 * 1 * 12",
            "Answer": 165,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 11 * 8 + 11 + 5 * 3 * 4",
            "Answer": 172,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 14 * 11 + 0 + 9 * 17 * 4",
            "Answer": 774,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 9 * 16 + 10 + 18 * 5 * 19",
            "Answer": 1870,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 16 * 10 + 8 + 12 * 3 * 17",
            "Answer": 782,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 2 * 15 + 18 + 18 * 8 * 5",
            "Answer": 770,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 5 * 7 + 10 + 8 * 18 * 16",
            "Answer": 2365,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 14 * 19 + 0 + 14 * 16 * 3",
            "Answer": 957,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 0 * 2 + 14 + 9 * 16 * 0",
            "Answer": 19,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 9 * 14 + 0 + 17 * 6 * 16",
            "Answer": 1764,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 3 * 2 + 15 + 4 * 8 * 2",
            "Answer": 97,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 6 * 10 + 1 + 12 * 14 * 6",
            "Answer": 1075,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 17 * 14 + 17 + 4 * 8 * 0",
            "Answer": 259,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 16 * 2 + 13 + 19 * 1 * 11",
            "Answer": 267,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 6 * 6 + 3 + 17 * 12 * 10",
            "Answer": 2094,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 16 * 1 + 16 + 16 * 18 * 1",
            "Answer": 329,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 14 * 14 + 19 + 8 * 13 * 16",
            "Answer": 1895,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 9 * 12 + 2 + 14 * 5 * 0",
            "Answer": 113,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 6 * 16 + 6 + 4 * 0 * 15",
            "Answer": 103,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 3 * 12 + 0 + 4 * 7 * 8",
            "Answer": 260,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 15 * 14 + 12 + 18 * 1 * 16",
            "Answer": 520,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 15 * 1 + 5 + 2 * 17 * 11",
            "Answer": 412,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # * #"
        }
    ],
    "# * # + # * # + # + # * #": [
        {
            "Question": "12 * 12 + 2 * 16 + 2 + 13 * 0",
            "Answer": 178,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 16 + 16 * 5 + 19 + 6 * 1",
            "Answer": 265,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 15 + 13 * 16 + 15 + 10 * 15",
            "Answer": 388,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 5 + 1 * 1 + 5 + 13 * 19",
            "Answer": 343,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 6 + 13 * 8 + 6 + 0 * 12",
            "Answer": 212,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 2 + 1 * 1 + 4 + 8 * 6",
            "Answer": 89,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 19 + 8 * 4 + 3 + 13 * 7",
            "Answer": 259,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 3 + 17 * 9 + 16 + 12 * 14",
            "Answer": 349,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 1 + 16 * 12 + 10 + 7 * 17",
            "Answer": 323,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 7 + 0 * 15 + 6 + 1 * 0",
            "Answer": 69,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 9 + 10 * 7 + 6 + 17 * 19",
            "Answer": 408,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 8 + 19 * 6 + 12 + 10 * 4",
            "Answer": 174,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 11 + 17 * 4 + 4 + 7 * 11",
            "Answer": 270,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 6 + 11 * 4 + 17 + 4 * 12",
            "Answer": 163,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 10 + 7 * 14 + 16 + 3 * 11",
            "Answer": 217,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 15 + 14 * 4 + 18 + 5 * 6",
            "Answer": 314,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 4 + 19 * 12 + 7 + 5 * 18",
            "Answer": 401,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 11 + 1 * 8 + 16 + 19 * 16",
            "Answer": 416,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 14 + 11 * 19 + 4 + 13 * 8",
            "Answer": 331,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 11 + 3 * 4 + 11 + 7 * 15",
            "Answer": 337,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 10 + 15 * 5 + 2 + 18 * 9",
            "Answer": 249,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 2 + 18 * 9 + 1 + 19 * 10",
            "Answer": 359,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 17 + 7 * 9 + 3 + 6 * 19",
            "Answer": 367,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 16 + 11 * 4 + 10 + 13 * 13",
            "Answer": 287,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 8 + 19 * 1 + 2 + 12 * 12",
            "Answer": 181,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 1 + 15 * 1 + 12 + 12 * 19",
            "Answer": 256,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 14 + 16 * 10 + 7 + 9 * 5",
            "Answer": 450,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 10 + 6 * 6 + 8 + 16 * 18",
            "Answer": 402,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 16 + 13 * 9 + 0 + 0 * 14",
            "Answer": 261,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 16 + 2 * 18 + 1 + 14 * 16",
            "Answer": 517,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 11 + 1 * 8 + 1 + 11 * 17",
            "Answer": 251,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 1 + 1 * 19 + 3 + 2 * 5",
            "Answer": 41,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 15 + 15 * 0 + 4 + 11 * 8",
            "Answer": 107,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 13 + 8 * 14 + 4 + 19 * 6",
            "Answer": 282,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 8 + 14 * 15 + 19 + 4 * 8",
            "Answer": 333,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 14 + 14 * 0 + 14 + 1 * 8",
            "Answer": 22,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 15 + 8 * 17 + 18 + 13 * 6",
            "Answer": 397,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 4 + 9 * 16 + 4 + 19 * 8",
            "Answer": 324,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 19 + 18 * 11 + 0 + 9 * 14",
            "Answer": 495,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 1 + 2 * 10 + 17 + 7 * 7",
            "Answer": 98,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 14 + 8 * 9 + 12 + 0 * 19",
            "Answer": 294,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 16 + 4 * 11 + 10 + 6 * 16",
            "Answer": 422,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 18 + 9 * 16 + 5 + 19 * 0",
            "Answer": 257,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 4 + 0 * 13 + 4 + 10 * 0",
            "Answer": 32,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 13 + 8 * 8 + 9 + 11 * 15",
            "Answer": 407,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 4 + 18 * 13 + 15 + 0 * 3",
            "Answer": 325,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 6 + 10 * 0 + 13 + 16 * 12",
            "Answer": 289,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 16 + 0 * 3 + 15 + 8 * 9",
            "Answer": 103,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 2 + 7 * 6 + 14 + 1 * 19",
            "Answer": 97,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 14 + 16 * 13 + 6 + 13 * 4",
            "Answer": 490,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 6 + 18 * 10 + 8 + 6 * 7",
            "Answer": 320,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 5 + 13 * 16 + 6 + 1 * 1",
            "Answer": 245,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 3 + 15 * 3 + 14 + 12 * 9",
            "Answer": 167,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 13 + 3 * 14 + 3 + 12 * 10",
            "Answer": 230,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 18 + 15 * 18 + 2 + 10 * 5",
            "Answer": 448,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 2 + 19 * 5 + 7 + 16 * 0",
            "Answer": 118,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 3 + 1 * 17 + 17 + 0 * 19",
            "Answer": 61,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 9 + 3 * 19 + 5 + 7 * 4",
            "Answer": 126,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 11 + 1 * 14 + 2 + 8 * 4",
            "Answer": 202,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 16 + 4 * 19 + 2 + 1 * 15",
            "Answer": 237,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 0 + 3 * 12 + 17 + 4 * 19",
            "Answer": 129,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 12 + 12 * 11 + 10 + 3 * 14",
            "Answer": 364,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 12 + 12 * 6 + 8 + 3 * 11",
            "Answer": 257,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 6 + 4 * 2 + 11 + 14 * 6",
            "Answer": 187,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 13 + 10 * 4 + 12 + 1 * 1",
            "Answer": 92,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 7 + 19 * 7 + 13 + 12 * 11",
            "Answer": 390,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 15 + 3 * 16 + 12 + 13 * 5",
            "Answer": 320,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 4 + 12 * 10 + 18 + 15 * 8",
            "Answer": 290,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 9 + 15 * 16 + 0 + 16 * 7",
            "Answer": 496,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 7 + 4 * 16 + 6 + 0 * 3",
            "Answer": 98,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 7 + 5 * 12 + 3 + 8 * 6",
            "Answer": 146,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 0 + 10 * 15 + 10 + 18 * 3",
            "Answer": 214,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 10 + 18 * 9 + 14 + 16 * 8",
            "Answer": 434,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 17 + 2 * 16 + 18 + 5 * 3",
            "Answer": 65,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 1 + 1 * 10 + 16 + 4 * 12",
            "Answer": 79,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 17 + 19 * 4 + 8 + 4 * 1",
            "Answer": 258,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 16 + 13 * 14 + 10 + 17 * 6",
            "Answer": 502,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 19 + 4 * 3 + 18 + 6 * 12",
            "Answer": 311,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 9 + 15 * 16 + 18 + 7 * 9",
            "Answer": 393,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 13 + 13 * 3 + 12 + 18 * 12",
            "Answer": 462,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 5 + 14 * 9 + 17 + 12 * 4",
            "Answer": 236,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 6 + 1 * 0 + 14 + 13 * 12",
            "Answer": 212,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 0 + 10 * 13 + 1 + 13 * 12",
            "Answer": 287,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 13 + 16 * 18 + 14 + 7 * 2",
            "Answer": 355,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 4 + 16 * 9 + 7 + 18 * 10",
            "Answer": 367,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 9 + 4 * 15 + 5 + 1 * 17",
            "Answer": 127,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 7 + 13 * 5 + 15 + 10 * 5",
            "Answer": 207,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 10 + 10 * 19 + 0 + 8 * 18",
            "Answer": 384,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 1 + 11 * 16 + 6 + 3 * 8",
            "Answer": 216,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 0 + 17 * 7 + 19 + 15 * 2",
            "Answer": 168,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 8 + 8 * 5 + 14 + 12 * 18",
            "Answer": 350,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 2 + 18 * 14 + 8 + 10 * 7",
            "Answer": 344,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 9 + 18 * 0 + 3 + 10 * 19",
            "Answer": 283,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 11 + 14 * 19 + 3 + 14 * 17",
            "Answer": 694,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 7 + 12 * 7 + 0 + 11 * 8",
            "Answer": 172,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 3 + 4 * 15 + 2 + 6 * 15",
            "Answer": 155,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 5 + 16 * 3 + 2 + 2 * 16",
            "Answer": 127,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 9 + 17 * 17 + 17 + 2 * 17",
            "Answer": 376,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 9 + 2 * 17 + 7 + 17 * 4",
            "Answer": 154,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 3 + 18 * 18 + 11 + 7 * 4",
            "Answer": 408,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # * #"
        }
    ],
    "# + # + # * # + # * # * #": [
        {
            "Question": "0 + 8 + 6 * 16 + 14 * 19 * 17",
            "Answer": 4626,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 7 + 6 * 14 + 6 * 7 * 6",
            "Answer": 352,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 17 + 13 * 7 + 11 * 9 * 13",
            "Answer": 1404,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 4 + 12 * 1 + 12 * 1 * 6",
            "Answer": 90,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 10 + 12 * 10 + 19 * 15 * 1",
            "Answer": 423,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 1 + 14 * 11 + 19 * 4 * 4",
            "Answer": 465,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 3 + 6 * 8 + 7 * 1 * 11",
            "Answer": 131,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 19 + 17 * 7 + 13 * 9 * 3",
            "Answer": 489,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 13 + 7 * 1 + 16 * 14 * 13",
            "Answer": 2939,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 14 + 3 * 14 + 5 * 3 * 3",
            "Answer": 115,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 12 + 2 * 5 + 19 * 18 * 2",
            "Answer": 720,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 14 + 5 * 15 + 8 * 7 * 16",
            "Answer": 991,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 4 + 1 * 0 + 12 * 6 * 12",
            "Answer": 881,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 7 + 19 * 1 + 6 * 19 * 13",
            "Answer": 1515,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 9 + 8 * 9 + 13 * 11 * 2",
            "Answer": 374,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 1 + 2 * 14 + 5 * 16 * 15",
            "Answer": 1241,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 14 + 5 * 6 + 12 * 4 * 16",
            "Answer": 830,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 14 + 15 * 19 + 4 * 0 * 15",
            "Answer": 300,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 2 + 8 * 12 + 7 * 7 * 19",
            "Answer": 1034,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 11 + 1 * 18 + 5 * 18 * 12",
            "Answer": 1115,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 17 + 8 * 10 + 12 * 11 * 5",
            "Answer": 762,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 5 + 7 * 9 + 16 * 8 * 2",
            "Answer": 331,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 7 + 10 * 16 + 14 * 10 * 14",
            "Answer": 2138,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 18 + 1 * 19 + 2 * 10 * 8",
            "Answer": 216,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 18 + 2 * 10 + 14 * 9 * 2",
            "Answer": 296,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 11 + 3 * 4 + 18 * 16 * 17",
            "Answer": 4921,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 11 + 7 * 17 + 19 * 7 * 5",
            "Answer": 797,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 10 + 10 * 14 + 10 * 7 * 13",
            "Answer": 1074,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 9 + 3 * 9 + 3 * 2 * 15",
            "Answer": 136,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 9 + 9 * 6 + 14 * 17 * 16",
            "Answer": 3875,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 13 + 2 * 11 + 17 * 2 * 19",
            "Answer": 697,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 5 + 8 * 10 + 2 * 18 * 18",
            "Answer": 746,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 7 + 1 * 18 + 7 * 7 * 19",
            "Answer": 961,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 18 + 3 * 15 + 19 * 12 * 14",
            "Answer": 3274,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 14 + 11 * 17 + 0 * 5 * 5",
            "Answer": 205,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 6 + 17 * 17 + 6 * 3 * 15",
            "Answer": 576,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 8 + 14 * 9 + 14 * 8 * 13",
            "Answer": 1604,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 10 + 10 * 4 + 2 * 16 * 7",
            "Answer": 284,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 6 + 8 * 13 + 5 * 2 * 10",
            "Answer": 216,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 17 + 5 * 4 + 3 * 6 * 0",
            "Answer": 44,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 13 + 15 * 11 + 0 * 7 * 3",
            "Answer": 189,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 1 + 14 * 5 + 0 * 18 * 2",
            "Answer": 88,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 10 + 13 * 14 + 5 * 11 * 17",
            "Answer": 1139,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 3 + 16 * 8 + 7 * 4 * 5",
            "Answer": 286,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 5 + 5 * 18 + 11 * 14 * 16",
            "Answer": 2571,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 12 + 0 * 17 + 18 * 1 * 12",
            "Answer": 228,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 7 + 12 * 3 + 7 * 8 * 19",
            "Answer": 1110,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 12 + 6 * 15 + 13 * 3 * 1",
            "Answer": 160,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 9 + 1 * 17 + 15 * 4 * 3",
            "Answer": 215,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 18 + 13 * 19 + 10 * 10 * 6",
            "Answer": 867,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 19 + 15 * 15 + 6 * 14 * 15",
            "Answer": 1504,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 5 + 2 * 15 + 4 * 16 * 3",
            "Answer": 228,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 11 + 6 * 17 + 15 * 19 * 17",
            "Answer": 4958,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 16 + 10 * 19 + 9 * 8 * 19",
            "Answer": 1588,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 16 + 12 * 10 + 13 * 7 * 12",
            "Answer": 1234,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 16 + 16 * 9 + 18 * 2 * 16",
            "Answer": 755,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 18 + 3 * 6 + 0 * 1 * 3",
            "Answer": 53,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 15 + 14 * 17 + 1 * 11 * 11",
            "Answer": 383,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 19 + 11 * 2 + 17 * 11 * 12",
            "Answer": 2294,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 11 + 0 * 0 + 4 * 7 * 18",
            "Answer": 525,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 10 + 1 * 9 + 16 * 19 * 11",
            "Answer": 3370,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 0 + 11 * 18 + 3 * 18 * 15",
            "Answer": 1018,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 16 + 7 * 5 + 4 * 4 * 4",
            "Answer": 119,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 15 + 3 * 1 + 12 * 17 * 2",
            "Answer": 427,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 16 + 12 * 13 + 9 * 7 * 15",
            "Answer": 1129,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 10 + 4 * 14 + 4 * 9 * 2",
            "Answer": 141,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 0 + 19 * 19 + 15 * 2 * 4",
            "Answer": 485,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 6 + 15 * 13 + 11 * 17 * 16",
            "Answer": 3203,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 7 + 10 * 11 + 4 * 13 * 11",
            "Answer": 691,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 19 + 13 * 15 + 8 * 14 * 6",
            "Answer": 895,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 9 + 0 * 14 + 3 * 6 * 12",
            "Answer": 237,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 6 + 17 * 4 + 0 * 4 * 10",
            "Answer": 90,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 0 + 9 * 10 + 8 * 14 * 4",
            "Answer": 547,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 18 + 10 * 7 + 19 * 12 * 19",
            "Answer": 4432,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 0 + 11 * 10 + 6 * 15 * 9",
            "Answer": 938,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 16 + 18 * 16 + 17 * 16 * 11",
            "Answer": 3296,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 15 + 3 * 9 + 12 * 12 * 16",
            "Answer": 2360,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 8 + 5 * 18 + 8 * 10 * 16",
            "Answer": 1380,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 16 + 1 * 2 + 3 * 18 * 13",
            "Answer": 738,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 2 + 15 * 13 + 3 * 6 * 1",
            "Answer": 229,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 7 + 7 * 1 + 11 * 8 * 14",
            "Answer": 1251,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 7 + 3 * 0 + 19 * 16 * 11",
            "Answer": 3351,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 19 + 2 * 9 + 3 * 2 * 10",
            "Answer": 111,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 19 + 1 * 4 + 11 * 2 * 1",
            "Answer": 56,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 2 + 3 * 4 + 14 * 16 * 15",
            "Answer": 3376,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 9 + 13 * 8 + 14 * 13 * 1",
            "Answer": 313,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 8 + 4 * 8 + 13 * 6 * 5",
            "Answer": 439,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 19 + 19 * 7 + 12 * 6 * 18",
            "Answer": 1463,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 6 + 11 * 19 + 5 * 1 * 7",
            "Answer": 261,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 13 + 16 * 7 + 14 * 7 * 17",
            "Answer": 1809,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 12 + 6 * 5 + 17 * 18 * 3",
            "Answer": 964,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 16 + 1 * 0 + 8 * 19 * 10",
            "Answer": 1545,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 1 + 11 * 6 + 0 * 13 * 4",
            "Answer": 78,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 17 + 1 * 2 + 9 * 12 * 17",
            "Answer": 1867,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 11 + 17 * 10 + 9 * 8 * 18",
            "Answer": 1496,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 7 + 2 * 11 + 13 * 4 * 0",
            "Answer": 29,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 18 + 7 * 1 + 16 * 17 * 10",
            "Answer": 2762,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 19 + 8 * 19 + 10 * 17 * 10",
            "Answer": 1875,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 19 + 15 * 13 + 3 * 9 * 12",
            "Answer": 540,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 0 + 10 * 16 + 6 * 17 * 13",
            "Answer": 1501,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # * #"
        }
    ],
    "# + # + # + # + # + # * #": [
        {
            "Question": "1 + 19 + 7 + 13 + 3 + 15 * 19",
            "Answer": 328,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 0 + 3 + 13 + 13 + 5 * 11",
            "Answer": 85,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 5 + 12 + 13 + 15 + 2 * 12",
            "Answer": 86,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 16 + 15 + 17 + 2 + 3 * 17",
            "Answer": 109,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 1 + 8 + 2 + 18 + 11 * 6",
            "Answer": 105,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 8 + 6 + 11 + 13 + 10 * 6",
            "Answer": 114,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 12 + 15 + 10 + 10 + 19 * 7",
            "Answer": 184,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 18 + 8 + 7 + 11 + 1 * 3",
            "Answer": 53,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 12 + 0 + 8 + 17 + 2 * 15",
            "Answer": 78,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 2 + 12 + 10 + 7 + 9 * 14",
            "Answer": 166,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 1 + 7 + 7 + 10 + 11 * 11",
            "Answer": 151,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 16 + 14 + 13 + 11 + 7 * 18",
            "Answer": 187,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 1 + 0 + 1 + 18 + 15 * 3",
            "Answer": 84,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 10 + 11 + 2 + 1 + 7 * 13",
            "Answer": 119,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 1 + 8 + 18 + 19 + 0 * 11",
            "Answer": 49,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 6 + 12 + 19 + 19 + 3 * 15",
            "Answer": 113,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 8 + 7 + 7 + 1 + 0 * 13",
            "Answer": 26,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 13 + 7 + 0 + 1 + 15 * 17",
            "Answer": 282,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 9 + 10 + 10 + 13 + 2 * 7",
            "Answer": 65,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 8 + 4 + 4 + 17 + 2 * 14",
            "Answer": 80,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 4 + 5 + 11 + 8 + 1 * 1",
            "Answer": 37,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 2 + 17 + 13 + 5 + 4 * 16",
            "Answer": 115,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 6 + 16 + 19 + 6 + 1 * 11",
            "Answer": 76,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 15 + 13 + 10 + 4 + 16 * 12",
            "Answer": 234,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 15 + 3 + 1 + 12 + 12 * 0",
            "Answer": 34,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 15 + 0 + 8 + 1 + 0 * 19",
            "Answer": 28,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 3 + 9 + 17 + 17 + 15 * 5",
            "Answer": 131,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 0 + 19 + 17 + 11 + 11 * 14",
            "Answer": 211,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 14 + 1 + 19 + 16 + 3 * 4",
            "Answer": 71,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 17 + 18 + 3 + 18 + 9 * 3",
            "Answer": 87,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 16 + 6 + 1 + 18 + 8 * 16",
            "Answer": 169,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 1 + 19 + 2 + 15 + 8 * 0",
            "Answer": 41,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 13 + 9 + 9 + 15 + 7 * 10",
            "Answer": 134,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 10 + 17 + 1 + 1 + 4 * 10",
            "Answer": 88,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 9 + 10 + 8 + 17 + 9 * 10",
            "Answer": 138,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 0 + 18 + 19 + 5 + 11 * 19",
            "Answer": 260,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 19 + 13 + 17 + 12 + 18 * 6",
            "Answer": 175,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 14 + 9 + 3 + 8 + 8 * 16",
            "Answer": 175,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 17 + 13 + 10 + 0 + 8 * 18",
            "Answer": 185,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 7 + 8 + 12 + 15 + 10 * 7",
            "Answer": 116,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 0 + 17 + 9 + 14 + 18 * 19",
            "Answer": 391,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 5 + 13 + 9 + 6 + 19 * 17",
            "Answer": 366,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 16 + 15 + 1 + 1 + 11 * 0",
            "Answer": 48,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 15 + 10 + 18 + 7 + 11 * 15",
            "Answer": 221,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 5 + 11 + 5 + 4 + 10 * 2",
            "Answer": 61,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 12 + 13 + 9 + 12 + 8 * 0",
            "Answer": 54,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 10 + 18 + 10 + 14 + 10 * 13",
            "Answer": 189,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 7 + 7 + 9 + 11 + 15 * 11",
            "Answer": 207,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 15 + 8 + 15 + 0 + 8 * 10",
            "Answer": 120,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 2 + 4 + 6 + 8 + 7 * 0",
            "Answer": 20,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 5 + 4 + 19 + 10 + 12 * 3",
            "Answer": 77,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 2 + 12 + 0 + 17 + 13 * 17",
            "Answer": 254,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 1 + 9 + 1 + 6 + 14 * 10",
            "Answer": 163,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 1 + 5 + 17 + 11 + 3 * 4",
            "Answer": 48,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 9 + 5 + 1 + 8 + 9 * 2",
            "Answer": 51,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 7 + 11 + 13 + 1 + 1 * 5",
            "Answer": 53,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 14 + 10 + 18 + 5 + 0 * 14",
            "Answer": 51,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 13 + 14 + 4 + 18 + 15 * 11",
            "Answer": 222,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 1 + 1 + 11 + 10 + 7 * 6",
            "Answer": 82,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 10 + 18 + 18 + 3 + 10 * 2",
            "Answer": 81,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 15 + 15 + 12 + 10 + 4 * 12",
            "Answer": 114,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 16 + 8 + 5 + 8 + 12 * 3",
            "Answer": 89,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 4 + 14 + 13 + 7 + 1 * 17",
            "Answer": 69,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 2 + 16 + 4 + 4 + 16 * 3",
            "Answer": 86,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 13 + 3 + 13 + 7 + 12 * 17",
            "Answer": 247,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 3 + 15 + 11 + 1 + 12 * 6",
            "Answer": 119,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 12 + 9 + 13 + 2 + 1 * 8",
            "Answer": 46,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 13 + 15 + 14 + 17 + 6 * 11",
            "Answer": 134,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 0 + 10 + 16 + 18 + 13 * 17",
            "Answer": 269,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 1 + 16 + 10 + 14 + 0 * 8",
            "Answer": 55,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 2 + 2 + 9 + 19 + 1 * 11",
            "Answer": 48,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 0 + 4 + 14 + 10 + 0 * 10",
            "Answer": 36,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 2 + 10 + 1 + 18 + 7 * 19",
            "Answer": 164,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 0 + 19 + 13 + 18 + 10 * 5",
            "Answer": 109,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 7 + 17 + 10 + 13 + 6 * 1",
            "Answer": 67,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 15 + 17 + 0 + 3 + 3 * 13",
            "Answer": 79,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 12 + 19 + 12 + 19 + 7 * 8",
            "Answer": 123,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 14 + 3 + 13 + 7 + 16 * 6",
            "Answer": 150,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 17 + 13 + 11 + 4 + 8 * 15",
            "Answer": 178,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 18 + 1 + 16 + 2 + 0 * 2",
            "Answer": 37,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 6 + 13 + 12 + 13 + 19 * 1",
            "Answer": 74,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 10 + 1 + 11 + 10 + 16 * 19",
            "Answer": 355,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 7 + 15 + 2 + 18 + 18 * 3",
            "Answer": 102,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 3 + 5 + 7 + 3 + 5 * 11",
            "Answer": 90,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 14 + 3 + 13 + 10 + 17 * 3",
            "Answer": 108,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 0 + 14 + 13 + 6 + 11 * 8",
            "Answer": 131,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 12 + 19 + 5 + 14 + 15 * 2",
            "Answer": 84,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 8 + 16 + 4 + 16 + 12 * 4",
            "Answer": 98,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 0 + 19 + 18 + 6 + 0 * 13",
            "Answer": 54,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 8 + 18 + 6 + 18 + 10 * 2",
            "Answer": 87,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 9 + 17 + 1 + 12 + 0 * 0",
            "Answer": 50,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 1 + 18 + 18 + 15 + 8 * 15",
            "Answer": 183,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 1 + 13 + 5 + 9 + 15 * 15",
            "Answer": 261,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 8 + 18 + 16 + 15 + 3 * 2",
            "Answer": 71,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 17 + 17 + 14 + 8 + 19 * 16",
            "Answer": 378,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 5 + 12 + 11 + 3 + 5 * 4",
            "Answer": 55,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 3 + 15 + 0 + 7 + 17 * 6",
            "Answer": 134,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 11 + 13 + 10 + 9 + 2 * 2",
            "Answer": 66,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 5 + 8 + 0 + 12 + 5 * 12",
            "Answer": 97,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 18 + 0 + 6 + 4 + 17 * 17",
            "Answer": 322,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # + # * #"
        }
    ],
    "# + # * # + # + # * # + #": [
        {
            "Question": "12 + 14 * 3 + 2 + 4 * 11 + 2",
            "Answer": 102,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 2 * 9 + 5 + 13 * 4 + 3",
            "Answer": 91,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 5 * 2 + 10 + 1 * 10 + 3",
            "Answer": 33,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 18 * 4 + 5 + 1 * 12 + 12",
            "Answer": 116,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 6 * 6 + 18 + 12 * 5 + 10",
            "Answer": 125,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 10 * 4 + 15 + 16 * 16 + 7",
            "Answer": 324,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 2 * 7 + 16 + 16 * 18 + 15",
            "Answer": 344,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 17 * 16 + 18 + 10 * 1 + 1",
            "Answer": 316,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 18 * 15 + 16 + 14 * 7 + 17",
            "Answer": 408,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 1 * 4 + 18 + 13 * 7 + 0",
            "Answer": 122,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 17 * 3 + 15 + 5 * 17 + 7",
            "Answer": 162,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 15 * 17 + 11 + 13 * 3 + 16",
            "Answer": 322,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 17 * 10 + 17 + 18 * 5 + 1",
            "Answer": 297,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 16 * 10 + 19 + 7 * 2 + 9",
            "Answer": 202,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 12 * 18 + 7 + 13 * 11 + 16",
            "Answer": 396,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 19 * 4 + 17 + 18 * 10 + 19",
            "Answer": 303,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 8 * 14 + 14 + 1 * 16 + 0",
            "Answer": 160,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 3 * 16 + 4 + 9 * 5 + 6",
            "Answer": 108,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 17 * 3 + 19 + 7 * 7 + 2",
            "Answer": 140,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 14 * 12 + 6 + 16 * 5 + 19",
            "Answer": 278,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 1 * 5 + 16 + 19 * 12 + 7",
            "Answer": 263,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 12 * 7 + 15 + 8 * 18 + 14",
            "Answer": 267,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 9 * 9 + 9 + 13 * 1 + 19",
            "Answer": 122,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 18 * 17 + 1 + 18 * 6 + 16",
            "Answer": 448,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 14 * 14 + 7 + 14 * 0 + 18",
            "Answer": 223,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 6 * 2 + 16 + 0 * 7 + 9",
            "Answer": 55,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 13 * 3 + 7 + 8 * 13 + 3",
            "Answer": 168,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 4 * 14 + 2 + 4 * 16 + 3",
            "Answer": 142,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 16 * 3 + 17 + 9 * 2 + 1",
            "Answer": 88,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 9 * 15 + 14 + 19 * 19 + 6",
            "Answer": 517,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 6 * 6 + 6 + 16 * 17 + 19",
            "Answer": 352,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 17 * 12 + 5 + 17 * 11 + 16",
            "Answer": 413,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 6 * 19 + 8 + 16 * 1 + 13",
            "Answer": 161,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 17 * 12 + 1 + 10 * 19 + 12",
            "Answer": 421,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 11 * 16 + 3 + 7 * 7 + 8",
            "Answer": 253,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 13 * 3 + 12 + 19 * 12 + 16",
            "Answer": 300,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 8 * 8 + 7 + 12 * 18 + 1",
            "Answer": 307,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 7 * 2 + 2 + 5 * 14 + 9",
            "Answer": 97,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 9 * 10 + 11 + 2 * 19 + 0",
            "Answer": 146,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 13 * 9 + 12 + 16 * 17 + 0",
            "Answer": 405,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 3 * 2 + 8 + 13 * 9 + 8",
            "Answer": 148,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 7 * 19 + 17 + 9 * 4 + 11",
            "Answer": 203,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 1 * 16 + 14 + 5 * 4 + 5",
            "Answer": 66,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 2 * 7 + 11 + 10 * 0 + 11",
            "Answer": 40,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 3 * 10 + 3 + 19 * 5 + 14",
            "Answer": 157,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 8 * 4 + 13 + 2 * 12 + 17",
            "Answer": 100,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 11 * 2 + 6 + 16 * 11 + 11",
            "Answer": 216,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 11 * 6 + 6 + 19 * 17 + 5",
            "Answer": 411,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 8 * 6 + 6 + 10 * 3 + 2",
            "Answer": 89,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 16 * 13 + 11 + 16 * 0 + 19",
            "Answer": 242,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 18 * 15 + 0 + 8 * 10 + 4",
            "Answer": 373,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 12 * 16 + 14 + 18 * 17 + 5",
            "Answer": 535,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 17 * 2 + 7 + 16 * 2 + 3",
            "Answer": 88,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 15 * 13 + 5 + 15 * 10 + 18",
            "Answer": 385,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 1 * 13 + 3 + 4 * 6 + 15",
            "Answer": 57,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 19 * 0 + 18 + 4 * 18 + 7",
            "Answer": 116,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 15 * 7 + 12 + 1 * 3 + 18",
            "Answer": 155,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 8 * 0 + 13 + 13 * 9 + 9",
            "Answer": 146,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 18 * 13 + 8 + 17 * 15 + 4",
            "Answer": 510,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 2 * 4 + 15 + 15 * 19 + 16",
            "Answer": 332,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 19 * 15 + 13 + 16 * 18 + 17",
            "Answer": 622,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 8 * 1 + 17 + 17 * 2 + 1",
            "Answer": 62,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 13 * 10 + 6 + 17 * 5 + 18",
            "Answer": 244,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 12 * 10 + 15 + 5 * 8 + 9",
            "Answer": 184,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 6 * 8 + 8 + 10 * 11 + 7",
            "Answer": 192,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 16 * 1 + 6 + 11 * 14 + 6",
            "Answer": 192,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 9 * 18 + 9 + 1 * 16 + 7",
            "Answer": 196,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 9 * 9 + 8 + 1 * 12 + 8",
            "Answer": 120,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 18 * 16 + 3 + 6 * 17 + 17",
            "Answer": 417,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 16 * 19 + 10 + 10 * 8 + 18",
            "Answer": 417,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 2 * 15 + 1 + 11 * 3 + 4",
            "Answer": 73,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 8 * 4 + 18 + 5 * 18 + 1",
            "Answer": 146,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 16 * 17 + 0 + 17 * 12 + 10",
            "Answer": 497,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 7 * 6 + 14 + 0 * 12 + 1",
            "Answer": 60,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 4 * 17 + 14 + 0 * 2 + 6",
            "Answer": 93,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 14 * 3 + 14 + 18 * 0 + 8",
            "Answer": 80,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 2 * 19 + 10 + 10 * 13 + 7",
            "Answer": 194,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 6 * 13 + 2 + 14 * 15 + 12",
            "Answer": 307,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 8 * 4 + 12 + 18 * 4 + 10",
            "Answer": 133,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 8 * 1 + 18 + 2 * 10 + 17",
            "Answer": 76,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 3 * 17 + 9 + 18 * 11 + 8",
            "Answer": 275,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 5 * 10 + 1 + 14 * 1 + 19",
            "Answer": 101,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 7 * 3 + 5 + 18 * 4 + 11",
            "Answer": 116,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 14 * 10 + 16 + 6 * 8 + 10",
            "Answer": 222,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 7 * 4 + 0 + 6 * 13 + 12",
            "Answer": 132,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 7 * 2 + 9 + 9 * 0 + 15",
            "Answer": 39,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 13 * 9 + 14 + 11 * 1 + 6",
            "Answer": 150,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 18 * 0 + 18 + 4 * 0 + 14",
            "Answer": 49,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 1 * 6 + 1 + 7 * 0 + 18",
            "Answer": 25,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 0 * 4 + 15 + 3 * 6 + 3",
            "Answer": 40,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 6 * 13 + 19 + 19 * 10 + 12",
            "Answer": 311,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 4 * 4 + 2 + 11 * 15 + 3",
            "Answer": 192,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 17 * 11 + 13 + 2 * 9 + 5",
            "Answer": 231,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 0 * 17 + 9 + 1 * 8 + 5",
            "Answer": 30,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 13 * 19 + 11 + 14 * 16 + 17",
            "Answer": 510,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 12 * 14 + 15 + 16 * 13 + 3",
            "Answer": 399,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 2 * 11 + 4 + 14 * 8 + 4",
            "Answer": 155,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 12 * 0 + 7 + 9 * 19 + 13",
            "Answer": 199,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 15 * 13 + 19 + 5 * 16 + 11",
            "Answer": 320,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 16 * 7 + 5 + 1 * 6 + 9",
            "Answer": 138,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # * # + #"
        }
    ],
    "# + # + # + # * # + # + #": [
        {
            "Question": "10 + 12 + 1 + 12 * 3 + 14 + 14",
            "Answer": 87,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 19 + 2 + 2 * 9 + 0 + 2",
            "Answer": 52,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 0 + 3 + 2 * 19 + 7 + 11",
            "Answer": 63,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 8 + 10 + 14 * 6 + 8 + 16",
            "Answer": 137,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 18 + 3 + 10 * 7 + 0 + 9",
            "Answer": 115,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 9 + 11 + 18 * 0 + 14 + 19",
            "Answer": 67,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 18 + 5 + 2 * 9 + 5 + 0",
            "Answer": 63,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 0 + 5 + 12 * 7 + 16 + 11",
            "Answer": 116,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 12 + 17 + 0 * 14 + 4 + 15",
            "Answer": 64,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 17 + 11 + 16 * 5 + 3 + 6",
            "Answer": 125,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 9 + 7 + 9 * 0 + 19 + 13",
            "Answer": 48,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 18 + 11 + 18 * 9 + 2 + 1",
            "Answer": 199,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 3 + 8 + 16 * 10 + 19 + 3",
            "Answer": 204,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 0 + 11 + 6 * 4 + 16 + 9",
            "Answer": 74,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 9 + 1 + 13 * 10 + 11 + 9",
            "Answer": 174,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 12 + 12 + 17 * 2 + 17 + 10",
            "Answer": 88,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 6 + 13 + 2 * 13 + 10 + 14",
            "Answer": 79,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 9 + 11 + 12 * 14 + 5 + 1",
            "Answer": 203,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 7 + 4 + 0 * 18 + 0 + 16",
            "Answer": 36,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 19 + 9 + 17 * 8 + 7 + 9",
            "Answer": 198,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 18 + 18 + 9 * 16 + 8 + 7",
            "Answer": 209,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 19 + 10 + 7 * 5 + 11 + 14",
            "Answer": 98,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 8 + 12 + 13 * 8 + 8 + 10",
            "Answer": 150,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 16 + 7 + 0 * 15 + 4 + 14",
            "Answer": 49,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 5 + 3 + 16 * 2 + 14 + 4",
            "Answer": 61,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 10 + 11 + 3 * 8 + 17 + 14",
            "Answer": 93,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 8 + 1 + 15 * 12 + 15 + 10",
            "Answer": 218,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 2 + 0 + 13 * 17 + 11 + 12",
            "Answer": 256,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 6 + 10 + 4 * 3 + 2 + 0",
            "Answer": 30,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 10 + 7 + 5 * 16 + 9 + 7",
            "Answer": 120,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 17 + 10 + 8 * 12 + 11 + 14",
            "Answer": 164,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 12 + 14 + 16 * 6 + 9 + 0",
            "Answer": 142,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 10 + 8 + 8 * 17 + 15 + 6",
            "Answer": 175,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 19 + 4 + 9 * 12 + 9 + 13",
            "Answer": 160,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 7 + 16 + 12 * 0 + 13 + 10",
            "Answer": 48,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 7 + 18 + 7 * 6 + 8 + 6",
            "Answer": 84,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 12 + 0 + 7 * 16 + 7 + 10",
            "Answer": 152,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 13 + 8 + 4 * 8 + 3 + 6",
            "Answer": 68,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 17 + 2 + 3 * 7 + 2 + 7",
            "Answer": 61,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 10 + 19 + 12 * 8 + 3 + 17",
            "Answer": 161,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 14 + 18 + 14 * 10 + 8 + 12",
            "Answer": 192,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 7 + 5 + 5 * 9 + 3 + 13",
            "Answer": 86,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 9 + 13 + 10 * 16 + 6 + 15",
            "Answer": 208,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 11 + 15 + 0 * 19 + 11 + 18",
            "Answer": 64,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 19 + 18 + 14 * 7 + 5 + 15",
            "Answer": 157,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 15 + 10 + 19 * 1 + 17 + 8",
            "Answer": 74,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 17 + 8 + 9 * 19 + 12 + 10",
            "Answer": 225,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 10 + 9 + 18 * 12 + 12 + 3",
            "Answer": 257,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 15 + 13 + 15 * 9 + 9 + 6",
            "Answer": 180,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 18 + 7 + 1 * 15 + 16 + 3",
            "Answer": 67,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 13 + 17 + 4 * 6 + 19 + 0",
            "Answer": 76,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 11 + 13 + 3 * 6 + 1 + 5",
            "Answer": 62,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 4 + 5 + 5 * 16 + 0 + 3",
            "Answer": 96,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 0 + 0 + 13 * 4 + 0 + 3",
            "Answer": 57,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 16 + 6 + 14 * 13 + 12 + 10",
            "Answer": 229,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 19 + 7 + 2 * 10 + 17 + 6",
            "Answer": 76,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 3 + 1 + 5 * 12 + 13 + 19",
            "Answer": 99,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 0 + 18 + 1 * 0 + 18 + 3",
            "Answer": 46,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 15 + 9 + 0 * 4 + 11 + 16",
            "Answer": 55,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 8 + 13 + 17 * 11 + 4 + 14",
            "Answer": 229,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 1 + 14 + 14 * 8 + 1 + 18",
            "Answer": 147,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 18 + 12 + 0 * 11 + 0 + 4",
            "Answer": 53,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 2 + 12 + 16 * 15 + 1 + 6",
            "Answer": 275,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 19 + 0 + 8 * 14 + 19 + 1",
            "Answer": 164,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 18 + 2 + 14 * 1 + 6 + 8",
            "Answer": 48,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 8 + 18 + 15 * 14 + 14 + 11",
            "Answer": 270,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 8 + 4 + 8 * 4 + 14 + 3",
            "Answer": 79,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 9 + 13 + 9 * 5 + 4 + 1",
            "Answer": 91,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 2 + 14 + 12 * 1 + 5 + 12",
            "Answer": 49,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 11 + 2 + 17 * 19 + 1 + 0",
            "Answer": 348,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 15 + 18 + 17 * 6 + 15 + 9",
            "Answer": 162,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 0 + 6 + 10 * 10 + 2 + 5",
            "Answer": 132,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 12 + 17 + 9 * 8 + 9 + 4",
            "Answer": 121,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 10 + 3 + 1 * 4 + 6 + 6",
            "Answer": 45,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 0 + 9 + 7 * 11 + 4 + 0",
            "Answer": 98,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 4 + 14 + 4 * 10 + 11 + 17",
            "Answer": 101,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 14 + 0 + 1 * 19 + 7 + 10",
            "Answer": 68,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 3 + 4 + 16 * 4 + 0 + 3",
            "Answer": 82,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 6 + 7 + 6 * 16 + 18 + 11",
            "Answer": 154,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 7 + 10 + 12 * 0 + 6 + 2",
            "Answer": 37,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 0 + 8 + 4 * 9 + 8 + 16",
            "Answer": 71,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 5 + 1 + 4 * 8 + 13 + 6",
            "Answer": 59,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 3 + 19 + 1 * 1 + 12 + 16",
            "Answer": 62,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 7 + 4 + 12 * 1 + 14 + 10",
            "Answer": 49,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 0 + 10 + 4 * 12 + 1 + 2",
            "Answer": 67,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 15 + 12 + 15 * 5 + 7 + 6",
            "Answer": 127,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 17 + 9 + 8 * 11 + 18 + 5",
            "Answer": 148,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 0 + 14 + 3 * 7 + 9 + 9",
            "Answer": 61,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 14 + 11 + 9 * 7 + 10 + 6",
            "Answer": 121,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 16 + 11 + 6 * 18 + 7 + 16",
            "Answer": 159,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 2 + 15 + 1 * 15 + 16 + 18",
            "Answer": 72,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 16 + 18 + 5 * 18 + 12 + 14",
            "Answer": 166,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 2 + 12 + 19 * 3 + 14 + 16",
            "Answer": 113,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 5 + 17 + 8 * 19 + 5 + 5",
            "Answer": 195,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 11 + 3 + 8 * 19 + 14 + 8",
            "Answer": 196,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 17 + 16 + 13 * 13 + 14 + 15",
            "Answer": 247,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 8 + 19 + 6 * 9 + 8 + 14",
            "Answer": 111,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 3 + 10 + 11 * 17 + 15 + 13",
            "Answer": 235,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 12 + 11 + 15 * 2 + 2 + 1",
            "Answer": 58,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 11 + 1 + 14 * 3 + 9 + 8",
            "Answer": 90,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # + # + #"
        }
    ],
    "# * # + # * # + # * # + #": [
        {
            "Question": "13 * 17 + 17 * 9 + 4 * 18 + 11",
            "Answer": 457,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 17 + 19 * 0 + 7 * 18 + 11",
            "Answer": 324,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 6 + 8 * 1 + 15 * 11 + 3",
            "Answer": 212,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 15 + 10 * 17 + 5 * 12 + 11",
            "Answer": 316,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 12 + 13 * 6 + 5 * 2 + 15",
            "Answer": 199,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 16 + 13 * 14 + 15 * 17 + 10",
            "Answer": 543,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 16 + 8 * 14 + 16 * 10 + 11",
            "Answer": 475,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 3 + 17 * 19 + 18 * 6 + 11",
            "Answer": 463,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 2 + 4 * 14 + 17 * 13 + 12",
            "Answer": 317,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 14 + 0 * 4 + 14 * 6 + 7",
            "Answer": 273,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 1 + 0 * 3 + 15 * 8 + 12",
            "Answer": 150,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 14 + 16 * 5 + 5 * 8 + 17",
            "Answer": 375,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 7 + 4 * 19 + 3 * 17 + 5",
            "Answer": 237,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 12 + 0 * 19 + 11 * 16 + 8",
            "Answer": 256,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 18 + 0 * 0 + 15 * 16 + 14",
            "Answer": 416,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 8 + 13 * 0 + 2 * 7 + 15",
            "Answer": 61,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 8 + 12 * 17 + 6 * 17 + 11",
            "Answer": 429,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 8 + 19 * 5 + 1 * 5 + 11",
            "Answer": 111,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 9 + 2 * 9 + 14 * 11 + 19",
            "Answer": 335,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 19 + 4 * 2 + 12 * 13 + 0",
            "Answer": 335,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 0 + 19 * 16 + 19 * 7 + 13",
            "Answer": 450,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 18 + 6 * 19 + 1 * 15 + 18",
            "Answer": 327,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 8 + 10 * 11 + 6 * 1 + 8",
            "Answer": 228,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 6 + 14 * 7 + 15 * 13 + 10",
            "Answer": 321,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 7 + 9 * 17 + 15 * 8 + 16",
            "Answer": 331,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 10 + 1 * 12 + 10 * 4 + 0",
            "Answer": 112,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 19 + 6 * 7 + 0 * 15 + 0",
            "Answer": 289,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 1 + 14 * 0 + 12 * 6 + 2",
            "Answer": 91,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 12 + 10 * 3 + 18 * 17 + 17",
            "Answer": 389,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 8 + 1 * 14 + 0 * 11 + 6",
            "Answer": 124,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 15 + 15 * 18 + 15 * 4 + 7",
            "Answer": 547,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 17 + 14 * 9 + 7 * 14 + 3",
            "Answer": 448,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 11 + 7 * 18 + 10 * 12 + 1",
            "Answer": 379,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 5 + 19 * 17 + 13 * 5 + 18",
            "Answer": 406,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 6 + 2 * 6 + 16 * 19 + 0",
            "Answer": 394,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 7 + 5 * 10 + 17 * 19 + 5",
            "Answer": 511,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 18 + 12 * 8 + 16 * 14 + 7",
            "Answer": 669,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 12 + 1 * 8 + 7 * 3 + 0",
            "Answer": 53,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 10 + 9 * 0 + 10 * 9 + 11",
            "Answer": 131,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 5 + 12 * 11 + 9 * 4 + 9",
            "Answer": 222,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 3 + 9 * 3 + 9 * 8 + 0",
            "Answer": 102,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 19 + 12 * 8 + 12 * 17 + 10",
            "Answer": 614,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 15 + 6 * 1 + 11 * 5 + 14",
            "Answer": 330,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 14 + 0 * 4 + 4 * 8 + 5",
            "Answer": 79,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 14 + 5 * 19 + 14 * 5 + 6",
            "Answer": 325,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 6 + 17 * 16 + 18 * 18 + 2",
            "Answer": 634,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 2 + 10 * 18 + 10 * 14 + 13",
            "Answer": 363,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 17 + 13 * 2 + 19 * 19 + 16",
            "Answer": 505,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 12 + 3 * 17 + 7 * 8 + 6",
            "Answer": 293,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 18 + 12 * 7 + 19 * 8 + 12",
            "Answer": 320,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 9 + 1 * 2 + 3 * 17 + 8",
            "Answer": 169,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 19 + 3 * 9 + 16 * 8 + 5",
            "Answer": 445,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 8 + 14 * 16 + 8 * 15 + 18",
            "Answer": 394,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 11 + 6 * 2 + 18 * 19 + 2",
            "Answer": 543,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 10 + 11 * 5 + 16 * 12 + 9",
            "Answer": 436,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 7 + 11 * 13 + 2 * 9 + 8",
            "Answer": 169,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 1 + 11 * 7 + 0 * 8 + 17",
            "Answer": 95,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 5 + 16 * 5 + 14 * 8 + 8",
            "Answer": 275,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 12 + 17 * 6 + 10 * 16 + 19",
            "Answer": 377,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 10 + 11 * 18 + 4 * 9 + 14",
            "Answer": 328,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 3 + 18 * 12 + 11 * 11 + 7",
            "Answer": 368,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 8 + 8 * 17 + 17 * 19 + 17",
            "Answer": 588,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 1 + 5 * 0 + 1 * 4 + 5",
            "Answer": 11,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 11 + 2 * 13 + 4 * 4 + 10",
            "Answer": 173,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 19 + 2 * 10 + 18 * 18 + 19",
            "Answer": 572,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 12 + 1 * 14 + 6 * 2 + 3",
            "Answer": 113,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 0 + 11 * 11 + 0 * 14 + 11",
            "Answer": 132,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 11 + 7 * 4 + 16 * 7 + 5",
            "Answer": 222,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 8 + 0 * 3 + 16 * 5 + 8",
            "Answer": 176,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 19 + 1 * 6 + 17 * 4 + 17",
            "Answer": 338,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 19 + 17 * 19 + 4 * 16 + 15",
            "Answer": 668,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 1 + 8 * 1 + 7 * 8 + 9",
            "Answer": 91,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 10 + 2 * 3 + 17 * 13 + 12",
            "Answer": 319,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 11 + 7 * 0 + 7 * 8 + 7",
            "Answer": 96,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 17 + 11 * 6 + 17 * 9 + 3",
            "Answer": 392,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 15 + 5 * 12 + 9 * 0 + 19",
            "Answer": 184,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 17 + 5 * 10 + 18 * 4 + 0",
            "Answer": 343,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 12 + 12 * 8 + 19 * 17 + 15",
            "Answer": 638,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 10 + 1 * 3 + 17 * 0 + 2",
            "Answer": 85,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 1 + 6 * 11 + 18 * 0 + 1",
            "Answer": 68,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 6 + 13 * 4 + 10 * 17 + 15",
            "Answer": 285,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 10 + 9 * 3 + 0 * 13 + 0",
            "Answer": 87,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 4 + 4 * 5 + 7 * 14 + 0",
            "Answer": 150,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 14 + 4 * 15 + 7 * 1 + 0",
            "Answer": 249,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 5 + 17 * 9 + 6 * 11 + 11",
            "Answer": 235,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 3 + 5 * 7 + 1 * 15 + 18",
            "Answer": 74,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 0 + 14 * 5 + 10 * 17 + 10",
            "Answer": 250,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 10 + 1 * 6 + 12 * 9 + 4",
            "Answer": 208,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 13 + 7 * 16 + 7 * 8 + 19",
            "Answer": 395,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 11 + 15 * 18 + 15 * 6 + 16",
            "Answer": 585,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 14 + 6 * 3 + 16 * 6 + 16",
            "Answer": 172,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 1 + 18 * 6 + 17 * 12 + 1",
            "Answer": 319,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 11 + 5 * 11 + 7 * 7 + 11",
            "Answer": 137,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 4 + 6 * 5 + 17 * 10 + 1",
            "Answer": 277,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 2 + 2 * 8 + 16 * 4 + 12",
            "Answer": 126,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 9 + 6 * 0 + 19 * 19 + 12",
            "Answer": 526,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 3 + 1 * 14 + 16 * 4 + 13",
            "Answer": 97,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 19 + 5 * 14 + 12 * 2 + 8",
            "Answer": 387,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 6 + 12 * 3 + 17 * 5 + 0",
            "Answer": 175,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 9 + 11 * 16 + 4 * 4 + 11",
            "Answer": 347,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # * # + #"
        }
    ],
    "# * # * # * # + # * # * #": [
        {
            "Question": "17 * 11 * 7 * 15 + 6 * 0 * 9",
            "Answer": 19635,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 15 * 12 * 14 + 5 * 5 * 17",
            "Answer": 25625,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 9 * 16 * 15 + 15 * 10 * 0",
            "Answer": 30240,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 0 * 9 * 12 + 11 * 4 * 9",
            "Answer": 396,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 8 * 4 * 8 + 7 * 19 * 3",
            "Answer": 2959,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 19 * 16 * 0 + 18 * 16 * 10",
            "Answer": 2880,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 15 * 0 * 5 + 19 * 10 * 13",
            "Answer": 2470,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 2 * 3 * 18 + 8 * 14 * 8",
            "Answer": 1004,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 5 * 16 * 14 + 13 * 18 * 11",
            "Answer": 20494,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 4 * 5 * 2 + 2 * 9 * 19",
            "Answer": 702,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 15 * 15 * 0 + 0 * 7 * 17",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 15 * 18 * 4 + 16 * 3 * 9",
            "Answer": 1512,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 16 * 3 * 10 + 14 * 11 * 13",
            "Answer": 2962,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 9 * 1 * 13 + 1 * 2 * 7",
            "Answer": 1535,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 9 * 19 * 11 + 12 * 18 * 16",
            "Answer": 3456,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 0 * 9 * 8 + 14 * 18 * 2",
            "Answer": 504,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 6 * 18 * 9 + 11 * 16 * 14",
            "Answer": 9268,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 9 * 18 * 17 + 1 * 17 * 3",
            "Answer": 2805,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 17 * 12 * 11 + 1 * 2 * 1",
            "Answer": 31418,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 9 * 15 * 8 + 18 * 6 * 5",
            "Answer": 18900,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 8 * 13 * 8 + 0 * 15 * 8",
            "Answer": 4992,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 4 * 8 * 12 + 15 * 8 * 13",
            "Answer": 2328,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 9 * 13 * 8 + 1 * 12 * 0",
            "Answer": 1872,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 16 * 6 * 11 + 15 * 0 * 5",
            "Answer": 7392,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 6 * 1 * 5 + 9 * 17 * 17",
            "Answer": 2871,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 11 * 3 * 2 + 17 * 11 * 16",
            "Answer": 3388,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 16 * 7 * 10 + 3 * 5 * 1",
            "Answer": 3375,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 7 * 5 * 3 + 7 * 7 * 11",
            "Answer": 1274,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 0 * 14 * 17 + 15 * 3 * 13",
            "Answer": 585,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 9 * 14 * 11 + 4 * 12 * 12",
            "Answer": 24138,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 13 * 9 * 9 + 9 * 4 * 4",
            "Answer": 4356,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 3 * 4 * 15 + 3 * 15 * 5",
            "Answer": 3465,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 5 * 0 * 8 + 6 * 18 * 18",
            "Answer": 1944,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 15 * 9 * 12 + 11 * 5 * 3",
            "Answer": 19605,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 3 * 7 * 7 + 4 * 7 * 13",
            "Answer": 2569,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 12 * 17 * 12 + 9 * 19 * 3",
            "Answer": 17649,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 14 * 17 * 1 + 6 * 10 * 17",
            "Answer": 3876,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 16 * 16 * 1 + 2 * 14 * 11",
            "Answer": 308,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 15 * 11 * 0 + 0 * 11 * 11",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 8 * 14 * 19 + 11 * 15 * 8",
            "Answer": 7704,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 10 * 1 * 2 + 12 * 9 * 17",
            "Answer": 1956,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 19 * 14 * 1 + 18 * 10 * 9",
            "Answer": 4812,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 11 * 9 * 13 + 7 * 18 * 19",
            "Answer": 3681,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 15 * 18 * 6 + 1 * 4 * 6",
            "Answer": 16224,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 0 * 10 * 1 + 1 * 4 * 6",
            "Answer": 24,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 0 * 8 * 8 + 2 * 5 * 2",
            "Answer": 20,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 11 * 18 * 4 + 1 * 5 * 6",
            "Answer": 6366,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 1 * 7 * 9 + 9 * 6 * 0",
            "Answer": 630,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 17 * 13 * 11 + 0 * 7 * 11",
            "Answer": 17017,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 18 * 14 * 13 + 2 * 4 * 15",
            "Answer": 42708,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 19 * 13 * 10 + 5 * 14 * 1",
            "Answer": 5010,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 6 * 4 * 18 + 1 * 2 * 6",
            "Answer": 6492,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 0 * 2 * 2 + 16 * 19 * 18",
            "Answer": 5472,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 4 * 13 * 6 + 15 * 15 * 8",
            "Answer": 3672,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 11 * 11 * 18 + 7 * 13 * 8",
            "Answer": 29042,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 0 * 10 * 17 + 15 * 17 * 11",
            "Answer": 2805,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 12 * 6 * 9 + 19 * 14 * 4",
            "Answer": 3656,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 4 * 18 * 16 + 7 * 13 * 6",
            "Answer": 14370,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 10 * 7 * 10 + 8 * 10 * 15",
            "Answer": 1200,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 18 * 12 * 11 + 10 * 10 * 1",
            "Answer": 100,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 0 * 11 * 19 + 17 * 12 * 6",
            "Answer": 1224,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 17 * 16 * 14 + 11 * 19 * 17",
            "Answer": 68289,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 17 * 8 * 3 + 16 * 12 * 2",
            "Answer": 3240,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 16 * 0 * 5 + 18 * 12 * 14",
            "Answer": 3024,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 5 * 15 * 8 + 17 * 14 * 0",
            "Answer": 0,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 14 * 7 * 14 + 1 * 10 * 0",
            "Answer": 12348,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 16 * 18 * 1 + 16 * 18 * 8",
            "Answer": 5184,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 3 * 0 * 0 + 12 * 17 * 10",
            "Answer": 2040,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 13 * 15 * 17 + 0 * 16 * 0",
            "Answer": 29835,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 17 * 18 * 19 + 15 * 11 * 19",
            "Answer": 61275,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 11 * 14 * 17 + 6 * 3 * 11",
            "Answer": 8052,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 16 * 6 * 0 + 13 * 2 * 19",
            "Answer": 494,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 3 * 0 * 4 + 19 * 6 * 4",
            "Answer": 456,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 3 * 10 * 6 + 13 * 8 * 9",
            "Answer": 3456,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 14 * 5 * 16 + 12 * 15 * 10",
            "Answer": 17480,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 19 * 1 * 0 + 8 * 8 * 5",
            "Answer": 320,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 1 * 16 * 7 + 7 * 4 * 18",
            "Answer": 1736,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 6 * 12 * 3 + 15 * 16 * 1",
            "Answer": 672,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 12 * 14 * 11 + 19 * 10 * 19",
            "Answer": 9154,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 0 * 3 * 1 + 16 * 4 * 2",
            "Answer": 128,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 16 * 19 * 7 + 18 * 11 * 6",
            "Answer": 39492,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 12 * 8 * 9 + 10 * 5 * 3",
            "Answer": 1878,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 11 * 17 * 18 + 16 * 8 * 12",
            "Answer": 15000,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 17 * 17 * 19 + 2 * 4 * 18",
            "Answer": 93491,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 0 * 11 * 18 + 4 * 18 * 18",
            "Answer": 1296,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 19 * 12 * 3 + 13 * 19 * 0",
            "Answer": 11628,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 6 * 5 * 17 + 4 * 3 * 1",
            "Answer": 2562,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 6 * 11 * 13 + 0 * 16 * 18",
            "Answer": 3432,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 0 * 10 * 17 + 12 * 2 * 13",
            "Answer": 312,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 5 * 10 * 1 + 12 * 2 * 14",
            "Answer": 1136,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 16 * 18 * 6 + 5 * 2 * 4",
            "Answer": 20776,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 2 * 19 * 18 + 15 * 19 * 12",
            "Answer": 15048,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 12 * 10 * 16 + 6 * 16 * 3",
            "Answer": 25248,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 1 * 1 * 4 + 12 * 19 * 13",
            "Answer": 2976,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 0 * 17 * 2 + 15 * 7 * 4",
            "Answer": 420,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 19 * 15 * 14 + 6 * 5 * 10",
            "Answer": 52170,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 16 * 2 * 13 + 9 * 15 * 15",
            "Answer": 4105,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 19 * 11 * 4 + 1 * 6 * 8",
            "Answer": 1720,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 8 * 11 * 8 + 13 * 1 * 19",
            "Answer": 12215,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 13 * 11 * 19 + 6 * 1 * 12",
            "Answer": 51695,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # * #"
        }
    ],
    "# + # * # + # + # + # + #": [
        {
            "Question": "8 + 12 * 14 + 15 + 19 + 1 + 17",
            "Answer": 228,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 14 * 12 + 2 + 13 + 12 + 13",
            "Answer": 222,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 0 * 12 + 13 + 15 + 0 + 5",
            "Answer": 52,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 4 * 8 + 8 + 2 + 5 + 11",
            "Answer": 59,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 5 * 14 + 15 + 12 + 0 + 5",
            "Answer": 110,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 11 * 8 + 9 + 12 + 14 + 4",
            "Answer": 145,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 15 * 1 + 8 + 14 + 3 + 6",
            "Answer": 46,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 16 * 9 + 5 + 7 + 12 + 5",
            "Answer": 188,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 10 * 4 + 0 + 7 + 8 + 8",
            "Answer": 76,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 6 * 11 + 0 + 13 + 15 + 15",
            "Answer": 113,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 13 * 13 + 6 + 18 + 19 + 10",
            "Answer": 234,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 9 * 18 + 9 + 18 + 1 + 0",
            "Answer": 192,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 14 * 13 + 10 + 15 + 7 + 7",
            "Answer": 230,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 17 * 18 + 10 + 17 + 13 + 19",
            "Answer": 365,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 4 * 0 + 0 + 1 + 17 + 18",
            "Answer": 42,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 17 * 6 + 14 + 4 + 8 + 9",
            "Answer": 151,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 9 * 14 + 9 + 17 + 16 + 5",
            "Answer": 180,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 18 * 6 + 4 + 5 + 7 + 15",
            "Answer": 149,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 4 * 17 + 4 + 3 + 19 + 18",
            "Answer": 118,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 2 * 7 + 12 + 19 + 1 + 12",
            "Answer": 65,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 2 * 0 + 7 + 19 + 14 + 3",
            "Answer": 54,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 15 * 15 + 4 + 8 + 16 + 8",
            "Answer": 279,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 8 * 6 + 11 + 0 + 6 + 18",
            "Answer": 98,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 19 * 16 + 9 + 4 + 6 + 5",
            "Answer": 330,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 15 * 8 + 18 + 19 + 8 + 5",
            "Answer": 185,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 17 * 2 + 7 + 14 + 11 + 15",
            "Answer": 83,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 8 * 8 + 19 + 12 + 18 + 6",
            "Answer": 121,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 4 * 0 + 10 + 17 + 17 + 6",
            "Answer": 51,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 8 * 5 + 16 + 14 + 12 + 5",
            "Answer": 89,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 11 * 13 + 4 + 6 + 2 + 13",
            "Answer": 176,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 12 * 2 + 1 + 18 + 6 + 3",
            "Answer": 70,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 0 * 6 + 7 + 10 + 0 + 1",
            "Answer": 29,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 9 * 9 + 3 + 5 + 8 + 4",
            "Answer": 108,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 14 * 9 + 14 + 3 + 14 + 13",
            "Answer": 182,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 16 * 1 + 7 + 10 + 19 + 1",
            "Answer": 70,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 10 * 18 + 16 + 7 + 6 + 12",
            "Answer": 240,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 1 * 18 + 3 + 14 + 2 + 10",
            "Answer": 63,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 0 * 14 + 4 + 1 + 8 + 9",
            "Answer": 41,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 11 * 2 + 10 + 7 + 13 + 7",
            "Answer": 70,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 13 * 1 + 15 + 0 + 11 + 19",
            "Answer": 69,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 12 * 11 + 13 + 5 + 19 + 12",
            "Answer": 184,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 13 * 17 + 6 + 12 + 16 + 16",
            "Answer": 279,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 16 * 4 + 13 + 9 + 4 + 16",
            "Answer": 118,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 12 * 10 + 0 + 1 + 0 + 3",
            "Answer": 140,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 10 * 8 + 7 + 9 + 4 + 13",
            "Answer": 127,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 1 * 7 + 19 + 10 + 11 + 16",
            "Answer": 66,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 0 * 16 + 3 + 11 + 9 + 12",
            "Answer": 44,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 11 * 19 + 18 + 6 + 13 + 13",
            "Answer": 278,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 15 * 0 + 11 + 7 + 13 + 17",
            "Answer": 59,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 16 * 18 + 3 + 9 + 18 + 5",
            "Answer": 340,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 4 * 16 + 4 + 14 + 3 + 3",
            "Answer": 104,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 18 * 8 + 3 + 12 + 16 + 17",
            "Answer": 200,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 6 * 19 + 18 + 2 + 16 + 0",
            "Answer": 154,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 8 * 17 + 11 + 1 + 9 + 16",
            "Answer": 182,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 14 * 5 + 15 + 11 + 9 + 3",
            "Answer": 121,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 7 * 0 + 17 + 9 + 1 + 12",
            "Answer": 50,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 16 * 18 + 9 + 15 + 17 + 12",
            "Answer": 359,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 17 * 12 + 7 + 16 + 12 + 9",
            "Answer": 265,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 16 * 16 + 1 + 17 + 3 + 11",
            "Answer": 288,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 13 * 9 + 0 + 15 + 16 + 17",
            "Answer": 177,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 16 * 19 + 2 + 10 + 17 + 19",
            "Answer": 359,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 12 * 11 + 10 + 8 + 15 + 1",
            "Answer": 171,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 7 * 17 + 4 + 5 + 12 + 5",
            "Answer": 155,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 8 * 16 + 9 + 10 + 17 + 11",
            "Answer": 185,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 17 * 5 + 10 + 4 + 12 + 1",
            "Answer": 113,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 14 * 14 + 5 + 18 + 7 + 17",
            "Answer": 259,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 1 * 5 + 6 + 19 + 12 + 12",
            "Answer": 57,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 10 * 0 + 9 + 13 + 10 + 12",
            "Answer": 49,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 1 * 16 + 3 + 3 + 17 + 17",
            "Answer": 73,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 10 * 5 + 14 + 1 + 15 + 17",
            "Answer": 98,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 3 * 2 + 13 + 17 + 2 + 14",
            "Answer": 70,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 0 * 9 + 12 + 12 + 6 + 18",
            "Answer": 55,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 4 * 6 + 10 + 18 + 8 + 11",
            "Answer": 89,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 12 * 7 + 16 + 10 + 18 + 13",
            "Answer": 159,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 0 * 13 + 9 + 6 + 9 + 17",
            "Answer": 60,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 11 * 6 + 12 + 6 + 9 + 17",
            "Answer": 128,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 10 * 3 + 19 + 1 + 6 + 14",
            "Answer": 73,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 9 * 8 + 19 + 4 + 2 + 0",
            "Answer": 109,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 1 * 1 + 13 + 7 + 1 + 12",
            "Answer": 39,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 10 * 4 + 15 + 5 + 9 + 13",
            "Answer": 85,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 5 * 14 + 19 + 13 + 14 + 2",
            "Answer": 135,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 3 * 19 + 4 + 15 + 8 + 9",
            "Answer": 93,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 0 * 7 + 14 + 3 + 18 + 9",
            "Answer": 48,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 15 * 8 + 9 + 6 + 12 + 2",
            "Answer": 150,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 9 * 11 + 8 + 16 + 15 + 18",
            "Answer": 157,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 0 * 17 + 14 + 2 + 5 + 3",
            "Answer": 27,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 6 * 2 + 19 + 1 + 15 + 6",
            "Answer": 71,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 10 * 2 + 9 + 19 + 5 + 8",
            "Answer": 61,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 6 * 13 + 6 + 4 + 10 + 5",
            "Answer": 106,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 7 * 17 + 19 + 5 + 4 + 0",
            "Answer": 156,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 2 * 4 + 10 + 17 + 1 + 8",
            "Answer": 44,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 0 * 14 + 13 + 10 + 18 + 10",
            "Answer": 62,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 16 * 0 + 2 + 1 + 7 + 17",
            "Answer": 37,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 15 * 19 + 17 + 1 + 8 + 15",
            "Answer": 337,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 8 * 16 + 10 + 0 + 6 + 1",
            "Answer": 146,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 19 * 9 + 12 + 8 + 12 + 9",
            "Answer": 229,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 4 * 8 + 15 + 9 + 5 + 2",
            "Answer": 76,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 5 * 6 + 11 + 3 + 6 + 17",
            "Answer": 84,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 0 * 16 + 10 + 3 + 5 + 8",
            "Answer": 41,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 1 * 13 + 14 + 16 + 1 + 10",
            "Answer": 67,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # + # + # + #"
        }
    ],
    "# + # * # + # * # * # + #": [
        {
            "Question": "4 + 16 * 13 + 15 * 18 * 7 + 0",
            "Answer": 2102,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 2 * 4 + 12 * 0 * 15 + 12",
            "Answer": 22,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 14 * 14 + 4 * 19 * 13 + 6",
            "Answer": 1201,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 0 * 8 + 17 * 13 * 19 + 16",
            "Answer": 4229,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 14 * 12 + 10 * 2 * 1 + 11",
            "Answer": 218,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 10 * 1 + 8 * 13 * 6 + 1",
            "Answer": 642,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 14 * 14 + 16 * 7 * 4 + 16",
            "Answer": 671,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 3 * 6 + 11 * 7 * 16 + 19",
            "Answer": 1274,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 17 * 2 + 18 * 4 * 4 + 2",
            "Answer": 335,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 0 * 1 + 5 * 15 * 19 + 5",
            "Answer": 1442,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 10 * 5 + 17 * 2 * 4 + 5",
            "Answer": 194,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 13 * 13 + 17 * 0 * 15 + 6",
            "Answer": 193,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 18 * 2 + 8 * 9 * 11 + 14",
            "Answer": 859,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 16 * 16 + 10 * 10 * 10 + 13",
            "Answer": 1282,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 18 * 11 + 10 * 14 * 8 + 1",
            "Answer": 1326,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 13 * 19 + 15 * 19 * 9 + 16",
            "Answer": 2834,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 15 * 5 + 16 * 14 * 13 + 14",
            "Answer": 3018,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 6 * 1 + 12 * 18 * 3 + 8",
            "Answer": 672,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 2 * 11 + 10 * 4 * 2 + 12",
            "Answer": 119,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 7 * 11 + 11 * 14 * 6 + 15",
            "Answer": 1025,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 0 * 8 + 8 * 11 * 11 + 13",
            "Answer": 997,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 17 * 5 + 9 * 0 * 18 + 4",
            "Answer": 105,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 9 * 17 + 15 * 15 * 3 + 10",
            "Answer": 848,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 4 * 1 + 1 * 2 * 19 + 5",
            "Answer": 57,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 15 * 14 + 16 * 12 * 5 + 3",
            "Answer": 1173,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 16 * 12 + 17 * 2 * 19 + 10",
            "Answer": 866,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 1 * 0 + 6 * 6 * 4 + 15",
            "Answer": 163,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 10 * 18 + 17 * 12 * 15 + 10",
            "Answer": 3250,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 7 * 7 + 16 * 18 * 9 + 3",
            "Answer": 2651,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 14 * 6 + 3 * 8 * 16 + 13",
            "Answer": 482,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 5 * 15 + 1 * 0 * 7 + 19",
            "Answer": 109,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 1 * 15 + 12 * 7 * 11 + 8",
            "Answer": 951,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 14 * 19 + 19 * 8 * 0 + 11",
            "Answer": 290,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 3 * 4 + 4 * 4 * 9 + 13",
            "Answer": 185,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 10 * 15 + 11 * 0 * 1 + 10",
            "Answer": 168,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 3 * 17 + 5 * 0 * 8 + 17",
            "Answer": 78,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 3 * 6 + 0 * 18 * 18 + 8",
            "Answer": 37,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 15 * 10 + 2 * 14 * 4 + 4",
            "Answer": 272,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 16 * 4 + 5 * 11 * 11 + 10",
            "Answer": 684,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 6 * 15 + 3 * 11 * 2 + 1",
            "Answer": 159,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 18 * 4 + 10 * 2 * 7 + 14",
            "Answer": 227,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 8 * 3 + 5 * 17 * 12 + 15",
            "Answer": 1063,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 1 * 5 + 17 * 15 * 6 + 19",
            "Answer": 1573,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 6 * 16 + 6 * 0 * 5 + 10",
            "Answer": 107,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 15 * 7 + 9 * 9 * 18 + 6",
            "Answer": 1571,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 6 * 18 + 13 * 10 * 18 + 17",
            "Answer": 2470,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 14 * 2 + 4 * 13 * 18 + 12",
            "Answer": 978,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 9 * 12 + 9 * 2 * 3 + 11",
            "Answer": 179,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 10 * 11 + 9 * 16 * 0 + 17",
            "Answer": 142,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 8 * 12 + 1 * 7 * 9 + 0",
            "Answer": 161,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 6 * 18 + 16 * 17 * 19 + 0",
            "Answer": 5291,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 14 * 1 + 10 * 10 * 18 + 3",
            "Answer": 1824,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 19 * 14 + 17 * 18 * 3 + 19",
            "Answer": 1214,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 17 * 3 + 14 * 3 * 8 + 12",
            "Answer": 410,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 19 * 7 + 18 * 15 * 10 + 5",
            "Answer": 2842,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 18 * 5 + 11 * 0 * 8 + 5",
            "Answer": 114,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 3 * 15 + 5 * 16 * 15 + 4",
            "Answer": 1257,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 19 * 5 + 14 * 14 * 7 + 14",
            "Answer": 1491,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 8 * 12 + 13 * 10 * 1 + 12",
            "Answer": 254,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 3 * 17 + 7 * 12 * 16 + 12",
            "Answer": 1422,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 4 * 5 + 18 * 17 * 0 + 6",
            "Answer": 41,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 12 * 12 + 2 * 14 * 4 + 6",
            "Answer": 267,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 1 * 3 + 15 * 12 * 5 + 2",
            "Answer": 919,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 2 * 8 + 6 * 18 * 7 + 0",
            "Answer": 786,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 4 * 15 + 18 * 1 * 3 + 19",
            "Answer": 145,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 3 * 19 + 0 * 0 * 12 + 7",
            "Answer": 71,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 13 * 5 + 19 * 14 * 7 + 12",
            "Answer": 1958,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 3 * 17 + 0 * 15 * 9 + 1",
            "Answer": 60,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 6 * 16 + 1 * 18 * 13 + 18",
            "Answer": 364,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 16 * 1 + 0 * 9 * 5 + 5",
            "Answer": 34,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 4 * 6 + 10 * 17 * 1 + 16",
            "Answer": 224,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 12 * 1 + 2 * 1 * 6 + 16",
            "Answer": 47,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 7 * 14 + 0 * 4 * 1 + 1",
            "Answer": 118,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 15 * 17 + 19 * 7 * 8 + 16",
            "Answer": 1340,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 0 * 10 + 8 * 7 * 2 + 9",
            "Answer": 135,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 13 * 10 + 16 * 9 * 8 + 4",
            "Answer": 1296,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 19 * 9 + 6 * 1 * 13 + 18",
            "Answer": 267,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 2 * 16 + 8 * 17 * 12 + 8",
            "Answer": 1690,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 17 * 19 + 15 * 14 * 2 + 5",
            "Answer": 748,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 10 * 15 + 10 * 15 * 0 + 0",
            "Answer": 157,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 10 * 5 + 0 * 7 * 12 + 10",
            "Answer": 79,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 12 * 5 + 9 * 17 * 1 + 2",
            "Answer": 219,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 3 * 19 + 1 * 6 * 17 + 14",
            "Answer": 174,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 6 * 5 + 6 * 7 * 7 + 0",
            "Answer": 333,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 0 * 13 + 13 * 0 * 11 + 14",
            "Answer": 16,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 11 * 19 + 13 * 3 * 12 + 15",
            "Answer": 693,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 2 * 18 + 16 * 2 * 7 + 19",
            "Answer": 284,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 13 * 19 + 5 * 0 * 19 + 18",
            "Answer": 277,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 14 * 17 + 0 * 1 * 13 + 5",
            "Answer": 247,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 0 * 8 + 18 * 1 * 3 + 8",
            "Answer": 78,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 15 * 10 + 5 * 9 * 0 + 18",
            "Answer": 187,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 11 * 0 + 1 * 13 * 16 + 17",
            "Answer": 237,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 15 * 15 + 19 * 11 * 17 + 2",
            "Answer": 3798,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 19 * 17 + 6 * 16 * 9 + 15",
            "Answer": 1205,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 14 * 11 + 1 * 18 * 12 + 8",
            "Answer": 383,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 15 * 15 + 19 * 14 * 11 + 10",
            "Answer": 3178,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 2 * 12 + 16 * 10 * 19 + 11",
            "Answer": 3088,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 4 * 2 + 12 * 7 * 15 + 14",
            "Answer": 1297,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 11 * 15 + 0 * 12 * 15 + 6",
            "Answer": 179,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 9 * 19 + 13 * 16 * 18 + 13",
            "Answer": 3932,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # + #"
        }
    ],
    "# + # + # * # + # * # + #": [
        {
            "Question": "19 + 14 + 16 * 3 + 16 * 10 + 15",
            "Answer": 256,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 4 + 3 * 16 + 7 * 4 + 9",
            "Answer": 102,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 5 + 5 * 15 + 12 * 12 + 13",
            "Answer": 242,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 10 + 15 * 14 + 9 * 16 + 7",
            "Answer": 389,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 5 + 6 * 18 + 18 * 2 + 6",
            "Answer": 169,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 11 + 7 * 1 + 17 * 9 + 16",
            "Answer": 205,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 8 + 2 * 19 + 8 * 2 + 14",
            "Answer": 91,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 13 + 4 * 3 + 14 * 3 + 15",
            "Answer": 94,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 9 + 15 * 11 + 7 * 16 + 19",
            "Answer": 316,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 11 + 17 * 12 + 0 * 5 + 6",
            "Answer": 236,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 16 + 19 * 19 + 13 * 14 + 1",
            "Answer": 574,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 3 + 10 * 1 + 1 * 14 + 3",
            "Answer": 36,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 8 + 11 * 3 + 2 * 9 + 13",
            "Answer": 83,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 12 + 18 * 7 + 8 * 14 + 2",
            "Answer": 256,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 3 + 7 * 4 + 16 * 3 + 4",
            "Answer": 97,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 12 + 9 * 17 + 1 * 13 + 17",
            "Answer": 208,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 10 + 10 * 8 + 1 * 16 + 6",
            "Answer": 127,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 13 + 2 * 14 + 9 * 9 + 10",
            "Answer": 140,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 4 + 19 * 5 + 15 * 5 + 5",
            "Answer": 180,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 4 + 4 * 0 + 11 * 12 + 9",
            "Answer": 157,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 5 + 2 * 14 + 6 * 5 + 10",
            "Answer": 75,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 10 + 2 * 17 + 12 * 12 + 8",
            "Answer": 207,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 8 + 14 * 0 + 0 * 18 + 19",
            "Answer": 27,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 17 + 16 * 2 + 5 * 3 + 6",
            "Answer": 72,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 5 + 2 * 16 + 17 * 3 + 7",
            "Answer": 100,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 3 + 15 * 4 + 13 * 7 + 13",
            "Answer": 173,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 12 + 9 * 16 + 10 * 18 + 13",
            "Answer": 363,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 10 + 5 * 12 + 3 * 4 + 3",
            "Answer": 85,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 10 + 7 * 18 + 0 * 5 + 12",
            "Answer": 157,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 1 + 18 * 3 + 6 * 19 + 17",
            "Answer": 187,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 15 + 12 * 1 + 19 * 5 + 3",
            "Answer": 127,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 8 + 3 * 17 + 17 * 19 + 4",
            "Answer": 396,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 13 + 1 * 4 + 4 * 7 + 15",
            "Answer": 69,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 7 + 12 * 7 + 6 * 14 + 0",
            "Answer": 181,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 17 + 14 * 5 + 13 * 7 + 6",
            "Answer": 203,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 8 + 5 * 2 + 5 * 14 + 7",
            "Answer": 108,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 14 + 5 * 9 + 2 * 6 + 14",
            "Answer": 94,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 8 + 11 * 1 + 12 * 2 + 16",
            "Answer": 61,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 18 + 4 * 0 + 11 * 0 + 8",
            "Answer": 45,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 14 + 19 * 13 + 12 * 6 + 1",
            "Answer": 350,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 19 + 11 * 6 + 5 * 7 + 8",
            "Answer": 137,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 4 + 19 * 4 + 14 * 12 + 8",
            "Answer": 259,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 7 + 2 * 15 + 13 * 12 + 1",
            "Answer": 196,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 0 + 10 * 3 + 7 * 12 + 8",
            "Answer": 123,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 1 + 7 * 19 + 6 * 8 + 14",
            "Answer": 206,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 0 + 4 * 10 + 13 * 8 + 6",
            "Answer": 169,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 10 + 11 * 16 + 7 * 13 + 17",
            "Answer": 308,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 5 + 16 * 17 + 0 * 17 + 4",
            "Answer": 294,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 19 + 17 * 1 + 6 * 2 + 18",
            "Answer": 70,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 0 + 11 * 12 + 4 * 13 + 15",
            "Answer": 216,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 16 + 6 * 19 + 19 * 15 + 6",
            "Answer": 429,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 10 + 1 * 16 + 11 * 12 + 5",
            "Answer": 175,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 15 + 5 * 6 + 18 * 15 + 4",
            "Answer": 319,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 18 + 4 * 16 + 6 * 4 + 2",
            "Answer": 121,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 11 + 12 * 9 + 15 * 10 + 3",
            "Answer": 276,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 2 + 9 * 1 + 11 * 5 + 13",
            "Answer": 86,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 15 + 6 * 3 + 1 * 3 + 1",
            "Answer": 46,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 14 + 18 * 18 + 2 * 1 + 15",
            "Answer": 363,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 9 + 9 * 16 + 11 * 11 + 3",
            "Answer": 289,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 13 + 0 * 17 + 10 * 4 + 19",
            "Answer": 90,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 14 + 9 * 9 + 1 * 2 + 18",
            "Answer": 134,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 19 + 15 * 0 + 17 * 10 + 3",
            "Answer": 195,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 1 + 12 * 3 + 11 * 4 + 6",
            "Answer": 87,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 1 + 6 * 6 + 15 * 5 + 7",
            "Answer": 123,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 17 + 13 * 14 + 3 * 0 + 12",
            "Answer": 220,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 13 + 16 * 17 + 4 * 18 + 11",
            "Answer": 375,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 0 + 0 * 6 + 13 * 3 + 4",
            "Answer": 53,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 19 + 9 * 1 + 11 * 15 + 17",
            "Answer": 223,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 3 + 6 * 15 + 18 * 7 + 9",
            "Answer": 229,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 12 + 17 * 14 + 5 * 8 + 19",
            "Answer": 327,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 11 + 12 * 2 + 10 * 12 + 16",
            "Answer": 174,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 10 + 13 * 4 + 10 * 12 + 17",
            "Answer": 204,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 18 + 4 * 18 + 13 * 14 + 10",
            "Answer": 300,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 19 + 18 * 9 + 12 * 18 + 8",
            "Answer": 406,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 4 + 18 * 13 + 17 * 17 + 2",
            "Answer": 544,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 2 + 15 * 17 + 1 * 12 + 18",
            "Answer": 305,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 19 + 2 * 9 + 4 * 16 + 19",
            "Answer": 133,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 3 + 17 * 10 + 11 * 15 + 9",
            "Answer": 366,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 3 + 13 * 6 + 6 * 19 + 0",
            "Answer": 208,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 4 + 4 * 6 + 13 * 16 + 15",
            "Answer": 252,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 18 + 13 * 19 + 2 * 12 + 13",
            "Answer": 317,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 6 + 1 * 12 + 15 * 7 + 17",
            "Answer": 157,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 11 + 3 * 0 + 12 * 16 + 17",
            "Answer": 235,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 16 + 2 * 13 + 2 * 15 + 0",
            "Answer": 75,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 9 + 18 * 17 + 15 * 19 + 17",
            "Answer": 628,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 12 + 11 * 18 + 2 * 19 + 14",
            "Answer": 268,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 13 + 15 * 8 + 12 * 19 + 6",
            "Answer": 383,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 0 + 0 * 13 + 12 * 12 + 19",
            "Answer": 163,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 19 + 12 * 9 + 16 * 1 + 13",
            "Answer": 167,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 19 + 10 * 18 + 18 * 2 + 5",
            "Answer": 242,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 15 + 2 * 19 + 9 * 10 + 4",
            "Answer": 165,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 16 + 12 * 14 + 19 * 19 + 4",
            "Answer": 562,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 8 + 10 * 7 + 12 * 2 + 9",
            "Answer": 111,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 14 + 11 * 14 + 5 * 12 + 0",
            "Answer": 237,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 10 + 9 * 4 + 16 * 5 + 7",
            "Answer": 134,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 12 + 15 * 18 + 8 * 0 + 13",
            "Answer": 298,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 10 + 7 * 6 + 14 * 2 + 16",
            "Answer": 110,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 1 + 19 * 1 + 13 * 4 + 13",
            "Answer": 104,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 4 + 3 * 14 + 9 * 19 + 0",
            "Answer": 217,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 4 + 6 * 17 + 13 * 9 + 0",
            "Answer": 227,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # + # * # + #"
        }
    ],
    "# + # * # + # * # * # * #": [
        {
            "Question": "7 + 0 * 16 + 0 * 8 * 17 * 5",
            "Answer": 7,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 9 * 15 + 1 * 11 * 12 * 17",
            "Answer": 2389,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 10 * 18 + 2 * 10 * 12 * 6",
            "Answer": 1624,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 9 * 19 + 18 * 11 * 8 * 19",
            "Answer": 30272,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 9 * 18 + 11 * 3 * 0 * 17",
            "Answer": 162,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 2 * 4 + 9 * 3 * 16 * 11",
            "Answer": 4760,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 13 * 14 + 1 * 0 * 1 * 6",
            "Answer": 190,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 18 * 8 + 6 * 17 * 15 * 1",
            "Answer": 1690,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 9 * 0 + 5 * 12 * 15 * 8",
            "Answer": 7212,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 8 * 14 + 18 * 10 * 16 * 12",
            "Answer": 34685,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 11 * 6 + 0 * 17 * 8 * 1",
            "Answer": 67,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 10 * 3 + 13 * 0 * 2 * 19",
            "Answer": 49,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 5 * 17 + 0 * 19 * 7 * 16",
            "Answer": 101,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 4 * 1 + 11 * 2 * 11 * 5",
            "Answer": 1225,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 16 * 3 + 6 * 10 * 8 * 19",
            "Answer": 9168,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 17 * 17 + 7 * 8 * 16 * 14",
            "Answer": 12848,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 15 * 3 + 16 * 11 * 12 * 2",
            "Answer": 4275,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 19 * 3 + 4 * 1 * 15 * 17",
            "Answer": 1081,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 4 * 9 + 3 * 18 * 7 * 18",
            "Answer": 6843,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 17 * 18 + 1 * 1 * 3 * 0",
            "Answer": 319,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 11 * 19 + 13 * 2 * 6 * 1",
            "Answer": 374,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 3 * 15 + 6 * 6 * 14 * 1",
            "Answer": 566,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 2 * 18 + 13 * 8 * 18 * 2",
            "Answer": 3798,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 17 * 3 + 18 * 17 * 2 * 6",
            "Answer": 3731,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 13 * 3 + 18 * 17 * 14 * 13",
            "Answer": 55734,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 0 * 2 + 2 * 4 * 9 * 14",
            "Answer": 1012,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 13 * 9 + 5 * 14 * 8 * 16",
            "Answer": 9087,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 0 * 11 + 6 * 13 * 18 * 12",
            "Answer": 16866,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 19 * 11 + 18 * 8 * 2 * 1",
            "Answer": 500,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 17 * 14 + 10 * 11 * 16 * 18",
            "Answer": 31924,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 2 * 17 + 10 * 16 * 1 * 13",
            "Answer": 2117,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 2 * 2 + 5 * 9 * 17 * 15",
            "Answer": 11484,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 3 * 17 + 14 * 15 * 3 * 3",
            "Answer": 1955,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 6 * 6 + 0 * 11 * 2 * 12",
            "Answer": 46,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 1 * 16 + 19 * 0 * 4 * 11",
            "Answer": 17,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 17 * 14 + 4 * 4 * 19 * 8",
            "Answer": 2679,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 2 * 19 + 8 * 0 * 12 * 14",
            "Answer": 44,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 19 * 0 + 18 * 15 * 8 * 19",
            "Answer": 41054,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 0 * 2 + 6 * 2 * 17 * 17",
            "Answer": 3481,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 9 * 4 + 16 * 16 * 12 * 10",
            "Answer": 30756,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 2 * 11 + 15 * 14 * 8 * 18",
            "Answer": 30271,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 16 * 9 + 18 * 17 * 5 * 11",
            "Answer": 16977,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 17 * 19 + 1 * 11 * 13 * 8",
            "Answer": 1480,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 13 * 11 + 3 * 15 * 6 * 7",
            "Answer": 2042,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 7 * 11 + 5 * 6 * 12 * 5",
            "Answer": 1895,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 6 * 14 + 17 * 3 * 17 * 9",
            "Answer": 7889,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 15 * 11 + 15 * 3 * 19 * 11",
            "Answer": 9581,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 2 * 0 + 16 * 12 * 17 * 7",
            "Answer": 22858,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 14 * 13 + 13 * 0 * 3 * 8",
            "Answer": 200,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 4 * 12 + 7 * 6 * 2 * 5",
            "Answer": 480,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 13 * 14 + 8 * 13 * 15 * 14",
            "Answer": 22023,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 19 * 13 + 9 * 1 * 1 * 4",
            "Answer": 288,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 6 * 19 + 10 * 7 * 5 * 12",
            "Answer": 4325,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 18 * 7 + 7 * 0 * 13 * 13",
            "Answer": 133,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 0 * 5 + 13 * 6 * 12 * 7",
            "Answer": 6558,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 5 * 6 + 3 * 18 * 2 * 19",
            "Answer": 2094,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 0 * 17 + 7 * 15 * 1 * 15",
            "Answer": 1583,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 13 * 13 + 5 * 18 * 7 * 14",
            "Answer": 9002,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 7 * 17 + 19 * 1 * 6 * 13",
            "Answer": 1611,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 1 * 14 + 14 * 3 * 2 * 4",
            "Answer": 359,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 2 * 1 + 14 * 3 * 4 * 16",
            "Answer": 2691,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 19 * 3 + 2 * 12 * 6 * 10",
            "Answer": 1512,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 6 * 5 + 6 * 12 * 17 * 14",
            "Answer": 17184,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 17 * 19 + 12 * 7 * 7 * 9",
            "Answer": 5623,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 9 * 17 + 15 * 11 * 4 * 2",
            "Answer": 1484,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 14 * 3 + 12 * 1 * 8 * 5",
            "Answer": 523,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 1 * 2 + 10 * 4 * 9 * 3",
            "Answer": 1085,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 12 * 14 + 19 * 0 * 6 * 7",
            "Answer": 180,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 15 * 11 + 16 * 13 * 0 * 0",
            "Answer": 179,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 14 * 17 + 10 * 3 * 19 * 15",
            "Answer": 8790,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 9 * 14 + 9 * 2 * 1 * 13",
            "Answer": 379,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 3 * 19 + 17 * 17 * 16 * 8",
            "Answer": 37053,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 2 * 8 + 17 * 16 * 14 * 2",
            "Answer": 7636,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 11 * 6 + 12 * 17 * 5 * 5",
            "Answer": 5178,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 13 * 17 + 15 * 13 * 11 * 7",
            "Answer": 15251,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 4 * 16 + 7 * 12 * 10 * 14",
            "Answer": 11825,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 18 * 13 + 13 * 3 * 1 * 18",
            "Answer": 955,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 16 * 9 + 2 * 9 * 1 * 18",
            "Answer": 473,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 13 * 17 + 8 * 8 * 4 * 19",
            "Answer": 5104,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 18 * 7 + 13 * 11 * 5 * 13",
            "Answer": 9425,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 13 * 7 + 3 * 4 * 6 * 15",
            "Answer": 1176,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 18 * 5 + 5 * 7 * 19 * 15",
            "Answer": 10078,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 2 * 17 + 9 * 18 * 11 * 4",
            "Answer": 7165,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 15 * 10 + 0 * 7 * 16 * 5",
            "Answer": 158,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 2 * 19 + 9 * 6 * 13 * 10",
            "Answer": 7062,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 9 * 7 + 4 * 0 * 6 * 6",
            "Answer": 82,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 10 * 17 + 6 * 15 * 17 * 18",
            "Answer": 27724,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 5 * 8 + 9 * 5 * 6 * 5",
            "Answer": 1397,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 0 * 14 + 13 * 12 * 1 * 7",
            "Answer": 1093,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 9 * 8 + 10 * 15 * 15 * 13",
            "Answer": 29325,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 10 * 9 + 7 * 15 * 0 * 15",
            "Answer": 108,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 11 * 2 + 12 * 9 * 12 * 12",
            "Answer": 15582,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 10 * 7 + 0 * 4 * 11 * 15",
            "Answer": 78,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 19 * 8 + 15 * 1 * 7 * 7",
            "Answer": 895,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 7 * 2 + 18 * 6 * 12 * 10",
            "Answer": 12993,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 1 * 12 + 16 * 0 * 11 * 15",
            "Answer": 12,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 4 * 11 + 14 * 19 * 11 * 12",
            "Answer": 35170,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 14 * 10 + 17 * 18 * 12 * 7",
            "Answer": 25846,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 17 * 14 + 3 * 11 * 3 * 17",
            "Answer": 1925,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 10 * 2 + 8 * 11 * 8 * 15",
            "Answer": 10592,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # * # * #"
        }
    ],
    "# + # + # + # * # * # * #": [
        {
            "Question": "1 + 5 + 2 + 7 * 4 * 1 * 12",
            "Answer": 344,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 14 + 19 + 1 * 6 * 7 * 18",
            "Answer": 797,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 4 + 14 + 19 * 8 * 3 * 8",
            "Answer": 3668,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 8 + 6 + 14 * 15 * 16 * 5",
            "Answer": 16830,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 3 + 1 + 1 * 3 * 9 * 0",
            "Answer": 12,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 16 + 6 + 4 * 1 * 4 * 19",
            "Answer": 334,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 12 + 13 + 16 * 0 * 0 * 8",
            "Answer": 32,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 17 + 9 + 2 * 6 * 18 * 16",
            "Answer": 3486,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 0 + 19 + 11 * 19 * 0 * 15",
            "Answer": 22,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 17 + 7 + 2 * 1 * 13 * 0",
            "Answer": 27,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 12 + 5 + 9 * 17 * 19 * 16",
            "Answer": 46544,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 18 + 5 + 12 * 12 * 2 * 13",
            "Answer": 3770,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 5 + 19 + 9 * 16 * 14 * 3",
            "Answer": 6075,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 16 + 0 + 16 * 17 * 15 * 5",
            "Answer": 20421,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 7 + 12 + 3 * 16 * 15 * 18",
            "Answer": 12986,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 13 + 7 + 4 * 1 * 8 * 8",
            "Answer": 278,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 0 + 15 + 3 * 3 * 2 * 1",
            "Answer": 52,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 8 + 17 + 5 * 6 * 12 * 18",
            "Answer": 6518,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 7 + 6 + 10 * 3 * 9 * 14",
            "Answer": 3799,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 17 + 5 + 16 * 10 * 0 * 9",
            "Answer": 29,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 18 + 14 + 7 * 17 * 4 * 9",
            "Answer": 4335,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 13 + 7 + 15 * 7 * 14 * 16",
            "Answer": 23543,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 19 + 0 + 1 * 15 * 17 * 14",
            "Answer": 3607,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 1 + 5 + 11 * 14 * 6 * 7",
            "Answer": 6482,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 11 + 2 + 17 * 14 * 1 * 1",
            "Answer": 264,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 5 + 9 + 13 * 15 * 1 * 19",
            "Answer": 3727,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 3 + 2 + 5 * 4 * 12 * 10",
            "Answer": 2412,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 3 + 10 + 8 * 5 * 11 * 17",
            "Answer": 7494,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 2 + 16 + 4 * 2 * 7 * 3",
            "Answer": 186,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 5 + 13 + 11 * 4 * 13 * 2",
            "Answer": 1163,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 16 + 19 + 13 * 9 * 13 * 3",
            "Answer": 4600,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 15 + 11 + 2 * 12 * 6 * 16",
            "Answer": 2335,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 6 + 0 + 7 * 3 * 11 * 10",
            "Answer": 2318,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 4 + 10 + 1 * 19 * 7 * 8",
            "Answer": 1084,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 16 + 12 + 3 * 14 * 7 * 13",
            "Answer": 3850,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 19 + 13 + 1 * 12 * 4 * 10",
            "Answer": 521,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 13 + 9 + 13 * 18 * 18 * 16",
            "Answer": 67414,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 6 + 17 + 11 * 12 * 7 * 4",
            "Answer": 3726,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 10 + 1 + 11 * 13 * 3 * 6",
            "Answer": 2592,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 9 + 6 + 15 * 18 * 5 * 13",
            "Answer": 17566,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 15 + 8 + 12 * 2 * 16 * 9",
            "Answer": 3495,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 13 + 8 + 17 * 19 * 4 * 0",
            "Answer": 26,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 3 + 14 + 14 * 16 * 11 * 14",
            "Answer": 34527,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 14 + 5 + 6 * 12 * 18 * 3",
            "Answer": 3918,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 16 + 3 + 8 * 15 * 0 * 14",
            "Answer": 21,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 15 + 13 + 19 * 8 * 12 * 1",
            "Answer": 1853,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 7 + 17 + 13 * 5 * 10 * 13",
            "Answer": 8482,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 6 + 11 + 15 * 16 * 12 * 5",
            "Answer": 14423,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 11 + 14 + 17 * 5 * 13 * 1",
            "Answer": 1134,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 19 + 16 + 6 * 16 * 16 * 6",
            "Answer": 9266,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 5 + 17 + 11 * 18 * 11 * 1",
            "Answer": 2210,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 5 + 4 + 8 * 3 * 10 * 15",
            "Answer": 3617,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 15 + 19 + 11 * 4 * 3 * 4",
            "Answer": 577,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 0 + 6 + 12 * 14 * 2 * 15",
            "Answer": 5047,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 12 + 6 + 7 * 18 * 2 * 10",
            "Answer": 2542,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 3 + 18 + 0 * 4 * 9 * 16",
            "Answer": 39,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 1 + 4 + 16 * 9 * 14 * 4",
            "Answer": 8072,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 10 + 8 + 3 * 2 * 2 * 12",
            "Answer": 166,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 0 + 12 + 11 * 4 * 4 * 11",
            "Answer": 1955,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 1 + 16 + 19 * 17 * 5 * 5",
            "Answer": 8109,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 1 + 1 + 7 * 17 * 4 * 1",
            "Answer": 497,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 10 + 12 + 12 * 19 * 0 * 7",
            "Answer": 39,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 19 + 9 + 19 * 2 * 8 * 9",
            "Answer": 2764,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 10 + 1 + 8 * 16 * 6 * 2",
            "Answer": 1564,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 6 + 14 + 1 * 0 * 17 * 6",
            "Answer": 34,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 15 + 8 + 5 * 1 * 8 * 10",
            "Answer": 435,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 9 + 19 + 0 * 16 * 19 * 1",
            "Answer": 36,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 0 + 13 + 17 * 2 * 3 * 10",
            "Answer": 1043,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 2 + 7 + 4 * 15 * 17 * 6",
            "Answer": 6143,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 17 + 6 + 11 * 6 * 15 * 5",
            "Answer": 4985,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 1 + 18 + 3 * 15 * 12 * 0",
            "Answer": 27,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 15 + 12 + 11 * 1 * 7 * 15",
            "Answer": 1182,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 2 + 9 + 1 * 2 * 6 * 8",
            "Answer": 108,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 18 + 1 + 2 * 6 * 15 * 5",
            "Answer": 928,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 11 + 7 + 6 * 0 * 3 * 13",
            "Answer": 34,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 16 + 5 + 13 * 9 * 18 * 3",
            "Answer": 6356,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 17 + 15 + 19 * 17 * 15 * 11",
            "Answer": 53329,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 10 + 16 + 7 * 0 * 16 * 4",
            "Answer": 27,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 18 + 19 + 6 * 3 * 17 * 6",
            "Answer": 1879,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 1 + 0 + 8 * 18 * 1 * 0",
            "Answer": 15,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 16 + 11 + 18 * 19 * 19 * 8",
            "Answer": 52011,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 12 + 13 + 11 * 0 * 2 * 6",
            "Answer": 27,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 0 + 7 + 17 * 8 * 16 * 9",
            "Answer": 19592,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 18 + 3 + 15 * 9 * 16 * 15",
            "Answer": 32434,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 6 + 3 + 3 * 4 * 12 * 16",
            "Answer": 2317,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 6 + 3 + 0 * 12 * 7 * 17",
            "Answer": 15,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 5 + 0 + 7 * 1 * 15 * 19",
            "Answer": 2013,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 12 + 18 + 6 * 11 * 0 * 4",
            "Answer": 46,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 4 + 8 + 0 * 1 * 15 * 15",
            "Answer": 31,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 6 + 13 + 6 * 4 * 15 * 17",
            "Answer": 6156,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 2 + 17 + 8 * 19 * 13 * 16",
            "Answer": 31653,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 18 + 17 + 9 * 16 * 13 * 8",
            "Answer": 15023,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 0 + 14 + 8 * 9 * 14 * 1",
            "Answer": 1028,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 9 + 2 + 15 * 15 * 5 * 5",
            "Answer": 5649,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 17 + 10 + 16 * 10 * 2 * 4",
            "Answer": 1319,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 19 + 16 + 19 * 4 * 10 * 6",
            "Answer": 4606,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 13 + 11 + 9 * 6 * 11 * 14",
            "Answer": 8342,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 7 + 18 + 8 * 15 * 15 * 13",
            "Answer": 23425,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 10 + 4 + 15 * 13 * 0 * 19",
            "Answer": 32,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 19 + 0 + 7 * 14 * 6 * 4",
            "Answer": 2383,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # * # * # * #"
        }
    ],
    "# * # + # * # * # * # + #": [
        {
            "Question": "14 * 9 + 15 * 18 * 2 * 10 + 8",
            "Answer": 5534,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 3 + 6 * 14 * 13 * 1 + 16",
            "Answer": 1138,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 11 + 17 * 13 * 13 * 9 + 3",
            "Answer": 26069,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 14 + 13 * 17 * 16 * 1 + 11",
            "Answer": 3617,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 16 + 18 * 6 * 13 * 4 + 3",
            "Answer": 5731,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 17 + 16 * 5 * 6 * 2 + 5",
            "Answer": 1203,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 9 + 0 * 14 * 14 * 7 + 7",
            "Answer": 115,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 3 + 16 * 8 * 1 * 12 + 0",
            "Answer": 1587,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 17 + 10 * 10 * 6 * 7 + 19",
            "Answer": 4542,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 0 + 10 * 0 * 0 * 6 + 6",
            "Answer": 6,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 11 + 15 * 3 * 12 * 16 + 8",
            "Answer": 8725,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 6 + 3 * 17 * 7 * 4 + 5",
            "Answer": 1541,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 10 + 7 * 4 * 15 * 2 + 5",
            "Answer": 1035,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 10 + 7 * 14 * 2 * 0 + 3",
            "Answer": 123,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 19 + 10 * 19 * 1 * 0 + 0",
            "Answer": 76,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 19 + 6 * 18 * 6 * 8 + 19",
            "Answer": 5431,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 16 + 8 * 5 * 4 * 7 + 5",
            "Answer": 1301,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 13 + 9 * 12 * 4 * 12 + 13",
            "Answer": 5431,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 10 + 6 * 15 * 7 * 13 + 2",
            "Answer": 8322,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 9 + 9 * 4 * 6 * 6 + 17",
            "Answer": 1457,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 4 + 10 * 13 * 10 * 9 + 6",
            "Answer": 11730,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 0 + 0 * 2 * 14 * 9 + 5",
            "Answer": 5,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 6 + 0 * 10 * 16 * 2 + 19",
            "Answer": 79,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 9 + 9 * 19 * 6 * 12 + 7",
            "Answer": 12463,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 8 + 1 * 6 * 3 * 19 + 10",
            "Answer": 376,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 6 + 14 * 3 * 12 * 2 + 4",
            "Answer": 1120,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 6 + 18 * 4 * 8 * 17 + 2",
            "Answer": 9872,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 9 + 11 * 1 * 12 * 1 + 5",
            "Answer": 218,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 9 + 19 * 3 * 5 * 13 + 14",
            "Answer": 3791,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 9 + 13 * 12 * 15 * 5 + 10",
            "Answer": 11719,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 13 + 3 * 12 * 17 * 5 + 3",
            "Answer": 3271,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 6 + 12 * 10 * 10 * 16 + 9",
            "Answer": 19227,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 7 + 16 * 15 * 18 * 11 + 7",
            "Answer": 47541,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 8 + 15 * 13 * 18 * 2 + 7",
            "Answer": 7131,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 19 + 5 * 5 * 16 * 11 + 3",
            "Answer": 4726,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 0 + 14 * 12 * 9 * 15 + 18",
            "Answer": 22698,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 19 + 7 * 17 * 6 * 17 + 0",
            "Answer": 12138,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 3 + 17 * 9 * 15 * 2 + 19",
            "Answer": 4660,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 14 + 9 * 9 * 16 * 7 + 4",
            "Answer": 9090,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 8 + 2 * 9 * 10 * 17 + 19",
            "Answer": 3215,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 12 + 5 * 13 * 7 * 19 + 1",
            "Answer": 8874,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 6 + 4 * 9 * 8 * 5 + 10",
            "Answer": 1522,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 15 + 7 * 13 * 12 * 11 + 15",
            "Answer": 12147,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 13 + 15 * 8 * 19 * 13 + 4",
            "Answer": 29787,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 18 + 2 * 7 * 4 * 14 + 2",
            "Answer": 1110,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 9 + 1 * 7 * 18 * 1 + 6",
            "Answer": 258,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 2 + 2 * 13 * 16 * 9 + 19",
            "Answer": 3793,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 12 + 10 * 6 * 4 * 19 + 6",
            "Answer": 4566,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 14 + 2 * 0 * 14 * 16 + 2",
            "Answer": 2,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 13 + 16 * 4 * 7 * 19 + 9",
            "Answer": 8677,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 1 + 10 * 13 * 5 * 12 + 9",
            "Answer": 7827,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 17 + 16 * 6 * 12 * 17 + 0",
            "Answer": 19635,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 9 + 2 * 0 * 10 * 10 + 12",
            "Answer": 75,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 1 + 8 * 4 * 1 * 9 + 16",
            "Answer": 311,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 3 + 4 * 5 * 13 * 9 + 15",
            "Answer": 2391,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 16 + 15 * 18 * 6 * 3 + 9",
            "Answer": 5125,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 15 + 11 * 0 * 17 * 3 + 10",
            "Answer": 205,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 7 + 0 * 0 * 6 * 8 + 6",
            "Answer": 20,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 17 + 1 * 3 * 15 * 11 + 7",
            "Answer": 621,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 8 + 19 * 12 * 5 * 11 + 11",
            "Answer": 12559,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 14 + 16 * 14 * 11 * 19 + 12",
            "Answer": 46842,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 13 + 14 * 8 * 16 * 8 + 7",
            "Answer": 14356,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 13 + 8 * 18 * 0 * 13 + 18",
            "Answer": 226,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 4 + 0 * 3 * 9 * 4 + 7",
            "Answer": 79,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 4 + 6 * 19 * 8 * 16 + 7",
            "Answer": 14647,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 2 + 15 * 6 * 8 * 5 + 16",
            "Answer": 3642,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 16 + 11 * 10 * 16 * 19 + 3",
            "Answer": 33603,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 19 + 6 * 8 * 9 * 12 + 7",
            "Answer": 5419,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 18 + 12 * 6 * 7 * 7 + 1",
            "Answer": 3601,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 4 + 5 * 5 * 18 * 8 + 17",
            "Answer": 3677,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 14 + 1 * 8 * 7 * 15 + 18",
            "Answer": 1068,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 11 + 19 * 14 * 19 * 1 + 2",
            "Answer": 5221,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 5 + 19 * 6 * 11 * 17 + 5",
            "Answer": 21363,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 17 + 16 * 8 * 5 * 17 + 12",
            "Answer": 10977,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 13 + 7 * 19 * 15 * 12 + 17",
            "Answer": 24152,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 0 + 5 * 1 * 15 * 6 + 5",
            "Answer": 455,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 17 + 10 * 1 * 19 * 4 + 11",
            "Answer": 822,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 6 + 11 * 1 * 15 * 9 + 1",
            "Answer": 1492,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 17 + 14 * 2 * 1 * 6 + 8",
            "Answer": 363,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 11 + 15 * 11 * 0 * 2 + 19",
            "Answer": 74,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 19 + 18 * 15 * 3 * 19 + 4",
            "Answer": 15622,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 2 + 10 * 3 * 1 * 3 + 10",
            "Answer": 124,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 7 + 18 * 1 * 12 * 6 + 10",
            "Answer": 1390,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 1 + 2 * 10 * 7 * 2 + 10",
            "Answer": 300,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 0 + 14 * 9 * 5 * 17 + 16",
            "Answer": 10726,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 12 + 5 * 9 * 4 * 13 + 19",
            "Answer": 2527,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 15 + 15 * 15 * 0 * 13 + 13",
            "Answer": 13,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 6 + 2 * 10 * 18 * 10 + 10",
            "Answer": 3646,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 13 + 5 * 3 * 4 * 18 + 13",
            "Answer": 1145,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 9 + 18 * 16 * 1 * 16 + 14",
            "Answer": 4793,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 5 + 18 * 13 * 18 * 11 + 3",
            "Answer": 46360,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 10 + 1 * 13 * 9 * 6 + 16",
            "Answer": 748,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 11 + 15 * 15 * 14 * 5 + 9",
            "Answer": 15946,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 5 + 12 * 7 * 19 * 12 + 7",
            "Answer": 19209,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 19 + 13 * 5 * 3 * 13 + 3",
            "Answer": 2823,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 13 + 16 * 17 * 13 * 17 + 1",
            "Answer": 60217,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 14 + 12 * 3 * 1 * 9 + 14",
            "Answer": 604,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 11 + 1 * 11 * 11 * 3 + 14",
            "Answer": 399,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 19 + 19 * 15 * 15 * 0 + 3",
            "Answer": 60,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 13 + 13 * 12 * 15 * 13 + 6",
            "Answer": 30478,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # * # + #"
        }
    ],
    "# * # + # + # * # * # + #": [
        {
            "Question": "16 * 2 + 13 + 7 * 19 * 11 + 16",
            "Answer": 1524,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 6 + 2 + 9 * 13 * 9 + 13",
            "Answer": 1182,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 17 + 16 + 6 * 13 * 7 + 17",
            "Answer": 732,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 1 + 18 + 0 * 13 * 1 + 13",
            "Answer": 32,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 6 + 18 + 11 * 1 * 9 + 16",
            "Answer": 241,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 18 + 17 + 8 * 7 * 3 + 18",
            "Answer": 419,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 16 + 1 + 15 * 9 * 18 + 12",
            "Answer": 2539,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 19 + 10 + 4 * 6 * 17 + 19",
            "Answer": 513,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 5 + 19 + 14 * 15 * 0 + 0",
            "Answer": 104,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 8 + 5 + 13 * 13 * 16 + 5",
            "Answer": 2866,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 10 + 2 + 0 * 7 * 0 + 14",
            "Answer": 146,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 6 + 15 + 14 * 2 * 1 + 12",
            "Answer": 121,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 13 + 17 + 16 * 11 * 0 + 2",
            "Answer": 71,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 18 + 16 + 18 * 19 * 10 + 16",
            "Answer": 3776,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 15 + 4 + 16 * 8 * 6 + 0",
            "Answer": 787,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 13 + 11 + 10 * 7 * 2 + 13",
            "Answer": 398,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 10 + 10 + 17 * 18 * 6 + 1",
            "Answer": 1937,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 2 + 14 + 14 * 4 * 5 + 9",
            "Answer": 307,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 18 + 13 + 19 * 3 * 4 + 10",
            "Answer": 395,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 14 + 2 + 3 * 12 * 8 + 18",
            "Answer": 504,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 6 + 6 + 16 * 9 * 9 + 12",
            "Answer": 1314,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 5 + 15 + 2 * 8 * 6 + 0",
            "Answer": 126,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 5 + 5 + 6 * 2 * 19 + 6",
            "Answer": 304,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 4 + 11 + 5 * 5 * 12 + 3",
            "Answer": 354,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 19 + 15 + 17 * 7 * 14 + 15",
            "Answer": 1715,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 7 + 13 + 9 * 11 * 13 + 13",
            "Answer": 1355,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 19 + 9 + 13 * 4 * 3 + 19",
            "Answer": 260,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 7 + 8 + 5 * 8 * 18 + 12",
            "Answer": 831,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 10 + 17 + 7 * 13 * 2 + 15",
            "Answer": 364,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 6 + 15 + 15 * 11 * 1 + 4",
            "Answer": 220,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 12 + 1 + 15 * 12 * 5 + 18",
            "Answer": 931,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 19 + 18 + 5 * 17 * 11 + 0",
            "Answer": 1295,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 6 + 10 + 14 * 16 * 9 + 14",
            "Answer": 2040,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 4 + 2 + 7 * 4 * 18 + 12",
            "Answer": 582,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 14 + 1 + 6 * 17 * 10 + 19",
            "Answer": 1110,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 11 + 16 + 9 * 19 * 15 + 14",
            "Answer": 2782,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 14 + 2 + 3 * 12 * 15 + 5",
            "Answer": 589,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 2 + 19 + 1 * 2 * 7 + 18",
            "Answer": 63,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 13 + 1 + 2 * 11 * 2 + 11",
            "Answer": 82,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 1 + 7 + 4 * 8 * 14 + 13",
            "Answer": 478,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 14 + 18 + 9 * 11 * 18 + 6",
            "Answer": 1960,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 18 + 17 + 8 * 2 * 14 + 5",
            "Answer": 444,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 2 + 12 + 2 * 13 * 18 + 2",
            "Answer": 512,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 17 + 10 + 10 * 12 * 8 + 11",
            "Answer": 1270,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 12 + 10 + 12 * 8 * 19 + 4",
            "Answer": 2042,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 10 + 7 + 9 * 3 * 1 + 7",
            "Answer": 191,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 14 + 3 + 18 * 6 * 13 + 1",
            "Answer": 1408,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 9 + 1 + 1 * 1 * 17 + 18",
            "Answer": 45,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 7 + 18 + 7 * 17 * 18 + 10",
            "Answer": 2296,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 9 + 18 + 9 * 18 * 12 + 15",
            "Answer": 2022,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 8 + 14 + 3 * 9 * 19 + 19",
            "Answer": 562,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 0 + 10 + 8 * 18 * 19 + 9",
            "Answer": 2755,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 7 + 17 + 16 * 9 * 17 + 16",
            "Answer": 2600,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 11 + 5 + 9 * 11 * 15 + 3",
            "Answer": 1603,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 8 + 17 + 18 * 18 * 0 + 15",
            "Answer": 72,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 14 + 2 + 15 * 19 * 7 + 5",
            "Answer": 2254,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 7 + 17 + 7 * 17 * 10 + 7",
            "Answer": 1270,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 4 + 2 + 4 * 10 * 5 + 8",
            "Answer": 266,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 9 + 7 + 12 * 18 * 5 + 15",
            "Answer": 1156,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 7 + 19 + 6 * 2 * 12 + 8",
            "Answer": 185,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 15 + 0 + 2 * 17 * 13 + 8",
            "Answer": 465,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 9 + 18 + 19 * 17 * 10 + 7",
            "Answer": 3318,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 6 + 16 + 19 * 13 * 8 + 19",
            "Answer": 2011,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 0 + 19 + 12 * 18 * 19 + 0",
            "Answer": 4123,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 4 + 15 + 10 * 19 * 5 + 18",
            "Answer": 1019,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 19 + 7 + 10 * 11 * 9 + 3",
            "Answer": 1133,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 3 + 10 + 7 * 18 * 10 + 19",
            "Answer": 1307,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 12 + 0 + 10 * 0 * 6 + 12",
            "Answer": 156,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 19 + 5 + 19 * 10 * 10 + 18",
            "Answer": 2075,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 3 + 12 + 12 * 12 * 11 + 5",
            "Answer": 1649,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 4 + 4 + 10 * 4 * 15 + 19",
            "Answer": 643,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 5 + 4 + 2 * 10 * 7 + 11",
            "Answer": 200,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 17 + 4 + 14 * 5 * 14 + 9",
            "Answer": 1044,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 4 + 9 + 18 * 15 * 7 + 15",
            "Answer": 1930,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 16 + 8 + 0 * 8 * 0 + 1",
            "Answer": 281,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 12 + 14 + 1 * 15 * 16 + 17",
            "Answer": 283,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 12 + 8 + 6 * 2 * 17 + 10",
            "Answer": 258,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 12 + 9 + 5 * 18 * 11 + 16",
            "Answer": 1051,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 19 + 5 + 5 * 1 * 10 + 19",
            "Answer": 397,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 17 + 18 + 15 * 7 * 13 + 15",
            "Answer": 1636,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 2 + 18 + 11 * 5 * 14 + 19",
            "Answer": 831,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 13 + 15 + 11 * 15 * 2 + 16",
            "Answer": 608,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 12 + 13 + 4 * 5 * 4 + 11",
            "Answer": 152,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 9 + 2 + 9 * 13 * 17 + 10",
            "Answer": 2037,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 14 + 5 + 6 * 19 * 6 + 1",
            "Answer": 928,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 1 + 6 + 10 * 4 * 1 + 16",
            "Answer": 64,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 15 + 18 + 15 * 11 * 10 + 6",
            "Answer": 1704,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 9 + 16 + 1 * 2 * 9 + 7",
            "Answer": 140,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 9 + 10 + 13 * 15 * 17 + 12",
            "Answer": 3382,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 5 + 11 + 14 * 15 * 8 + 0",
            "Answer": 1781,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 15 + 4 + 5 * 14 * 9 + 11",
            "Answer": 885,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 6 + 19 + 10 * 15 * 11 + 11",
            "Answer": 1764,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 14 + 18 + 2 * 19 * 11 + 2",
            "Answer": 494,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 2 + 6 + 3 * 1 * 10 + 9",
            "Answer": 81,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 4 + 2 + 7 * 8 * 6 + 15",
            "Answer": 369,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 6 + 17 + 10 * 19 * 13 + 18",
            "Answer": 2583,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 14 + 8 + 14 * 14 * 1 + 0",
            "Answer": 344,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 19 + 4 + 10 * 9 * 2 + 19",
            "Answer": 355,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 15 + 18 + 6 * 11 * 12 + 18",
            "Answer": 1083,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 7 + 18 + 0 * 13 * 3 + 15",
            "Answer": 61,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # * # + #"
        }
    ],
    "# + # * # * # * # + # + #": [
        {
            "Question": "18 + 2 * 6 * 1 * 3 + 7 + 14",
            "Answer": 75,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 18 * 4 * 17 * 3 + 11 + 2",
            "Answer": 3701,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 0 * 9 * 12 * 17 + 15 + 3",
            "Answer": 28,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 19 * 18 * 5 * 8 + 0 + 14",
            "Answer": 13698,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 10 * 11 * 0 * 5 + 18 + 11",
            "Answer": 32,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 17 * 13 * 11 * 10 + 5 + 2",
            "Answer": 24332,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 13 * 0 * 4 * 17 + 18 + 9",
            "Answer": 32,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 14 * 7 * 11 * 12 + 16 + 19",
            "Answer": 12987,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 7 * 2 * 16 * 15 + 2 + 11",
            "Answer": 3390,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 5 * 19 * 9 * 7 + 3 + 14",
            "Answer": 6014,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 10 * 13 * 4 * 18 + 1 + 8",
            "Answer": 9376,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 13 * 11 * 14 * 9 + 10 + 16",
            "Answer": 18053,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 10 * 17 * 4 * 18 + 12 + 8",
            "Answer": 12260,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 12 * 3 * 4 * 14 + 17 + 17",
            "Answer": 2064,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 10 * 18 * 13 * 10 + 8 + 14",
            "Answer": 23431,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 19 * 0 * 18 * 18 + 9 + 12",
            "Answer": 35,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 5 * 0 * 7 * 14 + 0 + 11",
            "Answer": 23,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 5 * 19 * 9 * 17 + 6 + 4",
            "Answer": 14559,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 6 * 11 * 7 * 17 + 7 + 15",
            "Answer": 7881,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 12 * 5 * 9 * 17 + 17 + 3",
            "Answer": 9201,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 0 * 1 * 6 * 9 + 14 + 12",
            "Answer": 39,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 19 * 14 * 12 * 3 + 4 + 5",
            "Answer": 9588,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 7 * 16 * 8 * 19 + 11 + 9",
            "Answer": 17055,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 16 * 2 * 13 * 12 + 15 + 17",
            "Answer": 5033,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 2 * 6 * 11 * 0 + 14 + 19",
            "Answer": 34,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 4 * 18 * 12 * 5 + 18 + 16",
            "Answer": 4355,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 4 * 19 * 16 * 14 + 14 + 19",
            "Answer": 17061,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 14 * 11 * 1 * 19 + 12 + 1",
            "Answer": 2941,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 18 * 18 * 8 * 0 + 1 + 4",
            "Answer": 7,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 2 * 4 * 13 * 12 + 7 + 0",
            "Answer": 1269,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 4 * 13 * 2 * 7 + 9 + 8",
            "Answer": 746,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 0 * 3 * 13 * 7 + 1 + 11",
            "Answer": 20,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 5 * 16 * 13 * 14 + 13 + 2",
            "Answer": 14584,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 17 * 11 * 15 * 0 + 2 + 5",
            "Answer": 15,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 16 * 8 * 9 * 3 + 10 + 7",
            "Answer": 3487,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 5 * 8 * 4 * 1 + 7 + 0",
            "Answer": 170,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 6 * 8 * 11 * 1 + 18 + 16",
            "Answer": 568,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 18 * 9 * 4 * 3 + 19 + 4",
            "Answer": 1972,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 13 * 1 * 6 * 1 + 7 + 8",
            "Answer": 100,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 9 * 16 * 4 * 2 + 12 + 0",
            "Answer": 1179,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 11 * 2 * 6 * 12 + 9 + 2",
            "Answer": 1601,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 8 * 10 * 1 * 9 + 2 + 12",
            "Answer": 746,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 10 * 15 * 2 * 7 + 2 + 17",
            "Answer": 2130,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 9 * 17 * 18 * 0 + 16 + 13",
            "Answer": 41,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 19 * 15 * 7 * 3 + 17 + 0",
            "Answer": 6011,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 19 * 19 * 0 * 18 + 6 + 15",
            "Answer": 26,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 10 * 12 * 16 * 2 + 5 + 17",
            "Answer": 3866,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 14 * 3 * 6 * 9 + 14 + 17",
            "Answer": 2313,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 16 * 6 * 2 * 19 + 18 + 9",
            "Answer": 3688,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 7 * 12 * 2 * 8 + 19 + 14",
            "Answer": 1390,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 4 * 17 * 13 * 10 + 12 + 5",
            "Answer": 8876,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 13 * 9 * 12 * 0 + 3 + 0",
            "Answer": 22,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 17 * 7 * 4 * 14 + 2 + 16",
            "Answer": 6685,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 18 * 8 * 10 * 3 + 17 + 18",
            "Answer": 4372,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 18 * 6 * 12 * 18 + 17 + 0",
            "Answer": 23356,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 8 * 12 * 19 * 3 + 2 + 12",
            "Answer": 5500,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 7 * 7 * 3 * 15 + 4 + 17",
            "Answer": 2243,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 4 * 18 * 13 * 12 + 9 + 3",
            "Answer": 11249,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 4 * 11 * 19 * 6 + 3 + 11",
            "Answer": 5037,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 5 * 18 * 4 * 14 + 3 + 12",
            "Answer": 5068,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 14 * 19 * 7 * 0 + 15 + 9",
            "Answer": 37,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 16 * 19 * 9 * 6 + 18 + 6",
            "Answer": 16440,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 8 * 16 * 14 * 7 + 6 + 15",
            "Answer": 12572,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 2 * 10 * 3 * 15 + 0 + 13",
            "Answer": 919,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 18 * 19 * 0 * 1 + 0 + 2",
            "Answer": 7,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 5 * 18 * 0 * 17 + 18 + 10",
            "Answer": 36,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 9 * 6 * 12 * 2 + 7 + 2",
            "Answer": 1305,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 5 * 8 * 4 * 11 + 2 + 6",
            "Answer": 1773,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 17 * 10 * 12 * 13 + 13 + 15",
            "Answer": 26556,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 4 * 16 * 16 * 9 + 4 + 12",
            "Answer": 9241,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 17 * 3 * 17 * 17 + 3 + 11",
            "Answer": 14769,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 0 * 0 * 0 * 3 + 4 + 5",
            "Answer": 21,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 1 * 7 * 6 * 2 + 12 + 13",
            "Answer": 115,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 16 * 2 * 18 * 8 + 19 + 9",
            "Answer": 4651,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 11 * 9 * 12 * 8 + 1 + 6",
            "Answer": 9514,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 2 * 7 * 16 * 19 + 16 + 11",
            "Answer": 4284,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 2 * 16 * 2 * 3 + 18 + 17",
            "Answer": 235,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 18 * 13 * 12 * 10 + 10 + 4",
            "Answer": 28106,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 1 * 4 * 19 * 17 + 10 + 7",
            "Answer": 1314,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 2 * 9 * 14 * 5 + 12 + 19",
            "Answer": 1298,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 6 * 2 * 4 * 13 + 3 + 19",
            "Answer": 664,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 5 * 14 * 4 * 16 + 16 + 15",
            "Answer": 4524,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 5 * 15 * 11 * 0 + 5 + 7",
            "Answer": 23,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 2 * 3 * 11 * 1 + 7 + 7",
            "Answer": 80,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 16 * 12 * 7 * 14 + 2 + 5",
            "Answer": 18828,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 2 * 16 * 1 * 0 + 15 + 7",
            "Answer": 34,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 7 * 6 * 19 * 9 + 17 + 2",
            "Answer": 7210,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 9 * 16 * 15 * 4 + 1 + 3",
            "Answer": 8653,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 15 * 7 * 2 * 3 + 11 + 2",
            "Answer": 655,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 17 * 19 * 11 * 8 + 7 + 2",
            "Answer": 28443,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 15 * 3 * 12 * 17 + 14 + 15",
            "Answer": 9210,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 11 * 9 * 12 * 3 + 18 + 9",
            "Answer": 3608,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 4 * 3 * 6 * 19 + 6 + 14",
            "Answer": 1402,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 14 * 7 * 19 * 11 + 1 + 5",
            "Answer": 20507,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 18 * 15 * 7 * 19 + 14 + 2",
            "Answer": 35940,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 0 * 10 * 9 * 14 + 7 + 6",
            "Answer": 18,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 16 * 2 * 14 * 15 + 6 + 9",
            "Answer": 6744,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 7 * 12 * 12 * 11 + 8 + 6",
            "Answer": 11110,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 2 * 15 * 6 * 4 + 19 + 18",
            "Answer": 771,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 12 * 2 * 15 * 3 + 6 + 1",
            "Answer": 1091,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # + #"
        }
    ],
    "# + # * # * # * # + # * #": [
        {
            "Question": "12 + 18 * 4 * 12 * 18 + 14 * 16",
            "Answer": 15788,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 6 * 7 * 8 * 13 + 1 * 6",
            "Answer": 4390,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 14 * 7 * 9 * 16 + 3 * 13",
            "Answer": 14169,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 7 * 1 * 3 * 3 + 3 * 13",
            "Answer": 115,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 7 * 2 * 4 * 9 + 17 * 15",
            "Answer": 764,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 12 * 15 * 19 * 13 + 1 * 2",
            "Answer": 44476,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 5 * 11 * 19 * 9 + 19 * 0",
            "Answer": 9420,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 12 * 18 * 11 * 7 + 18 * 11",
            "Answer": 16833,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 3 * 10 * 12 * 7 + 9 * 16",
            "Answer": 2671,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 12 * 13 * 11 * 5 + 2 * 9",
            "Answer": 8613,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 3 * 11 * 13 * 13 + 9 * 5",
            "Answer": 5632,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 1 * 9 * 11 * 4 + 6 * 1",
            "Answer": 411,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 4 * 14 * 17 * 4 + 3 * 18",
            "Answer": 3871,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 13 * 14 * 6 * 15 + 11 * 4",
            "Answer": 16436,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 3 * 7 * 11 * 4 + 18 * 10",
            "Answer": 1111,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 1 * 6 * 10 * 12 + 7 * 15",
            "Answer": 839,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 18 * 12 * 14 * 18 + 9 * 0",
            "Answer": 54445,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 12 * 19 * 3 * 4 + 4 * 15",
            "Answer": 2799,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 3 * 5 * 16 * 16 + 3 * 1",
            "Answer": 3862,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 18 * 18 * 0 * 10 + 0 * 2",
            "Answer": 10,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 9 * 6 * 3 * 14 + 8 * 8",
            "Answer": 2343,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 12 * 1 * 9 * 14 + 7 * 13",
            "Answer": 1604,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 12 * 5 * 6 * 7 + 1 * 2",
            "Answer": 2524,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 10 * 17 * 18 * 13 + 9 * 3",
            "Answer": 39813,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 1 * 2 * 19 * 18 + 14 * 6",
            "Answer": 774,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 2 * 6 * 1 * 0 + 11 * 17",
            "Answer": 194,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 16 * 13 * 1 * 16 + 19 * 19",
            "Answer": 3702,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 18 * 10 * 10 * 0 + 9 * 8",
            "Answer": 77,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 10 * 0 * 13 * 2 + 7 * 5",
            "Answer": 42,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 17 * 10 * 15 * 6 + 14 * 9",
            "Answer": 15435,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 11 * 3 * 9 * 14 + 15 * 11",
            "Answer": 4330,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 4 * 14 * 2 * 11 + 4 * 18",
            "Answer": 1322,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 8 * 8 * 16 * 14 + 6 * 4",
            "Answer": 14360,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 4 * 15 * 7 * 12 + 0 * 18",
            "Answer": 5053,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 2 * 5 * 18 * 11 + 16 * 2",
            "Answer": 2026,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 16 * 7 * 12 * 14 + 2 * 8",
            "Answer": 18849,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 1 * 13 * 5 * 10 + 0 * 12",
            "Answer": 657,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 10 * 19 * 12 * 5 + 15 * 1",
            "Answer": 11416,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 18 * 8 * 7 * 6 + 16 * 14",
            "Answer": 6289,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 19 * 5 * 6 * 2 + 1 * 13",
            "Answer": 1168,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 12 * 16 * 19 * 17 + 12 * 16",
            "Answer": 62224,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 1 * 16 * 1 * 1 + 7 * 4",
            "Answer": 58,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 2 * 8 * 0 * 0 + 17 * 1",
            "Answer": 22,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 17 * 4 * 17 * 19 + 1 * 8",
            "Answer": 21982,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 4 * 8 * 2 * 12 + 3 * 14",
            "Answer": 818,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 4 * 12 * 8 * 17 + 19 * 14",
            "Answer": 6794,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 0 * 15 * 8 * 16 + 5 * 9",
            "Answer": 63,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 4 * 12 * 8 * 5 + 2 * 8",
            "Answer": 1952,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 19 * 12 * 15 * 3 + 19 * 14",
            "Answer": 10543,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 17 * 9 * 15 * 12 + 1 * 4",
            "Answer": 27552,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 5 * 8 * 16 * 18 + 10 * 0",
            "Answer": 11525,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 7 * 12 * 1 * 9 + 5 * 9",
            "Answer": 819,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 16 * 5 * 8 * 12 + 10 * 2",
            "Answer": 7713,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 10 * 6 * 14 * 15 + 1 * 11",
            "Answer": 12623,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 7 * 1 * 15 * 9 + 13 * 7",
            "Answer": 1055,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 0 * 8 * 1 * 12 + 17 * 11",
            "Answer": 197,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 6 * 13 * 5 * 14 + 15 * 18",
            "Answer": 5748,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 7 * 8 * 4 * 4 + 15 * 14",
            "Answer": 1114,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 3 * 8 * 1 * 10 + 2 * 12",
            "Answer": 276,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 13 * 10 * 7 * 2 + 10 * 8",
            "Answer": 1901,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 2 * 15 * 7 * 5 + 18 * 16",
            "Answer": 1350,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 7 * 8 * 17 * 13 + 18 * 9",
            "Answer": 12548,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 5 * 10 * 13 * 1 + 5 * 19",
            "Answer": 748,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 4 * 6 * 4 * 4 + 13 * 2",
            "Answer": 424,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 8 * 17 * 11 * 0 + 11 * 5",
            "Answer": 61,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 7 * 14 * 10 * 15 + 18 * 11",
            "Answer": 14911,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 19 * 13 * 12 * 10 + 0 * 0",
            "Answer": 29657,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 18 * 19 * 14 * 17 + 9 * 7",
            "Answer": 81468,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 12 * 12 * 18 * 3 + 4 * 0",
            "Answer": 7794,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 13 * 6 * 3 * 11 + 0 * 11",
            "Answer": 2587,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 6 * 3 * 11 * 10 + 13 * 2",
            "Answer": 2023,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 12 * 1 * 1 * 2 + 5 * 0",
            "Answer": 32,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 6 * 5 * 4 * 19 + 14 * 10",
            "Answer": 2435,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 10 * 18 * 9 * 0 + 17 * 1",
            "Answer": 24,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 4 * 4 * 6 * 6 + 3 * 17",
            "Answer": 633,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 14 * 6 * 4 * 12 + 9 * 19",
            "Answer": 4213,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 2 * 17 * 18 * 14 + 17 * 18",
            "Answer": 8893,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 3 * 13 * 3 * 16 + 11 * 8",
            "Answer": 1973,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 3 * 6 * 13 * 14 + 13 * 10",
            "Answer": 3406,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 0 * 0 * 11 * 19 + 15 * 15",
            "Answer": 240,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 12 * 6 * 15 * 15 + 5 * 9",
            "Answer": 16252,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 8 * 18 * 0 * 7 + 19 * 12",
            "Answer": 231,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 19 * 15 * 8 * 3 + 6 * 15",
            "Answer": 6947,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 4 * 7 * 2 * 18 + 0 * 17",
            "Answer": 1015,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 1 * 11 * 5 * 15 + 8 * 0",
            "Answer": 825,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 15 * 4 * 11 * 10 + 17 * 19",
            "Answer": 6936,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 17 * 13 * 0 * 5 + 14 * 19",
            "Answer": 277,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 6 * 19 * 16 * 11 + 6 * 8",
            "Answer": 20118,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 3 * 1 * 15 * 17 + 2 * 4",
            "Answer": 784,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 16 * 17 * 9 * 8 + 16 * 0",
            "Answer": 19599,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 3 * 8 * 2 * 17 + 7 * 5",
            "Answer": 860,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 4 * 1 * 6 * 5 + 7 * 1",
            "Answer": 127,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 18 * 6 * 12 * 7 + 4 * 9",
            "Answer": 9122,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 8 * 19 * 19 * 16 + 14 * 3",
            "Answer": 46266,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 6 * 18 * 15 * 0 + 7 * 4",
            "Answer": 33,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 12 * 9 * 4 * 11 + 4 * 4",
            "Answer": 4770,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 7 * 1 * 7 * 1 + 11 * 8",
            "Answer": 144,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 1 * 1 * 12 * 4 + 9 * 10",
            "Answer": 143,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 15 * 16 * 14 * 18 + 2 * 6",
            "Answer": 60493,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 2 * 0 * 7 * 16 + 17 * 12",
            "Answer": 221,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # * # + # * #"
        }
    ],
    "# + # * # * # + # + # + #": [
        {
            "Question": "15 + 16 * 10 * 5 + 6 + 11 + 0",
            "Answer": 832,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 7 * 7 * 11 + 18 + 7 + 10",
            "Answer": 575,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 15 * 2 * 19 + 1 + 13 + 9",
            "Answer": 606,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 1 * 18 * 12 + 10 + 1 + 17",
            "Answer": 245,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 10 * 2 * 8 + 14 + 15 + 16",
            "Answer": 211,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 4 * 8 * 2 + 11 + 2 + 2",
            "Answer": 88,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 8 * 15 * 6 + 4 + 19 + 8",
            "Answer": 764,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 15 * 7 * 9 + 18 + 0 + 11",
            "Answer": 985,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 1 * 18 * 17 + 12 + 6 + 19",
            "Answer": 355,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 15 * 9 * 18 + 8 + 16 + 2",
            "Answer": 2466,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 7 * 0 * 18 + 12 + 15 + 11",
            "Answer": 40,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 6 * 19 * 18 + 6 + 12 + 16",
            "Answer": 2093,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 12 * 4 * 6 + 6 + 5 + 10",
            "Answer": 328,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 10 * 4 * 9 + 2 + 9 + 12",
            "Answer": 386,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 18 * 18 * 0 + 1 + 16 + 9",
            "Answer": 43,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 3 * 4 * 0 + 1 + 10 + 6",
            "Answer": 25,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 16 * 8 * 14 + 19 + 0 + 0",
            "Answer": 1827,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 5 * 12 * 13 + 14 + 2 + 2",
            "Answer": 808,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 15 * 18 * 9 + 5 + 15 + 5",
            "Answer": 2465,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 9 * 12 * 1 + 17 + 17 + 13",
            "Answer": 163,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 14 * 15 * 1 + 5 + 11 + 4",
            "Answer": 234,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 19 * 1 * 12 + 1 + 8 + 2",
            "Answer": 246,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 8 * 0 * 15 + 18 + 19 + 14",
            "Answer": 55,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 4 * 8 * 0 + 9 + 9 + 17",
            "Answer": 47,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 18 * 1 * 10 + 6 + 2 + 6",
            "Answer": 210,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 4 * 12 * 19 + 10 + 15 + 12",
            "Answer": 952,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 13 * 16 * 8 + 4 + 18 + 1",
            "Answer": 1697,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 4 * 16 * 4 + 5 + 9 + 15",
            "Answer": 296,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 5 * 10 * 13 + 12 + 15 + 16",
            "Answer": 710,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 6 * 8 * 3 + 17 + 5 + 5",
            "Answer": 173,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 18 * 4 * 4 + 16 + 9 + 3",
            "Answer": 319,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 5 * 11 * 5 + 16 + 15 + 1",
            "Answer": 321,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 13 * 14 * 1 + 12 + 10 + 14",
            "Answer": 220,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 1 * 16 * 19 + 11 + 7 + 15",
            "Answer": 343,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 7 * 6 * 1 + 16 + 0 + 7",
            "Answer": 67,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 4 * 14 * 17 + 11 + 13 + 13",
            "Answer": 990,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 13 * 12 * 8 + 15 + 13 + 2",
            "Answer": 1286,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 1 * 0 * 1 + 13 + 15 + 18",
            "Answer": 59,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 19 * 16 * 12 + 16 + 10 + 18",
            "Answer": 3696,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 0 * 1 * 13 + 10 + 14 + 17",
            "Answer": 49,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 12 * 3 * 10 + 15 + 19 + 14",
            "Answer": 409,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 15 * 8 * 4 + 0 + 4 + 9",
            "Answer": 499,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 15 * 16 * 15 + 9 + 18 + 7",
            "Answer": 3652,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 2 * 7 * 5 + 14 + 14 + 12",
            "Answer": 126,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 0 * 4 * 19 + 10 + 18 + 16",
            "Answer": 47,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 15 * 18 * 14 + 0 + 11 + 13",
            "Answer": 3820,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 11 * 17 * 9 + 5 + 14 + 2",
            "Answer": 1710,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 0 * 7 * 19 + 3 + 6 + 12",
            "Answer": 28,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 5 * 13 * 18 + 18 + 19 + 8",
            "Answer": 1223,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 18 * 15 * 1 + 13 + 7 + 17",
            "Answer": 309,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 7 * 16 * 11 + 19 + 16 + 14",
            "Answer": 1282,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 14 * 14 * 0 + 13 + 5 + 2",
            "Answer": 24,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 8 * 10 * 17 + 7 + 17 + 0",
            "Answer": 1396,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 17 * 7 * 11 + 10 + 17 + 18",
            "Answer": 1361,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 0 * 2 * 14 + 1 + 9 + 18",
            "Answer": 43,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 4 * 14 * 12 + 18 + 14 + 13",
            "Answer": 730,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 7 * 12 * 5 + 18 + 10 + 9",
            "Answer": 463,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 6 * 5 * 18 + 4 + 15 + 10",
            "Answer": 587,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 11 * 13 * 13 + 8 + 7 + 11",
            "Answer": 1887,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 16 * 19 * 13 + 17 + 0 + 18",
            "Answer": 3998,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 13 * 8 * 16 + 3 + 19 + 10",
            "Answer": 1699,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 14 * 2 * 2 + 12 + 7 + 19",
            "Answer": 99,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 10 * 18 * 19 + 5 + 4 + 16",
            "Answer": 3462,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 7 * 13 * 6 + 13 + 17 + 15",
            "Answer": 609,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 19 * 2 * 19 + 4 + 0 + 4",
            "Answer": 744,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 8 * 11 * 1 + 4 + 15 + 19",
            "Answer": 127,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 6 * 11 * 2 + 2 + 0 + 16",
            "Answer": 153,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 0 * 3 * 18 + 10 + 1 + 2",
            "Answer": 32,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 12 * 7 * 17 + 3 + 14 + 0",
            "Answer": 1453,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 0 * 13 * 10 + 5 + 3 + 10",
            "Answer": 19,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 7 * 3 * 13 + 6 + 8 + 15",
            "Answer": 316,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 19 * 8 * 17 + 14 + 19 + 1",
            "Answer": 2631,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 11 * 9 * 15 + 3 + 15 + 1",
            "Answer": 1518,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 1 * 10 * 17 + 9 + 9 + 5",
            "Answer": 199,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 8 * 15 * 0 + 1 + 13 + 15",
            "Answer": 47,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 8 * 10 * 12 + 4 + 13 + 16",
            "Answer": 1011,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 12 * 18 * 8 + 19 + 10 + 10",
            "Answer": 1785,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 11 * 13 * 5 + 14 + 5 + 7",
            "Answer": 750,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 15 * 15 * 14 + 6 + 5 + 3",
            "Answer": 3175,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 7 * 11 * 15 + 0 + 18 + 0",
            "Answer": 1187,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 12 * 12 * 12 + 18 + 18 + 0",
            "Answer": 1775,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 14 * 9 * 3 + 13 + 11 + 18",
            "Answer": 425,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 18 * 10 * 18 + 1 + 14 + 8",
            "Answer": 3269,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 14 * 19 * 18 + 12 + 12 + 9",
            "Answer": 4830,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 3 * 0 * 13 + 16 + 12 + 6",
            "Answer": 41,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 2 * 5 * 12 + 15 + 9 + 18",
            "Answer": 167,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 14 * 3 * 15 + 7 + 16 + 8",
            "Answer": 664,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 13 * 6 * 8 + 19 + 13 + 11",
            "Answer": 679,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 12 * 8 * 14 + 17 + 17 + 9",
            "Answer": 1388,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 6 * 0 * 7 + 1 + 5 + 9",
            "Answer": 34,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 14 * 8 * 19 + 2 + 13 + 6",
            "Answer": 2165,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 10 * 2 * 19 + 10 + 0 + 10",
            "Answer": 418,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 1 * 8 * 6 + 7 + 7 + 15",
            "Answer": 85,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 13 * 3 * 3 + 12 + 15 + 9",
            "Answer": 160,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 19 * 4 * 8 + 12 + 2 + 14",
            "Answer": 654,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 17 * 14 * 19 + 13 + 3 + 12",
            "Answer": 4556,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 19 * 11 * 11 + 5 + 13 + 15",
            "Answer": 2344,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 19 * 18 * 11 + 2 + 18 + 11",
            "Answer": 3801,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 17 * 18 * 18 + 0 + 4 + 14",
            "Answer": 5534,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 0 * 4 * 13 + 6 + 12 + 8",
            "Answer": 27,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # + # + #"
        }
    ],
    "# + # * # + # * # + # + #": [
        {
            "Question": "13 + 19 * 17 + 15 * 3 + 10 + 13",
            "Answer": 404,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 4 * 9 + 18 * 19 + 10 + 18",
            "Answer": 422,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 5 * 4 + 10 * 13 + 5 + 16",
            "Answer": 189,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 0 * 7 + 14 * 12 + 13 + 19",
            "Answer": 219,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 14 * 15 + 7 * 6 + 18 + 7",
            "Answer": 289,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 5 * 12 + 11 * 19 + 19 + 1",
            "Answer": 298,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 1 * 10 + 13 * 15 + 19 + 6",
            "Answer": 242,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 5 * 13 + 12 * 10 + 18 + 16",
            "Answer": 227,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 7 * 5 + 0 * 15 + 8 + 9",
            "Answer": 71,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 8 * 16 + 1 * 9 + 4 + 11",
            "Answer": 152,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 12 * 0 + 16 * 7 + 16 + 7",
            "Answer": 135,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 8 * 6 + 3 * 16 + 4 + 10",
            "Answer": 125,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 7 * 6 + 2 * 18 + 18 + 10",
            "Answer": 114,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 15 * 16 + 4 * 0 + 17 + 19",
            "Answer": 280,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 18 * 4 + 0 * 16 + 15 + 15",
            "Answer": 110,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 6 * 14 + 4 * 15 + 9 + 4",
            "Answer": 172,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 14 * 12 + 2 * 6 + 10 + 11",
            "Answer": 205,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 6 * 9 + 15 * 17 + 15 + 8",
            "Answer": 339,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 12 * 13 + 5 * 13 + 1 + 2",
            "Answer": 225,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 9 * 14 + 10 * 19 + 10 + 9",
            "Answer": 350,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 13 * 13 + 19 * 13 + 7 + 0",
            "Answer": 442,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 3 * 10 + 2 * 7 + 16 + 16",
            "Answer": 83,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 12 * 8 + 19 * 10 + 4 + 10",
            "Answer": 312,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 13 * 18 + 16 * 4 + 13 + 18",
            "Answer": 343,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 11 * 15 + 18 * 3 + 19 + 9",
            "Answer": 262,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 7 * 2 + 17 * 11 + 19 + 12",
            "Answer": 250,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 11 * 9 + 4 * 14 + 16 + 14",
            "Answer": 199,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 4 * 19 + 15 * 9 + 14 + 7",
            "Answer": 245,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 11 * 0 + 13 * 1 + 9 + 0",
            "Answer": 30,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 4 * 4 + 3 * 16 + 17 + 14",
            "Answer": 108,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 7 * 16 + 18 * 18 + 18 + 13",
            "Answer": 476,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 6 * 16 + 4 * 2 + 8 + 6",
            "Answer": 128,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 6 * 5 + 15 * 18 + 14 + 2",
            "Answer": 331,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 0 * 19 + 1 * 4 + 10 + 1",
            "Answer": 19,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 8 * 12 + 0 * 15 + 7 + 16",
            "Answer": 130,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 17 * 19 + 4 * 19 + 1 + 19",
            "Answer": 423,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 4 * 16 + 19 * 8 + 16 + 19",
            "Answer": 254,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 3 * 7 + 7 * 11 + 13 + 8",
            "Answer": 137,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 4 * 8 + 13 * 8 + 8 + 13",
            "Answer": 159,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 2 * 0 + 19 * 3 + 9 + 5",
            "Answer": 79,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 3 * 10 + 16 * 0 + 6 + 10",
            "Answer": 46,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 8 * 17 + 11 * 4 + 13 + 2",
            "Answer": 200,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 1 * 0 + 5 * 4 + 5 + 19",
            "Answer": 52,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 16 * 11 + 17 * 3 + 10 + 3",
            "Answer": 256,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 11 * 2 + 15 * 0 + 5 + 13",
            "Answer": 43,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 5 * 3 + 10 * 4 + 3 + 17",
            "Answer": 85,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 19 * 3 + 16 * 1 + 6 + 11",
            "Answer": 92,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 19 * 10 + 19 * 19 + 13 + 10",
            "Answer": 589,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 7 * 0 + 6 * 10 + 11 + 8",
            "Answer": 89,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 16 * 14 + 3 * 14 + 13 + 10",
            "Answer": 292,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 4 * 17 + 12 * 12 + 0 + 15",
            "Answer": 238,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 17 * 4 + 5 * 10 + 14 + 18",
            "Answer": 155,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 7 * 16 + 16 * 15 + 19 + 13",
            "Answer": 395,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 12 * 2 + 10 * 16 + 6 + 9",
            "Answer": 201,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 14 * 16 + 17 * 18 + 1 + 19",
            "Answer": 560,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 4 * 4 + 5 * 5 + 10 + 1",
            "Answer": 57,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 8 * 14 + 1 * 14 + 17 + 3",
            "Answer": 149,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 14 * 9 + 19 * 16 + 14 + 4",
            "Answer": 457,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 8 * 18 + 18 * 7 + 4 + 13",
            "Answer": 295,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 9 * 5 + 14 * 16 + 9 + 13",
            "Answer": 292,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 8 * 4 + 14 * 2 + 2 + 0",
            "Answer": 64,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 17 * 11 + 18 * 5 + 13 + 16",
            "Answer": 321,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 2 * 19 + 2 * 3 + 7 + 0",
            "Answer": 59,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 17 * 16 + 4 * 8 + 17 + 10",
            "Answer": 346,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 9 * 8 + 3 * 8 + 0 + 8",
            "Answer": 113,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 1 * 8 + 2 * 14 + 0 + 0",
            "Answer": 52,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 16 * 11 + 14 * 2 + 2 + 16",
            "Answer": 227,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 6 * 9 + 8 * 3 + 17 + 15",
            "Answer": 121,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 12 * 9 + 14 * 15 + 6 + 4",
            "Answer": 333,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 0 * 16 + 5 * 8 + 2 + 1",
            "Answer": 49,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 0 * 1 + 14 * 9 + 8 + 11",
            "Answer": 160,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 5 * 19 + 6 * 1 + 13 + 2",
            "Answer": 124,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 13 * 0 + 3 * 12 + 6 + 7",
            "Answer": 54,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 11 * 4 + 12 * 2 + 6 + 14",
            "Answer": 93,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 11 * 18 + 7 * 5 + 10 + 6",
            "Answer": 254,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 17 * 2 + 16 * 5 + 2 + 3",
            "Answer": 136,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 15 * 16 + 0 * 15 + 7 + 17",
            "Answer": 270,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 9 * 1 + 16 * 19 + 4 + 6",
            "Answer": 337,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 16 * 19 + 2 * 14 + 11 + 6",
            "Answer": 365,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 13 * 17 + 4 * 2 + 17 + 1",
            "Answer": 250,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 17 * 3 + 16 * 6 + 11 + 1",
            "Answer": 164,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 2 * 0 + 3 * 11 + 3 + 19",
            "Answer": 73,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 9 * 0 + 9 * 11 + 13 + 13",
            "Answer": 139,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 19 * 19 + 9 * 8 + 8 + 0",
            "Answer": 441,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 8 * 7 + 11 * 9 + 11 + 17",
            "Answer": 194,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 13 * 9 + 8 * 11 + 0 + 9",
            "Answer": 230,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 1 * 13 + 16 * 17 + 2 + 12",
            "Answer": 300,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 7 * 19 + 12 * 11 + 0 + 0",
            "Answer": 273,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 1 * 0 + 1 * 14 + 15 + 3",
            "Answer": 38,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 2 * 5 + 18 * 11 + 11 + 8",
            "Answer": 229,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 12 * 13 + 5 * 6 + 19 + 11",
            "Answer": 221,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 0 * 8 + 12 * 14 + 9 + 0",
            "Answer": 191,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 19 * 0 + 9 * 1 + 13 + 7",
            "Answer": 43,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 19 * 10 + 17 * 10 + 18 + 7",
            "Answer": 403,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 11 * 3 + 6 * 11 + 11 + 10",
            "Answer": 120,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 18 * 6 + 19 * 7 + 3 + 8",
            "Answer": 263,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 19 * 7 + 14 * 16 + 12 + 18",
            "Answer": 396,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 4 * 2 + 18 * 5 + 13 + 17",
            "Answer": 141,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 7 * 7 + 4 * 10 + 13 + 11",
            "Answer": 128,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 15 * 15 + 0 * 1 + 6 + 16",
            "Answer": 263,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # + # * # + # + #"
        }
    ],
    "# * # + # * # + # + # + #": [
        {
            "Question": "8 * 11 + 13 * 4 + 13 + 1 + 6",
            "Answer": 160,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 0 + 12 * 1 + 10 + 4 + 1",
            "Answer": 27,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 3 + 16 * 17 + 0 + 10 + 1",
            "Answer": 322,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 8 + 11 * 12 + 12 + 12 + 5",
            "Answer": 185,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 9 + 18 * 13 + 12 + 0 + 2",
            "Answer": 320,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 4 + 11 * 8 + 11 + 6 + 4",
            "Answer": 181,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 9 + 13 * 17 + 7 + 2 + 0",
            "Answer": 275,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 18 + 19 * 16 + 1 + 5 + 4",
            "Answer": 314,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 2 + 5 * 19 + 13 + 5 + 11",
            "Answer": 130,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 16 + 14 * 3 + 6 + 5 + 0",
            "Answer": 293,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 12 + 14 * 12 + 12 + 17 + 16",
            "Answer": 309,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 0 + 5 * 10 + 2 + 16 + 17",
            "Answer": 85,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 17 + 8 * 0 + 1 + 5 + 0",
            "Answer": 312,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 0 + 9 * 3 + 11 + 16 + 12",
            "Answer": 66,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 4 + 18 * 7 + 9 + 18 + 2",
            "Answer": 175,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 12 + 9 * 5 + 14 + 5 + 18",
            "Answer": 106,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 19 + 17 * 8 + 1 + 0 + 4",
            "Answer": 502,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 7 + 9 * 16 + 19 + 15 + 12",
            "Answer": 218,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 5 + 17 * 0 + 3 + 9 + 6",
            "Answer": 18,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 2 + 3 * 16 + 15 + 2 + 2",
            "Answer": 77,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 2 + 0 * 6 + 16 + 10 + 2",
            "Answer": 66,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 3 + 3 * 5 + 4 + 7 + 2",
            "Answer": 40,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 4 + 6 * 5 + 11 + 3 + 6",
            "Answer": 106,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 15 + 0 * 13 + 11 + 5 + 10",
            "Answer": 41,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 15 + 0 * 6 + 15 + 4 + 3",
            "Answer": 217,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 17 + 5 * 11 + 9 + 14 + 9",
            "Answer": 87,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 7 + 8 * 16 + 3 + 5 + 3",
            "Answer": 146,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 2 + 15 * 9 + 12 + 5 + 18",
            "Answer": 206,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 4 + 10 * 19 + 19 + 1 + 6",
            "Answer": 288,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 9 + 14 * 14 + 0 + 5 + 5",
            "Answer": 215,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 18 + 18 * 11 + 11 + 7 + 4",
            "Answer": 328,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 11 + 5 * 16 + 4 + 4 + 8",
            "Answer": 206,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 5 + 6 * 17 + 17 + 4 + 16",
            "Answer": 184,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 14 + 18 * 11 + 2 + 6 + 19",
            "Answer": 225,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 11 + 13 * 4 + 14 + 17 + 18",
            "Answer": 101,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 1 + 7 * 9 + 4 + 3 + 13",
            "Answer": 100,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 8 + 8 * 3 + 15 + 16 + 8",
            "Answer": 87,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 17 + 18 * 13 + 6 + 0 + 2",
            "Answer": 514,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 4 + 4 * 10 + 2 + 1 + 13",
            "Answer": 112,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 10 + 8 * 0 + 16 + 8 + 15",
            "Answer": 219,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 10 + 4 * 16 + 7 + 1 + 1",
            "Answer": 243,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 12 + 18 * 16 + 15 + 6 + 10",
            "Answer": 523,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 0 + 11 * 7 + 2 + 14 + 4",
            "Answer": 97,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 7 + 4 * 6 + 10 + 5 + 8",
            "Answer": 110,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 9 + 6 * 17 + 1 + 15 + 9",
            "Answer": 199,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 18 + 0 * 13 + 11 + 15 + 12",
            "Answer": 272,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 7 + 0 * 0 + 19 + 10 + 13",
            "Answer": 105,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 17 + 12 * 15 + 15 + 10 + 15",
            "Answer": 475,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 12 + 12 * 12 + 0 + 13 + 12",
            "Answer": 301,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 4 + 1 * 6 + 0 + 16 + 11",
            "Answer": 77,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 2 + 10 * 7 + 3 + 4 + 2",
            "Answer": 107,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 4 + 1 * 12 + 3 + 14 + 13",
            "Answer": 90,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 17 + 2 * 12 + 19 + 0 + 19",
            "Answer": 249,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 12 + 12 * 8 + 16 + 19 + 14",
            "Answer": 337,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 1 + 13 * 10 + 19 + 11 + 3",
            "Answer": 167,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 12 + 16 * 19 + 17 + 10 + 19",
            "Answer": 578,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 5 + 10 * 6 + 12 + 3 + 19",
            "Answer": 174,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 18 + 0 * 2 + 9 + 13 + 11",
            "Answer": 69,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 14 + 3 * 9 + 11 + 1 + 15",
            "Answer": 278,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 12 + 11 * 14 + 4 + 8 + 14",
            "Answer": 240,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 15 + 8 * 18 + 12 + 0 + 9",
            "Answer": 285,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 6 + 2 * 10 + 4 + 18 + 13",
            "Answer": 163,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 5 + 16 * 15 + 0 + 1 + 13",
            "Answer": 334,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 4 + 16 * 1 + 8 + 14 + 12",
            "Answer": 70,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 11 + 13 * 15 + 8 + 1 + 6",
            "Answer": 353,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 15 + 15 * 9 + 9 + 10 + 18",
            "Answer": 322,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 4 + 2 * 9 + 3 + 10 + 8",
            "Answer": 79,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 13 + 18 * 6 + 8 + 2 + 4",
            "Answer": 239,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 18 + 9 * 4 + 8 + 8 + 3",
            "Answer": 289,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 11 + 10 * 14 + 18 + 7 + 16",
            "Answer": 346,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 2 + 14 * 12 + 7 + 7 + 16",
            "Answer": 224,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 13 + 16 * 5 + 18 + 16 + 14",
            "Answer": 297,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 12 + 5 * 17 + 7 + 0 + 2",
            "Answer": 166,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 13 + 7 * 19 + 1 + 11 + 11",
            "Answer": 169,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 7 + 5 * 6 + 2 + 10 + 17",
            "Answer": 143,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 6 + 8 * 2 + 1 + 0 + 5",
            "Answer": 124,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 7 + 12 * 9 + 18 + 9 + 17",
            "Answer": 257,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 3 + 13 * 8 + 7 + 1 + 15",
            "Answer": 166,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 16 + 5 * 0 + 2 + 4 + 5",
            "Answer": 283,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 17 + 5 * 9 + 8 + 13 + 6",
            "Answer": 157,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 3 + 3 * 17 + 5 + 0 + 9",
            "Answer": 68,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 3 + 1 * 9 + 7 + 8 + 14",
            "Answer": 56,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 15 + 11 * 15 + 4 + 9 + 11",
            "Answer": 339,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 0 + 14 * 9 + 9 + 7 + 7",
            "Answer": 149,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 2 + 8 * 2 + 6 + 6 + 17",
            "Answer": 61,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 6 + 14 * 3 + 9 + 2 + 8",
            "Answer": 175,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 2 + 10 * 13 + 16 + 12 + 10",
            "Answer": 174,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 0 + 9 * 6 + 12 + 13 + 5",
            "Answer": 84,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 11 + 13 * 10 + 11 + 5 + 7",
            "Answer": 219,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 7 + 15 * 8 + 14 + 12 + 3",
            "Answer": 254,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 15 + 19 * 7 + 16 + 11 + 16",
            "Answer": 251,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 7 + 7 * 19 + 12 + 16 + 17",
            "Answer": 178,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 12 + 19 * 12 + 18 + 6 + 11",
            "Answer": 371,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 1 + 12 * 7 + 12 + 10 + 5",
            "Answer": 125,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 14 + 17 * 14 + 1 + 7 + 19",
            "Answer": 363,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 13 + 5 * 9 + 7 + 0 + 5",
            "Answer": 148,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 10 + 11 * 6 + 9 + 14 + 17",
            "Answer": 116,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 16 + 13 * 2 + 6 + 7 + 10",
            "Answer": 145,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 14 + 16 * 14 + 14 + 19 + 8",
            "Answer": 265,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 10 + 16 * 7 + 13 + 11 + 11",
            "Answer": 187,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # + # + # + #"
        }
    ],
    "# * # * # * # * # + # + #": [
        {
            "Question": "10 * 0 * 6 * 0 * 10 + 18 + 14",
            "Answer": 32,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 18 * 1 * 12 * 6 + 2 + 10",
            "Answer": 20748,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 9 * 16 * 5 * 3 + 12 + 15",
            "Answer": 2187,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 1 * 6 * 19 * 13 + 4 + 6",
            "Answer": 4456,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 3 * 15 * 19 * 14 + 16 + 11",
            "Answer": 11997,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 13 * 13 * 14 * 4 + 11 + 14",
            "Answer": 132521,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 11 * 0 * 1 * 4 + 1 + 6",
            "Answer": 7,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 12 * 17 * 12 * 0 + 11 + 16",
            "Answer": 27,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 15 * 3 * 8 * 17 + 6 + 5",
            "Answer": 85691,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 14 * 1 * 9 * 16 + 11 + 19",
            "Answer": 34302,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 9 * 0 * 8 * 15 + 13 + 12",
            "Answer": 25,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 19 * 17 * 17 * 8 + 15 + 2",
            "Answer": 571081,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 8 * 11 * 3 * 15 + 1 + 2",
            "Answer": 75243,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 1 * 1 * 9 * 5 + 18 + 8",
            "Answer": 881,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 16 * 19 * 17 * 16 + 13 + 10",
            "Answer": 578839,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 4 * 11 * 11 * 1 + 4 + 10",
            "Answer": 982,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 18 * 15 * 18 * 0 + 16 + 6",
            "Answer": 22,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 11 * 14 * 15 * 3 + 2 + 14",
            "Answer": 6946,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 16 * 2 * 18 * 15 + 4 + 18",
            "Answer": 138262,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 14 * 1 * 3 * 12 + 7 + 5",
            "Answer": 7068,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 7 * 17 * 17 * 0 + 19 + 4",
            "Answer": 23,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 14 * 7 * 10 * 2 + 3 + 15",
            "Answer": 15698,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 8 * 15 * 15 * 10 + 11 + 19",
            "Answer": 18030,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 14 * 3 * 13 * 2 + 7 + 5",
            "Answer": 18576,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 3 * 5 * 0 * 6 + 2 + 12",
            "Answer": 14,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 0 * 4 * 11 * 9 + 5 + 14",
            "Answer": 19,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 15 * 16 * 5 * 13 + 18 + 17",
            "Answer": 109235,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 18 * 13 * 3 * 7 + 11 + 11",
            "Answer": 24592,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 3 * 18 * 18 * 17 + 1 + 17",
            "Answer": 66114,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 6 * 18 * 3 * 1 + 5 + 0",
            "Answer": 6161,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 14 * 3 * 4 * 5 + 7 + 2",
            "Answer": 7569,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 4 * 14 * 2 * 11 + 16 + 7",
            "Answer": 2487,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 2 * 3 * 4 * 0 + 1 + 15",
            "Answer": 16,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 4 * 15 * 16 * 15 + 13 + 5",
            "Answer": 115218,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 10 * 19 * 2 * 2 + 12 + 14",
            "Answer": 5346,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 10 * 10 * 6 * 6 + 7 + 19",
            "Answer": 64826,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 1 * 7 * 17 * 9 + 8 + 0",
            "Answer": 12860,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 11 * 13 * 8 * 12 + 17 + 13",
            "Answer": 178494,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 17 * 7 * 2 * 1 + 19 + 9",
            "Answer": 2884,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 9 * 7 * 15 * 1 + 12 + 3",
            "Answer": 1905,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 14 * 1 * 19 * 18 + 7 + 7",
            "Answer": 90986,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 12 * 5 * 11 * 3 + 1 + 0",
            "Answer": 21781,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 9 * 1 * 11 * 12 + 0 + 1",
            "Answer": 22573,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 12 * 6 * 5 * 7 + 3 + 8",
            "Answer": 10091,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 16 * 3 * 6 * 15 + 5 + 7",
            "Answer": 82092,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 6 * 8 * 16 * 14 + 10 + 8",
            "Answer": 96786,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 17 * 12 * 6 * 1 + 13 + 2",
            "Answer": 23271,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 12 * 9 * 17 * 6 + 7 + 13",
            "Answer": 22052,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 15 * 13 * 13 * 6 + 7 + 7",
            "Answer": 182534,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 19 * 11 * 14 * 0 + 5 + 13",
            "Answer": 18,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 0 * 18 * 19 * 6 + 7 + 2",
            "Answer": 9,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 11 * 5 * 16 * 14 + 1 + 7",
            "Answer": 135528,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 3 * 6 * 8 * 7 + 17 + 4",
            "Answer": 12117,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 7 * 19 * 14 * 16 + 18 + 0",
            "Answer": 268146,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 12 * 18 * 1 * 16 + 12 + 2",
            "Answer": 3470,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 16 * 15 * 13 * 11 + 11 + 1",
            "Answer": 514812,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 19 * 18 * 1 * 17 + 8 + 4",
            "Answer": 93036,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 17 * 1 * 18 * 15 + 6 + 19",
            "Answer": 82645,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 12 * 19 * 19 * 17 + 7 + 4",
            "Answer": 810095,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 7 * 18 * 13 * 19 + 15 + 1",
            "Answer": 155626,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 11 * 15 * 9 * 2 + 19 + 19",
            "Answer": 26768,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 2 * 8 * 12 * 3 + 9 + 15",
            "Answer": 600,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 6 * 19 * 18 * 5 + 14 + 14",
            "Answer": 194968,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 19 * 7 * 4 * 9 + 10 + 14",
            "Answer": 81420,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 3 * 8 * 8 * 14 + 5 + 18",
            "Answer": 10775,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 8 * 9 * 10 * 4 + 12 + 19",
            "Answer": 43231,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 6 * 4 * 0 * 19 + 6 + 4",
            "Answer": 10,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 13 * 4 * 6 * 10 + 9 + 10",
            "Answer": 34339,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 9 * 16 * 4 * 8 + 7 + 9",
            "Answer": 27664,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 19 * 16 * 16 * 6 + 7 + 0",
            "Answer": 350215,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 9 * 9 * 14 * 9 + 9 + 17",
            "Answer": 10232,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 15 * 12 * 15 * 6 + 9 + 12",
            "Answer": 226821,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 2 * 2 * 8 * 15 + 10 + 4",
            "Answer": 494,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 16 * 0 * 19 * 11 + 15 + 7",
            "Answer": 22,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 9 * 18 * 11 * 4 + 16 + 8",
            "Answer": 71304,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 11 * 0 * 12 * 14 + 11 + 2",
            "Answer": 13,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 18 * 8 * 11 * 18 + 1 + 2",
            "Answer": 484707,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 17 * 7 * 13 * 7 + 4 + 5",
            "Answer": 64983,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 19 * 1 * 10 * 15 + 1 + 17",
            "Answer": 22818,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 11 * 14 * 5 * 7 + 11 + 17",
            "Answer": 91658,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 17 * 2 * 4 * 9 + 5 + 0",
            "Answer": 1229,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 19 * 2 * 7 * 11 + 13 + 2",
            "Answer": 23423,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 14 * 17 * 6 * 11 + 13 + 10",
            "Answer": 141395,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 8 * 11 * 10 * 19 + 19 + 8",
            "Answer": 167227,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 3 * 16 * 2 * 15 + 7 + 14",
            "Answer": 23061,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 8 * 12 * 17 * 11 + 11 + 8",
            "Answer": 215443,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 6 * 10 * 8 * 11 + 18 + 15",
            "Answer": 15873,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 3 * 2 * 0 * 10 + 1 + 16",
            "Answer": 17,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 12 * 3 * 0 * 10 + 8 + 5",
            "Answer": 13,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 14 * 12 * 6 * 10 + 13 + 6",
            "Answer": 191539,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 9 * 16 * 12 * 8 + 6 + 0",
            "Answer": 124422,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 12 * 0 * 0 * 18 + 17 + 9",
            "Answer": 26,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 8 * 9 * 8 * 4 + 16 + 12",
            "Answer": 13852,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 5 * 11 * 14 * 10 + 13 + 16",
            "Answer": 100129,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 2 * 8 * 13 * 9 + 16 + 4",
            "Answer": 11252,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 13 * 2 * 1 * 8 + 17 + 9",
            "Answer": 2522,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 7 * 4 * 11 * 14 + 1 + 0",
            "Answer": 34497,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 17 * 5 * 6 * 16 + 18 + 16",
            "Answer": 73474,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 12 * 12 * 14 * 6 + 4 + 9",
            "Answer": 13,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 10 * 5 * 18 * 3 + 10 + 1",
            "Answer": 16211,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # * # + # + #"
        }
    ],
    "# * # * # + # + # + # + #": [
        {
            "Question": "2 * 9 * 10 + 4 + 0 + 6 + 0",
            "Answer": 190,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 16 * 15 + 2 + 7 + 0 + 5",
            "Answer": 1214,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 7 * 3 + 14 + 1 + 0 + 4",
            "Answer": 82,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 9 * 17 + 2 + 18 + 11 + 15",
            "Answer": 1270,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 11 * 11 + 14 + 9 + 1 + 10",
            "Answer": 639,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 9 * 19 + 11 + 4 + 6 + 5",
            "Answer": 3275,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 0 * 19 + 5 + 5 + 9 + 11",
            "Answer": 30,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 14 * 16 + 18 + 17 + 2 + 9",
            "Answer": 2510,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 8 * 15 + 16 + 2 + 1 + 8",
            "Answer": 1707,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 7 * 9 + 11 + 14 + 4 + 18",
            "Answer": 110,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 1 * 3 + 16 + 18 + 16 + 14",
            "Answer": 79,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 4 * 4 + 14 + 0 + 7 + 11",
            "Answer": 288,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 2 * 5 + 5 + 6 + 7 + 2",
            "Answer": 20,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 4 * 8 + 12 + 14 + 10 + 7",
            "Answer": 491,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 1 * 17 + 13 + 11 + 1 + 13",
            "Answer": 174,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 6 * 12 + 17 + 8 + 5 + 11",
            "Answer": 41,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 11 * 15 + 18 + 7 + 19 + 3",
            "Answer": 377,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 8 * 13 + 18 + 5 + 14 + 4",
            "Answer": 1185,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 5 * 6 + 5 + 15 + 9 + 4",
            "Answer": 303,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 12 * 1 + 10 + 4 + 11 + 9",
            "Answer": 262,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 19 * 14 + 12 + 15 + 15 + 10",
            "Answer": 4840,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 15 * 9 + 16 + 11 + 16 + 18",
            "Answer": 1141,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 16 * 7 + 2 + 9 + 18 + 18",
            "Answer": 1951,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 1 * 2 + 6 + 6 + 4 + 6",
            "Answer": 58,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 3 * 9 + 16 + 13 + 7 + 17",
            "Answer": 485,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 10 * 12 + 9 + 3 + 15 + 15",
            "Answer": 402,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 19 * 6 + 15 + 3 + 1 + 1",
            "Answer": 1616,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 4 * 19 + 17 + 19 + 11 + 4",
            "Answer": 811,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 18 * 8 + 15 + 17 + 0 + 12",
            "Answer": 1772,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 12 * 3 + 6 + 3 + 5 + 12",
            "Answer": 62,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 13 * 8 + 7 + 7 + 5 + 10",
            "Answer": 29,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 15 * 0 + 19 + 9 + 15 + 8",
            "Answer": 51,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 10 * 9 + 5 + 6 + 7 + 5",
            "Answer": 653,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 0 * 12 + 1 + 13 + 11 + 18",
            "Answer": 43,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 5 * 4 + 8 + 19 + 9 + 16",
            "Answer": 432,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 4 * 3 + 16 + 14 + 11 + 16",
            "Answer": 105,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 18 * 3 + 18 + 16 + 6 + 15",
            "Answer": 1027,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 10 * 1 + 19 + 1 + 9 + 4",
            "Answer": 163,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 19 * 0 + 8 + 10 + 8 + 6",
            "Answer": 32,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 15 * 3 + 8 + 4 + 15 + 15",
            "Answer": 807,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 3 * 3 + 11 + 0 + 16 + 4",
            "Answer": 76,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 19 * 7 + 6 + 14 + 12 + 4",
            "Answer": 1100,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 3 * 8 + 16 + 12 + 18 + 16",
            "Answer": 134,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 16 * 1 + 11 + 17 + 16 + 1",
            "Answer": 333,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 0 * 3 + 1 + 15 + 0 + 2",
            "Answer": 18,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 1 * 14 + 11 + 11 + 19 + 12",
            "Answer": 109,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 1 * 9 + 14 + 14 + 2 + 3",
            "Answer": 204,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 12 * 8 + 15 + 10 + 12 + 6",
            "Answer": 427,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 19 * 1 + 2 + 8 + 3 + 4",
            "Answer": 55,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 9 * 10 + 16 + 11 + 4 + 14",
            "Answer": 1395,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 11 * 1 + 19 + 10 + 8 + 16",
            "Answer": 119,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 19 * 7 + 16 + 7 + 12 + 13",
            "Answer": 1112,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 17 * 10 + 13 + 12 + 8 + 19",
            "Answer": 1072,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 19 * 10 + 14 + 13 + 16 + 11",
            "Answer": 434,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 0 * 1 + 1 + 13 + 16 + 11",
            "Answer": 41,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 4 * 9 + 1 + 6 + 0 + 13",
            "Answer": 344,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 7 * 4 + 8 + 9 + 15 + 10",
            "Answer": 210,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 2 * 1 + 14 + 3 + 12 + 14",
            "Answer": 63,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 11 * 17 + 16 + 19 + 0 + 14",
            "Answer": 1545,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 7 * 19 + 2 + 13 + 3 + 18",
            "Answer": 435,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 2 * 13 + 9 + 11 + 14 + 15",
            "Answer": 179,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 8 * 11 + 18 + 12 + 18 + 5",
            "Answer": 1021,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 2 * 0 + 2 + 2 + 0 + 1",
            "Answer": 5,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 11 * 4 + 15 + 1 + 17 + 4",
            "Answer": 389,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 18 * 9 + 17 + 8 + 7 + 1",
            "Answer": 2949,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 16 * 10 + 8 + 11 + 13 + 6",
            "Answer": 2438,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 12 * 5 + 18 + 18 + 18 + 0",
            "Answer": 1134,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 8 * 7 + 1 + 4 + 11 + 14",
            "Answer": 870,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 6 * 19 + 4 + 2 + 11 + 6",
            "Answer": 1391,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 6 * 12 + 14 + 3 + 1 + 7",
            "Answer": 241,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 0 * 3 + 8 + 0 + 15 + 5",
            "Answer": 28,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 17 * 1 + 10 + 15 + 10 + 3",
            "Answer": 344,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 15 * 18 + 0 + 4 + 0 + 3",
            "Answer": 1087,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 6 * 12 + 10 + 2 + 6 + 18",
            "Answer": 1332,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 0 * 15 + 14 + 0 + 2 + 3",
            "Answer": 19,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 19 * 18 + 17 + 4 + 12 + 2",
            "Answer": 2771,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 3 * 13 + 12 + 9 + 19 + 4",
            "Answer": 512,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 10 * 11 + 9 + 10 + 12 + 8",
            "Answer": 589,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 15 * 1 + 3 + 1 + 4 + 14",
            "Answer": 67,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 7 * 16 + 18 + 8 + 17 + 0",
            "Answer": 827,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 13 * 7 + 13 + 5 + 12 + 1",
            "Answer": 1123,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 17 * 18 + 12 + 15 + 13 + 1",
            "Answer": 5243,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 19 * 13 + 3 + 9 + 7 + 0",
            "Answer": 1995,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 6 * 13 + 15 + 6 + 8 + 15",
            "Answer": 590,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 6 * 17 + 7 + 16 + 11 + 9",
            "Answer": 1675,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 17 * 7 + 7 + 4 + 16 + 16",
            "Answer": 995,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 1 * 10 + 2 + 18 + 7 + 10",
            "Answer": 217,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 13 * 17 + 6 + 5 + 10 + 10",
            "Answer": 473,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 13 * 9 + 10 + 11 + 19 + 13",
            "Answer": 1691,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 12 * 0 + 4 + 17 + 3 + 11",
            "Answer": 35,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 9 * 4 + 19 + 4 + 5 + 16",
            "Answer": 80,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 2 * 17 + 11 + 13 + 12 + 4",
            "Answer": 618,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 9 * 2 + 7 + 0 + 12 + 18",
            "Answer": 73,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 12 * 11 + 10 + 4 + 15 + 9",
            "Answer": 2282,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 5 * 16 + 7 + 18 + 17 + 15",
            "Answer": 1577,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 16 * 0 + 11 + 12 + 18 + 0",
            "Answer": 41,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 16 * 19 + 8 + 17 + 11 + 8",
            "Answer": 5820,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 1 * 18 + 15 + 8 + 2 + 14",
            "Answer": 291,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 10 * 5 + 14 + 12 + 14 + 16",
            "Answer": 506,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 13 * 4 + 8 + 18 + 7 + 16",
            "Answer": 153,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # + # + #"
        }
    ],
    "# * # * # * # + # + # * #": [
        {
            "Question": "18 * 19 * 13 * 4 + 13 + 2 * 11",
            "Answer": 17819,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 8 * 1 * 9 + 10 + 7 * 3",
            "Answer": 751,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 9 * 7 * 14 + 15 + 13 * 17",
            "Answer": 16112,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 19 * 18 * 6 + 8 + 17 * 17",
            "Answer": 10557,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 6 * 13 * 15 + 10 + 5 * 13",
            "Answer": 3585,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 18 * 14 * 11 + 9 + 14 * 4",
            "Answer": 41645,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 10 * 18 * 16 + 8 + 2 * 4",
            "Answer": 28816,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 5 * 19 * 5 + 11 + 11 * 9",
            "Answer": 110,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 4 * 1 * 16 + 1 + 1 * 12",
            "Answer": 461,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 4 * 15 * 18 + 15 + 13 * 5",
            "Answer": 13040,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 9 * 11 * 14 + 8 + 10 * 4",
            "Answer": 5592,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 17 * 15 * 18 + 4 + 2 * 6",
            "Answer": 82636,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 18 * 12 * 2 + 11 + 4 * 17",
            "Answer": 1375,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 9 * 15 * 19 + 12 + 11 * 14",
            "Answer": 166,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 11 * 18 * 13 + 0 + 15 * 14",
            "Answer": 43968,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 17 * 10 * 13 + 1 + 15 * 6",
            "Answer": 91,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 10 * 1 * 1 + 11 + 16 * 0",
            "Answer": 151,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 15 * 17 * 9 + 19 + 11 * 2",
            "Answer": 22991,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 13 * 17 * 5 + 2 + 17 * 9",
            "Answer": 8995,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 18 * 19 * 0 + 18 + 7 * 4",
            "Answer": 46,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 11 * 2 * 4 + 10 + 1 * 2",
            "Answer": 1332,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 18 * 18 * 14 + 19 + 19 * 5",
            "Answer": 63618,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 15 * 12 * 8 + 4 + 19 * 4",
            "Answer": 21680,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 5 * 6 * 6 + 4 + 15 * 10",
            "Answer": 334,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 15 * 18 * 16 + 14 + 11 * 8",
            "Answer": 47622,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 19 * 7 * 2 + 17 + 17 * 17",
            "Answer": 3764,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 1 * 14 * 19 + 16 + 19 * 7",
            "Answer": 3075,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 16 * 15 * 12 + 19 + 2 * 8",
            "Answer": 28835,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 19 * 13 * 16 + 8 + 18 * 14",
            "Answer": 43732,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 17 * 3 * 13 + 3 + 15 * 17",
            "Answer": 6225,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 16 * 12 * 17 + 3 + 15 * 18",
            "Answer": 32913,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 18 * 13 * 12 + 13 + 6 * 19",
            "Answer": 36631,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 19 * 6 * 10 + 18 + 18 * 19",
            "Answer": 7200,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 8 * 11 * 3 + 1 + 2 * 6",
            "Answer": 541,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 13 * 2 * 0 + 19 + 16 * 19",
            "Answer": 323,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 9 * 2 * 1 + 8 + 12 * 11",
            "Answer": 410,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 1 * 2 * 14 + 4 + 17 * 14",
            "Answer": 466,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 19 * 16 * 13 + 12 + 0 * 1",
            "Answer": 39532,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 14 * 17 * 11 + 9 + 9 * 0",
            "Answer": 20953,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 17 * 2 * 3 + 16 + 6 * 12",
            "Answer": 1414,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 15 * 1 * 6 + 2 + 14 * 8",
            "Answer": 114,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 5 * 17 * 3 + 0 + 3 * 6",
            "Answer": 4608,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 2 * 12 * 17 + 9 + 12 * 19",
            "Answer": 237,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 0 * 12 * 13 + 18 + 3 * 13",
            "Answer": 57,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 9 * 10 * 11 + 9 + 19 * 18",
            "Answer": 351,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 13 * 18 * 16 + 2 + 6 * 7",
            "Answer": 44972,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 15 * 2 * 12 + 12 + 9 * 15",
            "Answer": 507,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 16 * 7 * 7 + 6 + 4 * 18",
            "Answer": 13406,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 10 * 15 * 18 + 5 + 12 * 15",
            "Answer": 13685,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 14 * 18 * 11 + 7 + 13 * 9",
            "Answer": 16756,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 6 * 15 * 14 + 14 + 0 * 18",
            "Answer": 23954,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 9 * 17 * 7 + 2 + 7 * 5",
            "Answer": 7534,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 13 * 12 * 3 + 3 + 17 * 5",
            "Answer": 7108,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 11 * 11 * 13 + 0 + 1 * 3",
            "Answer": 14160,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 4 * 12 * 1 + 16 + 11 * 1",
            "Answer": 555,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 18 * 15 * 13 + 0 + 1 * 16",
            "Answer": 16,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 7 * 9 * 0 + 13 + 13 * 6",
            "Answer": 91,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 12 * 6 * 16 + 8 + 17 * 3",
            "Answer": 16187,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 10 * 18 * 10 + 14 + 9 * 8",
            "Answer": 86,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 15 * 16 * 1 + 15 + 16 * 2",
            "Answer": 527,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 19 * 13 * 0 + 13 + 10 * 19",
            "Answer": 203,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 15 * 7 * 4 + 8 + 5 * 5",
            "Answer": 5493,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 2 * 2 * 4 + 0 + 0 * 18",
            "Answer": 288,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 1 * 15 * 11 + 16 + 18 * 19",
            "Answer": 2173,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 19 * 17 * 1 + 18 + 2 * 18",
            "Answer": 2315,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 7 * 8 * 18 + 17 + 10 * 10",
            "Answer": 8181,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 0 * 17 * 11 + 13 + 10 * 12",
            "Answer": 133,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 15 * 18 * 3 + 11 + 5 * 0",
            "Answer": 11351,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 6 * 6 * 2 + 8 + 14 * 1",
            "Answer": 22,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 18 * 14 * 7 + 11 + 7 * 12",
            "Answer": 31847,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 13 * 8 * 10 + 7 + 5 * 19",
            "Answer": 102,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 19 * 2 * 7 + 10 + 18 * 14",
            "Answer": 3720,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 1 * 12 * 10 + 2 + 18 * 13",
            "Answer": 356,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 3 * 5 * 14 + 15 + 9 * 17",
            "Answer": 3318,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 4 * 15 * 7 + 2 + 16 * 11",
            "Answer": 1438,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 4 * 3 * 16 + 7 + 5 * 1",
            "Answer": 2316,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 13 * 10 * 13 + 1 + 7 * 14",
            "Answer": 25449,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 9 * 5 * 8 + 3 + 10 * 17",
            "Answer": 893,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 18 * 7 * 15 + 7 + 16 * 7",
            "Answer": 7679,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 7 * 19 * 6 + 1 + 7 * 13",
            "Answer": 1688,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 12 * 10 * 18 + 0 + 17 * 17",
            "Answer": 289,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 6 * 17 * 14 + 3 + 18 * 5",
            "Answer": 10089,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 18 * 6 * 18 + 18 + 11 * 1",
            "Answer": 5861,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 3 * 15 * 14 + 9 + 5 * 11",
            "Answer": 9514,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 1 * 3 * 16 + 18 + 9 * 2",
            "Answer": 708,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 14 * 6 * 4 + 15 + 0 * 1",
            "Answer": 5727,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 12 * 14 * 7 + 14 + 17 * 14",
            "Answer": 16716,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 7 * 15 * 9 + 19 + 8 * 19",
            "Answer": 3951,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 0 * 19 * 11 + 12 + 1 * 0",
            "Answer": 12,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 13 * 19 * 19 + 11 + 19 * 7",
            "Answer": 28302,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 9 * 0 * 7 + 6 + 16 * 19",
            "Answer": 310,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 11 * 1 * 17 + 12 + 14 * 6",
            "Answer": 844,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 11 * 18 * 8 + 15 + 5 * 14",
            "Answer": 28597,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 17 * 2 * 8 + 12 + 15 * 0",
            "Answer": 2732,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 17 * 0 * 0 + 13 + 10 * 3",
            "Answer": 43,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 5 * 5 * 7 + 19 + 13 * 15",
            "Answer": 3014,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 16 * 7 * 12 + 10 + 4 * 5",
            "Answer": 21534,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 4 * 16 * 18 + 10 + 17 * 18",
            "Answer": 316,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 19 * 6 * 7 + 6 + 12 * 12",
            "Answer": 3342,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 5 * 18 * 9 + 7 + 3 * 18",
            "Answer": 13831,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # * #"
        }
    ],
    "# * # + # + # * # + # + #": [
        {
            "Question": "4 * 5 + 2 + 6 * 18 + 19 + 15",
            "Answer": 164,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 17 + 14 + 5 * 13 + 10 + 15",
            "Answer": 410,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 7 + 1 + 12 * 8 + 17 + 0",
            "Answer": 205,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 16 + 15 + 4 * 12 + 4 + 15",
            "Answer": 82,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 9 + 8 + 9 * 13 + 8 + 5",
            "Answer": 255,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 14 + 7 + 18 * 16 + 11 + 9",
            "Answer": 525,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 8 + 0 + 3 * 14 + 13 + 1",
            "Answer": 152,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 3 + 10 + 9 * 1 + 0 + 0",
            "Answer": 76,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 6 + 19 + 16 * 19 + 14 + 16",
            "Answer": 455,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 3 + 10 + 14 * 18 + 6 + 12",
            "Answer": 325,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 8 + 15 + 7 * 12 + 15 + 18",
            "Answer": 148,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 1 + 14 + 12 * 15 + 4 + 16",
            "Answer": 223,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 11 + 3 + 16 * 11 + 9 + 9",
            "Answer": 252,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 6 + 5 + 17 * 6 + 14 + 8",
            "Answer": 219,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 18 + 19 + 7 * 17 + 17 + 10",
            "Answer": 489,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 7 + 19 + 10 * 10 + 19 + 13",
            "Answer": 235,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 10 + 17 + 1 * 1 + 19 + 18",
            "Answer": 165,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 17 + 1 + 19 * 13 + 15 + 6",
            "Answer": 422,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 10 + 13 + 8 * 4 + 7 + 10",
            "Answer": 192,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 9 + 14 + 1 * 14 + 0 + 3",
            "Answer": 31,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 5 + 0 + 14 * 15 + 14 + 0",
            "Answer": 229,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 9 + 19 + 1 * 4 + 5 + 8",
            "Answer": 99,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 11 + 16 + 18 * 11 + 13 + 9",
            "Answer": 357,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 8 + 4 + 2 * 9 + 0 + 1",
            "Answer": 151,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 5 + 2 + 7 * 18 + 18 + 11",
            "Answer": 252,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 1 + 5 + 15 * 13 + 4 + 7",
            "Answer": 211,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 5 + 15 + 1 * 0 + 1 + 4",
            "Answer": 110,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 16 + 5 + 11 * 13 + 5 + 5",
            "Answer": 222,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 1 + 2 + 9 * 11 + 10 + 19",
            "Answer": 138,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 8 + 13 + 3 * 0 + 6 + 1",
            "Answer": 92,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 16 + 16 + 17 * 15 + 6 + 15",
            "Answer": 324,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 10 + 18 + 11 * 3 + 10 + 5",
            "Answer": 76,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 15 + 0 + 1 * 11 + 7 + 15",
            "Answer": 183,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 2 + 2 + 18 * 5 + 0 + 11",
            "Answer": 119,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 4 + 2 + 6 * 10 + 3 + 3",
            "Answer": 104,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 12 + 14 + 16 * 9 + 0 + 1",
            "Answer": 231,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 2 + 6 + 9 * 18 + 9 + 2",
            "Answer": 191,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 7 + 0 + 2 * 16 + 17 + 3",
            "Answer": 80,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 9 + 10 + 7 * 3 + 3 + 18",
            "Answer": 151,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 6 + 19 + 16 * 19 + 14 + 10",
            "Answer": 395,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 0 + 14 + 15 * 8 + 19 + 4",
            "Answer": 157,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 18 + 2 + 7 * 9 + 7 + 0",
            "Answer": 324,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 15 + 3 + 15 * 18 + 4 + 9",
            "Answer": 361,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 15 + 7 + 12 * 12 + 9 + 2",
            "Answer": 342,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 15 + 3 + 7 * 3 + 0 + 13",
            "Answer": 232,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 14 + 8 + 10 * 17 + 17 + 1",
            "Answer": 210,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 12 + 1 + 1 * 13 + 9 + 12",
            "Answer": 263,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 19 + 3 + 6 * 3 + 16 + 13",
            "Answer": 278,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 8 + 16 + 14 * 10 + 6 + 17",
            "Answer": 323,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 12 + 1 + 3 * 13 + 3 + 9",
            "Answer": 52,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 3 + 13 + 19 * 5 + 6 + 13",
            "Answer": 184,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 17 + 1 + 17 * 16 + 15 + 9",
            "Answer": 586,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 6 + 6 + 7 * 13 + 2 + 11",
            "Answer": 206,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 8 + 6 + 7 * 14 + 11 + 16",
            "Answer": 147,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 10 + 5 + 16 * 19 + 10 + 17",
            "Answer": 466,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 19 + 3 + 2 * 13 + 7 + 1",
            "Answer": 37,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 13 + 11 + 13 * 16 + 3 + 1",
            "Answer": 392,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 2 + 18 + 17 * 13 + 12 + 16",
            "Answer": 293,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 11 + 3 + 9 * 4 + 19 + 11",
            "Answer": 201,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 19 + 19 + 2 * 8 + 13 + 5",
            "Answer": 53,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 16 + 7 + 14 * 5 + 5 + 1",
            "Answer": 83,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 3 + 12 + 13 * 19 + 10 + 8",
            "Answer": 277,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 10 + 6 + 6 * 14 + 4 + 1",
            "Answer": 265,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 2 + 7 + 8 * 17 + 4 + 9",
            "Answer": 170,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 14 + 7 + 0 * 18 + 19 + 19",
            "Answer": 59,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 5 + 9 + 11 * 2 + 9 + 10",
            "Answer": 115,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 6 + 9 + 6 * 2 + 0 + 17",
            "Answer": 122,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 14 + 13 + 6 * 4 + 3 + 1",
            "Answer": 195,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 0 + 2 + 14 * 15 + 4 + 8",
            "Answer": 224,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 10 + 1 + 8 * 9 + 12 + 17",
            "Answer": 212,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 16 + 16 + 6 * 1 + 13 + 2",
            "Answer": 37,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 3 + 3 + 4 * 15 + 7 + 4",
            "Answer": 128,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 17 + 8 + 3 * 0 + 12 + 4",
            "Answer": 126,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 6 + 13 + 19 * 1 + 7 + 16",
            "Answer": 133,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 0 + 14 + 12 * 6 + 14 + 7",
            "Answer": 107,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 4 + 1 + 4 * 19 + 12 + 11",
            "Answer": 160,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 13 + 2 + 2 * 7 + 6 + 7",
            "Answer": 81,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 16 + 9 + 6 * 0 + 1 + 8",
            "Answer": 66,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 10 + 13 + 10 * 5 + 1 + 10",
            "Answer": 134,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 15 + 4 + 19 * 0 + 14 + 4",
            "Answer": 37,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 16 + 19 + 18 * 17 + 13 + 12",
            "Answer": 494,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 13 + 4 + 13 * 0 + 14 + 4",
            "Answer": 48,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 16 + 7 + 8 * 15 + 19 + 1",
            "Answer": 323,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 7 + 5 + 10 * 0 + 5 + 11",
            "Answer": 56,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 1 + 5 + 7 * 7 + 3 + 12",
            "Answer": 79,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 6 + 3 + 15 * 15 + 4 + 13",
            "Answer": 359,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 18 + 7 + 8 * 11 + 13 + 4",
            "Answer": 346,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 19 + 10 + 16 * 14 + 12 + 13",
            "Answer": 620,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 19 + 3 + 19 * 10 + 17 + 0",
            "Answer": 362,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 15 + 15 + 9 * 15 + 16 + 15",
            "Answer": 376,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 2 + 2 + 16 * 13 + 1 + 9",
            "Answer": 246,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 16 + 6 + 9 * 1 + 16 + 15",
            "Answer": 46,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 5 + 3 + 12 * 13 + 6 + 18",
            "Answer": 188,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 6 + 6 + 8 * 3 + 18 + 0",
            "Answer": 156,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 2 + 16 + 7 * 2 + 11 + 11",
            "Answer": 72,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 14 + 9 + 10 * 16 + 18 + 19",
            "Answer": 444,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 0 + 18 + 1 * 12 + 4 + 3",
            "Answer": 37,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 1 + 10 + 5 * 6 + 4 + 16",
            "Answer": 77,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 0 + 19 + 9 * 18 + 19 + 14",
            "Answer": 214,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 12 + 9 + 7 * 17 + 14 + 3",
            "Answer": 181,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # * # + # + #"
        }
    ],
    "# + # * # * # + # * # + #": [
        {
            "Question": "2 + 14 * 6 * 18 + 5 * 2 + 16",
            "Answer": 1540,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 18 * 16 * 9 + 1 * 4 + 2",
            "Answer": 2614,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 19 * 10 * 18 + 0 * 17 + 16",
            "Answer": 3445,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 3 * 4 * 15 + 15 * 18 + 5",
            "Answer": 466,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 11 * 17 * 3 + 3 * 3 + 14",
            "Answer": 601,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 2 * 16 * 12 + 14 * 3 + 17",
            "Answer": 462,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 16 * 15 * 0 + 14 * 11 + 15",
            "Answer": 175,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 5 * 3 * 13 + 10 * 18 + 13",
            "Answer": 407,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 4 * 18 * 4 + 13 * 14 + 0",
            "Answer": 480,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 4 * 4 * 9 + 17 * 11 + 15",
            "Answer": 349,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 13 * 9 * 5 + 13 * 3 + 7",
            "Answer": 644,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 0 * 13 * 17 + 9 * 3 + 13",
            "Answer": 49,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 7 * 18 * 6 + 2 * 17 + 17",
            "Answer": 820,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 15 * 12 * 4 + 7 * 17 + 0",
            "Answer": 847,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 8 * 10 * 18 + 6 * 17 + 13",
            "Answer": 1563,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 2 * 0 * 9 + 18 * 16 + 16",
            "Answer": 323,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 18 * 11 * 7 + 4 * 0 + 4",
            "Answer": 1393,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 19 * 5 * 6 + 9 * 5 + 6",
            "Answer": 639,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 7 * 1 * 1 + 5 * 10 + 15",
            "Answer": 91,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 0 * 3 * 3 + 1 * 0 + 7",
            "Answer": 13,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 13 * 5 * 14 + 19 * 18 + 3",
            "Answer": 1266,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 8 * 17 * 9 + 18 * 15 + 17",
            "Answer": 1511,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 4 * 3 * 1 + 19 * 11 + 0",
            "Answer": 229,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 19 * 19 * 9 + 4 * 5 + 14",
            "Answer": 3292,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 19 * 8 * 0 + 7 * 8 + 12",
            "Answer": 81,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 4 * 13 * 13 + 8 * 10 + 8",
            "Answer": 782,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 14 * 17 * 2 + 19 * 10 + 19",
            "Answer": 700,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 19 * 5 * 18 + 1 * 15 + 4",
            "Answer": 1741,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 19 * 8 * 1 + 10 * 0 + 12",
            "Answer": 172,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 0 * 4 * 11 + 0 * 12 + 10",
            "Answer": 25,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 0 * 3 * 0 + 13 * 0 + 11",
            "Answer": 27,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 14 * 1 * 11 + 6 * 9 + 7",
            "Answer": 219,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 0 * 18 * 1 + 0 * 16 + 0",
            "Answer": 17,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 12 * 8 * 10 + 10 * 17 + 1",
            "Answer": 1141,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 5 * 16 * 18 + 0 * 1 + 4",
            "Answer": 1447,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 1 * 14 * 6 + 10 * 18 + 18",
            "Answer": 292,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 13 * 10 * 6 + 16 * 3 + 6",
            "Answer": 838,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 19 * 19 * 0 + 7 * 8 + 17",
            "Answer": 77,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 15 * 18 * 13 + 1 * 19 + 2",
            "Answer": 3543,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 4 * 1 * 2 + 7 * 4 + 5",
            "Answer": 47,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 2 * 0 * 19 + 15 * 12 + 14",
            "Answer": 200,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 15 * 14 * 2 + 5 * 7 + 0",
            "Answer": 468,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 13 * 2 * 6 + 1 * 9 + 16",
            "Answer": 200,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 8 * 9 * 10 + 14 * 13 + 3",
            "Answer": 908,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 14 * 4 * 5 + 10 * 13 + 17",
            "Answer": 436,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 3 * 19 * 15 + 17 * 6 + 17",
            "Answer": 985,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 4 * 17 * 18 + 7 * 16 + 6",
            "Answer": 1355,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 9 * 16 * 2 + 17 * 9 + 2",
            "Answer": 457,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 5 * 3 * 13 + 4 * 15 + 13",
            "Answer": 285,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 5 * 0 * 8 + 2 * 19 + 18",
            "Answer": 71,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 14 * 12 * 0 + 14 * 11 + 0",
            "Answer": 162,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 1 * 1 * 7 + 8 * 8 + 12",
            "Answer": 93,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 18 * 7 * 19 + 2 * 0 + 14",
            "Answer": 2422,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 7 * 3 * 14 + 16 * 12 + 11",
            "Answer": 499,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 17 * 19 * 2 + 15 * 13 + 8",
            "Answer": 854,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 2 * 14 * 1 + 0 * 16 + 10",
            "Answer": 49,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 12 * 5 * 5 + 16 * 13 + 10",
            "Answer": 526,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 3 * 7 * 13 + 6 * 15 + 7",
            "Answer": 370,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 19 * 14 * 10 + 3 * 7 + 0",
            "Answer": 2681,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 3 * 1 * 14 + 13 * 5 + 10",
            "Answer": 123,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 2 * 6 * 0 + 14 * 1 + 13",
            "Answer": 45,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 10 * 3 * 4 + 10 * 4 + 8",
            "Answer": 186,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 15 * 14 * 4 + 17 * 16 + 3",
            "Answer": 1119,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 12 * 3 * 15 + 11 * 19 + 19",
            "Answer": 783,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 9 * 9 * 18 + 5 * 4 + 15",
            "Answer": 1507,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 1 * 11 * 0 + 8 * 17 + 19",
            "Answer": 173,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 13 * 7 * 4 + 10 * 11 + 8",
            "Answer": 499,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 17 * 12 * 9 + 19 * 18 + 19",
            "Answer": 2203,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 14 * 18 * 18 + 14 * 0 + 14",
            "Answer": 4557,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 9 * 2 * 17 + 7 * 16 + 16",
            "Answer": 450,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 13 * 0 * 16 + 14 * 5 + 8",
            "Answer": 80,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 14 * 13 * 4 + 12 * 6 + 0",
            "Answer": 811,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 4 * 4 * 16 + 11 * 12 + 3",
            "Answer": 409,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 17 * 15 * 2 + 9 * 11 + 11",
            "Answer": 622,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 9 * 5 * 12 + 19 * 10 + 16",
            "Answer": 748,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 0 * 16 * 14 + 6 * 7 + 15",
            "Answer": 66,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 4 * 9 * 17 + 14 * 16 + 15",
            "Answer": 857,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 11 * 0 * 6 + 0 * 1 + 5",
            "Answer": 8,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 2 * 19 * 8 + 4 * 18 + 1",
            "Answer": 392,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 0 * 1 * 0 + 10 * 0 + 1",
            "Answer": 18,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 1 * 14 * 11 + 17 * 6 + 6",
            "Answer": 275,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 9 * 9 * 14 + 4 * 10 + 19",
            "Answer": 1207,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 5 * 19 * 0 + 5 * 17 + 1",
            "Answer": 87,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 7 * 5 * 3 + 1 * 0 + 19",
            "Answer": 128,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 9 * 8 * 2 + 10 * 13 + 10",
            "Answer": 288,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 8 * 12 * 7 + 13 * 7 + 4",
            "Answer": 768,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 9 * 17 * 19 + 19 * 15 + 0",
            "Answer": 3208,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 15 * 4 * 15 + 18 * 12 + 12",
            "Answer": 1141,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 0 * 11 * 0 + 4 * 6 + 18",
            "Answer": 43,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 18 * 14 * 14 + 5 * 5 + 3",
            "Answer": 3563,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 0 * 19 * 14 + 3 * 9 + 4",
            "Answer": 38,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 5 * 5 * 2 + 15 * 0 + 8",
            "Answer": 67,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 16 * 8 * 4 + 7 * 12 + 16",
            "Answer": 622,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 12 * 16 * 3 + 5 * 14 + 16",
            "Answer": 670,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 8 * 11 * 2 + 4 * 11 + 10",
            "Answer": 237,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 15 * 19 * 9 + 5 * 3 + 5",
            "Answer": 2602,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 17 * 12 * 9 + 0 * 19 + 12",
            "Answer": 1863,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 4 * 2 * 12 + 15 * 18 + 9",
            "Answer": 381,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 4 * 6 * 10 + 6 * 18 + 3",
            "Answer": 366,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 0 * 13 * 17 + 18 * 9 + 12",
            "Answer": 185,
            "Predicate": "# + # * # * # + # * # + #"
        }
    ],
    "# * # + # * # * # + # * #": [
        {
            "Question": "4 * 5 + 12 * 11 * 3 + 5 * 18",
            "Answer": 506,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 2 + 10 * 15 * 9 + 8 * 5",
            "Answer": 1406,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 3 + 4 * 0 * 5 + 2 * 15",
            "Answer": 39,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 6 + 18 * 0 * 7 + 0 * 13",
            "Answer": 36,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 12 + 4 * 19 * 11 + 4 * 9",
            "Answer": 1016,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 10 + 2 * 8 * 8 + 2 * 1",
            "Answer": 250,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 4 + 14 * 3 * 17 + 1 * 15",
            "Answer": 777,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 6 + 7 * 2 * 0 + 12 * 8",
            "Answer": 192,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 2 + 12 * 9 * 9 + 1 * 0",
            "Answer": 988,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 18 + 2 * 13 * 3 + 18 * 16",
            "Answer": 366,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 3 + 5 * 14 * 17 + 5 * 3",
            "Answer": 1256,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 17 + 11 * 12 * 15 + 19 * 9",
            "Answer": 2440,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 6 + 13 * 19 * 11 + 13 * 3",
            "Answer": 2822,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 15 + 1 * 16 * 13 + 5 * 5",
            "Answer": 368,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 15 + 2 * 17 * 0 + 4 * 14",
            "Answer": 236,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 11 + 2 * 19 * 18 + 10 * 0",
            "Answer": 871,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 2 + 4 * 13 * 1 + 7 * 10",
            "Answer": 160,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 11 + 4 * 15 * 16 + 7 * 14",
            "Answer": 1113,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 19 + 1 * 11 * 9 + 4 * 5",
            "Answer": 195,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 14 + 14 * 6 * 3 + 11 * 0",
            "Answer": 448,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 9 + 17 * 7 * 19 + 7 * 12",
            "Answer": 2372,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 15 + 15 * 16 * 14 + 9 * 18",
            "Answer": 3747,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 15 + 5 * 14 * 12 + 8 * 10",
            "Answer": 935,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 11 + 4 * 15 * 7 + 17 * 5",
            "Answer": 582,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 0 + 10 * 19 * 6 + 1 * 3",
            "Answer": 1143,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 0 + 7 * 19 * 8 + 10 * 15",
            "Answer": 1214,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 18 + 0 * 12 * 13 + 2 * 10",
            "Answer": 254,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 10 + 9 * 15 * 15 + 4 * 6",
            "Answer": 2129,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 9 + 11 * 15 * 10 + 12 * 0",
            "Answer": 1776,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 13 + 17 * 7 * 6 + 8 * 7",
            "Answer": 952,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 7 + 8 * 8 * 11 + 4 * 9",
            "Answer": 803,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 1 + 9 * 1 * 13 + 13 * 13",
            "Answer": 301,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 19 + 11 * 16 * 12 + 10 * 16",
            "Answer": 2405,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 0 + 1 * 12 * 3 + 8 * 1",
            "Answer": 44,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 7 + 3 * 14 * 11 + 8 * 0",
            "Answer": 539,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 13 + 0 * 9 * 11 + 5 * 4",
            "Answer": 215,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 8 + 12 * 12 * 14 + 18 * 12",
            "Answer": 2304,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 15 + 13 * 14 * 13 + 13 * 6",
            "Answer": 2699,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 1 + 1 * 12 * 19 + 6 * 14",
            "Answer": 325,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 19 + 1 * 16 * 5 + 14 * 17",
            "Answer": 546,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 7 + 14 * 15 * 19 + 13 * 13",
            "Answer": 4180,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 7 + 15 * 16 * 17 + 9 * 11",
            "Answer": 4221,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 5 + 7 * 9 * 4 + 11 * 11",
            "Answer": 393,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 19 + 10 * 2 * 14 + 14 * 3",
            "Answer": 379,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 17 + 18 * 6 * 2 + 1 * 6",
            "Answer": 528,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 8 + 3 * 18 * 10 + 16 * 11",
            "Answer": 724,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 7 + 9 * 15 * 7 + 10 * 19",
            "Answer": 1184,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 15 + 17 * 3 * 0 + 19 * 12",
            "Answer": 408,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 2 + 5 * 14 * 0 + 15 * 0",
            "Answer": 36,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 9 + 1 * 0 * 2 + 4 * 19",
            "Answer": 247,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 11 + 6 * 16 * 11 + 8 * 16",
            "Answer": 1195,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 19 + 8 * 10 * 0 + 19 * 4",
            "Answer": 228,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 4 + 7 * 6 * 8 + 6 * 13",
            "Answer": 418,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 0 + 10 * 19 * 3 + 12 * 12",
            "Answer": 714,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 2 + 19 * 18 * 7 + 11 * 10",
            "Answer": 2508,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 12 + 8 * 11 * 1 + 8 * 14",
            "Answer": 356,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 8 + 11 * 1 * 13 + 4 * 17",
            "Answer": 243,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 17 + 4 * 1 * 2 + 10 * 14",
            "Answer": 148,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 19 + 16 * 1 * 1 + 13 * 11",
            "Answer": 311,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 14 + 19 * 7 * 3 + 3 * 13",
            "Answer": 690,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 11 + 10 * 18 * 3 + 7 * 3",
            "Answer": 594,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 17 + 18 * 3 * 13 + 5 * 17",
            "Answer": 1042,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 13 + 7 * 13 * 13 + 1 * 3",
            "Answer": 1251,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 8 + 9 * 19 * 5 + 18 * 6",
            "Answer": 1115,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 3 + 0 * 4 * 6 + 11 * 17",
            "Answer": 187,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 4 + 5 * 4 * 16 + 11 * 18",
            "Answer": 590,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 12 + 19 * 9 * 16 + 14 * 2",
            "Answer": 2992,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 13 + 10 * 9 * 11 + 4 * 3",
            "Answer": 1184,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 7 + 8 * 19 * 0 + 0 * 13",
            "Answer": 84,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 13 + 13 * 8 * 19 + 16 * 8",
            "Answer": 2195,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 16 + 11 * 12 * 19 + 1 * 4",
            "Answer": 2768,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 15 + 18 * 16 * 6 + 14 * 1",
            "Answer": 1967,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 15 + 14 * 5 * 7 + 0 * 3",
            "Answer": 745,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 12 + 8 * 19 * 17 + 9 * 15",
            "Answer": 2887,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 6 + 9 * 13 * 16 + 10 * 11",
            "Answer": 1982,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 18 + 18 * 15 * 12 + 11 * 3",
            "Answer": 3345,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 12 + 16 * 0 * 14 + 19 * 2",
            "Answer": 50,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 8 + 10 * 13 * 6 + 0 * 5",
            "Answer": 804,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 9 + 3 * 16 * 5 + 12 * 11",
            "Answer": 444,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 5 + 2 * 18 * 15 + 10 * 6",
            "Answer": 625,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 3 + 10 * 12 * 0 + 2 * 6",
            "Answer": 48,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 18 + 1 * 3 * 5 + 7 * 4",
            "Answer": 331,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 6 + 0 * 5 * 8 + 19 * 3",
            "Answer": 129,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 13 + 8 * 3 * 15 + 8 * 19",
            "Answer": 590,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 10 + 14 * 1 * 2 + 15 * 0",
            "Answer": 98,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 11 + 6 * 19 * 14 + 10 * 18",
            "Answer": 1787,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 3 + 12 * 12 * 4 + 6 * 0",
            "Answer": 609,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 7 + 14 * 0 * 18 + 17 * 14",
            "Answer": 273,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 12 + 12 * 15 * 3 + 16 * 11",
            "Answer": 920,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 6 + 17 * 15 * 3 + 17 * 0",
            "Answer": 801,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 5 + 4 * 6 * 18 + 17 * 10",
            "Answer": 692,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 8 + 4 * 3 * 5 + 18 * 7",
            "Answer": 210,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 15 + 13 * 11 * 6 + 10 * 18",
            "Answer": 1308,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 1 + 0 * 13 * 9 + 13 * 1",
            "Answer": 14,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 18 + 1 * 14 * 0 + 18 * 5",
            "Answer": 306,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 10 + 15 * 2 * 19 + 8 * 11",
            "Answer": 768,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 8 + 12 * 11 * 4 + 4 * 10",
            "Answer": 696,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 9 + 2 * 14 * 16 + 2 * 12",
            "Answer": 553,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 15 + 10 * 15 * 7 + 19 * 12",
            "Answer": 1308,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 16 + 5 * 8 * 15 + 8 * 19",
            "Answer": 1008,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # * #"
        }
    ],
    "# + # + # + # + # * # * #": [
        {
            "Question": "2 + 8 + 5 + 18 + 0 * 12 * 5",
            "Answer": 33,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 14 + 13 + 4 + 19 * 10 * 8",
            "Answer": 1554,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 5 + 10 + 1 + 12 * 7 * 5",
            "Answer": 437,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 6 + 15 + 13 + 5 * 13 * 8",
            "Answer": 571,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 8 + 10 + 2 + 7 * 15 * 15",
            "Answer": 1614,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 0 + 19 + 9 + 14 * 19 * 7",
            "Answer": 1909,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 18 + 18 + 17 + 17 * 4 * 9",
            "Answer": 674,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 13 + 0 + 2 + 13 * 7 * 12",
            "Answer": 1108,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 19 + 14 + 7 + 5 * 7 * 11",
            "Answer": 444,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 10 + 15 + 9 + 6 * 3 * 4",
            "Answer": 114,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 0 + 14 + 7 + 6 * 4 * 9",
            "Answer": 239,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 11 + 12 + 2 + 7 * 17 * 7",
            "Answer": 868,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 11 + 15 + 0 + 19 * 8 * 15",
            "Answer": 2314,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 11 + 19 + 12 + 5 * 15 * 9",
            "Answer": 721,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 10 + 7 + 13 + 14 * 3 * 12",
            "Answer": 544,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 5 + 9 + 10 + 7 * 3 * 3",
            "Answer": 88,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 12 + 0 + 5 + 11 * 14 * 3",
            "Answer": 486,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 16 + 7 + 13 + 1 * 10 * 9",
            "Answer": 126,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 0 + 15 + 1 + 15 * 17 * 6",
            "Answer": 1555,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 4 + 5 + 8 + 8 * 6 * 8",
            "Answer": 415,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 13 + 5 + 13 + 15 * 11 * 8",
            "Answer": 1356,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 17 + 7 + 13 + 2 * 8 * 4",
            "Answer": 110,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 7 + 5 + 13 + 7 * 19 * 12",
            "Answer": 1621,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 17 + 19 + 5 + 16 * 11 * 18",
            "Answer": 3226,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 8 + 15 + 5 + 9 * 12 * 4",
            "Answer": 466,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 10 + 19 + 16 + 11 * 10 * 1",
            "Answer": 165,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 3 + 5 + 9 + 7 * 1 * 11",
            "Answer": 111,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 6 + 7 + 11 + 13 * 4 * 16",
            "Answer": 860,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 12 + 15 + 14 + 15 * 4 * 9",
            "Answer": 585,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 18 + 10 + 2 + 9 * 18 * 11",
            "Answer": 1818,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 2 + 10 + 13 + 8 * 1 * 3",
            "Answer": 64,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 12 + 17 + 1 + 10 * 1 * 18",
            "Answer": 221,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 3 + 10 + 6 + 1 * 15 * 0",
            "Answer": 25,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 5 + 16 + 17 + 13 * 0 * 4",
            "Answer": 45,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 14 + 8 + 12 + 8 * 1 * 16",
            "Answer": 172,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 14 + 17 + 18 + 0 * 12 * 1",
            "Answer": 61,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 1 + 5 + 16 + 6 * 13 * 5",
            "Answer": 417,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 15 + 2 + 7 + 11 * 1 * 1",
            "Answer": 35,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 16 + 12 + 18 + 18 * 5 * 1",
            "Answer": 143,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 1 + 12 + 18 + 4 * 10 * 6",
            "Answer": 283,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 16 + 0 + 14 + 1 * 6 * 18",
            "Answer": 143,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 2 + 14 + 11 + 10 * 9 * 10",
            "Answer": 934,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 12 + 1 + 18 + 9 * 18 * 12",
            "Answer": 1979,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 0 + 11 + 8 + 18 * 5 * 1",
            "Answer": 123,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 1 + 19 + 1 + 18 * 4 * 10",
            "Answer": 752,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 13 + 12 + 15 + 4 * 19 * 17",
            "Answer": 1351,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 8 + 10 + 2 + 3 * 6 * 4",
            "Answer": 101,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 8 + 16 + 1 + 17 * 18 * 11",
            "Answer": 3394,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 7 + 18 + 11 + 7 * 15 * 15",
            "Answer": 1617,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 12 + 7 + 15 + 12 * 19 * 19",
            "Answer": 4378,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 5 + 15 + 8 + 14 * 9 * 12",
            "Answer": 1544,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 14 + 5 + 16 + 6 * 2 * 1",
            "Answer": 66,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 18 + 15 + 19 + 18 * 4 * 3",
            "Answer": 285,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 5 + 5 + 1 + 11 * 5 * 9",
            "Answer": 509,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 3 + 8 + 9 + 5 * 12 * 14",
            "Answer": 866,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 0 + 17 + 16 + 10 * 19 * 11",
            "Answer": 2130,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 13 + 16 + 17 + 13 * 4 * 5",
            "Answer": 310,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 18 + 0 + 3 + 19 * 3 * 5",
            "Answer": 307,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 14 + 3 + 11 + 13 * 12 * 19",
            "Answer": 3005,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 6 + 19 + 17 + 8 * 4 * 4",
            "Answer": 189,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 3 + 4 + 2 + 3 * 2 * 13",
            "Answer": 94,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 7 + 14 + 0 + 1 * 19 * 12",
            "Answer": 250,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 19 + 8 + 16 + 17 * 5 * 3",
            "Answer": 314,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 15 + 11 + 19 + 10 * 11 * 1",
            "Answer": 174,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 3 + 15 + 14 + 9 * 2 * 7",
            "Answer": 166,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 18 + 13 + 5 + 13 * 10 * 19",
            "Answer": 2518,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 0 + 12 + 19 + 16 * 19 * 16",
            "Answer": 4901,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 2 + 18 + 15 + 1 * 13 * 6",
            "Answer": 116,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 5 + 15 + 1 + 8 * 13 * 12",
            "Answer": 1288,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 19 + 17 + 9 + 8 * 4 * 15",
            "Answer": 539,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 7 + 11 + 12 + 7 * 1 * 13",
            "Answer": 126,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 0 + 11 + 8 + 15 * 17 * 8",
            "Answer": 2078,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 4 + 17 + 13 + 2 * 3 * 15",
            "Answer": 135,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 11 + 3 + 15 + 8 * 4 * 14",
            "Answer": 477,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 18 + 1 + 13 + 9 * 9 * 7",
            "Answer": 608,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 2 + 10 + 17 + 5 * 16 * 10",
            "Answer": 829,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 17 + 17 + 12 + 14 * 7 * 6",
            "Answer": 640,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 4 + 10 + 2 + 12 * 7 * 11",
            "Answer": 946,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 7 + 4 + 4 + 11 * 18 * 13",
            "Answer": 2608,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 7 + 8 + 15 + 5 * 11 * 15",
            "Answer": 855,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 0 + 3 + 4 + 5 * 3 * 2",
            "Answer": 44,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 17 + 7 + 18 + 12 * 3 * 9",
            "Answer": 367,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 17 + 14 + 13 + 5 * 9 * 18",
            "Answer": 868,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 16 + 14 + 7 + 1 * 9 * 8",
            "Answer": 110,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 10 + 19 + 9 + 16 * 6 * 5",
            "Answer": 526,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 4 + 17 + 18 + 7 * 19 * 9",
            "Answer": 1248,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 4 + 17 + 13 + 14 * 17 * 9",
            "Answer": 2181,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 5 + 15 + 8 + 8 * 8 * 15",
            "Answer": 1000,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 9 + 18 + 10 + 12 * 0 * 16",
            "Answer": 39,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 15 + 9 + 13 + 14 * 13 * 6",
            "Answer": 1143,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 17 + 15 + 18 + 0 * 4 * 11",
            "Answer": 61,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 19 + 13 + 0 + 2 * 19 * 11",
            "Answer": 460,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 11 + 3 + 19 + 14 * 6 * 13",
            "Answer": 1137,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 3 + 8 + 13 + 11 * 13 * 18",
            "Answer": 2603,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 7 + 12 + 15 + 6 * 0 * 3",
            "Answer": 35,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 6 + 10 + 11 + 7 * 18 * 16",
            "Answer": 2056,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 19 + 14 + 18 + 8 * 14 * 10",
            "Answer": 1184,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 13 + 17 + 13 + 7 * 19 * 7",
            "Answer": 978,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 14 + 19 + 16 + 4 * 19 * 2",
            "Answer": 206,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 3 + 16 + 19 + 19 * 13 * 11",
            "Answer": 2770,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # + # + # * # * #"
        }
    ],
    "# * # * # * # + # * # + #": [
        {
            "Question": "0 * 6 * 11 * 17 + 0 * 4 + 15",
            "Answer": 15,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 7 * 15 * 8 + 13 * 12 + 17",
            "Answer": 11933,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 9 * 8 * 7 + 6 * 8 + 8",
            "Answer": 2072,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 5 * 1 * 18 + 6 * 14 + 8",
            "Answer": 1082,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 14 * 19 * 14 + 1 * 11 + 1",
            "Answer": 14908,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 14 * 0 * 12 + 17 * 4 + 10",
            "Answer": 78,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 12 * 16 * 10 + 10 * 5 + 18",
            "Answer": 36548,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 11 * 11 * 5 + 7 * 17 + 12",
            "Answer": 1341,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 9 * 13 * 9 + 7 * 8 + 18",
            "Answer": 8498,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 13 * 14 * 11 + 1 * 9 + 12",
            "Answer": 26047,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 18 * 14 * 12 + 8 * 5 + 1",
            "Answer": 24233,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 3 * 17 * 11 + 5 * 11 + 9",
            "Answer": 10723,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 11 * 5 * 4 + 5 * 10 + 4",
            "Answer": 2254,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 5 * 3 * 8 + 4 * 7 + 12",
            "Answer": 1600,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 0 * 11 * 11 + 0 * 14 + 18",
            "Answer": 18,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 18 * 7 * 14 + 2 * 17 + 14",
            "Answer": 15924,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 4 * 0 * 14 + 19 * 6 + 4",
            "Answer": 118,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 2 * 17 * 11 + 5 * 1 + 3",
            "Answer": 3748,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 13 * 9 * 16 + 12 * 6 + 14",
            "Answer": 33782,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 11 * 6 * 14 + 4 * 19 + 4",
            "Answer": 14864,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 4 * 4 * 18 + 1 * 19 + 4",
            "Answer": 4631,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 8 * 2 * 4 + 5 * 6 + 13",
            "Answer": 491,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 12 * 16 * 8 + 2 * 3 + 16",
            "Answer": 9238,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 18 * 0 * 19 + 9 * 9 + 16",
            "Answer": 97,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 4 * 0 * 16 + 11 * 2 + 10",
            "Answer": 32,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 18 * 14 * 18 + 5 * 14 + 8",
            "Answer": 31830,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 10 * 15 * 9 + 18 * 19 + 16",
            "Answer": 358,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 6 * 0 * 12 + 18 * 8 + 9",
            "Answer": 153,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 6 * 19 * 7 + 13 * 14 + 12",
            "Answer": 4982,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 13 * 6 * 15 + 0 * 19 + 1",
            "Answer": 7021,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 15 * 8 * 10 + 14 * 12 + 5",
            "Answer": 4973,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 2 * 10 * 8 + 5 * 9 + 16",
            "Answer": 221,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 7 * 2 * 8 + 19 * 13 + 4",
            "Answer": 1483,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 2 * 2 * 18 + 9 * 4 + 10",
            "Answer": 694,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 17 * 5 * 18 + 2 * 17 + 12",
            "Answer": 46,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 0 * 7 * 2 + 15 * 19 + 4",
            "Answer": 289,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 5 * 5 * 4 + 12 * 14 + 0",
            "Answer": 1568,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 13 * 1 * 2 + 15 * 8 + 19",
            "Answer": 347,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 18 * 16 * 6 + 1 * 12 + 9",
            "Answer": 29397,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 9 * 13 * 7 + 11 * 19 + 14",
            "Answer": 7594,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 14 * 2 * 4 + 16 * 7 + 12",
            "Answer": 1692,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 7 * 0 * 1 + 19 * 11 + 11",
            "Answer": 220,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 9 * 1 * 9 + 2 * 8 + 16",
            "Answer": 275,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 10 * 11 * 17 + 4 * 16 + 14",
            "Answer": 26258,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 18 * 0 * 0 + 8 * 5 + 5",
            "Answer": 45,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 2 * 11 * 7 + 14 * 5 + 14",
            "Answer": 2086,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 1 * 0 * 3 + 10 * 3 + 3",
            "Answer": 33,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 5 * 13 * 14 + 8 * 17 + 8",
            "Answer": 10154,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 11 * 16 * 18 + 1 * 1 + 12",
            "Answer": 3181,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 6 * 6 * 18 + 11 * 2 + 14",
            "Answer": 4572,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 19 * 19 * 7 + 11 * 13 + 13",
            "Answer": 15318,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 4 * 18 * 12 + 14 * 0 + 12",
            "Answer": 5196,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 17 * 0 * 2 + 2 * 12 + 11",
            "Answer": 35,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 0 * 14 * 2 + 1 * 1 + 11",
            "Answer": 12,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 4 * 4 * 19 + 14 * 4 + 13",
            "Answer": 2805,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 0 * 0 * 4 + 1 * 0 + 14",
            "Answer": 14,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 17 * 12 * 1 + 9 * 16 + 18",
            "Answer": 570,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 1 * 15 * 14 + 2 * 0 + 1",
            "Answer": 1681,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 9 * 12 * 1 + 14 * 1 + 8",
            "Answer": 1210,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 12 * 7 * 12 + 11 * 1 + 14",
            "Answer": 4057,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 12 * 6 * 16 + 14 * 0 + 10",
            "Answer": 8074,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 11 * 12 * 8 + 8 * 9 + 4",
            "Answer": 2188,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 0 * 8 * 7 + 12 * 5 + 6",
            "Answer": 66,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 9 * 5 * 1 + 6 * 10 + 18",
            "Answer": 843,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 10 * 7 * 19 + 4 * 18 + 2",
            "Answer": 17364,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 6 * 3 * 3 + 0 * 9 + 19",
            "Answer": 289,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 8 * 9 * 19 + 10 * 19 + 10",
            "Answer": 2936,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 5 * 8 * 9 + 16 * 14 + 9",
            "Answer": 3473,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 2 * 5 * 0 + 12 * 14 + 16",
            "Answer": 184,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 9 * 15 * 9 + 18 * 11 + 15",
            "Answer": 16008,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 5 * 8 * 18 + 0 * 13 + 13",
            "Answer": 5053,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 14 * 6 * 13 + 10 * 6 + 18",
            "Answer": 5538,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 16 * 18 * 2 + 10 * 14 + 5",
            "Answer": 5905,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 19 * 14 * 19 + 18 * 2 + 12",
            "Answer": 40480,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 6 * 10 * 14 + 10 * 2 + 1",
            "Answer": 13461,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 15 * 18 * 19 + 17 * 0 + 8",
            "Answer": 51308,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 1 * 18 * 8 + 13 * 8 + 6",
            "Answer": 974,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 1 * 10 * 6 + 10 * 12 + 12",
            "Answer": 192,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 8 * 9 * 13 + 14 * 13 + 18",
            "Answer": 3944,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 7 * 3 * 2 + 13 * 4 + 3",
            "Answer": 517,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 7 * 2 * 5 + 12 * 15 + 8",
            "Answer": 538,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 14 * 9 * 19 + 1 * 15 + 10",
            "Answer": 7207,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 6 * 16 * 8 + 18 * 12 + 17",
            "Answer": 1001,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 15 * 6 * 0 + 2 * 16 + 6",
            "Answer": 38,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 3 * 15 * 4 + 9 * 3 + 6",
            "Answer": 1473,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 8 * 14 * 8 + 1 * 8 + 3",
            "Answer": 13451,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 10 * 2 * 19 + 7 * 12 + 6",
            "Answer": 2370,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 7 * 17 * 7 + 4 * 2 + 17",
            "Answer": 858,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 7 * 17 * 5 + 2 * 10 + 5",
            "Answer": 1810,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 6 * 7 * 15 + 12 * 3 + 17",
            "Answer": 2573,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 13 * 12 * 2 + 2 * 4 + 12",
            "Answer": 1892,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 11 * 1 * 10 + 2 * 1 + 16",
            "Answer": 568,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 5 * 6 * 2 + 3 * 14 + 2",
            "Answer": 1124,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 12 * 11 * 12 + 3 * 4 + 6",
            "Answer": 11106,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 0 * 6 * 1 + 4 * 13 + 6",
            "Answer": 58,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 9 * 16 * 11 + 3 * 5 + 3",
            "Answer": 1602,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 4 * 7 * 12 + 2 * 7 + 5",
            "Answer": 1027,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 10 * 8 * 0 + 15 * 2 + 14",
            "Answer": 44,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 10 * 17 * 1 + 17 * 3 + 19",
            "Answer": 1430,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 5 * 13 * 14 + 8 * 16 + 7",
            "Answer": 1045,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # * # + #"
        }
    ],
    "# * # * # + # * # + # * #": [
        {
            "Question": "17 * 8 * 11 + 14 * 12 + 1 * 7",
            "Answer": 1671,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 4 * 5 + 17 * 19 + 1 * 1",
            "Answer": 504,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 6 * 4 + 3 * 11 + 7 * 16",
            "Answer": 529,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 6 * 9 + 9 * 15 + 19 * 8",
            "Answer": 719,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 2 * 14 + 7 * 16 + 19 * 16",
            "Answer": 696,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 2 * 18 + 10 * 18 + 16 * 1",
            "Answer": 196,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 18 * 1 + 4 * 19 + 13 * 1",
            "Answer": 215,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 8 * 13 + 4 * 8 + 9 * 18",
            "Answer": 818,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 5 * 12 + 10 * 18 + 1 * 7",
            "Answer": 427,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 5 * 6 + 0 * 11 + 8 * 14",
            "Answer": 142,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 6 * 11 + 0 * 10 + 1 * 10",
            "Answer": 1066,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 0 * 8 + 15 * 16 + 9 * 8",
            "Answer": 312,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 4 * 3 + 0 * 8 + 10 * 6",
            "Answer": 132,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 10 * 10 + 4 * 5 + 8 * 7",
            "Answer": 776,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 9 * 6 + 1 * 2 + 19 * 3",
            "Answer": 59,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 9 * 11 + 9 * 2 + 7 * 4",
            "Answer": 1531,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 8 * 7 + 6 * 10 + 5 * 13",
            "Answer": 853,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 5 * 8 + 19 * 9 + 10 * 3",
            "Answer": 361,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 18 * 8 + 0 * 2 + 13 * 4",
            "Answer": 2356,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 5 * 5 + 19 * 17 + 4 * 8",
            "Answer": 405,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 4 * 17 + 11 * 12 + 12 * 19",
            "Answer": 836,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 19 * 15 + 0 * 11 + 18 * 17",
            "Answer": 1731,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 6 * 11 + 14 * 6 + 1 * 6",
            "Answer": 1014,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 16 * 15 + 9 * 7 + 1 * 2",
            "Answer": 1265,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 0 * 1 + 17 * 0 + 3 * 4",
            "Answer": 12,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 1 * 12 + 17 * 9 + 10 * 3",
            "Answer": 207,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 3 * 18 + 12 * 15 + 1 * 13",
            "Answer": 679,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 13 * 16 + 10 * 8 + 10 * 11",
            "Answer": 1022,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 8 * 18 + 19 * 18 + 14 * 14",
            "Answer": 1546,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 2 * 15 + 10 * 2 + 9 * 8",
            "Answer": 302,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 8 * 2 + 15 * 19 + 7 * 15",
            "Answer": 630,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 8 * 4 + 13 * 4 + 14 * 2",
            "Answer": 272,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 6 * 19 + 4 * 19 + 17 * 10",
            "Answer": 1158,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 11 * 10 + 11 * 0 + 15 * 5",
            "Answer": 1175,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 17 * 9 + 9 * 16 + 9 * 2",
            "Answer": 1692,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 10 * 1 + 10 * 2 + 12 * 12",
            "Answer": 314,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 11 * 13 + 3 * 12 + 1 * 9",
            "Answer": 617,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 6 * 2 + 18 * 0 + 1 * 8",
            "Answer": 32,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 3 * 9 + 13 * 15 + 0 * 7",
            "Answer": 492,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 12 * 0 + 18 * 12 + 15 * 2",
            "Answer": 246,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 19 * 18 + 19 * 0 + 19 * 15",
            "Answer": 1653,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 18 * 19 + 12 * 10 + 3 * 14",
            "Answer": 3582,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 18 * 8 + 9 * 18 + 5 * 14",
            "Answer": 2248,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 6 * 10 + 1 * 15 + 0 * 13",
            "Answer": 195,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 1 * 4 + 12 * 19 + 1 * 0",
            "Answer": 280,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 14 * 11 + 16 * 17 + 1 * 0",
            "Answer": 1504,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 1 * 15 + 19 * 7 + 17 * 1",
            "Answer": 345,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 16 * 18 + 8 * 16 + 6 * 1",
            "Answer": 2726,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 12 * 18 + 0 * 17 + 18 * 9",
            "Answer": 2754,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 10 * 16 + 4 * 5 + 3 * 2",
            "Answer": 26,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 14 * 13 + 10 * 7 + 9 * 19",
            "Answer": 2061,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 14 * 7 + 9 * 8 + 9 * 11",
            "Answer": 1249,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 7 * 2 + 0 * 14 + 5 * 3",
            "Answer": 281,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 18 * 18 + 8 * 9 + 9 * 11",
            "Answer": 1791,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 10 * 15 + 6 * 9 + 0 * 3",
            "Answer": 2304,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 16 * 16 + 16 * 12 + 2 * 11",
            "Answer": 4822,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 15 * 18 + 19 * 14 + 15 * 14",
            "Answer": 3176,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 7 * 19 + 8 * 11 + 10 * 0",
            "Answer": 2083,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 2 * 15 + 10 * 4 + 11 * 14",
            "Answer": 524,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 6 * 10 + 8 * 16 + 8 * 7",
            "Answer": 904,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 4 * 8 + 6 * 3 + 5 * 15",
            "Answer": 317,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 12 * 16 + 3 * 1 + 7 * 13",
            "Answer": 1438,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 8 * 16 + 15 * 4 + 1 * 9",
            "Answer": 69,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 6 * 0 + 1 * 16 + 10 * 10",
            "Answer": 116,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 15 * 11 + 14 * 12 + 13 * 5",
            "Answer": 3038,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 1 * 18 + 10 * 4 + 11 * 11",
            "Answer": 161,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 8 * 8 + 16 * 5 + 9 * 17",
            "Answer": 489,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 9 * 1 + 12 * 6 + 5 * 4",
            "Answer": 200,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 18 * 15 + 17 * 13 + 4 * 11",
            "Answer": 1345,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 12 * 18 + 7 * 2 + 6 * 0",
            "Answer": 3470,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 14 * 17 + 2 * 2 + 14 * 2",
            "Answer": 1698,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 19 * 6 + 16 * 3 + 17 * 7",
            "Answer": 2219,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 14 * 3 + 4 * 7 + 7 * 11",
            "Answer": 231,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 13 * 11 + 7 * 16 + 12 * 1",
            "Answer": 124,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 10 * 1 + 18 * 19 + 15 * 10",
            "Answer": 542,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 6 * 3 + 1 * 9 + 18 * 16",
            "Answer": 405,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 13 * 16 + 9 * 8 + 7 * 3",
            "Answer": 2589,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 19 * 18 + 0 * 3 + 2 * 8",
            "Answer": 2410,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 5 * 13 + 11 * 17 + 18 * 7",
            "Answer": 1288,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 13 * 6 + 14 * 1 + 17 * 5",
            "Answer": 411,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 18 * 10 + 7 * 14 + 0 * 18",
            "Answer": 1718,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 0 * 1 + 16 * 16 + 1 * 8",
            "Answer": 264,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 12 * 18 + 9 * 6 + 0 * 16",
            "Answer": 3942,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 9 * 6 + 3 * 8 + 11 * 12",
            "Answer": 318,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 0 * 7 + 14 * 3 + 10 * 12",
            "Answer": 162,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 6 * 17 + 3 * 17 + 11 * 11",
            "Answer": 274,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 6 * 0 + 9 * 3 + 15 * 13",
            "Answer": 222,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 6 * 1 + 16 * 8 + 18 * 19",
            "Answer": 530,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 2 * 14 + 1 * 18 + 7 * 12",
            "Answer": 466,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 13 * 19 + 0 * 8 + 9 * 19",
            "Answer": 2147,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 11 * 13 + 10 * 11 + 8 * 11",
            "Answer": 770,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 2 * 5 + 2 * 18 + 3 * 9",
            "Answer": 113,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 14 * 0 + 7 * 13 + 6 * 1",
            "Answer": 97,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 13 * 2 + 18 * 15 + 3 * 5",
            "Answer": 701,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 9 * 9 + 11 * 18 + 10 * 2",
            "Answer": 1352,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 5 * 14 + 0 * 13 + 6 * 3",
            "Answer": 928,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 18 * 9 + 17 * 14 + 0 * 0",
            "Answer": 1210,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 7 * 4 + 9 * 7 + 13 * 12",
            "Answer": 611,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 6 * 15 + 4 * 3 + 4 * 6",
            "Answer": 36,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 9 * 4 + 17 * 18 + 13 * 6",
            "Answer": 708,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # * #"
        }
    ],
    "# * # * # + # * # + # + #": [
        {
            "Question": "0 * 9 * 1 + 17 * 5 + 2 + 18",
            "Answer": 105,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 5 * 13 + 5 * 11 + 14 + 13",
            "Answer": 862,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 15 * 11 + 7 * 5 + 1 + 17",
            "Answer": 1868,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 19 * 16 + 4 * 5 + 13 + 6",
            "Answer": 647,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 14 * 9 + 17 * 15 + 5 + 11",
            "Answer": 2413,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 3 * 1 + 12 * 15 + 8 + 9",
            "Answer": 215,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 16 * 5 + 13 * 19 + 14 + 14",
            "Answer": 1235,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 19 * 16 + 4 * 16 + 0 + 10",
            "Answer": 1594,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 6 * 7 + 2 * 14 + 17 + 16",
            "Answer": 565,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 17 * 10 + 17 * 2 + 18 + 0",
            "Answer": 1752,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 0 * 8 + 7 * 10 + 8 + 18",
            "Answer": 96,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 16 * 3 + 4 * 0 + 6 + 5",
            "Answer": 299,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 6 * 11 + 7 * 1 + 2 + 1",
            "Answer": 1198,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 7 * 6 + 16 * 13 + 7 + 9",
            "Answer": 392,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 11 * 13 + 12 * 18 + 11 + 6",
            "Answer": 519,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 7 * 19 + 11 * 12 + 1 + 9",
            "Answer": 1605,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 8 * 12 + 16 * 11 + 2 + 16",
            "Answer": 962,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 12 * 1 + 15 * 18 + 5 + 16",
            "Answer": 363,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 19 * 7 + 12 * 16 + 2 + 5",
            "Answer": 199,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 12 * 17 + 11 * 14 + 11 + 13",
            "Answer": 586,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 3 * 7 + 17 * 18 + 7 + 13",
            "Answer": 326,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 8 * 16 + 5 * 4 + 6 + 13",
            "Answer": 935,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 11 * 4 + 1 * 14 + 3 + 15",
            "Answer": 384,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 17 * 3 + 11 * 17 + 8 + 18",
            "Answer": 1029,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 1 * 11 + 6 * 15 + 19 + 11",
            "Answer": 307,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 5 * 5 + 5 * 12 + 7 + 16",
            "Answer": 483,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 0 * 15 + 19 * 1 + 7 + 2",
            "Answer": 28,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 5 * 10 + 0 * 2 + 2 + 4",
            "Answer": 556,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 8 * 19 + 12 * 7 + 13 + 19",
            "Answer": 1332,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 19 * 17 + 10 * 10 + 8 + 17",
            "Answer": 5939,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 12 * 1 + 0 * 13 + 14 + 2",
            "Answer": 88,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 9 * 19 + 1 * 16 + 2 + 16",
            "Answer": 2428,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 19 * 5 + 8 * 9 + 13 + 10",
            "Answer": 1045,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 3 * 18 + 3 * 13 + 8 + 2",
            "Answer": 535,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 4 * 18 + 8 * 1 + 3 + 19",
            "Answer": 246,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 9 * 11 + 7 * 14 + 11 + 8",
            "Answer": 711,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 11 * 4 + 15 * 7 + 0 + 13",
            "Answer": 602,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 12 * 10 + 1 * 6 + 14 + 3",
            "Answer": 1823,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 14 * 10 + 6 * 3 + 5 + 14",
            "Answer": 1577,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 13 * 2 + 5 * 14 + 11 + 11",
            "Answer": 352,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 14 * 10 + 14 * 0 + 17 + 12",
            "Answer": 1149,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 12 * 18 + 0 * 3 + 4 + 8",
            "Answer": 876,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 2 * 7 + 9 * 5 + 10 + 1",
            "Answer": 322,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 13 * 16 + 1 * 4 + 2 + 19",
            "Answer": 2729,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 7 * 0 + 17 * 3 + 5 + 17",
            "Answer": 73,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 8 * 18 + 4 * 14 + 12 + 5",
            "Answer": 1513,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 18 * 6 + 18 * 1 + 9 + 12",
            "Answer": 471,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 14 * 6 + 0 * 1 + 18 + 8",
            "Answer": 614,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 3 * 8 + 7 * 11 + 8 + 10",
            "Answer": 287,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 17 * 12 + 8 * 19 + 4 + 17",
            "Answer": 989,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 2 * 1 + 4 * 7 + 14 + 2",
            "Answer": 48,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 17 * 17 + 19 * 1 + 12 + 19",
            "Answer": 3229,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 11 * 3 + 10 * 18 + 1 + 17",
            "Answer": 726,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 1 * 11 + 9 * 2 + 13 + 17",
            "Answer": 81,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 6 * 14 + 15 * 16 + 17 + 9",
            "Answer": 1442,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 15 * 5 + 8 * 4 + 5 + 5",
            "Answer": 1167,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 19 * 7 + 17 * 19 + 19 + 15",
            "Answer": 1155,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 2 * 12 + 2 * 1 + 3 + 14",
            "Answer": 139,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 1 * 10 + 3 * 4 + 5 + 1",
            "Answer": 208,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 7 * 4 + 19 * 11 + 15 + 8",
            "Answer": 624,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 13 * 12 + 17 * 12 + 15 + 12",
            "Answer": 2103,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 17 * 11 + 0 * 16 + 10 + 14",
            "Answer": 24,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 14 * 4 + 8 * 15 + 12 + 6",
            "Answer": 194,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 10 * 17 + 11 * 17 + 17 + 14",
            "Answer": 1918,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 0 * 2 + 3 * 14 + 11 + 6",
            "Answer": 59,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 12 * 1 + 13 * 10 + 5 + 12",
            "Answer": 315,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 3 * 18 + 17 * 0 + 16 + 6",
            "Answer": 886,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 15 * 2 + 15 * 5 + 10 + 0",
            "Answer": 535,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 0 * 14 + 9 * 9 + 11 + 14",
            "Answer": 106,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 18 * 14 + 9 * 2 + 3 + 3",
            "Answer": 4812,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 0 * 2 + 5 * 9 + 17 + 19",
            "Answer": 81,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 17 * 14 + 11 * 7 + 10 + 18",
            "Answer": 2009,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 0 * 2 + 5 * 14 + 1 + 17",
            "Answer": 88,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 2 * 10 + 3 * 14 + 4 + 9",
            "Answer": 315,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 12 * 19 + 15 * 14 + 11 + 2",
            "Answer": 451,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 12 * 5 + 10 * 18 + 0 + 18",
            "Answer": 1038,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 4 * 11 + 3 * 18 + 3 + 14",
            "Answer": 731,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 15 * 6 + 12 * 4 + 10 + 12",
            "Answer": 430,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 3 * 2 + 6 * 15 + 1 + 7",
            "Answer": 128,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 4 * 11 + 16 * 2 + 11 + 11",
            "Answer": 406,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 3 * 2 + 10 * 6 + 19 + 12",
            "Answer": 157,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 1 * 18 + 6 * 18 + 10 + 14",
            "Answer": 186,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 6 * 15 + 2 * 15 + 8 + 9",
            "Answer": 227,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 2 * 1 + 4 * 2 + 4 + 1",
            "Answer": 25,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 19 * 4 + 1 * 7 + 19 + 2",
            "Answer": 712,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 19 * 14 + 11 * 1 + 16 + 17",
            "Answer": 3768,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 16 * 11 + 17 * 5 + 7 + 6",
            "Answer": 98,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 10 * 5 + 0 * 10 + 18 + 9",
            "Answer": 227,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 5 * 15 + 8 * 9 + 7 + 0",
            "Answer": 904,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 1 * 18 + 5 * 10 + 18 + 18",
            "Answer": 428,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 1 * 8 + 15 * 19 + 16 + 12",
            "Answer": 457,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 14 * 18 + 12 * 14 + 6 + 14",
            "Answer": 440,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 9 * 17 + 10 * 8 + 8 + 15",
            "Answer": 1939,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 2 * 14 + 16 * 13 + 4 + 13",
            "Answer": 645,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 18 * 3 + 13 * 12 + 17 + 12",
            "Answer": 887,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 16 * 9 + 17 * 6 + 5 + 8",
            "Answer": 2131,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 6 * 13 + 6 * 11 + 10 + 0",
            "Answer": 934,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 6 * 4 + 7 * 16 + 10 + 5",
            "Answer": 391,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 4 * 12 + 4 * 2 + 13 + 15",
            "Answer": 708,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 17 * 6 + 10 * 15 + 14 + 8",
            "Answer": 1498,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # * # + # + #"
        }
    ],
    "# * # * # + # + # * # + #": [
        {
            "Question": "0 * 11 * 8 + 9 + 1 * 12 + 18",
            "Answer": 39,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 14 * 14 + 17 + 18 * 8 + 9",
            "Answer": 2914,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 8 * 2 + 13 + 15 * 19 + 13",
            "Answer": 391,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 7 * 19 + 16 + 14 * 5 + 10",
            "Answer": 1692,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 17 * 19 + 0 + 1 * 1 + 14",
            "Answer": 1307,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 19 * 18 + 7 + 5 * 1 + 10",
            "Answer": 5152,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 9 * 6 + 19 + 11 * 10 + 1",
            "Answer": 508,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 16 * 11 + 9 + 12 * 7 + 18",
            "Answer": 287,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 12 * 11 + 18 + 10 * 1 + 6",
            "Answer": 694,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 13 * 16 + 1 + 4 * 14 + 6",
            "Answer": 63,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 7 * 19 + 10 + 13 * 2 + 12",
            "Answer": 846,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 18 * 16 + 14 + 16 * 6 + 19",
            "Answer": 4161,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 15 * 9 + 7 + 19 * 12 + 8",
            "Answer": 1053,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 16 * 4 + 9 + 5 * 8 + 5",
            "Answer": 566,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 17 * 15 + 4 + 0 * 6 + 12",
            "Answer": 3841,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 18 * 9 + 19 + 1 * 7 + 16",
            "Answer": 1662,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 11 * 13 + 7 + 15 * 0 + 3",
            "Answer": 582,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 18 * 0 + 8 + 19 * 2 + 12",
            "Answer": 58,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 14 * 1 + 19 + 11 * 1 + 11",
            "Answer": 293,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 10 * 4 + 5 + 14 * 12 + 10",
            "Answer": 943,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 6 * 6 + 8 + 15 * 5 + 6",
            "Answer": 521,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 4 * 3 + 16 + 11 * 18 + 9",
            "Answer": 283,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 7 * 6 + 5 + 15 * 15 + 15",
            "Answer": 665,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 6 * 1 + 15 + 9 * 10 + 3",
            "Answer": 126,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 8 * 12 + 10 + 14 * 10 + 6",
            "Answer": 1404,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 4 * 9 + 5 + 2 * 19 + 19",
            "Answer": 62,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 15 * 14 + 5 + 4 * 13 + 13",
            "Answer": 3640,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 16 * 3 + 6 + 3 * 6 + 15",
            "Answer": 423,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 10 * 15 + 14 + 15 * 13 + 0",
            "Answer": 1859,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 3 * 2 + 0 + 3 * 10 + 17",
            "Answer": 53,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 2 * 17 + 0 + 18 * 9 + 11",
            "Answer": 513,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 2 * 5 + 18 + 1 * 13 + 4",
            "Answer": 65,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 14 * 10 + 14 + 3 * 2 + 12",
            "Answer": 312,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 18 * 11 + 4 + 17 * 3 + 2",
            "Answer": 2631,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 0 * 9 + 12 + 14 * 5 + 8",
            "Answer": 90,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 7 * 3 + 19 + 19 * 10 + 13",
            "Answer": 369,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 14 * 14 + 13 + 8 * 2 + 2",
            "Answer": 1991,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 15 * 6 + 9 + 7 * 7 + 4",
            "Answer": 242,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 17 * 11 + 12 + 3 * 12 + 2",
            "Answer": 1920,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 5 * 19 + 16 + 13 * 18 + 0",
            "Answer": 345,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 1 * 19 + 8 + 8 * 18 + 3",
            "Answer": 383,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 13 * 13 + 9 + 14 * 1 + 5",
            "Answer": 1549,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 14 * 4 + 11 + 12 * 2 + 19",
            "Answer": 726,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 13 * 6 + 15 + 6 * 11 + 8",
            "Answer": 1337,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 14 * 16 + 13 + 3 * 5 + 9",
            "Answer": 1157,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 16 * 6 + 9 + 2 * 12 + 5",
            "Answer": 38,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 19 * 3 + 15 + 13 * 18 + 13",
            "Answer": 1345,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 19 * 19 + 6 + 5 * 9 + 14",
            "Answer": 6924,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 2 * 17 + 3 + 4 * 18 + 19",
            "Answer": 94,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 17 * 11 + 15 + 0 * 4 + 4",
            "Answer": 2263,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 17 * 3 + 11 + 0 * 2 + 3",
            "Answer": 983,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 11 * 14 + 0 + 2 * 8 + 18",
            "Answer": 2960,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 3 * 4 + 0 + 15 * 17 + 14",
            "Answer": 365,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 7 * 8 + 3 + 13 * 16 + 12",
            "Answer": 503,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 14 * 19 + 11 + 7 * 0 + 2",
            "Answer": 1609,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 17 * 6 + 15 + 6 * 9 + 2",
            "Answer": 1601,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 12 * 4 + 14 + 19 * 14 + 3",
            "Answer": 379,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 5 * 2 + 2 + 10 * 8 + 8",
            "Answer": 220,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 9 * 15 + 19 + 17 * 10 + 18",
            "Answer": 612,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 17 * 13 + 11 + 0 * 12 + 4",
            "Answer": 678,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 9 * 7 + 14 + 2 * 13 + 11",
            "Answer": 996,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 17 * 12 + 17 + 13 * 4 + 5",
            "Answer": 2114,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 9 * 11 + 17 + 3 * 14 + 7",
            "Answer": 66,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 2 * 1 + 13 + 0 * 0 + 7",
            "Answer": 26,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 1 * 7 + 1 + 3 * 5 + 4",
            "Answer": 20,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 4 * 7 + 17 + 19 * 11 + 3",
            "Answer": 257,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 2 * 11 + 15 + 4 * 17 + 6",
            "Answer": 485,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 8 * 10 + 19 + 5 * 16 + 8",
            "Answer": 187,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 17 * 3 + 1 + 10 * 4 + 0",
            "Answer": 143,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 14 * 11 + 8 + 1 * 0 + 3",
            "Answer": 2629,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 14 * 5 + 17 + 16 * 11 + 5",
            "Answer": 688,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 2 * 2 + 16 + 1 * 2 + 7",
            "Answer": 101,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 4 * 13 + 15 + 4 * 11 + 2",
            "Answer": 685,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 16 * 5 + 12 + 3 * 0 + 17",
            "Answer": 29,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 9 * 12 + 19 + 6 * 0 + 17",
            "Answer": 252,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 15 * 16 + 15 + 13 * 1 + 3",
            "Answer": 1711,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 5 * 4 + 17 + 7 * 10 + 16",
            "Answer": 323,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 7 * 17 + 4 + 18 * 10 + 3",
            "Answer": 2091,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 14 * 4 + 8 + 8 * 17 + 4",
            "Answer": 540,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 13 * 4 + 2 + 4 * 4 + 3",
            "Answer": 853,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 15 * 4 + 7 + 10 * 2 + 9",
            "Answer": 1176,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 9 * 12 + 15 + 11 * 16 + 13",
            "Answer": 204,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 12 * 12 + 14 + 18 * 16 + 1",
            "Answer": 2031,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 13 * 1 + 11 + 11 * 4 + 6",
            "Answer": 256,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 2 * 19 + 18 + 0 * 6 + 14",
            "Answer": 32,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 6 * 6 + 0 + 1 * 14 + 15",
            "Answer": 533,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 11 * 17 + 2 + 19 * 8 + 0",
            "Answer": 3333,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 19 * 0 + 7 + 14 * 10 + 6",
            "Answer": 153,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 4 * 8 + 19 + 3 * 15 + 2",
            "Answer": 354,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 3 * 4 + 9 + 19 * 8 + 15",
            "Answer": 176,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 19 * 19 + 12 + 4 * 15 + 17",
            "Answer": 2977,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 16 * 11 + 12 + 19 * 19 + 11",
            "Answer": 1616,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 12 * 12 + 18 + 2 * 7 + 2",
            "Answer": 1762,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 9 * 7 + 8 + 6 * 14 + 3",
            "Answer": 914,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 19 * 17 + 8 + 13 * 7 + 2",
            "Answer": 424,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 19 * 14 + 16 + 13 * 2 + 15",
            "Answer": 4579,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 4 * 3 + 5 + 3 * 11 + 14",
            "Answer": 268,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 13 * 1 + 6 + 2 * 8 + 8",
            "Answer": 160,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 11 * 19 + 7 + 4 * 1 + 13",
            "Answer": 3786,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 12 * 14 + 18 + 19 * 16 + 3",
            "Answer": 3517,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # + # + # * # + #"
        }
    ],
    "# * # + # * # * # + # + #": [
        {
            "Question": "12 * 14 + 7 * 16 * 5 + 4 + 7",
            "Answer": 739,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 0 + 8 * 0 * 15 + 16 + 5",
            "Answer": 21,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 17 + 15 * 15 * 5 + 9 + 0",
            "Answer": 1389,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 14 + 10 * 5 * 3 + 17 + 19",
            "Answer": 396,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 3 + 13 * 7 * 16 + 3 + 1",
            "Answer": 1490,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 10 + 0 * 8 * 11 + 12 + 4",
            "Answer": 106,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 7 + 2 * 15 * 2 + 13 + 6",
            "Answer": 156,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 5 + 8 * 7 * 10 + 11 + 18",
            "Answer": 659,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 13 + 10 * 12 * 6 + 4 + 11",
            "Answer": 904,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 0 + 0 * 18 * 6 + 14 + 19",
            "Answer": 33,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 5 + 2 * 9 * 17 + 17 + 2",
            "Answer": 385,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 18 + 15 * 1 * 13 + 2 + 10",
            "Answer": 477,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 0 + 17 * 1 * 1 + 18 + 11",
            "Answer": 46,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 11 + 2 * 17 * 16 + 17 + 19",
            "Answer": 580,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 8 + 5 * 12 * 13 + 5 + 10",
            "Answer": 851,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 18 + 9 * 14 * 16 + 2 + 13",
            "Answer": 2211,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 5 + 15 * 2 * 14 + 12 + 16",
            "Answer": 528,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 13 + 5 * 19 * 12 + 14 + 14",
            "Answer": 1272,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 17 + 9 * 11 * 12 + 6 + 19",
            "Answer": 1400,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 11 + 13 * 17 * 16 + 0 + 17",
            "Answer": 3674,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 13 + 19 * 14 * 17 + 7 + 5",
            "Answer": 4716,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 14 + 17 * 10 * 12 + 1 + 8",
            "Answer": 2217,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 4 + 15 * 10 * 3 + 10 + 11",
            "Answer": 479,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 16 + 10 * 5 * 19 + 19 + 14",
            "Answer": 1095,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 17 + 5 * 13 * 19 + 8 + 4",
            "Answer": 1451,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 5 + 17 * 12 * 7 + 5 + 12",
            "Answer": 1540,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 17 + 12 * 0 * 3 + 0 + 7",
            "Answer": 194,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 10 + 2 * 9 * 10 + 11 + 17",
            "Answer": 358,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 13 + 15 * 18 * 8 + 17 + 3",
            "Answer": 2232,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 14 + 8 * 18 * 1 + 3 + 5",
            "Answer": 166,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 17 + 2 * 11 * 2 + 12 + 14",
            "Answer": 308,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 18 + 12 * 0 * 16 + 5 + 6",
            "Answer": 335,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 1 + 14 * 2 * 5 + 18 + 18",
            "Answer": 195,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 18 + 19 * 3 * 9 + 5 + 1",
            "Answer": 609,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 18 + 15 * 13 * 15 + 11 + 1",
            "Answer": 3279,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 18 + 18 * 19 * 4 + 3 + 9",
            "Answer": 1596,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 9 + 13 * 18 * 11 + 10 + 16",
            "Answer": 2654,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 7 + 9 * 14 * 12 + 14 + 1",
            "Answer": 1604,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 3 + 18 * 18 * 19 + 7 + 17",
            "Answer": 6189,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 5 + 16 * 4 * 18 + 18 + 15",
            "Answer": 1235,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 3 + 7 * 10 * 6 + 0 + 19",
            "Answer": 478,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 8 + 3 * 19 * 7 + 11 + 19",
            "Answer": 453,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 2 + 13 * 19 * 10 + 17 + 8",
            "Answer": 2513,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 19 + 9 * 7 * 14 + 6 + 17",
            "Answer": 943,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 19 + 3 * 5 * 16 + 10 + 8",
            "Answer": 391,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 3 + 5 * 19 * 15 + 13 + 19",
            "Answer": 1514,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 15 + 9 * 1 * 4 + 2 + 2",
            "Answer": 250,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 7 + 4 * 3 * 18 + 4 + 10",
            "Answer": 279,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 11 + 5 * 13 * 18 + 16 + 1",
            "Answer": 1363,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 15 + 5 * 18 * 1 + 19 + 6",
            "Answer": 400,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 1 + 11 * 16 * 16 + 4 + 16",
            "Answer": 2837,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 15 + 3 * 7 * 9 + 10 + 13",
            "Answer": 422,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 18 + 17 * 12 * 14 + 19 + 19",
            "Answer": 3020,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 6 + 16 * 6 * 16 + 19 + 17",
            "Answer": 1674,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 6 + 2 * 5 * 6 + 5 + 17",
            "Answer": 142,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 7 + 13 * 4 * 13 + 11 + 10",
            "Answer": 802,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 3 + 12 * 12 * 0 + 4 + 13",
            "Answer": 41,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 1 + 6 * 5 * 11 + 3 + 0",
            "Answer": 335,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 12 + 11 * 0 * 4 + 15 + 19",
            "Answer": 70,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 15 + 19 * 19 * 13 + 18 + 19",
            "Answer": 4730,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 5 + 9 * 5 * 11 + 5 + 0",
            "Answer": 560,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 13 + 5 * 13 * 8 + 14 + 9",
            "Answer": 738,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 6 + 14 * 2 * 18 + 1 + 7",
            "Answer": 596,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 17 + 18 * 5 * 1 + 12 + 16",
            "Answer": 271,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 12 + 16 * 1 * 12 + 17 + 19",
            "Answer": 228,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 16 + 5 * 7 * 1 + 5 + 12",
            "Answer": 324,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 3 + 3 * 19 * 12 + 0 + 18",
            "Answer": 726,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 6 + 17 * 7 * 10 + 19 + 14",
            "Answer": 1259,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 4 + 5 * 9 * 10 + 10 + 1",
            "Answer": 513,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 16 + 10 * 12 * 18 + 19 + 19",
            "Answer": 2470,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 14 + 1 * 17 * 4 + 16 + 5",
            "Answer": 285,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 6 + 18 * 10 * 3 + 1 + 9",
            "Answer": 598,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 0 + 12 * 12 * 16 + 3 + 13",
            "Answer": 2320,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 5 + 15 * 17 * 1 + 13 + 18",
            "Answer": 296,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 8 + 13 * 3 * 11 + 0 + 19",
            "Answer": 536,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 4 + 11 * 5 * 7 + 6 + 11",
            "Answer": 426,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 4 + 3 * 7 * 10 + 17 + 2",
            "Answer": 269,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 18 + 17 * 3 * 19 + 4 + 13",
            "Answer": 1274,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 3 + 15 * 5 * 10 + 18 + 17",
            "Answer": 842,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 14 + 13 * 10 * 4 + 17 + 19",
            "Answer": 738,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 14 + 3 * 8 * 3 + 8 + 6",
            "Answer": 254,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 18 + 14 * 9 * 17 + 17 + 4",
            "Answer": 2307,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 14 + 1 * 16 * 15 + 6 + 13",
            "Answer": 315,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 17 + 3 * 4 * 14 + 6 + 2",
            "Answer": 465,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 4 + 10 * 17 * 2 + 19 + 8",
            "Answer": 415,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 18 + 7 * 2 * 5 + 5 + 7",
            "Answer": 298,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 11 + 7 * 18 * 19 + 7 + 17",
            "Answer": 2550,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 17 + 6 * 7 * 13 + 3 + 4",
            "Answer": 842,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 4 + 0 * 13 * 11 + 7 + 14",
            "Answer": 61,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 9 + 13 * 4 * 2 + 9 + 7",
            "Answer": 246,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 18 + 13 * 17 * 12 + 7 + 7",
            "Answer": 2954,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 17 + 10 * 2 * 0 + 19 + 10",
            "Answer": 250,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 17 + 9 * 1 * 15 + 4 + 8",
            "Answer": 215,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 6 + 1 * 3 * 4 + 8 + 15",
            "Answer": 131,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 12 + 5 * 18 * 3 + 9 + 2",
            "Answer": 473,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 12 + 11 * 10 * 2 + 11 + 16",
            "Answer": 415,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 14 + 7 * 0 * 18 + 5 + 10",
            "Answer": 239,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 14 + 1 * 16 * 15 + 12 + 0",
            "Answer": 462,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 18 + 18 * 17 * 12 + 4 + 18",
            "Answer": 3910,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 12 + 6 * 17 * 0 + 1 + 10",
            "Answer": 215,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # * # * # + # + #"
        }
    ],
    "# + # + # * # * # + # + #": [
        {
            "Question": "8 + 8 + 12 * 16 * 3 + 14 + 1",
            "Answer": 607,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 10 + 11 * 18 * 12 + 2 + 15",
            "Answer": 2413,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 16 + 4 * 14 * 14 + 13 + 13",
            "Answer": 828,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 6 + 16 * 10 * 11 + 18 + 10",
            "Answer": 1794,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 9 + 4 * 10 * 5 + 4 + 16",
            "Answer": 232,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 3 + 14 * 8 * 9 + 18 + 1",
            "Answer": 1035,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 10 + 14 * 4 * 0 + 10 + 17",
            "Answer": 51,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 5 + 9 * 13 * 11 + 18 + 8",
            "Answer": 1326,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 13 + 15 * 15 * 6 + 17 + 16",
            "Answer": 1412,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 14 + 19 * 17 * 4 + 11 + 6",
            "Answer": 1337,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 4 + 12 * 6 * 7 + 0 + 4",
            "Answer": 513,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 18 + 15 * 19 * 18 + 9 + 10",
            "Answer": 5183,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 0 + 2 * 11 * 16 + 9 + 19",
            "Answer": 383,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 4 + 16 * 2 * 9 + 19 + 19",
            "Answer": 338,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 7 + 11 * 1 * 6 + 14 + 15",
            "Answer": 107,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 9 + 15 * 2 * 19 + 6 + 8",
            "Answer": 611,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 7 + 12 * 6 * 6 + 6 + 13",
            "Answer": 466,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 11 + 7 * 17 * 13 + 1 + 17",
            "Answer": 1593,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 17 + 16 * 5 * 9 + 0 + 7",
            "Answer": 756,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 18 + 6 * 2 * 7 + 5 + 18",
            "Answer": 130,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 2 + 10 * 0 * 7 + 2 + 9",
            "Answer": 15,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 17 + 5 * 18 * 14 + 16 + 14",
            "Answer": 1308,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 3 + 5 * 14 * 6 + 0 + 9",
            "Answer": 445,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 12 + 7 * 12 * 13 + 11 + 12",
            "Answer": 1131,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 4 + 14 * 0 * 8 + 10 + 8",
            "Answer": 27,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 5 + 8 * 14 * 5 + 10 + 11",
            "Answer": 594,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 8 + 11 * 10 * 11 + 11 + 9",
            "Answer": 1243,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 2 + 2 * 1 * 14 + 10 + 12",
            "Answer": 61,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 12 + 11 * 13 * 12 + 11 + 18",
            "Answer": 1768,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 12 + 12 * 13 * 18 + 7 + 9",
            "Answer": 2852,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 8 + 14 * 9 * 1 + 12 + 15",
            "Answer": 167,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 1 + 3 * 3 * 4 + 13 + 16",
            "Answer": 73,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 11 + 11 * 1 * 3 + 17 + 12",
            "Answer": 86,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 1 + 6 * 14 * 18 + 19 + 16",
            "Answer": 1563,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 19 + 5 * 5 * 18 + 10 + 1",
            "Answer": 498,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 5 + 7 * 3 * 12 + 13 + 16",
            "Answer": 289,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 3 + 19 * 0 * 10 + 8 + 8",
            "Answer": 24,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 10 + 5 * 17 * 17 + 1 + 7",
            "Answer": 1480,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 17 + 19 * 18 * 1 + 4 + 17",
            "Answer": 388,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 11 + 10 * 7 * 18 + 17 + 18",
            "Answer": 1322,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 2 + 9 * 17 * 19 + 14 + 10",
            "Answer": 2936,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 8 + 11 * 8 * 3 + 8 + 15",
            "Answer": 300,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 8 + 18 * 0 * 11 + 18 + 17",
            "Answer": 61,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 10 + 8 * 15 * 2 + 17 + 15",
            "Answer": 287,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 15 + 15 * 16 * 13 + 4 + 1",
            "Answer": 3152,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 3 + 3 * 14 * 4 + 4 + 16",
            "Answer": 192,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 8 + 15 * 12 * 16 + 4 + 0",
            "Answer": 2895,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 17 + 19 * 3 * 15 + 18 + 7",
            "Answer": 912,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 5 + 0 * 9 * 15 + 17 + 5",
            "Answer": 42,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 7 + 3 * 14 * 14 + 16 + 7",
            "Answer": 618,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 15 + 16 * 17 * 14 + 18 + 2",
            "Answer": 3859,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 18 + 5 * 0 * 19 + 11 + 11",
            "Answer": 48,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 4 + 15 * 12 * 4 + 9 + 14",
            "Answer": 759,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 2 + 19 * 11 * 1 + 12 + 2",
            "Answer": 242,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 8 + 18 * 14 * 12 + 9 + 14",
            "Answer": 3062,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 7 + 16 * 8 * 3 + 9 + 2",
            "Answer": 411,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 17 + 7 * 19 * 4 + 0 + 6",
            "Answer": 570,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 3 + 3 * 9 * 1 + 3 + 14",
            "Answer": 59,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 15 + 12 * 8 * 6 + 5 + 5",
            "Answer": 609,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 8 + 18 * 9 * 5 + 12 + 14",
            "Answer": 862,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 4 + 18 * 4 * 17 + 15 + 18",
            "Answer": 1262,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 14 + 6 * 0 * 17 + 0 + 9",
            "Answer": 23,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 13 + 14 * 16 * 12 + 14 + 7",
            "Answer": 2722,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 9 + 3 * 3 * 12 + 7 + 1",
            "Answer": 140,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 8 + 6 * 13 * 10 + 16 + 12",
            "Answer": 835,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 15 + 7 * 2 * 11 + 12 + 1",
            "Answer": 186,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 15 + 11 * 6 * 15 + 4 + 16",
            "Answer": 1037,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 15 + 12 * 10 * 4 + 6 + 18",
            "Answer": 522,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 10 + 17 * 1 * 4 + 8 + 19",
            "Answer": 111,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 7 + 7 * 18 * 5 + 0 + 4",
            "Answer": 658,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 7 + 17 * 12 * 15 + 9 + 0",
            "Answer": 3077,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 7 + 1 * 3 * 16 + 17 + 8",
            "Answer": 90,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 7 + 0 * 10 * 3 + 4 + 6",
            "Answer": 33,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 11 + 3 * 16 * 5 + 4 + 3",
            "Answer": 274,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 10 + 13 * 10 * 7 + 14 + 12",
            "Answer": 946,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 18 + 12 * 16 * 6 + 4 + 0",
            "Answer": 1181,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 15 + 14 * 3 * 3 + 12 + 5",
            "Answer": 161,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 0 + 8 * 12 * 13 + 1 + 17",
            "Answer": 1284,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 14 + 2 * 7 * 17 + 4 + 1",
            "Answer": 260,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 14 + 7 * 7 * 14 + 14 + 12",
            "Answer": 742,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 5 + 5 * 4 * 1 + 1 + 18",
            "Answer": 63,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 3 + 4 * 19 * 7 + 17 + 19",
            "Answer": 571,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 19 + 2 * 7 * 15 + 4 + 9",
            "Answer": 256,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 7 + 5 * 7 * 14 + 18 + 2",
            "Answer": 527,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 2 + 11 * 13 * 19 + 10 + 19",
            "Answer": 2766,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 8 + 10 * 10 * 5 + 6 + 19",
            "Answer": 545,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 15 + 6 * 19 * 10 + 11 + 1",
            "Answer": 1175,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 12 + 6 * 15 * 3 + 0 + 13",
            "Answer": 299,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 10 + 1 * 3 * 7 + 12 + 9",
            "Answer": 67,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 7 + 16 * 1 * 4 + 3 + 15",
            "Answer": 106,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 7 + 12 * 9 * 11 + 8 + 10",
            "Answer": 1227,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 14 + 10 * 8 * 8 + 6 + 3",
            "Answer": 663,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 2 + 17 * 16 * 14 + 16 + 1",
            "Answer": 3832,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 3 + 11 * 8 * 8 + 7 + 2",
            "Answer": 721,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 12 + 11 * 4 * 16 + 14 + 6",
            "Answer": 751,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 2 + 7 * 3 * 19 + 1 + 18",
            "Answer": 420,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 13 + 14 * 7 * 9 + 16 + 15",
            "Answer": 930,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 3 + 4 * 1 * 18 + 16 + 3",
            "Answer": 95,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 17 + 16 * 18 * 11 + 9 + 1",
            "Answer": 3197,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 18 + 8 * 16 * 0 + 1 + 19",
            "Answer": 42,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # + #"
        }
    ],
    "# * # + # + # + # + # + #": [
        {
            "Question": "19 * 7 + 2 + 7 + 16 + 1 + 2",
            "Answer": 161,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 0 + 7 + 12 + 6 + 10 + 12",
            "Answer": 47,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 5 + 13 + 0 + 16 + 8 + 13",
            "Answer": 50,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 8 + 11 + 12 + 1 + 19 + 15",
            "Answer": 138,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 0 + 14 + 19 + 17 + 8 + 19",
            "Answer": 77,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 14 + 4 + 10 + 17 + 3 + 0",
            "Answer": 202,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 2 + 7 + 3 + 9 + 11 + 18",
            "Answer": 54,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 8 + 16 + 6 + 17 + 17 + 18",
            "Answer": 122,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 17 + 6 + 3 + 14 + 1 + 5",
            "Answer": 182,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 17 + 11 + 19 + 0 + 0 + 15",
            "Answer": 45,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 12 + 9 + 0 + 9 + 18 + 19",
            "Answer": 175,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 9 + 13 + 11 + 8 + 11 + 11",
            "Answer": 54,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 7 + 11 + 1 + 19 + 4 + 4",
            "Answer": 60,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 18 + 17 + 12 + 5 + 2 + 0",
            "Answer": 288,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 14 + 13 + 10 + 1 + 13 + 4",
            "Answer": 209,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 0 + 10 + 19 + 2 + 0 + 10",
            "Answer": 41,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 15 + 6 + 5 + 1 + 3 + 1",
            "Answer": 196,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 7 + 3 + 19 + 11 + 18 + 2",
            "Answer": 165,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 17 + 1 + 4 + 8 + 12 + 6",
            "Answer": 184,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 19 + 11 + 7 + 1 + 9 + 6",
            "Answer": 91,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 13 + 2 + 5 + 10 + 6 + 5",
            "Answer": 262,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 2 + 15 + 10 + 14 + 5 + 6",
            "Answer": 76,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 10 + 3 + 19 + 18 + 13 + 11",
            "Answer": 104,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 11 + 6 + 1 + 15 + 19 + 18",
            "Answer": 103,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 2 + 13 + 3 + 6 + 19 + 3",
            "Answer": 52,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 9 + 8 + 11 + 17 + 19 + 14",
            "Answer": 240,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 7 + 14 + 12 + 19 + 11 + 4",
            "Answer": 172,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 10 + 8 + 17 + 18 + 7 + 1",
            "Answer": 221,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 2 + 11 + 0 + 8 + 6 + 9",
            "Answer": 72,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 13 + 5 + 1 + 2 + 18 + 17",
            "Answer": 160,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 6 + 7 + 12 + 13 + 14 + 1",
            "Answer": 59,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 10 + 1 + 14 + 2 + 5 + 19",
            "Answer": 191,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 15 + 2 + 9 + 17 + 18 + 15",
            "Answer": 301,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 15 + 10 + 17 + 0 + 4 + 8",
            "Answer": 204,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 1 + 15 + 0 + 9 + 7 + 15",
            "Answer": 52,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 5 + 4 + 8 + 12 + 11 + 2",
            "Answer": 77,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 18 + 19 + 6 + 7 + 7 + 7",
            "Answer": 334,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 5 + 6 + 12 + 19 + 11 + 6",
            "Answer": 144,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 8 + 5 + 18 + 14 + 18 + 5",
            "Answer": 148,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 5 + 5 + 10 + 7 + 11 + 5",
            "Answer": 43,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 19 + 11 + 6 + 9 + 13 + 14",
            "Answer": 53,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 17 + 15 + 6 + 18 + 5 + 3",
            "Answer": 234,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 5 + 17 + 17 + 14 + 11 + 18",
            "Answer": 127,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 6 + 2 + 4 + 16 + 15 + 0",
            "Answer": 73,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 17 + 7 + 17 + 0 + 6 + 6",
            "Answer": 359,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 2 + 15 + 0 + 15 + 5 + 16",
            "Answer": 63,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 1 + 8 + 4 + 17 + 6 + 16",
            "Answer": 51,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 18 + 4 + 8 + 8 + 12 + 13",
            "Answer": 297,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 5 + 19 + 6 + 12 + 18 + 17",
            "Answer": 157,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 16 + 1 + 8 + 5 + 7 + 3",
            "Answer": 264,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 0 + 16 + 9 + 13 + 11 + 4",
            "Answer": 53,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 6 + 6 + 5 + 7 + 3 + 9",
            "Answer": 108,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 3 + 8 + 18 + 15 + 1 + 15",
            "Answer": 66,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 1 + 0 + 19 + 3 + 0 + 11",
            "Answer": 49,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 8 + 6 + 11 + 12 + 0 + 15",
            "Answer": 44,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 19 + 3 + 2 + 9 + 5 + 11",
            "Answer": 258,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 7 + 17 + 14 + 0 + 3 + 3",
            "Answer": 72,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 4 + 2 + 5 + 5 + 17 + 4",
            "Answer": 69,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 1 + 13 + 17 + 10 + 8 + 2",
            "Answer": 59,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 5 + 1 + 10 + 13 + 14 + 1",
            "Answer": 89,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 5 + 15 + 1 + 5 + 15 + 10",
            "Answer": 136,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 7 + 18 + 5 + 13 + 0 + 18",
            "Answer": 117,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 9 + 12 + 5 + 3 + 0 + 16",
            "Answer": 54,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 11 + 3 + 0 + 18 + 9 + 0",
            "Answer": 184,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 2 + 12 + 1 + 8 + 12 + 7",
            "Answer": 42,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 7 + 9 + 14 + 7 + 17 + 1",
            "Answer": 132,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 19 + 14 + 15 + 9 + 9 + 4",
            "Answer": 355,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 16 + 17 + 17 + 4 + 14 + 15",
            "Answer": 275,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 15 + 15 + 2 + 13 + 1 + 5",
            "Answer": 261,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 7 + 4 + 8 + 13 + 13 + 3",
            "Answer": 97,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 11 + 16 + 12 + 13 + 10 + 2",
            "Answer": 75,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 19 + 0 + 7 + 8 + 16 + 2",
            "Answer": 71,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 8 + 2 + 9 + 10 + 12 + 11",
            "Answer": 148,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 5 + 15 + 13 + 4 + 14 + 4",
            "Answer": 140,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 8 + 2 + 16 + 9 + 15 + 0",
            "Answer": 90,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 1 + 3 + 11 + 12 + 7 + 15",
            "Answer": 56,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 9 + 11 + 9 + 5 + 14 + 16",
            "Answer": 154,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 18 + 0 + 14 + 19 + 10 + 9",
            "Answer": 52,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 1 + 19 + 8 + 9 + 7 + 17",
            "Answer": 65,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 5 + 3 + 2 + 8 + 1 + 14",
            "Answer": 73,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 18 + 12 + 1 + 3 + 7 + 17",
            "Answer": 292,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 15 + 16 + 1 + 9 + 19 + 17",
            "Answer": 227,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 15 + 9 + 11 + 18 + 1 + 8",
            "Answer": 137,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 2 + 0 + 7 + 3 + 17 + 1",
            "Answer": 64,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 6 + 8 + 18 + 13 + 1 + 11",
            "Answer": 63,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 1 + 11 + 6 + 2 + 4 + 18",
            "Answer": 42,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 14 + 4 + 7 + 18 + 14 + 12",
            "Answer": 293,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 16 + 1 + 14 + 15 + 9 + 0",
            "Answer": 119,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 5 + 14 + 4 + 17 + 10 + 18",
            "Answer": 158,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 16 + 14 + 8 + 15 + 12 + 11",
            "Answer": 316,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 12 + 2 + 10 + 16 + 12 + 3",
            "Answer": 235,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 4 + 3 + 14 + 4 + 1 + 9",
            "Answer": 47,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 13 + 1 + 9 + 18 + 10 + 6",
            "Answer": 96,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 10 + 18 + 16 + 5 + 9 + 13",
            "Answer": 71,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 3 + 0 + 9 + 2 + 4 + 19",
            "Answer": 73,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 14 + 1 + 14 + 11 + 11 + 12",
            "Answer": 273,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 19 + 3 + 0 + 6 + 5 + 9",
            "Answer": 156,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 5 + 12 + 15 + 1 + 9 + 11",
            "Answer": 133,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 * 17 + 16 + 11 + 1 + 3 + 14",
            "Answer": 317,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 16 + 13 + 11 + 19 + 10 + 12",
            "Answer": 177,
            "Predicate": "# * # + # + # + # + # + #"
        }
    ],
    "# + # + # * # * # + # * #": [
        {
            "Question": "6 + 12 + 11 * 6 * 3 + 14 * 7",
            "Answer": 314,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 19 + 6 * 3 * 15 + 10 * 11",
            "Answer": 406,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 7 + 15 * 5 * 6 + 7 * 17",
            "Answer": 577,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 16 + 0 * 1 * 18 + 10 * 17",
            "Answer": 195,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 9 + 14 * 6 * 11 + 13 * 18",
            "Answer": 1174,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 19 + 16 * 12 * 19 + 0 * 9",
            "Answer": 3680,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 12 + 11 * 19 * 3 + 7 * 2",
            "Answer": 653,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 17 + 5 * 7 * 0 + 17 * 17",
            "Answer": 313,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 0 + 12 * 11 * 3 + 7 * 2",
            "Answer": 427,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 9 + 13 * 10 * 6 + 15 * 12",
            "Answer": 988,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 19 + 7 * 18 * 9 + 18 * 9",
            "Answer": 1327,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 1 + 18 * 4 * 7 + 12 * 14",
            "Answer": 684,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 9 + 3 * 17 * 2 + 15 * 9",
            "Answer": 256,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 13 + 18 * 4 * 15 + 14 * 18",
            "Answer": 1362,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 19 + 10 * 12 * 8 + 10 * 9",
            "Answer": 1071,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 16 + 17 * 0 * 0 + 3 * 8",
            "Answer": 47,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 13 + 11 * 2 * 3 + 2 * 2",
            "Answer": 98,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 6 + 14 * 1 * 18 + 17 * 12",
            "Answer": 480,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 3 + 14 * 4 * 18 + 3 * 9",
            "Answer": 1048,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 13 + 3 * 12 * 5 + 6 * 10",
            "Answer": 261,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 16 + 16 * 2 * 8 + 7 * 15",
            "Answer": 378,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 5 + 19 * 19 * 15 + 6 * 5",
            "Answer": 5466,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 3 + 16 * 3 * 4 + 19 * 10",
            "Answer": 385,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 16 + 13 * 3 * 3 + 3 * 3",
            "Answer": 160,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 15 + 8 * 6 * 0 + 4 * 19",
            "Answer": 107,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 0 + 11 * 15 * 0 + 16 * 14",
            "Answer": 238,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 11 + 16 * 14 * 10 + 4 * 6",
            "Answer": 2292,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 5 + 3 * 14 * 14 + 12 * 8",
            "Answer": 699,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 2 + 15 * 15 * 3 + 2 * 8",
            "Answer": 699,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 5 + 4 * 12 * 8 + 4 * 13",
            "Answer": 452,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 12 + 7 * 0 * 0 + 14 * 4",
            "Answer": 76,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 15 + 7 * 7 * 15 + 9 * 19",
            "Answer": 930,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 8 + 13 * 1 * 18 + 2 * 0",
            "Answer": 254,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 + 5 + 18 * 18 * 12 + 1 * 17",
            "Answer": 3910,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 6 + 12 * 16 * 19 + 8 * 3",
            "Answer": 3694,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 3 + 5 * 3 * 4 + 12 * 10",
            "Answer": 196,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 18 + 18 * 13 * 0 + 0 * 8",
            "Answer": 23,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 17 + 2 * 6 * 15 + 7 * 12",
            "Answer": 296,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 11 + 5 * 16 * 12 + 11 * 8",
            "Answer": 1065,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 1 + 3 * 4 * 14 + 1 * 0",
            "Answer": 173,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 + 15 + 10 * 12 * 4 + 8 * 7",
            "Answer": 569,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 18 + 4 * 1 * 15 + 2 * 4",
            "Answer": 102,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 7 + 9 * 4 * 0 + 9 * 14",
            "Answer": 140,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 14 + 19 * 17 * 8 + 8 * 3",
            "Answer": 2641,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 12 + 8 * 12 * 0 + 13 * 5",
            "Answer": 79,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 + 12 + 16 * 11 * 17 + 13 * 5",
            "Answer": 3083,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 19 + 0 * 15 * 19 + 17 * 2",
            "Answer": 65,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 16 + 18 * 1 * 12 + 1 * 13",
            "Answer": 252,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 4 + 2 * 14 * 2 + 6 * 16",
            "Answer": 161,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 6 + 9 * 10 * 1 + 6 * 11",
            "Answer": 167,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 15 + 14 * 1 * 16 + 1 * 9",
            "Answer": 260,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 6 + 7 * 13 * 12 + 3 * 18",
            "Answer": 1161,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 6 + 16 * 11 * 5 + 8 * 0",
            "Answer": 905,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 14 + 13 * 19 * 1 + 9 * 14",
            "Answer": 391,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 + 4 + 0 * 12 * 4 + 8 * 6",
            "Answer": 63,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 + 1 + 14 * 6 * 10 + 7 * 19",
            "Answer": 978,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 11 + 5 * 1 * 17 + 11 * 12",
            "Answer": 236,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 5 + 5 * 0 * 3 + 15 * 2",
            "Answer": 45,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 7 + 8 * 0 * 11 + 17 * 7",
            "Answer": 133,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 17 + 8 * 13 * 10 + 13 * 15",
            "Answer": 1271,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 13 + 2 * 1 * 0 + 2 * 5",
            "Answer": 25,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 16 + 9 * 12 * 4 + 9 * 19",
            "Answer": 626,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 7 + 6 * 13 * 4 + 3 * 11",
            "Answer": 354,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 13 + 4 * 4 * 3 + 10 * 18",
            "Answer": 243,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 2 + 5 * 16 * 11 + 6 * 4",
            "Answer": 914,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 1 + 3 * 12 * 15 + 8 * 7",
            "Answer": 612,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 9 + 1 * 8 * 17 + 11 * 6",
            "Answer": 217,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 6 + 3 * 7 * 17 + 18 * 3",
            "Answer": 436,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 + 16 + 17 * 11 * 3 + 14 * 1",
            "Answer": 594,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 16 + 16 * 1 * 13 + 10 * 4",
            "Answer": 280,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 5 + 4 * 1 * 2 + 5 * 12",
            "Answer": 86,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 17 + 8 * 4 * 6 + 0 * 4",
            "Answer": 218,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 14 + 16 * 11 * 9 + 11 * 17",
            "Answer": 1792,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 5 + 19 * 1 * 13 + 19 * 3",
            "Answer": 316,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 + 2 + 10 * 6 * 7 + 13 * 13",
            "Answer": 600,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 + 16 + 12 * 0 * 12 + 16 * 13",
            "Answer": 237,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 18 + 13 * 6 * 4 + 19 * 5",
            "Answer": 444,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 + 0 + 0 * 2 * 6 + 8 * 7",
            "Answer": 58,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 5 + 11 * 10 * 12 + 2 * 8",
            "Answer": 1357,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 + 0 + 11 * 1 * 9 + 9 * 5",
            "Answer": 161,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 9 + 6 * 7 * 4 + 7 * 0",
            "Answer": 184,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 17 + 10 * 1 * 12 + 8 * 1",
            "Answer": 164,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 18 + 17 * 9 * 1 + 11 * 18",
            "Answer": 376,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "16 + 6 + 2 * 19 * 0 + 3 * 11",
            "Answer": 55,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 + 9 + 9 * 4 * 1 + 11 * 10",
            "Answer": 174,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 15 + 13 * 4 * 5 + 10 * 7",
            "Answer": 353,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 + 15 + 13 * 15 * 2 + 14 * 0",
            "Answer": 410,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 17 + 7 * 9 * 2 + 19 * 7",
            "Answer": 277,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 5 + 0 * 12 * 5 + 10 * 5",
            "Answer": 70,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 4 + 15 * 4 * 3 + 13 * 6",
            "Answer": 270,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 + 2 + 1 * 13 * 7 + 18 * 2",
            "Answer": 139,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 9 + 14 * 19 * 2 + 13 * 4",
            "Answer": 605,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 8 + 1 * 16 * 7 + 17 * 4",
            "Answer": 200,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 5 + 13 * 17 * 10 + 2 * 0",
            "Answer": 2222,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 + 9 + 12 * 18 * 1 + 17 * 17",
            "Answer": 521,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 + 9 + 17 * 17 * 17 + 8 * 17",
            "Answer": 5073,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 + 11 + 15 * 3 * 9 + 18 * 0",
            "Answer": 422,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 + 8 + 0 * 8 * 7 + 0 * 15",
            "Answer": 16,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 + 14 + 3 * 14 * 5 + 2 * 16",
            "Answer": 268,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 + 3 + 2 * 3 * 5 + 4 * 16",
            "Answer": 98,
            "Predicate": "# + # + # * # * # + # * #"
        }
    ],
    "# * # * # * # + # + # + #": [
        {
            "Question": "15 * 3 * 18 * 15 + 6 + 9 + 7",
            "Answer": 12172,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 11 * 1 * 16 + 16 + 13 + 18",
            "Answer": 1631,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 12 * 13 * 10 + 18 + 7 + 11",
            "Answer": 10956,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 6 * 12 * 12 + 15 + 3 + 3",
            "Answer": 14709,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 17 * 19 * 10 + 15 + 15 + 0",
            "Answer": 29100,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 2 * 16 * 5 + 6 + 18 + 2",
            "Answer": 26,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 7 * 9 * 7 + 3 + 2 + 7",
            "Answer": 5304,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 18 * 14 * 18 + 11 + 16 + 0",
            "Answer": 81675,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 19 * 15 * 15 + 3 + 5 + 13",
            "Answer": 59871,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 9 * 7 * 19 + 1 + 7 + 17",
            "Answer": 15586,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 13 * 12 * 7 + 15 + 10 + 2",
            "Answer": 10947,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 16 * 16 * 19 + 18 + 13 + 19",
            "Answer": 92466,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 4 * 8 * 9 + 11 + 14 + 7",
            "Answer": 3488,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 3 * 13 * 16 + 18 + 9 + 14",
            "Answer": 3161,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 0 * 3 * 17 + 16 + 2 + 8",
            "Answer": 26,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 12 * 14 * 5 + 10 + 19 + 7",
            "Answer": 876,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 14 * 2 * 18 + 12 + 2 + 13",
            "Answer": 1539,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 14 * 13 * 7 + 19 + 10 + 10",
            "Answer": 2587,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 4 * 2 * 10 + 10 + 11 + 5",
            "Answer": 266,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "10 * 11 * 18 * 0 + 4 + 9 + 6",
            "Answer": 19,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 6 * 1 * 16 + 9 + 13 + 4",
            "Answer": 506,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 15 * 12 * 2 + 8 + 19 + 14",
            "Answer": 4001,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 8 * 15 * 15 + 1 + 15 + 0",
            "Answer": 14416,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 17 * 12 * 4 + 11 + 2 + 10",
            "Answer": 4919,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 11 * 16 * 18 + 18 + 19 + 17",
            "Answer": 28566,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 18 * 15 * 17 + 17 + 14 + 11",
            "Answer": 36762,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 16 * 1 * 17 + 13 + 15 + 15",
            "Answer": 2491,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 0 * 5 * 0 + 5 + 6 + 9",
            "Answer": 20,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 10 * 3 * 5 + 8 + 8 + 8",
            "Answer": 1224,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 6 * 19 * 2 + 0 + 6 + 1",
            "Answer": 1147,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 10 * 7 * 12 + 16 + 12 + 1",
            "Answer": 5069,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 5 * 2 * 7 + 9 + 15 + 12",
            "Answer": 456,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 0 * 10 * 2 + 9 + 15 + 14",
            "Answer": 38,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 9 * 11 * 2 + 14 + 6 + 8",
            "Answer": 1216,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 17 * 9 * 13 + 9 + 16 + 16",
            "Answer": 4019,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 13 * 12 * 9 + 15 + 7 + 0",
            "Answer": 5638,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 8 * 9 * 15 + 16 + 19 + 1",
            "Answer": 15156,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 6 * 17 * 11 + 4 + 2 + 3",
            "Answer": 7863,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 17 * 7 * 18 + 6 + 16 + 0",
            "Answer": 6448,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 9 * 4 * 2 + 12 + 1 + 3",
            "Answer": 304,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 1 * 19 * 9 + 15 + 1 + 15",
            "Answer": 3280,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 18 * 7 * 13 + 16 + 2 + 10",
            "Answer": 18046,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 8 * 7 * 12 + 11 + 10 + 6",
            "Answer": 699,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 3 * 7 * 3 + 15 + 4 + 3",
            "Answer": 904,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 10 * 17 * 11 + 17 + 5 + 5",
            "Answer": 5637,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 14 * 10 * 10 + 5 + 2 + 5",
            "Answer": 5612,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 11 * 14 * 8 + 16 + 5 + 11",
            "Answer": 23440,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 15 * 15 * 11 + 14 + 6 + 16",
            "Answer": 29736,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 4 * 18 * 17 + 3 + 4 + 1",
            "Answer": 8576,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "14 * 19 * 13 * 5 + 1 + 17 + 1",
            "Answer": 17309,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 8 * 13 * 9 + 5 + 2 + 15",
            "Answer": 4702,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 15 * 4 * 3 + 12 + 11 + 7",
            "Answer": 30,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 8 * 18 * 16 + 16 + 3 + 1",
            "Answer": 16148,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 7 * 17 * 1 + 18 + 11 + 13",
            "Answer": 399,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 6 * 17 * 7 + 1 + 5 + 0",
            "Answer": 12858,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 14 * 4 * 1 + 17 + 16 + 3",
            "Answer": 260,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 14 * 11 * 6 + 15 + 18 + 14",
            "Answer": 13907,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 14 * 16 * 8 + 2 + 11 + 18",
            "Answer": 3615,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 7 * 5 * 9 + 18 + 0 + 3",
            "Answer": 2541,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 1 * 12 * 11 + 17 + 14 + 19",
            "Answer": 1502,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 19 * 13 * 0 + 17 + 7 + 9",
            "Answer": 33,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 7 * 1 * 11 + 16 + 18 + 8",
            "Answer": 1351,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 15 * 17 * 19 + 4 + 6 + 14",
            "Answer": 63009,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 0 * 15 * 15 + 9 + 11 + 7",
            "Answer": 27,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 12 * 6 * 2 + 5 + 18 + 6",
            "Answer": 893,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 6 * 10 * 10 + 18 + 17 + 3",
            "Answer": 10838,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 2 * 17 * 10 + 11 + 19 + 11",
            "Answer": 1061,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 9 * 10 * 9 + 13 + 8 + 16",
            "Answer": 12187,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 8 * 3 * 6 + 5 + 3 + 13",
            "Answer": 741,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "19 * 9 * 10 * 7 + 10 + 1 + 14",
            "Answer": 11995,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 15 * 9 * 1 + 12 + 6 + 0",
            "Answer": 423,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "2 * 0 * 19 * 17 + 0 + 8 + 1",
            "Answer": 9,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 5 * 0 * 15 + 3 + 5 + 6",
            "Answer": 14,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 4 * 3 * 2 + 19 + 5 + 15",
            "Answer": 135,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 1 * 2 * 12 + 0 + 16 + 14",
            "Answer": 54,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 3 * 2 * 11 + 8 + 10 + 14",
            "Answer": 98,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "5 * 18 * 8 * 5 + 0 + 16 + 18",
            "Answer": 3634,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 7 * 6 * 11 + 11 + 2 + 9",
            "Answer": 3718,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 13 * 1 * 7 + 16 + 3 + 7",
            "Answer": 299,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "7 * 4 * 6 * 6 + 11 + 18 + 5",
            "Answer": 1042,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 14 * 9 * 5 + 19 + 16 + 11",
            "Answer": 676,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 7 * 16 * 0 + 19 + 11 + 8",
            "Answer": 38,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 5 * 16 * 9 + 8 + 19 + 6",
            "Answer": 10833,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 8 * 4 * 11 + 2 + 16 + 18",
            "Answer": 2852,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 1 * 7 * 13 + 0 + 10 + 16",
            "Answer": 845,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "6 * 12 * 18 * 7 + 5 + 13 + 18",
            "Answer": 9108,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 8 * 5 * 19 + 14 + 3 + 6",
            "Answer": 12943,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "13 * 10 * 12 * 1 + 12 + 15 + 14",
            "Answer": 1601,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "8 * 2 * 7 * 2 + 0 + 14 + 6",
            "Answer": 244,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "1 * 2 * 2 * 17 + 9 + 5 + 4",
            "Answer": 86,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "4 * 19 * 19 * 2 + 9 + 0 + 13",
            "Answer": 2910,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "15 * 18 * 17 * 6 + 15 + 0 + 11",
            "Answer": 27566,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "3 * 7 * 5 * 0 + 9 + 3 + 5",
            "Answer": 17,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "18 * 4 * 3 * 15 + 1 + 5 + 14",
            "Answer": 3260,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "0 * 8 * 19 * 16 + 14 + 4 + 15",
            "Answer": 33,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 4 * 0 * 18 + 12 + 5 + 14",
            "Answer": 31,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "11 * 11 * 0 * 4 + 13 + 12 + 18",
            "Answer": 43,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "12 * 6 * 17 * 19 + 0 + 3 + 14",
            "Answer": 23273,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "17 * 16 * 2 * 3 + 9 + 7 + 17",
            "Answer": 1665,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        },
        {
            "Question": "9 * 12 * 8 * 13 + 2 + 5 + 0",
            "Answer": 11239,
            "Predicate": "# * # * # * # + # + # + #"
        }
    ]
}